<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669301-ian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669301-ian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 15:22:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4216-each-day-the-storm-clouds-were-opening-like-great-purple</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 15:22:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4216-each-day-the-storm-clouds-were-opening-like-great-purple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each day the storm clouds were opening like great purple flowers and pouring out their dark thunder. Each nightfall, the storm was laid down on their houses like a burden the day had carried." -- Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47655-there-were-hints-of-sunrise-on-the-rim-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 13:47:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47655-there-were-hints-of-sunrise-on-the-rim-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were hints of sunrise on the rim of the sky, yet it was still dark, and the traces of morning color were like goldfish swimming in ink." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252700-the-hedge-was-a-half-painted-picture-which-would-be-finished</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 12:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252700-the-hedge-was-a-half-painted-picture-which-would-be-finished]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hedge was a half-painted picture which would be finished in a few days." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47691-robert-jordan-saw-them-there-on-the-slope-close-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 15:00:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47691-robert-jordan-saw-them-there-on-the-slope-close-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Robert Jordan saw them there on the slope, close to him now, and below he saw the road and the bridge and the long lines of vehicles below it. He was completely integrated now and he took a good long look at everything. Then he looked up at the sky. There were big white clouds in it. He touched the palm of his hand against the pine needles where he lay and he touched the bark of the pine trunk that he lay behind... He was waiting until the officer reached the sunlit place where the first trees of the pine forest joined the green slope of the meadow. He could feel his heart beating against the pine needle floor of the forest." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47692-they-refused-seconds-and-i-insisted-and-the-division-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 15:05:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47692-they-refused-seconds-and-i-insisted-and-the-division-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They refused seconds and I insisted.  And the division of thirds was put on the basis that there wasn't enough to save.  And with the few divided drops of that third there came into Rocinante a triumphant human magic that can bless a house, or a truck for that matter-- nine people gathered in complete silence and the nine parts making a whole as surely as my arms and legs are a part of me, separate and inseparable." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143598-italian-in-the-mouth-of-italians-is-a-deep-voiced-stream</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 13:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143598-italian-in-the-mouth-of-italians-is-a-deep-voiced-stream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Italian in the mouth of Italians is a deep-voiced stream, with unexpected cataracts and boulders to preserve it from monotony.  In Mr. Eager's mouth it resembled nothing so much as an acid whistling fountain which played ever higher and higher, and quicker and quicker, and more and more shrilly, till abruptly it was turned off with a click." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145921-strolling-keeping-step-his-stout-polished-well-made-boots-setting-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 19:04:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Katherine Anne Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145921-strolling-keeping-step-his-stout-polished-well-made-boots-setting-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strolling, keeping step, his stout polished well-made boots setting themselves down firmly beside her thin-soled black suede, they put off as long as they could the end of their moment together, and kept up as well as they could their small talk that flew back and forth over little grooves worn in the thin upper suface of the brain, things you could say and hear clink reassuringly at once without disturbing the radiance which played and darted about the simple and lovely miracle of being two persons named Adam and Miranda, twenty-four years old each, alive and on earth at the same moment: 'Are you in the mood for dancing, Miranda?' and 'I'm always in the mood for dancing, Adam!' but there were things in the way, the day that ended with dancing was a long way to go." -- Katherine Anne Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148464-in-the-fall-the-war-was-always-there-but-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2009 18:54:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148464-in-the-fall-the-war-was-always-there-but-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the fall the war was always there, but we did not go to it anymore." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183477-his-daughters-watched-in-the-rain-the-prettiest-shyest-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 14:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183477-his-daughters-watched-in-the-rain-the-prettiest-shyest-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His daughters watched in the rain.  The prettiest, shyest one hid far back in the field to watch and she had good reason because she was absolutely the most beautiful girl Dean and I ever saw in all our lives.  She was about sixteen, and had Plains complexion like wild roses, and the bluest eyes, the most lovely hair, and the modesty and quickness of a wild antelope.  At every look from us she flinched.  She stood there with the immense winds that blew clear down from Saskatchewan knocking her hair about her lovely head like shrouds, living curls of them.  She blushed and blushed...  'Oh a girl like that scares me,' I said.  'I'd give up everything and throw myself on her mercy and if she didn't want me I'd just as simply go and throw myself off the edge of the world'." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183502-i-did-not-know-whether-i-would-ever-speak-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 14:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183502-i-did-not-know-whether-i-would-ever-speak-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not know whether I would ever speak to her or not or, if I spoke to her, how I could tell her of my confused adoration.  But my body was like a harp and her words and gestures were like fingers running upon the wires." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33473-i-cannot-fix-on-the-hour-or-the-spot-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 18:18:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33473-i-cannot-fix-on-the-hour-or-the-spot-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot fix on the hour, or the spot, or the look or the words, which laid the foundation. It is too long ago. I was in the middle before I knew that I had begun." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198801-all-the-passengers-were-crowded-over-on-the-landside-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 12:53:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198801-all-the-passengers-were-crowded-over-on-the-landside-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the passengers were crowded over on the landside of the ship, watching through the narrow windows the careened hulk of a freighter, visibly damaged by shellfire, which had driven ashore to beach her cargo.  She lay aground, looking against the sand in that clear water like a whale with smokestacks that had come to the beach to die." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230278-and-it-was-in-the-midst-of-shouts-rolling-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 18:03:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230278-and-it-was-in-the-midst-of-shouts-rolling-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it was in the midst of shouts rolling against the terrace wall in massive waves that waxed in volume and duration, while cataracts of colored fire fell thicker through the darkness, that Dr. Rieux resolved to compile this chronicle, so that he should not be one of those who hold their peace but should bear witness in favor of those plague-stricken people; so that some memorial of the injustice and outrage done them might endure; and to state quite simply what we learn in time of pestilence: that there are more things to admire in men than to despise." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230283-sometimes-at-midnight-in-the-great-silence-of-the-sleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 18:15:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230283-sometimes-at-midnight-in-the-great-silence-of-the-sleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes at midnight, in the great silence of the sleep bound town, the doctor turned on his radio before going to bed for the few hours' sleep he allowed himself. And from the ends of the earth, across thousands of miles of land and sea, kindly, well-meaning speakers tried to voice their fellow-feeling, and indeed did so, but at the same time proved the utter incapacity of every man truly to share in the suffering that he cannot see. &quot;Oran! Oran!&quot; In vain the call rang over oceans, in vain Rieux listened hopefully; always the tide of eloquence began to flow, bringing home still more the unbridgeable gulf that lay between Grand and the speaker. &quot;Oran, we're with you!&quot; they called emotionally. But not, the doctor told himself, to love or to die together-- and that's the only way..." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280517-those-were-the-ones-which-would-turn-loose-their-grip</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2010 16:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280517-those-were-the-ones-which-would-turn-loose-their-grip]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those were the ones which would turn loose their grip on the branch before long-- not in any breeze, the fibers would just relax, in the middle of the day maybe with the sunshine bright and the air so still it aches like the place where the tooth was on the morning after you've been to the dentist or aches like your heart in the bosom when you stand on the street corner waiting for the light to change and happen to recollect how things once were and how they might have been yet if what happened had not happened." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282131-upon-my-return-i-found-the-call-in-my-box</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2010 14:46:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282131-upon-my-return-i-found-the-call-in-my-box]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Upon my return I found the call in my box.  It was Anne's number, then Anne's voice on the wire, and, as always, the little leap and plunk in my heart like a frog jumping into a lily pool.  With the ripples spreading round." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282396-t-here-is-nothing-brighter-crisper-more-antiseptic-and-cooler-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 14:46:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282396-t-here-is-nothing-brighter-crisper-more-antiseptic-and-cooler-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[T]here is nothing brighter, crisper, more antiseptic, and cooler than a really first-rate corner drugstore on a hot summer night.  If Anne Stanton is inside the door and the air conditioning is working." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283228-that-summer-we-had-been-absolutely-alone-together-even-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 07:20:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ian add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283228-that-summer-we-had-been-absolutely-alone-together-even-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That summer we had been absolutely alone, together, even when people were around, the only inhabitants of the kind of floating island or magic carpet which being in love is." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
