<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669422-veronica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669422-veronica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 14:54:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4213-still-there-are-times-i-am-bewildered-by-each-mile</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 14:54:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronica add a quote by Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4213-still-there-are-times-i-am-bewildered-by-each-mile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still, there are times I am bewildered by each mile I have traveled, each meal I have eaten, each person I have known, each room in which I have slept. As ordinary as it all appears, there are times when it is beyond my imagination." -- Jhumpa Lahiri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44330-beneatha-love-him-there-is-nothing-left-to-love-mama</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 13:56:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronica add a quote by Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44330-beneatha-love-him-there-is-nothing-left-to-love-mama]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beneatha: Love him? There is nothing left to love.

Mama: There is always something left to love. And if you ain't learned that, you ain't learned nothing. (Looking at her) Have you cried for that boy today? I don't mean for yourself and for the family 'cause we lost the money. I mean for him: what he been through and what it done to him. Child, when do you think is the time to love somebody the most? When they done good and made things easy for everybody? Well then, you ain't through learning - because that ain't the time at all. It's when he's at his lowest and can't believe in hisself 'cause the world done whipped him so! when you starts measuring somebody, measure him right, child, measure him right. Make sure you done taken into account what hills and valleys he come through before he got to wherever he is." -- Lorraine Hansberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46301-when-each-day-is-the-same-as-the-next-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 16:44:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronica add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46301-when-each-day-is-the-same-as-the-next-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When each day is the same as the next, it’s because people fail to recognize the good things that happen in their lives every day that the sun rises." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206521-yes-the-world-may-aspire-to-vacuousness-lost-souls-mourn</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 21:17:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronica add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206521-yes-the-world-may-aspire-to-vacuousness-lost-souls-mourn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, the world may aspire to vacuousness, lost souls mourn beauty, insignificance surrounds us. Then let us drink a cup of tea. Silence descends, one hears the wind outside, autumn leaves rustle and take flight, the cat sleeps in a warm pool of light. And, with each swallow, time is sublimed." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
