<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669616-ryan-parr]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/669616-ryan-parr" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 06:57:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429839-those-touchy-mediocrities-who-sit-trembling-lest-someone-s-work-prove</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 06:57:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429839-those-touchy-mediocrities-who-sit-trembling-lest-someone-s-work-prove]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those touchy mediocrities who sit trembling lest someone's work prove greater than their own - they have no inkling of the loneliness that comes when you reach the top. The loneliness for an equal - for a mind to respect and an achievement to admire." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430247-people-don-t-want-to-think-and-the-deeper-they-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 06:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430247-people-don-t-want-to-think-and-the-deeper-they-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People don't want to think. And the deeper they get into trouble, the less they want to think. But by some sort of instinct, they feel that they ought to and it makes them feel guilty. So they'll bless and follow anyone who gives them a justification for not thinking. Anyone who makes a virtue - a highly intellectual virtue - out of what they know to be their sin, their weakness and their guilt... They envy achievement, and their dream of greatness is a world where all men have become their acknowledged inferiors. They don't know that that dream is the infallible proof of mediocrity, because that sort of world is what the man of achievement would not be able to bear" -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129945-stupidity-lies-in-wanting-to-draw-conclusions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 06:58:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129945-stupidity-lies-in-wanting-to-draw-conclusions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stupidity lies in wanting to draw conclusions." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114406-everyone-either-from-modesty-or-egotism-hides-away-the-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 06:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114406-everyone-either-from-modesty-or-egotism-hides-away-the-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, either from modesty or egotism, hides away the best and most delicate of his soul’s possessions; to gain the esteem of others, we must only ever show our ugliest sides; this is how we keep ourselves on the common level" -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464064-creative-people-are-often-found-either-disagreeable-or-intimidating-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 07:00:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Criss Jami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464064-creative-people-are-often-found-either-disagreeable-or-intimidating-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creative people are often found either disagreeable or intimidating by mediocrities." -- Criss Jami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277466-simply-moderate-giftedness-has-been-made-worthless-by-the-printing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 07:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277466-simply-moderate-giftedness-has-been-made-worthless-by-the-printing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...simply moderate giftedness has been made worthless by the printing press and radio and television and satellites and all that.  A moderately gifted person who would have been a community treasure a thousand years ago has to give up, has to go into some other line of work, since modern communications put him or her into daily competition with nothing but world's champions.... A moderately gifted person has to keep his or her gifts all bottled up until, in a manner of speaking, he or she gets drunk at a wedding and tap-dances on the coffee table like Fred Astaire or Ginger Rogers.  We have a name for him or her.  We call him or her an &quot;exhibitionist.&quot;  How do we reward such an exhibitionist?  We say to him or her the next morning, &quot;Wow!  Were you ever drunk  last night!" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128542-i-ll-be-long-gone-before-some-smart-person-ever-figures</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 21:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by George W. Bush]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128542-i-ll-be-long-gone-before-some-smart-person-ever-figures]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll be long gone before some smart person ever figures out what happened inside this Oval Office.&quot;
(Washington DC, 12 May, 2008)" -- George W. Bush]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 07:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ideally, what should be said to every child, repeatedly, throughout his or her school life is something like this: 'You are in the process of being indoctrinated. We have not yet evolved a system of education that is not a system of indoctrination. We are sorry, but it is the best we can do. What you are being taught here is an amalgam of current prejudice and the choices of this particular culture. The slightest look at history will show how impermanent these must be. You are being taught by people who have been able to accommodate themselves to a regime of thought laid down by their predecessors. It is a self-perpetuating system. Those of you who are more robust and individual than others will be encouraged to leave and find ways of educating yourself — educating your own judgements. Those that stay must remember, always, and all the time, that they are being moulded and patterned to fit into the narrow and particular needs of this particular society." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
