<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67057-samantha-thompson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67057-samantha-thompson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 18:05:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 18:05:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40501-enjoy-the-power-and-beauty-of-your-youth-oh-nevermind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth; oh nevermind; you will not 
understand the power and beauty of your youth until they have faded. 
But trust me, in 20 years you’ll look back at photos of yourself and 
recall in a way you can’t grasp now how much possibility lay before 
you and how fabulous you really looked….You’re not as fat as you 
imagine. Don’t worry about the future; or worry, but know that worrying is as 
effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing 
bubblegum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that 
never crossed your worried mind; the kind that blindside you at 4pm 
on some idle Tuesday. Do one thing everyday that scares you Sing Don’t be reckless with other people’s hearts, don’t put up with 
people who are reckless with yours. Floss Don’t waste your time on jealousy; sometimes you’re ahead, sometimes 
you’re behind…the race is long, and in the end, it’s only with 
yourself. Remember the compliments you receive, forget the insults; if you 
succeed in doing this, tell me how. Keep your old love letters, throw away your old bank statements. Stretch Don’t feel guilty if you don’t know what you want to do with your 
life…the most interesting people I know didn’t know at 22 what they 
wanted to do with their lives, some of the most interesting 40 year 
olds I know still don’t. Get plenty of calcium. Be kind to your knees, you’ll miss them when they’re gone. Maybe you’ll marry, maybe you won’t, maybe you’ll have children,maybe 
you won’t, maybe you’ll divorce at 40, maybe you’ll dance the funky 
chicken on your 75th wedding anniversary…what ever you do, don’t 
congratulate yourself too much or berate yourself either – your 
choices are half chance, so are everybody else’s. Enjoy your body, 
use it every way you can…don’t be afraid of it, or what other people 
think of it, it’s the greatest instrument you’ll ever 
own.. Dance…even if you have nowhere to do it but in your own living room. Read the directions, even if you don’t follow them. Do NOT read beauty magazines, they will only make you feel ugly. Get to know your parents, you never know when they’ll be gone for 
good. Be nice to your siblings; they are the best link to your past and the 
people most likely to stick with you in the future. Understand that friends come and go,but for the precious few you 
should hold on. Work hard to bridge the gaps in geography and 
lifestyle because the older you get, the more you need the people you 
knew when you were young." -- Baz Luhrmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333348-resilience-is-accepting-your-new-reality-even-if-it-s-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 19:16:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Elizabeth Edwards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333348-resilience-is-accepting-your-new-reality-even-if-it-s-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Resilience is accepting your new reality, even if it's less good than the one you had before. You can fight it, you can do nothing but scream about what you've lost, or you can accept that and try to put together something that's good." -- Elizabeth Edwards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40318-sometimes-the-bible-in-the-hand-of-one-man-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 12:19:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40318-sometimes-the-bible-in-the-hand-of-one-man-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the Bible in the hand of one man is worse than a whisky bottle in the hand of (another)... There are just some kind of men who - who're so busy worrying about the next world they've never learned to live in this one, and you can look down the street and see the results." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159856-miss-gates-is-a-nice-lady-ain-t-she-why-sure</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 12:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159856-miss-gates-is-a-nice-lady-ain-t-she-why-sure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miss Gates is a nice lady, ain't she?&quot;
Why sure,&quot; said Jem.  &quot;I liked her when I was in her room.&quot;
She hates Hitler a lot . . .&quot;
What's wrong with that?&quot;
Well, she went on today about how bad it was him treating the Jews like that.  Jem, it's not right to persecute anybody, is it?  I mean have mean thoughts about anybody, even, is it?&quot;
Gracious no, Scout.  What's eatin' you?&quot;
Well, coming out of the courthouse that night Miss Gates was--- she was going' down the steps in front of us, you  musta not seen her--- she was talking with Miss Stephanie Crawford.  I heard her say it's time somebody time somebody taught 'em a lesson, they were gettin' way above themelves, an' the next thing they think they can do is marry us.  Jem, how can you hate Hitler so bad an' then turn around and be ugly about folks right at home---" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 12:16:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Samantha add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
