<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/670573-daniel-jafari]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/670573-daniel-jafari" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 21:13:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245912-and-do-you-think-that-unto-such-as-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 21:13:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Omar Khayyâm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245912-and-do-you-think-that-unto-such-as-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And do you think that unto such as you
A maggot-minded, starved, fanatic crew
God gave a secret, and denied it me?
Well, well—what matters it? Believe that, too!" -- Omar Khayyâm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63966-live-a-good-life-if-there-are-gods-and-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 21:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63966-live-a-good-life-if-there-are-gods-and-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live a good life. If there are gods and they are just, then they will not care how devout you have been, but will welcome you based on the virtues you have lived by. If there are gods, but unjust, then you should not want to worship them. If there are no gods, then you will be gone, but will have lived a noble life that will live on in the memories of your loved ones." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267767-alcohol-makes-other-people-less-tedious-and-food-less-bland</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 21:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Daniel add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267767-alcohol-makes-other-people-less-tedious-and-food-less-bland]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alcohol makes other people less tedious, and food less bland, and can help provide what the Greeks called &lt;i&gt;entheos&lt;/i&gt;, or the slight buzz of inspiration when reading or writing. The only worthwhile miracle in the New Testament—the transmutation of water into wine during the wedding at Cana—is a tribute to the persistence of Hellenism in an otherwise austere Judaea. The same applies to the seder at Passover, which is obviously modeled on the Platonic symposium: questions are asked (especially of the young) while wine is circulated. No better form of sodality has ever been devised: at Oxford one was positively expected to take wine during tutorials. The tongue must be untied. It's not a coincidence that Omar Khayyam, rebuking and ridiculing the stone-faced Iranian mullahs of his time, pointed to the value of the grape as a mockery of their joyless and sterile regime. Visiting today's Iran, I was delighted to find that citizens made a point of defying the clerical ban on booze, keeping it in their homes for visitors even if they didn't particularly take to it themselves, and bootlegging it with great &lt;i&gt;brio&lt;/i&gt; and ingenuity. These small revolutions affirm the human." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
