<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671551-walker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671551-walker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:33:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149747-success-means-we-go-to-sleep-at-night-knowing-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:33:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149747-success-means-we-go-to-sleep-at-night-knowing-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success means we go to sleep at night knowing that our talents and ablities were used in a way that served others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228691-usually-when-we-think-of-power-we-think-of-external</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228691-usually-when-we-think-of-power-we-think-of-external]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually, when we think of power, we think of external power. And we think of powerful people as those who have made it in the world. A powerful woman isn’t necessarily someone who has money, but we think of her as someone with a boldness or a spark that makes her manifest in a dramatic way.  When we think of a powerful man, we think of his ability to manifest abundance, usually money, in the world.
Most people say that a powerful woman does best with a powerful man, that she needs someone who understands the bigness of her situation, a man who can meet her at the same or even greater level of power in the world. 
Now this is true, if power is defined as material abundance.  A woman often faces cultural prejudice when she makes more money than a man, as does he. A woman who defines power by worldly standards can rarely feel totally relaxed in the arms of a man who doesn’t have it.  
If power is seen as an internal matter, then the situation changes drastically. Internal power has less to do with money and worldly position, and more to do than with emotional expansiveness, spirituality and conscious living…
I used to think I needed a powerful man, someone who could protect me from the harshness and evils of the world.  What I have come to realize is that…the powerful man I was looking for would be foremost, someone who supported me in keeping myself on track spiritually, and in so maintaining clarity within myself, that life would present fewer problems. When it did get rough, he would help me forgive. 
I no longer wanted somebody who would say to me, “Don’t worry honey, if they’re mean to you I’ll beat them up or buy them out.”  Instead, I want someone who prays and meditates with me regularly so that fewer monsters from the outer world disturb me, and who when they do, helps me look within my own consciousness for answers, instead of looking to false power to combat false power.
There’s a big difference between a gentle man and a weak man. Weak men make us nervous. Gentle men make us calm." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18168-available-people-are-the-ones-who-are-dangerous-because-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:35:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18168-available-people-are-the-ones-who-are-dangerous-because-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...available people are the ones who are dangerous, because they confront us with the possibility of real intimacy." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320878-always-seek-less-turbulent-skies-hurt-fly-above-it-betrayal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320878-always-seek-less-turbulent-skies-hurt-fly-above-it-betrayal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always seek less turbulent skies. 
Hurt. Fly above it. 
Betrayal. Fly above it. 
Anger. Fly above it. 
You are the one who is flying the plane." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387102-something-amazing-happens-when-we-surrender-and-just-love-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:36:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by marianne williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387102-something-amazing-happens-when-we-surrender-and-just-love-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something amazing happens when we surrender and just love. We melt into another world, a realm of power already within us. The world changes when we change. the world softens when we soften. The world loves us when we choose to love the world." -- marianne williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377057-the-highest-prize-we-can-receive-for-creative-work-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:37:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377057-the-highest-prize-we-can-receive-for-creative-work-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The highest prize we can receive for creative work is the joy of being creative. Creative effort spent for any other reason than the joy of being in that light filled space, love, god, whatever we want to call it, is lacking in integrity. . ." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553527-only-write-from-your-own-passion-your-own-truth-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 22:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Walker add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553527-only-write-from-your-own-passion-your-own-truth-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only write from your own passion, your own truth. That's the only thing you really know about, and anything else leads you away from the pulse." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
