<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671761-jaclyn-michele]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671761-jaclyn-michele" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 21:41:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329516-it-s-the-way-that-life-asserts-itself-no-matter-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 21:41:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329516-it-s-the-way-that-life-asserts-itself-no-matter-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the way that life asserts itself, no matter what the circumstances. Of course it must be a miserable existence. How could it not be? Yet those little girls manage to live; to breathe; to enjoy themselves. They laugh and they are full of curiosity and tenderness. They adjust, I believe that's the word. They adjust and they reach for the stars in their own way. I tell you it's wondrous to me. They make me think of the wild flowers that grow in the cracks of pavement, just pushing up into the sun, no matter how many feet crush them down." -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 21:42:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255103-i-wanted-so-badly-to-lie-down-next-to-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 21:41:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255103-i-wanted-so-badly-to-lie-down-next-to-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted so badly to lie down next to her on the couch, to wrap my arms around her and sleep. Not fuck, like in those movies. Not even have sex. Just sleep together in the most innocent sense of the phrase. But I lacked the courage and she had a boyfriend and I was gawky and she was gorgeous and I was hopelessly boring and she was endlessly fascinating. So I walked back to my room and collapsed on the bottom bunk, thinking that if people were rain, I was drizzle and she was hurricane." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204645-the-greatest-danger-to-our-future-is-apathy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 21:41:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Jane Goodall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204645-the-greatest-danger-to-our-future-is-apathy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest danger to our future is apathy." -- Jane Goodall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 18:56:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314205-ruin-is-a-gift-ruin-is-the-road-to-transformation</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 13:09:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314205-ruin-is-a-gift-ruin-is-the-road-to-transformation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ruin is a gift. Ruin is the road to transformation." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25766-for-us-to-maintain-our-way-of-living-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 11:52:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25766-for-us-to-maintain-our-way-of-living-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For us to maintain our way of living, we must tell lies to each other and especially to ourselves. The lies are necessary because, without them, many deplorable acts would become impossibilities." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 11:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if the point of life has nothing to do with the creation of an ever-expanding region of control? What if the point is not to keep at bay all those people, beings, objects and emotions that we so needlessly fear? What if the point instead is to let go of that control? What if the point of life, the primary reason for existence, is to lie naked with your lover in a shady grove of trees? What if the point is to taste each other's sweat and feel the delicate pressure of finger on chest, thigh on thigh, lip on cheek? What if the point is to stop, then, in your slow movements together, and listen to the birdsong, to watch the dragonflies hover, to look at your lover's face, then up at the undersides of leaves moving together in the breeze? What if the point is to invite these others into your movement, to bring trees, wind, grass, dragonflies into your family and in so doing abandon any attempt to control them? What if the point all along has been to get along, to relate, to experience things on their own terms? What if the point is to feel joy when joyous, love when loving, anger when angry, thoughtful when full of thought? What if the point from the beginning has been to simply be?" -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293404-if-you-had-a-person-in-your-life-treating-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 12:10:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Cheri Huber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293404-if-you-had-a-person-in-your-life-treating-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you had a person in your life treating you the way you treat yourself, you would have gotten rid of them a long time ago..." -- Cheri Huber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25076-i-m-not-telling-you-it-s-going-to-be-easy--</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 09:25:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by Art Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25076-i-m-not-telling-you-it-s-going-to-be-easy--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not telling you it's going to be easy - I'm telling you it's going to be worth it." -- Art Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 21:12:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jaclyn Michele add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227321-never-forget-what-you-are-for-surely-the-world-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget what you are, for surely the world will not. Make it your strength. Then it can never be your weakness. Armour yourself in it, and it will never be used to hurt you." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
