<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671856-sgillesp]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/671856-sgillesp" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 09:44:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 09:44:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sgillesp add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175716-we-have-to-create-culture-don-t-watch-tv-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to create culture, don't watch TV, don't read magazines, don't even listen to NPR. Create your own roadshow. The nexus of space and time where you are now is the most immediate sector of your universe, and if you're worrying about Michael Jackson or Bill Clinton or somebody else, then you are disempowered, you're giving it all away to icons, icons which are maintained by an electronic media so that you want to dress like X or have lips like Y. This is shit-brained, this kind of thinking. That is all cultural diversion, and what is real is you and your friends and your associations, your highs, your orgasms, your hopes, your plans, your fears. And we are told 'no', we're unimportant, we're peripheral. 'Get a degree, get a job, get a this, get a that.' And then you're a player, you don't want to even play in that game. You want to reclaim your mind and get it out of the hands of the cultural engineers who want to turn you into a half-baked moron consuming all this trash that's being manufactured out of the bones of a dying world." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153496-be-willing-to-be-a-beginner-every-single-morning</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 13:10:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sgillesp add a quote by Meister Eckhart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153496-be-willing-to-be-a-beginner-every-single-morning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be willing to be a beginner every single morning." -- Meister Eckhart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314258-if-children-were-brought-into-the-world-by-an-act</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 18:54:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sgillesp add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314258-if-children-were-brought-into-the-world-by-an-act]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If children were brought into the world by an act of pure reason alone, would the human race continue to exist? Would not a man rather have so much sympathy with the coming generation as to spare it the burden of existence, or at any rate not take it upon himself to impose that burden upon it in cold blood?" -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207207-in-astrology-the-rules-happen-to-be-about-stars-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 10:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sgillesp add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207207-in-astrology-the-rules-happen-to-be-about-stars-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In astrology the rules happen to be about stars and planets, but they could be about ducks and drakes for all the difference it would make. It's just a way of thinking about a problem which lets the shape of that problem begin to emerge. The more rules, the tinier the rules, the more arbitrary they are, the better. It's like throwing a handful of fine graphite dust on a piece of paper to see where the hidden indentations are. It lets you see the words that were written on the piece of paper above it that's now been taken away and hidden. The graphite's not important. It's just the means of revealing the indentations. So you see, astrology's nothing to do with astronomy. It's just to do with people thinking about people." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
