<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/673476-lina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/673476-lina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:41:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62573-there-s-more-to-life-than-books-you-know-but-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:41:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62573-there-s-more-to-life-than-books-you-know-but-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's more to life than books, you know.  But not much more." -- Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5325-if-we-citizens-do-not-support-our-artists-then-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:43:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5325-if-we-citizens-do-not-support-our-artists-then-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we, citizens, do not support our artists, then we sacrifice our imagination on the altar of crude reality and we end up believing in nothing and having worthless dreams." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147838-writers-don-t-make-any-money-at-all-we-make-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 09:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147838-writers-don-t-make-any-money-at-all-we-make-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writers don't make any money at all. We make about a dollar. It is terrible. But then again we don't work either. We sit around in our underwear until noon then go downstairs and make coffee, fry some eggs, read the paper, read part of a book, smell the book, wonder if perhaps we ourselves should work on our book, smell the book again, throw the book across the room because we are quite jealous that any other person wrote a book, feel terribly guilty about throwing the schmuck's book across the room because we secretly wonder if God in heaven noticed our evil jealousy, or worse, our laziness. We then lie across the couch facedown and mumble to God to forgive us because we are secretly afraid He is going to dry up all our words because we envied another man's stupid words. And for this, as I said, we are paid a dollar. We are worth so much more." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205242-i-think-this-is-when-most-people-give-up-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 10:04:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205242-i-think-this-is-when-most-people-give-up-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think this is when most people give up on their stories. They come out of college wanting to change the world, wanting to get married, wanting to have kids and change the way people buy office supplies. But they get into the middle and discover it was harder than they thought. They can't see the distant shore anymore, and they wonder if their paddling is moving them forward. None of the trees behind them are getting smaller and none of the trees ahead are getting bigger. They take it out on their spouses, and they go looking for an easier story." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212753-i-don-t-wonder-anymore-what-i-ll-tell-god-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 10:05:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212753-i-don-t-wonder-anymore-what-i-ll-tell-god-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't wonder anymore what I'll tell God when I go to heaven when we sit in the chairs under the tree, outside the city........I'll tell these things to God, and he'll laugh, I think and he'll remind me of the parts I forgot, the parts that were his favorite.  We'll sit and remember my story together, and then he'll stand and put his arms around me and say, &quot;well done,&quot; and that he liked my story.  And my soul won't be thirsty anymore.  Finally he'll turn and we'll walk toward the city, a city he will have spoken into existence a city built in a place where once there'd been nothing.  " -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422893-this-was-my-one-brush-with-love-was-it-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 23:17:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Paula McLain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422893-this-was-my-one-brush-with-love-was-it-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was my one brush with love. Was it love? It felt awful enough. I spent another two years crawling around in the skin of it, smoking too much and growing too thin and having stray thoughts of jumping from my balcony like a tortured heroine in a Russian novel." -- Paula McLain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
