<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67454-martin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67454-martin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 12:24:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 12:24:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martin add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jazz presumes that it would be nice if the four of us--simpatico dudes that we are--while playing this complicated song together, might somehow be free and autonomous as well. Tragically, this never quite works out. At best, we can only be free one or two at a time--while the other dudes hold onto the wire. Which is not to say that no one has tried to dispense with wires. Many have, and sometimes it works--but it doesn't feel like &lt;i&gt;jazz&lt;/i&gt; when it does. The music simply drifts away into the stratosphere of formal dialectic, beyond our social concerns.

Rock-and-roll, on the other hand, presumes that the four of us--as damaged and anti-social as we are--might possibly get it &lt;i&gt;to-fucking-gether&lt;/i&gt;, man, and play this simple song. And play it right, okay? Just this once, in tune and on the beat. But we can't. The song's too simple, and we're too complicated and too excited. We try like hell, but the guitars distort, the intonation bends, and the beat just moves, imperceptibly, against our formal expectations, whetehr we want it to or not. Just because we're &lt;i&gt;breathing&lt;/i&gt;, man. Thus, in the process of trying to play this very simple song together, we create this hurricane of noise, this infinitely complicated, fractal filigree of delicate distinctions.

And you can thank the wanking eighties, if you wish, and digital sequencers, too, for proving to everyone that technologically &quot;perfect&quot; rock--like &quot;free&quot; jazz--sucks rockets. Because order sucks. I mean, look at the Stones. Keith Richards is &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; on top of the beat, and Bill Wyman, until he quit, was always behind it, because Richards is leading the band and Charlie Watts is listening to him and Wyman is listening to Watts. So the beat is sliding on those tiny neural lapses, not so you can tell, of course, but so you can feel it in your stomach. And the intonation is wavering, too, with the pulse in the finger on the amplified string. This is the delicacy of rock-and-roll, the bodily rhetoric of tiny increments, necessary imperfections, and contingent community. And it has its virtues, because jazz only works if we're trying to be free and are, in fact, together. Rock-and-roll works because we're all a bunch of flakes. That's something you can &lt;i&gt;depend&lt;/i&gt; on, and a good thing too, because in the twentieth century, that's all there is: jazz and rock-and-roll. The rest is term papers and advertising." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165309-he-thought-that-in-the-beauty-of-the-world-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 18:38:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martin add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165309-he-thought-that-in-the-beauty-of-the-world-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought that in the beauty of the world were hid a secret. He thought that the world’s heart beat at some terrible cost and that the world’s pain and its beauty moved in a relationship of diverging equity and that in this headlong deficit the blood of multitudes might ultimately be exacted for the vision of a single flower." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193520-i-am-here-because-of-a-certain-man-i-came</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 18:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martin add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193520-i-am-here-because-of-a-certain-man-i-came]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am here because of a certain man.  I came to retrace his steps.  Perhaps to see if there were not some alternate course.  What was here to be found was not a thing.  Things separate from their stories have no meaning.  They are only shapes.  Of a certain size and color.  A certain weight.  When their meaning has become lost to us they no longer have even a name.  The story on the other hand can never be lost from its place in the world for it is that place.  And that is what was to be found here.  The corrido.  That tale.  And like all corridos it ultimately told one story only, for there is only one to tell.

The cats shifted and stirred, the fire creaked in the stove.  Outside in the abandoned village the profoundest silence.

What is the story? the boy said.

In the town of Caborca on the Altar River there was a man who lived there who was an old man.  He was born in Caborca and in Caborca he died.  Yet he lived once in this town, in Huisiachepic.

What does Caborca know of Huisiachepic, Huisiachepic of Caborca?  They are different worlds, you must agree.  Yet even so there is but one world and everything that is imaginable is necessary to it.  For this world also which seems to us a thing of stone and flower and blood is not a thing at all but a tale.  And all in it is a tale and each tale the sum of all lesser tales and yet they are the selfsame tale and contain as well all else within them.  So everything is necessary.  Every least thing.  This is a hard lesson.  Nothing can be dispensed with.  Nothing despised.  Because the seems are hid from us, you see.  The joinery.  The way in which the world is made.  We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall.  And those seams that are hid from us are of course in the tale itself and the tale had no abode or place of being except in the telling only and there it lives and makes its home and therefore we can never be done with the telling.  Of the telling there is no end.  And whether in Caborca or Huisiachepic or in whatever other place by whatever other name or by no name at all I say again all tales are one.  Rightly heard all tales are one." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63883-bad-taste-is-real-taste-of-course-and-good-taste</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 18:56:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martin add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63883-bad-taste-is-real-taste-of-course-and-good-taste]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bad taste is real taste, of course, and good taste is the residue of someone else's privilege." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 19:36:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Martin add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was about eleven o'clock in the morning, mid October, with the sun not shining and a look of hard wet rain in the clearness of the foothills. I was wearing my powder-blue suit, with dark blue shirt, tie and display handkerchief, black brogues, black wool socks with dark little clocks on them. I was neat, clean, shaved and sober, and I didn't care who knew it. I was everything the well-dressed private detective ought to be. I was calling on four million dollars." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
