<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67523-joel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67523-joel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 16:02:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 16:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511136-in-one-of-his-puckish-moods-saul-talked-the-president</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 12:00:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by Nicholas von Hoffman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511136-in-one-of-his-puckish-moods-saul-talked-the-president]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In one of his puckish moods Saul talked the president of a university into letting him anonymously take an examination being administered to candidates for a doctorate in community organization. &quot;Three of the questions were on the philosophy of and motivations of Saul Alinsky,&quot; writes Saul. &quot;I answered two of them incorrectly." -- Nicholas von Hoffman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19767-grades-are-a-problem-on-the-most-general-level-they-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2013 21:45:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19767-grades-are-a-problem-on-the-most-general-level-they-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grades are a problem. On the most general level, they're an explicit acknowledgment that what you're doing is insufficiently interesting or rewarding for you to do it on your own. Nobody ever gave you a grade for learning how to play, how to ride a bicycle, or how to kiss. One of the best ways to destroy love for any of these activities would be through the use of grades, and the coercion and judgment they represent. Grades are a cudgel to bludgeon the unwilling into doing what they don't want to do, an important instrument in inculcating children into a lifelong subservience to whatever authority happens to be thrust over them." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
