<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67633-angie-ungaro]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/67633-angie-ungaro" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 12:57:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111051-i-have-for-the-first-time-found-what-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 12:57:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111051-i-have-for-the-first-time-found-what-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have for the first time found what I can truly love–I have found you. You are my sympathy–my better self–my good angel–I am bound to you with a strong attachment. I think you good, gifted, lovely: a fervent, a solemn passion is conceived in my heart; it leans to you, draws you to my centre and spring of life, wrap my existence about you–and, kindling in pure, powerful flame, fuses you and me in one." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2013 19:36:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
