<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/676753-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/676753-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:39:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440564-here-and-there-among-men-there-are-those-who-pause</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:39:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440564-here-and-there-among-men-there-are-those-who-pause]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here and there among men, there are those who pause in the hurried rush to listen to the call of a life that is more real… He who sees and hears too much is cursed for a dreamer, a fanatic, or a fool, by the mad mob who, having eyes, see not, ears and hear not, and refuse to understand… " -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97485-and-it-was-no-shame-to-her-that-she-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:39:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97485-and-it-was-no-shame-to-her-that-she-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it was no shame to her that she so dreamed. It was no shame that she called before her, one by one, those who had asked her to cross with them the threshold (of marriage) and those who might still ask her. It was no shame that, while her heart said always, &quot;no,&quot; she still waited - waited for one whom she knew not, but only knew that she would know him when he came. And it was no shame to her that, even while this was so, she saw herself in the years to come a wife and mother. " -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620247-there-is-a-bond-of-fellowship-in-sorrow-that-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:39:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620247-there-is-a-bond-of-fellowship-in-sorrow-that-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a bond of fellowship in sorrow that knows no conventionality." -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410457-i-have-always-been-taught-that-every-man-is-divinely</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410457-i-have-always-been-taught-that-every-man-is-divinely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always been taught… that every man is divinely called to his work, if that work is for the good of all men. His faithfulness or unfaithfulness to the call is revealed in the motives that prompt him to choose his field." -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:43:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 10:45:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18542-all-that-i-am-or-ever-hope-to-be-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 07:17:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18542-all-that-i-am-or-ever-hope-to-be-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that I am or ever hope to be, I owe to my angel mother." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18297-be-a-mother-who-is-committed-to-loving-her-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 07:18:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Marjorie Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18297-be-a-mother-who-is-committed-to-loving-her-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be a Mother who is committed to loving her children into standing on higher ground than the enviroment surrounding them. Mothers are endowed with a love that is unlike any other love on the face of the earth." -- Marjorie Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31829-you-are-doing-god-s-work-you-are-doing-it-wonderfully</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 07:19:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31829-you-are-doing-god-s-work-you-are-doing-it-wonderfully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are doing God's work. You are doing it wonderfully well. He is blessing you, and He will bless you, --even--no, -especially--when your days and your nights may be most challenging. Like the woman who anonymously, meekly, perhaps even with hesitation and some embarrassment, fought her way through the crowd just to touch the hem of the Master's garment, so Christ will say to the women who worry and wonder and weep over their responsibility as mothers, `Daughter, be of good comfort; thy faith hath made thee whole.' And it will make your children whole as well." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222390-always-remember-son-the-best-boss-is-the-one-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 08:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Ralph Moody]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222390-always-remember-son-the-best-boss-is-the-one-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always remember, Son, the best boss is the one who bosses the least. Whether it's cattle, or horses, or men; the least government is the best government.  " -- Ralph Moody]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222410-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-men-in-this-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 08:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Ralph Moody]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222410-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-men-in-this-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two kinds of men in this world: Honest men and dishonest men. ...Any man who says the world owes him a living is dishonest. The same God that made you and me made this earth. And He planned it so that it would yield every single thing that the people on it need. But He was careful to plan it so that it would only yield up its wealth in exchange for the labor of man. Any man who tries to share in that wealth without contributing the work of his brain or his hands is dishonest." -- Ralph Moody]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147399-do-not-let-yourself-be-bothered-by-the-inconsequential-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 22:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Louis L'Amour]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147399-do-not-let-yourself-be-bothered-by-the-inconsequential-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not let yourself be bothered by the inconsequential. One has only so much time in this world, so devote it to the work and the people most important to you, to those you love and things that matter. One can waste half a lifetime with people one doesn't really like, or doing things when one would be better off somewhere else." -- Louis L'Amour]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317537-i-want-to-do-something-splendid-something-heroic-or-wonderful-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 12:10:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317537-i-want-to-do-something-splendid-something-heroic-or-wonderful-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to do something splendid...something heroic or wonderful that won't be forgotten after I'm dead. I don't know what, but I'm on the watch for it and mean to astonish you all someday." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155224-in-a-perfect-friendship-this-appreciative-love-is-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 10:53:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155224-in-a-perfect-friendship-this-appreciative-love-is-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a perfect Friendship this Appreciative love is, I think, often so great and so firmly based that each member of the circle feels, in his secret heart, humbled before the rest. Sometimes he wonders what he is doing there among his betters. He is lucky beyond desert to be in such company. Especially when the whole group is together; each bringing out all that is best, wisest, or funniest in all the others. Those are the golden sessions; when four or five of us after a hard day's walk have come to our inn; when our slippers are on, our feet spread out toward the blaze and our drinks are at our elbows; when the whole world, and something beyond the world, opens itself to our minds as we talk; and no one has any claim on or any responsibility for another, but all are freemen and equals as if we had first met an hour ago, while at the same time an Affection mellowed by the years enfolds us. Life — natural life — has no better gift to give. Who could have deserved it?" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 11:00:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
