<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678185-marc]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678185-marc" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 04:12:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407711-floote-what-is-going-on-do-they-think-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 04:12:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407711-floote-what-is-going-on-do-they-think-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Floote, what is going on? Do they think I
am contagious? Should I assure them I was
born with a nose this size?" -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295050-i-mean-to-say-really-i-am-near-to-developing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 02:50:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295050-i-mean-to-say-really-i-am-near-to-developing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean to say, really, I am near to developing a neurosis - is there anyone around who doesn't want to study or kill me?&quot;
Floote raised a tentative hand.
&quot;Ah, yes, thank you, Floote.&quot;
&quot;There is also Mrs Tunstell, madam,&quot; he offered hopefully, is if Ivy were some kind of consolation prize.
&quot;I notice you don't mention my fair-weather husband.&quot;
&quot;I suspect, at this moment, madam, he probably wants to kill you.&quot;
Alexia couldn't help smiling. &quot;Good point." -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429946-mary-lou-et-moi-on-est-amies-depuis-qu-on-est</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 00:16:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Janet Evanovich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429946-mary-lou-et-moi-on-est-amies-depuis-qu-on-est]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mary Lou et moi, on est amies depuis qu’on est toutes petites. J’étais le boute-en-train de service, et elle, le cancre de la classe. « Cancre » n’est peut-être pas le mot juste. Disons que ses objectifs n’étaient pas très hauts. Elle voulait se marier et fonder une famille. Et si elle pouvait épouser le capitaine d’une équipe de foot, c’était encore mieux. [...]
Moi, à la même époque, je rêvais d’épouser Aladin pour qu’il m’emmène sur son tapis volant. Donc, vous voyez : on n’avait pas les mêmes valeurs." -- Janet Evanovich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221706-i-said-i-know-why-you-re-afraid-to-fight-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:50:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Ilona Andrews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221706-i-said-i-know-why-you-re-afraid-to-fight-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said, I know why you’re afraid to fight with me.”
&quot;And why is that?” If he flexed again, I’d have to implement emergency measures. Maybe I could kick some sand at him or something. Hard to look hot brushing sand out of your eyes.
&quot;You want me.”
Oh boy.
&quot;You can’t resist my subtle charm, so you’re afraid you’re going to make a spectacle out of yourself.”
&quot;You know what? Don’t talk to me." -- Ilona Andrews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291827-the-phone-rang-i-picked-it-up-are-you-sitting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 02:50:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Ilona Andrews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291827-the-phone-rang-i-picked-it-up-are-you-sitting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The phone rang. I picked it up. 

“Are you sitting down?” Curran's voice asked. 
“Yes.” 
“Good.” 

&lt;i&gt;Click.&lt;/i&gt;

I listened to the disconnect signal. If he wanted me to sit, then I'd stand. I got up. The chair got up with me and I ended up bent over my desk, with the chair stuck to my butt. I grabbed the edge of the chair and tried to pull it off. 

It remained stuck. 

I would murder him. Slowly. And I'd enjoy every second of it." -- Ilona Andrews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561380-eat-slowly-the-blueblood-said-don-t-cut-your-food-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 07:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Ilona Andrews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561380-eat-slowly-the-blueblood-said-don-t-cut-your-food-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eat slowly,&quot; the blueblood said. &quot;Don't cut your food with the fork. Cut it with the knife, and make the pieces small enough so you can answer a question without having to swallow first.&quot; 

Why me? &quot;Right. Any other tips?&quot; Her sarcasm whistled right over his head. 

&quot;Yes. Look at me and not at your plate. If you have to look at your plate, glance at it occasionally.&quot; 

Rose put down her fork. &quot;Lord Submarine...&quot; 

&quot;Camarine.&quot; 

&quot;Whatever.&quot; 

&quot;You can call me Declan.&quot; He said it as if granting her a knighthood. The nerve. 

&quot;Declan, then. How did you spend your day?&quot; 

He frowned. 

&quot;It's a simple question: How did you spend your day? What did you do prior to the fight and the pancake making?&quot; 

&quot;I rested from my journey,&quot; he said with a sudden regal air. 

&quot;You took a nap&quot; 

&quot;Possibly.&quot; 

&quot;I spent my day scrubbing, vacuuming and dusting ten offices in the Broken. I got there at seven thirty in the morning and left at six. My back hurts, I can still smell bleach on my fingers, and my feet feel as flat as these pancakes. Tomorrow, I have to go back to work, and I want to eat my food in peace and quiet. I have good table manners. They may not be good enough for you, but they're definitely good enough for the Edge, and they are the height of social graces in this house. So please keep your critique to yourself.&quot; 

The look on his face was worth having him under her roof. As if he had gotten slapped.

She smiled at him. &quot;Oh and thank you for the pancakes. They are delicious." -- Ilona Andrews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726238-what-s-that-she-asked-the-girl-wrinkling-her-nose-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 00:56:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Gail Carriger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/726238-what-s-that-she-asked-the-girl-wrinkling-her-nose-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What’s that?” she asked the girl, wrinkling her nose.

“Oh, that? That’s just Pillover.”

“And what’s a pillover, when it’s at home?”

“My little brother.”

“Ah, I commiserate. I have several of my own. Dashed inconvenient, brothers." -- Gail Carriger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288177-you-slept-with-curran-and-you-didn-t-tell-me-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 15:09:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marc add a quote by Ilona Andrews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288177-you-slept-with-curran-and-you-didn-t-tell-me-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You slept with Curran and you didn’t tell me? I’m your best friend.”
“It didn’t come up.”
“How disappointing for you.”
Ha-ha. “That’s not what I meant." -- Ilona Andrews]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
