<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678779-charlsie-paine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678779-charlsie-paine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:19:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:19:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27324-here-s-to-alcohol-the-rose-colored-glasses-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to alcohol, the rose colored glasses of life." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48412-things-are-sweeter-when-they-re-lost-i-know--because-once-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:19:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48412-things-are-sweeter-when-they-re-lost-i-know--because-once-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things are sweeter when they're lost. I know--because once I wanted something and got it. It was the only thing I ever wanted badly, Dot, and when I got it it turned to dust in my hand." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48407-she-was-dazzling---alight-it-was-agony-to-comprehend-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:19:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48407-she-was-dazzling---alight-it-was-agony-to-comprehend-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was dazzling-- alight; it was agony to comprehend her beauty in a glance." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:21:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first thing you notice about New Orleans are the burying grounds - the cemeteries - and they're a cold proposition, one of the best things there are here. Going by, you try to be as quiet as possible, better to let them sleep. Greek, Roman, sepulchres- palatial mausoleums made to order, phantomesque, signs and symbols of hidden decay - ghosts of women and men who have sinned and who've died and are now living in tombs. The past doesn't pass away so quickly here. You could be dead for a long time.

The ghosts race towards the light, you can almost hear the heavy breathing spirits, all determined to get somewhere. New Orleans, unlike a lot of those places you go back to and that don't have the magic anymore, still has got it. Night can swallow you up, yet none of it touches you. Around any corner, there's a promise of something daring and ideal and things are just getting going. There's something obscenely joyful behind every door, either that or somebody crying with their head in their hands. A lazy rhythm looms in the dreamy air and the atmosphere pulsates with bygone duels, past-life romance, comrades requesting comrades to aid them in some way. You can't see it, but you know it's here. Somebody is always sinking. Everyone seems to be from some very old Southern families. Either that or a foreigner. I like the way it is.

There are a lot of places I like, but I like New Orleans better. There's a thousand different angles at any moment. At any time you could run into a ritual honoring some vaguely known queen. Bluebloods, titled persons like crazy drunks, lean weakly against the walls and drag themselves through the gutter. Even they seem to have insights you might want to listen to. No action seems inappropriate here. The city is one very long poem. Gardens full of pansies, pink petunias, opiates. Flower-bedecked shrines, white myrtles, bougainvillea and purple oleander stimulate your senses, make you feel cool and clear inside.

Everything in New Orleans is a good idea. Bijou temple-type cottages and lyric cathedrals side by side. Houses and mansions, structures of wild grace. Italianate, Gothic, Romanesque, Greek Revival standing in a long line in the rain. Roman Catholic art. Sweeping front porches, turrets, cast-iron balconies, colonnades- 30-foot columns, gloriously beautiful- double pitched roofs, all the architecture of the whole wide world and it doesn't move. All that and a town square where public executions took place. In New Orleans you could almost see other dimensions. There's only one day at a time here, then it's tonight and then tomorrow will be today again. Chronic melancholia hanging from the trees. You never get tired of it. After a while you start to feel like a ghost from one of the tombs, like you're in a wax museum below crimson clouds. Spirit empire. Wealthy empire. One of Napoleon's generals, Lallemaud, was said to have come here to check it out, looking for a place for his commander to seek refuge after Waterloo. He scouted around and left, said that here the devil is damned, just like everybody else, only worse. The devil comes here and sighs. New Orleans. Exquisite, old-fashioned. A great place to live vicariously. Nothing makes any difference and you never feel hurt, a great place to really hit on things. Somebody puts something in front of you here and you might as well drink it. Great place to be intimate or do nothing. A place to come and hope you'll get smart - to feed pigeons looking for handouts" -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244849-first-one-gives-off-his-best-picture-the-bright-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:29:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244849-first-one-gives-off-his-best-picture-the-bright-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First one gives off his best picture, the bright and finished product mended with bluff and falsehood and humor. Then more details are required and one paints a second portrait, and third---before long the best lines cancel out---and the secret is exposed at last; the planes of the picture have intermingled and given us away, and though we paint and paint we can no longer sell a picture. We must be satisfied with hoping such fatuous accounts of ourselves as we make to our wives and children and business associates are accepted as true." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442174-a-sense-of-responsibility-would-spoil-her-she-s-too-pretty</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:29:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442174-a-sense-of-responsibility-would-spoil-her-she-s-too-pretty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sense of responsibility would spoil her. She's too pretty." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193303-the-difference-between-treason-and-patriotism-is-only-a-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:47:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193303-the-difference-between-treason-and-patriotism-is-only-a-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difference between treason and patriotism is only a matter of dates." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94420-until-the-day-when-god-shall-deign-to-reveal-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:47:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94420-until-the-day-when-god-shall-deign-to-reveal-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until the day when God shall deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is summed up in these two words,-Wait and hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228797-life-is-a-storm-my-young-friend-you-will-bask</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:47:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228797-life-is-a-storm-my-young-friend-you-will-bask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a storm, my young friend. You will bask in the sunlight one moment, be shattered on the rocks the next. What makes you a man is what you do when that storm comes. You must look into that storm and shout as you did in Rome. Do your worst, for I will do mine! Then the fates will know you as we know you" -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227655-we-are-always-in-a-hurry-to-be-happy-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:48:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227655-we-are-always-in-a-hurry-to-be-happy-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are always in a hurry to be happy...; for when we have suffered a long time, we have great difficulty in believing in good fortune." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248662-abbe-faria-here-is-your-final-lesson---do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:49:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248662-abbe-faria-here-is-your-final-lesson---do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Abbe Faria: Here is your final lesson - do not commit the crime for which you now serve the sentence. God said, Vengeance is mine.
Edmond Dantes: I don't believe in God.
Abbe Faria: It doesn't matter. He believes in you. " -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280724-hatred-is-blind-rage-carries-you-away-and-he-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:49:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280724-hatred-is-blind-rage-carries-you-away-and-he-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hatred is blind; rage carries you away; and he who pours out vengeance runs the risk of tasting a bitter draught." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255401-the-friends-we-have-lost-do-not-repose-under-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:50:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255401-the-friends-we-have-lost-do-not-repose-under-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...The friends we have lost do not repose under the ground...they are buried deep in our hearts. It has been thus ordained that they may always accompany us..." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97238-so-much-the-worse-for-those-who-fear-wine-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:50:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97238-so-much-the-worse-for-those-who-fear-wine-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So much the worse for those who fear wine, for it is because they have some bad thoughts which they are afraid the liquor will extract from their hearts." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262465-to-learn-is-not-to-know-there-are-the-learners</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:56:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262465-to-learn-is-not-to-know-there-are-the-learners]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To learn is not to know; there are the learners and the learned.  Memory makes the one, philosophy the others." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327517-often-we-pass-beside-happiness-without-seeing-it-without-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 10:56:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327517-often-we-pass-beside-happiness-without-seeing-it-without-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often we pass beside happiness without seeing it, without looking at it, or even if we have seen and looked at it, without recognizing it." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76360-if-only-we-d-stop-trying-to-be-happy-we-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76360-if-only-we-d-stop-trying-to-be-happy-we-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only we'd stop trying to be happy, we could have a pretty good time." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42621-i-don-t-know-if-i-should-care-for-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:52:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42621-i-don-t-know-if-i-should-care-for-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know if I should care for a man who made life easy; I should want someone who made it interesting." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7205-ah-good-conversation---there-s-nothing-like-it-is-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7205-ah-good-conversation---there-s-nothing-like-it-is-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, good conversation - there's nothing like it, is there?  The air of ideas is the only air worth breathing." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41729-my-little-dog-a-heartbeat-at-my-feet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:52:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41729-my-little-dog-a-heartbeat-at-my-feet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My little dog—a heartbeat at my feet." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44461-genius-is-of-small-use-to-a-woman-who-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:52:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44461-genius-is-of-small-use-to-a-woman-who-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genius is of small use to a woman who does not know how to do her hair." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28371-nothing-is-more-perplexing-to-a-man-than-the-mental</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28371-nothing-is-more-perplexing-to-a-man-than-the-mental]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is more perplexing to a man than the mental process of a woman who reasons her emotions." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213706-a-classic-is-classic-not-because-it-conforms-to-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 12:57:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213706-a-classic-is-classic-not-because-it-conforms-to-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A classic is classic not because it conforms to certain structural rules, or fits certain definitions (of which its author had quite probably never heard). It is classic because of a certain eternal and irrepressible freshness." -- Edith Wharton ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118379-the-visible-world-is-a-daily-miracle-for-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 13:05:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118379-the-visible-world-is-a-daily-miracle-for-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The visible world is a daily miracle for those who have eyes and ears; and I still warm hands thankfully at the old fire, though every year it is fed with the dry wood of more old memories. " -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 14:28:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone needs to tell those tales.  When the battles are fought and won and lost, when the pirates find their treasures and the dragons eat their foes for breakfast with a nice cup of Lapsang souchong, someone needs to tell their bits of overlapping narrative.  There's magic in that.  It's in the listener, and for each and every ear it will be different, and it will affect them in ways they can never predict.  From the mundane to the profound.  You may tell a tale that takes up residence in someone's soul, becomes their blood and self and purpose.  That tale will move them and drive them and who knows what they might do because of it, because of your words.  That is your role, your gift.  Your sister may be able to see the future, but you yourself can shape it, boy.  Do not forget that... there are many kinds of magic, after all." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458310-life-takes-us-to-unexpected-places-sometimes-the-future-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 14:29:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458310-life-takes-us-to-unexpected-places-sometimes-the-future-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life takes us to unexpected places sometimes. The future is never set in stone, remember that." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475691-most-maidens-are-perfectly-capable-of-rescuing-themselves-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 14:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475691-most-maidens-are-perfectly-capable-of-rescuing-themselves-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most maidens are perfectly capable of rescuing themselves in my experience, at least the ones worth something, in any case." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 14:29:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We lead strange lives, chasing our dreams around from place to place." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462422-i-am-tired-of-trying-to-hold-things-together-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 14:29:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/462422-i-am-tired-of-trying-to-hold-things-together-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am tired of trying to hold things together that cannot be held. Trying to  control what cannot be controlled. I am tired of denying myself what I want for fear of breaking things I cannot fix. They will break no matter what we do." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109461-when-you-will-not-fly-into-a-passion-people-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 07:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Charlsie add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109461-when-you-will-not-fly-into-a-passion-people-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you will not fly into a passion people know you are stronger than they are, because you are strong enough to hold in your rage, and they are not, and they say stupid things they wish they hadn't said afterward. There's nothing so strong as rage, except what makes you hold it in--that's stronger. It's a good thing not to answer your enemies." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
