<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678742-kindell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678742-kindell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:15:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2792-and-so-it-goes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:16:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2792-and-so-it-goes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so it goes..." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300857-i-give-in-and-light-another-cigarette-even-though-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:47:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300857-i-give-in-and-light-another-cigarette-even-though-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I give in and light another cigarette even though last night the surgeon general came on the television set and shook his finger at everybody, trying to convince us that smoking will kill us.  But Mother once told me tongue kissing would turn me blind and I'm starting to think it's all just a big plot between the surgeon general and Mother to make sure no one ever has any fun." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233607-her-nose-wrinkle-up-cause-now-she-got-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233607-her-nose-wrinkle-up-cause-now-she-got-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her nose wrinkle up cause now she got to remember to say she Mae Mobley Three, when her whole life she can remember, she been telling people she Mae Mobley Two.  When you little, you only get asked two questions, what's your name and how old you is, so you better get em right." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199890-constantine-sat-down-next-to-me-at-the-kitchen-table</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:52:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199890-constantine-sat-down-next-to-me-at-the-kitchen-table]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Constantine sat down next to me, at the kitchen table,  I heard the cracking of her swollen joints.  She pressed her thumb hard in the palm of my hand, something we both knew meant 'Listen to me.'  &quot;Every morning, until you dead in the ground, you gone have to make this decision.&quot; Constantine was so close, I could see the blackness of her gums. &quot;You gone have to ask yourself, am I gone believe what them fools say about me today?&quot;  She kept her thumb pressed hard in my hand.  I nodded that I understood.  I was just smart enough to realize she meant white people.  And even though I still felt miserable, and knew that I was, most likely, ugly, it was the first time she ever talked to me like I was something besides my mother's white child.  All my life I'd been told what to believe about politics, coloreds, being a girl.  But with Constantine's thumb pressed in my hand, I realized I actually had a choice in what I could believe." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310469-i-haven-t-had-the-chance-to-look-at-too-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:54:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310469-i-haven-t-had-the-chance-to-look-at-too-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I haven’t had the chance to look at too many men’s faces up close. And I noticed how his skin was thicker than mine, and a gorgeous shade of toast.  The stiff blond hairs on his cheeks and chin seemed to be growing before my eyes.  He smelled like starch.  Like pine.  His nose wasn’t so pointy afterall.  …And out of the blue, he kissed me. Right in the middle of the Robert E. Lee Hotel Restaurant, he kissed me so slowly with an open mouth and every single thing in my body-my skin, my collarbone, the hollow backs of my knees, everything inside of me filled up with light." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427860-because-ain-t-that-white-people-for-you-wondering-if-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:54:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427860-because-ain-t-that-white-people-for-you-wondering-if-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because ain’t that white people for you, wondering if they are happy enough." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440270-miss-celia-stares-down-into-the-pot-like-she-s-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 18:56:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kindell add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440270-miss-celia-stares-down-into-the-pot-like-she-s-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miss Celia stares down into the pot like she's looking for her future.  &quot;Are you happy, Minny?&quot;
&quot;Why you ask me funny questions like that?&quot;
&quot;But are you?&quot;
&quot;Course I's happy.  You happy too. Big house, big yard, husband looking after you.&quot;  I frown at Miss Celia and I make sure she can see it.  Because ain't that white people for you, wondering if they are happy ENOUGH." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
