<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678828-terence]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/678828-terence" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:42:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488967-when-its-100-degrees-in-new-york-it-s-72-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:42:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Neil Simon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488967-when-its-100-degrees-in-new-york-it-s-72-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When its 100 degrees in New York, it's 72 in Los Angeles. When its 30 degrees in New York, in Los Angeles it's still 72. However, there are 6 million interesting people in New York, and only 72 in Los Angeles." -- Neil Simon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488972-new-york-is-to-the-nation-what-the-white-church</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:44:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488972-new-york-is-to-the-nation-what-the-white-church]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New York is to the nation what the white church spire is to the village - the visible symbol of aspiration and faith, the white plume saying the way is up" -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488547-once-you-have-lived-in-new-york-and-made-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:44:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488547-once-you-have-lived-in-new-york-and-made-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have lived in New York and made it your home, no place else is good enough" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488545-skyscraper-national-park</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:45:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488545-skyscraper-national-park]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Skyscraper National Park" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488991-new-york-had-all-the-iridescence-of-the-beginning-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488991-new-york-had-all-the-iridescence-of-the-beginning-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New York had all the iridescence of the beginning of the world." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488986-if-man-can-live-in-manhattan-he-can-live-anywhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:46:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488986-if-man-can-live-in-manhattan-he-can-live-anywhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If man can live in Manhattan, he can live anywhere." -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392598-it-couldn-t-have-happened-anywhere-but-in-little-old-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:46:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by O. Henry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392598-it-couldn-t-have-happened-anywhere-but-in-little-old-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It couldn't have happened anywhere but in little old New York." -- O. Henry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70459-this-is-the-city-and-i-am-one-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:48:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70459-this-is-the-city-and-i-am-one-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the city, and I am one of the citizens/Whatever interests the rest interests me" -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489003-when-you-leave-new-york-you-are-astonished-at-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:48:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Fran Lebowitz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489003-when-you-leave-new-york-you-are-astonished-at-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you leave New York, you are astonished at how clean the rest of the world is. Clean is not enough." -- Fran Lebowitz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172182-it-was-generally-agreed-that-a-coffin-size-studio-on-avenue</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:48:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172182-it-was-generally-agreed-that-a-coffin-size-studio-on-avenue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was generally agreed that a coffin-size studio on Avenue D was preferable to living in one of the boroughs. Moving from one Brooklyn or Staten Island neighborhood to another was fine, but unless you had children to think about, even the homeless saw it as a step down to leave Manhattan. Customers quitting the island for Astoria or Cobble Hill would claim to welcome the change of pace, saying it would be nice to finally have a garden or live a little closer to the airport. They’d put a good face one it, but one could always detect an underlying sense of defeat. The apartments might be bigger and cheaper in other places, but one could never count on their old circle of friend making the long trip to attend a birthday party. Even Washington Heights was considered a stretch. People referred to it as Upstate New York, though it was right there in Manhattan." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70929-chapter-1-he-adored-new-york-city-he-idolized-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:50:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70929-chapter-1-he-adored-new-york-city-he-idolized-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chapter 1.
He adored New York City. He idolized it all out of proportion...&lt;i&gt;no, make that:&lt;/i&gt; he - he romanticized it all out of proportion. &lt;i&gt;Yes.&lt;/i&gt; To him, no matter what the season was, this was still a town that existed in black and white and pulsated to the great tunes of George Gershwin.'

&lt;i&gt;Uh, no let me start this over.&lt;/i&gt;

'Chapter 1.
He was too romantic about Manhattan, as he was about everything else. He thrived on the hustle bustle of the crowds and the traffic. To him, New York meant beautiful women and street-smart guys who seemed to know all the angles...'. 

&lt;i&gt;Ah, corny, too corny for my taste. Can we ... can we try and make it more profound?&lt;/i&gt;

'Chapter 1.
He adored New York City. For him, it was a metaphor for the decay of contemporary culture. The same lack of individual integrity that caused so many people to take the easy way out was rapidly turning the town of his dreams in...'

&lt;i&gt;No, that's a little bit too preachy. I mean, you know, let's face it, I want to sell some books here.&lt;/i&gt;

'Chapter 1.
He adored New York City, although to him it was a metaphor for the decay of contemporary culture. How hard it was to exist in a society desensitized by drugs, loud music, television, crime, garbage...'

&lt;i&gt;Too angry, I don't want to be angry.&lt;/i&gt;

'Chapter 1.
He was as tough and romantic as the city he loved. Behind his black-rimmed glasses was the coiled sexual power of a jungle cat.'

&lt;i&gt;I love this.&lt;/i&gt;

'New York was his town, and it always would be." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18940-i-would-give-the-greatest-sunset-in-the-world-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:50:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18940-i-would-give-the-greatest-sunset-in-the-world-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would give the greatest sunset in the world for one sight of New York's skyline. Particularly when one can't see the details. Just the shapes. The shapes and the thought that made them. The sky over New York and the will of man made visible. What other religion do we need? And then people tell me about pilgrimages to some dank pesthole in a jungle where they go to do homage to a crumbling temple, to a leering stone monster with a pot belly, created by some leprous savage. Is it beauty and genius they want to see? Do they seek a sense of the sublime? Let them come to New York, stand on the shore of the Hudson, look and kneel. When I see the city from my window - no, I don't feel how small I am - but I feel that if a war came to threaten this, I would throw myself into space, over the city, and protect these buildings with my body." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39647-i-love-new-york-even-though-it-isn-t-mine-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39647-i-love-new-york-even-though-it-isn-t-mine-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love New York, even though it isn't mine, the way something has to be, a tree or a street or a house, something, anyway, that belongs to me because I belong to it." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60427-there-is-no-question-that-there-is-an-unseen-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:50:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60427-there-is-no-question-that-there-is-an-unseen-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no question that there is an unseen world. The problem is, how far is it from midtown and how late is it open?" -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121588-one-belongs-to-new-york-instantly-one-belongs-to-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Tom Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121588-one-belongs-to-new-york-instantly-one-belongs-to-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One belongs to New York instantly, one belongs to it as much in five minutes as in five years." -- Tom Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176010-of-course-in-los-angeles-everything-is-based-on-driving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176010-of-course-in-los-angeles-everything-is-based-on-driving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course, in Los Angeles, &lt;I&gt;everything&lt;/i&gt; is based on driving, even the killings. In New York, most people don't have cars, so if you want to kill a person, you have to take the subway to their house. And sometimes on the way, the train is delayed and you get impatient, so you have to kill someone on the subway. That's why there are so many subway murders; no one has a car." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417341-people-go-to-la-to-find-themselves-they-come-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:51:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Lindsey Kelk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417341-people-go-to-la-to-find-themselves-they-come-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People go to LA to &quot;find themselves&quot;, they come to New York to become someone new." -- Lindsey Kelk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9253-the-city-seen-from-the-queensboro-bridge-is-always-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:52:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9253-the-city-seen-from-the-queensboro-bridge-is-always-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The city seen from the Queensboro Bridge is always the city seen for the first time, in its first wild promise of all the mystery and the beauty in the world." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69243-the-true-new-yorker-secretly-believes-that-people-living-anywhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69243-the-true-new-yorker-secretly-believes-that-people-living-anywhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true New Yorker secretly believes that people living anywhere else have to be, in some sense, kidding." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18260-cut-off-as-i-am-it-is-inevitable-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18260-cut-off-as-i-am-it-is-inevitable-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cut off as I am, it is inevitable that I should sometimes feel like a shadow walking in a shadowy world. When this happens I ask to be taken to New York City. Always I return home weary but I have the comforting certainty that mankind is real flesh and I myself am not a dream." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277464-so-i-went-to-new-york-city-to-be-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 08:53:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277464-so-i-went-to-new-york-city-to-be-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So I went to New York City to be born again.  It was and remains easy for most Americans to go somewhere else and start anew.  I wasn't like my parents.  I didn't have any supposedly sacred piece of land or shoals of friends to leave behind.  Nowhere has the number zero been of more philisophical value than in the United States.... and when the [train] plunged into a tunnel under New York City, with it's lining of pipes and wires, I was out of the womb and into the birth canal." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
