<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/680224-bill]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/680224-bill" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 11:14:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5186-this-is-the-sixty-nine-i-told-him-presenting-the-magazine</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2007 11:14:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5186-this-is-the-sixty-nine-i-told-him-presenting-the-magazine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the sixty-nine,&quot; I told him, presenting the magazine in front of him. I put my fingers -- two of them -- on the action, so that he would not overlook it. &quot;Why is it dubbed sixty-nine?&quot; he asked, because he is a person hot on fire with curiosity. &quot;It was invented in 1969. My friend Gregory knows a friend of the nephew of the inventor.&quot; &quot;What did people do before 1969?&quot; &quot;Merely blowjobs and masticating box, but never in chorus." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682-the-street-finds-its-own-uses-for-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 18:28:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682-the-street-finds-its-own-uses-for-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The street finds its own uses for things." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37886-war-is-like-any-other-bad-relationship-of-course-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 10:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Richard K Morgan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37886-war-is-like-any-other-bad-relationship-of-course-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is like any other bad relationship. Of course you want out, but at what price? And perhaps more importantly, once you get out, will you be any better off?&quot;
   - Quellcrist Falconer" -- Richard K Morgan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12561-telling-me-i-can-do-anything-i-want-is-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12561-telling-me-i-can-do-anything-i-want-is-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Telling me I can do anything I want is like pulling the plug out of the bath and then telling the water it can go anywhere it wants. Try it, and see what happens." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do people, like, not curse? How is it possible? There are these gaps in speech where you just have to put a &quot;fuck.&quot; I'll tell you who the most admirable people in the world are: newscasters. If that was me, I'd be like, &quot;And the motherfuckers flew the fucking plane right into the Twin Towers.&quot; How could you not, if you're a human being? Maybe they're not so admirable. Maybe they're robot zombies." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:19:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until a man is twenty-five, he still thinks, every so often, that under the right circumstances he could be the baddest motherfucker in the world. If I moved to a martial-arts monastery in China and studied real hard for ten years. If my family was wiped out by Colombian drug dealers and I swore myself to revenge. If I got a fatal disease, had one year to live, and devoted it to wiping out street crime. If I just dropped out and devoted my life to being bad." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64560-arguing-with-anonymous-strangers-on-the-internet-is-a-sucker-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:20:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64560-arguing-with-anonymous-strangers-on-the-internet-is-a-sucker-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Arguing with anonymous strangers on the Internet is a sucker's game because they almost always turn out to be&amp;mdash;or to be indistinguishable from&amp;mdash;self-righteous sixteen-year-olds possessing infinite amounts of free time." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:21:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:21:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you wake up. Sometimes the fall kills you. And sometimes, when you fall, you fly." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 22:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83325-they-were-jesuits-she-told-me-that-means-they-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 16:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83325-they-were-jesuits-she-told-me-that-means-they-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were Jesuits,&quot; she told me. &quot;That means they believe in God but not in terlet paper. You should have seen their underwear. Disgusting." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84525-this-is-hurting-me-a-lot-more-than-it-s-hurting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 10:59:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84525-this-is-hurting-me-a-lot-more-than-it-s-hurting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is hurting me a lot more than it’s hurting you,&quot; he said. It was his standard line, but I knew that this time he was right. Worse than the boil was the stuff that came out of it. What got to me, and got to him even worse, was the stench, which was unbearable, and unlike anything I had come across before. It was, I thought, what evil must smell like—not an evil person but the wicked ideas that have made him that way. How could a person continue to live with something so rotten inside? And so much of it!" -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101330-our-opponent-is-an-alien-starship-packed-with-atomic-bombs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2008 08:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101330-our-opponent-is-an-alien-starship-packed-with-atomic-bombs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our opponent is an alien starship packed with atomic bombs,&quot; I said. &quot;We have a protractor." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102211-that-s-funny-because-if-anyone-actually-did-prove-the-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 11:18:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102211-that-s-funny-because-if-anyone-actually-did-prove-the-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's funny because if anyone actually did prove the existence of God we'd just tell him 'nice proof, Fraa Bly' and start believing in God." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 13:17:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who thinks sitting in church can make you a Christian must also think that sitting in a garage can make you a car." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123746-i-no-longer-drink-nearly-as-much-as-i-used</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 16:09:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123746-i-no-longer-drink-nearly-as-much-as-i-used]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer drink nearly as much as I used to but, still, my motto is Sine coffea nihil sum. Without coffee, I'm nothing." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 18:28:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 19:29:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If more of us valued food  and cheer and song above hoarded gold, it would be a merrier world." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655618-just-get-up-what-s-your-name-kid-g-man-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 11:01:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Tad Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655618-just-get-up-what-s-your-name-kid-g-man-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just get up.  What's your name, kid?&quot;  
&quot;G-man&quot;
&quot;I don't mean your codename down at the Dickhead Club.  What does it say on your driver's license?" -- Tad Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
