<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/681569-david-mahaffey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/681569-david-mahaffey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 13:22:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 13:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6029-in-every-important-way-we-are-such-secrets-from-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In every important way we are such secrets from one another, and I do believe that there is a separate language in each of us, also a separate aesthetics and a separate jurisprudence. Every single one of us is a little civilization built on the ruins of any number of preceding civilizations, but with our own variant notions of what is beautiful and what is acceptable - which, I hasten to add, we generally do not satisfy and by which we struggle to live. We take fortuitous resemblances among us to be actual likeness, because those around us have also fallen heir to the same customs, trade in the same coin, acknowledge, more or less, the same notions of decency and sanity. But all that really just allows us to coexist with the inviolable, intraversable, and utterly vast spaces between us." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 13:33:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61878-the-answer-to-the-great-question-of-life-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 13:59:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61878-the-answer-to-the-great-question-of-life-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Answer to the Great Question... Of Life, the Universe and Everything... Is... Forty-two,' said Deep Thought, with infinite majesty and calm." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40115-trust-me-i-m-telling-you-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 14:05:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40115-trust-me-i-m-telling-you-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trust me, I'm telling you stories." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154370-lies-1-there-is-only-the-present-and-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 14:10:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154370-lies-1-there-is-only-the-present-and-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lies 1: There is only the present and nothing to remember.
Lies 2: Time is a straight line.
Lies 3: The difference between the past and the futures is that one has happened while the other has not.
Lies 4: We can only be in one place at a time.
Lies 5: Any proposition that contains the word 'finite' (the world, the universe, experience, ourselves...)
Lies 6: Reality as something which can be agreed upon.
Lies 7: Reality is truth." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309606-it-takes-four-angels-to-oversee-an-apocalypse-a-recorder</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 09:14:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Chris Adrian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309606-it-takes-four-angels-to-oversee-an-apocalypse-a-recorder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes four angels to oversee an apocalypse: a recorder to make the book that would be scripture in the new world; a preserver to comfort and save those selected to be the first generation; an accuser to remind them why they suffer; and a destroyer to revoke the promise of survival and redemption, and to teach them the awful truth about furious sheltering grace." -- Chris Adrian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148770-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 12:49:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148770-your-cold-mornings-are-filled-with-the-heartache-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your cold mornings are filled with the heartache about the fact that although we are not at ease in this world, it is all we have, that it is ours but that it is full of strife, so that all we can call our own is strife; but even that is better than nothing at all, isn't it? And as you split the frost-laced wood with numb hands, rejoice that your uncertainty is God's will and His grace toward you that that is beautiful, and a part of a greater certainty, as your own father always said in his sermons and to you at home.  And as the ax bites into  the wood, be comforted in the fact that the ache in your heart and the confusion in your soul means that you are still alive, still human, and still open to the beauty of the world, even though you have done nothing to deserve it. And when you resent the ache in your heart, remember: You will be dead and buried soon enough." -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268158-there-was-a-moment-of-sorrow-disappointment-and-deep-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2010 12:51:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268158-there-was-a-moment-of-sorrow-disappointment-and-deep-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a moment of sorrow, disappointment, and deep love for his son, whom he at that second wished had had a chance of real escape.  Never mind why or whether or who or what consequence or ramification--the wake of sorrow and bitterness and resentment you would trail behind you, probably mostly for me--I just wish that you had made it beyond the bounds of this cold little radius, that when the archaeologists brush off this layer of our world in a million years and string off the boundaries of our rooms and tag and number every plate and table leg and shinbone, you would not be there; yours would not be the remains they would find and label &lt;i&gt;juvenile male.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353408-lane-himself-lit-a-cigarette-as-the-train-pulled-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 19:36:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353408-lane-himself-lit-a-cigarette-as-the-train-pulled-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lane himself lit a cigarette as the train pulled in. Then, like so many people, who, perhaps, ought to be issued only a very probational pass to meet trains, he tried to empty his face of all expression that might quite simply, perhaps even beautifully, reveal how he felt about the arriving person.
Franny was among the first of the girls to get off the train, from a car at the far, northern end of the platform. Lane spotted her immediately, and despite whatever it was he was trying to do with his face, his arm that shot up into the air was the whole truth." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360640-she-is-nine-beloved-as-open-faced-as-the-sky-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 10:02:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360640-she-is-nine-beloved-as-open-faced-as-the-sky-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is nine, beloved, as open-faced as the sky and as self-contained. I have watched her grow. As recently as three or four years ago, she had a young child's perfectly shallow receptiveness; she fitted into the world of time, it fitted into her, as thoughtlessly as sky fits its edges, or a river its banks. But as she has grown, her smile has widened with a touch of fear and her glance has taken on depth. Now she is aware of some of the losses you incur by being here--the extortionary rent you have to pay as long as you stay." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159902-it-s-funny-i-always-imagined-when-i-was-a-kid</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:38:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159902-it-s-funny-i-always-imagined-when-i-was-a-kid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's funny: I always imagined when I was a kid that adults had some kind of inner toolbox full of shiny tools: the saw of discernment, the hammer of wisdom, the sandpaper of patience.  But then when I grew up I found that life handed you these rusty bent old tools - friendships, prayer, conscience, honesty - and said 'do the best you can with these, they will have to do'.  And mostly, against all odds, they do." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369280-the-thing-about-light-is-that-it-really-isn-t-yours</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:39:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369280-the-thing-about-light-is-that-it-really-isn-t-yours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about light is that it really isn’t yours; it’s what you gather and shine back. And it gets more power from reflectiveness; if you sit still and take it in, it fills your cup, and then you can give it off yourself." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375650-it-is-unearned-love--the-love-that-goes-before-that-greets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 11:45:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375650-it-is-unearned-love--the-love-that-goes-before-that-greets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is unearned love--the love that goes before, that greets us on the way. It's the help you receive when you have no bright ideas left, when you are empty and desperate and have discovered that your best thinking and most charming charm have failed you. Grace is the light or electricity or juice or breeze that takes you from that isolated place and puts you with others who are as startled and embarrassed and eventually grateful as you are to be there." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8425-i-have-hated-words-and-i-have-loved-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 07:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8425-i-have-hated-words-and-i-have-loved-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have hated words and I have loved them, and I hope I have made them right." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 08:47:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506012-and-in-the-bloodlit-dark-behind-his-eyes-silver-phosphenes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 09:43:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506012-and-in-the-bloodlit-dark-behind-his-eyes-silver-phosphenes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in the bloodlit dark behind his eyes, silver phosphenes boiled in from the edge of space, hypnagogic images jerking past like a film compiled of random frames. Symbols, figures, faces, a blurred, fragmented mandala of visual information." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165309-he-thought-that-in-the-beauty-of-the-world-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 07:12:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165309-he-thought-that-in-the-beauty-of-the-world-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He thought that in the beauty of the world were hid a secret. He thought that the world’s heart beat at some terrible cost and that the world’s pain and its beauty moved in a relationship of diverging equity and that in this headlong deficit the blood of multitudes might ultimately be exacted for the vision of a single flower." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 19:53:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything is necessary. Every least thing. This is the hard lesson. Nothing can be dispensed with. Nothing despised. Because the seams are hid from us, you see. The joinery. The way in which the world is made. We have no way to know what could be taken away. What omitted. We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 19:54:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the nature of his profession that his experience with death should be greater than for most and he said that while it was true that time heals bereavement it does so only at the cost of the slow extinction of those loved ones from the heart's memory which is the sole place of their abode then or now. Faces fade, voices dim. Seize them back, whispered the sepulturero. Speak with them. Call their names. Do this and do not let sorrow die for it is the sweetening of every gift." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377948-nature-is-to-zoos-as-god-is-to-churches</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 09:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377948-nature-is-to-zoos-as-god-is-to-churches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nature is to zoos as God is to churches." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928145-we-cannot-see-the-universe-we-are-in-the-darkness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 19:15:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928145-we-cannot-see-the-universe-we-are-in-the-darkness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot see the universe. We are in the darkness of a trench, a deep cut, dark water heavier than earth, presences lit by our own blood, little biolumes, heroic and pathetic Promethei too afraid or weak to steal fire but able still to love. Gods are among us and they care nothing and are nothing like us.

This is how we are brave: we worship them anyway." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
