<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/68308-tammy-boyd-perlmutter]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/68308-tammy-boyd-perlmutter" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 15:56:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286606-i-am-forever-engaged-in-a-silent-battle-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 15:56:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Jena Morrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286606-i-am-forever-engaged-in-a-silent-battle-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am forever engaged in a silent battle in my head over whether or not to lift the fork to my mouth, and when I talk myself into doing so, I taste only shame. I have an eating disorder." -- Jena Morrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 15:17:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we find ourselves with a desire that nothing in this world can satisfy, the most probable explanation is that we were made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 14:19:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43352-i-will-have-nothing-to-do-with-a-god-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 19:23:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43352-i-will-have-nothing-to-do-with-a-god-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will have nothing to do with a God who cares only occasionally. I need a God who is with us always, everywhere, in the deepest depths as well as the highest heights. It is when things go wrong, when good things do not happen, when our prayers seem to have been lost, that God is most present. We do not need the sheltering wings when things go smoothly. We are closest to God in the darkness, stumbling along blindly." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420968-we-sometimes-choose-the-most-locked-up-dark-versions-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:08:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Shauna Niequist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420968-we-sometimes-choose-the-most-locked-up-dark-versions-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We sometimes choose the most locked up, dark versions of the story, but what a good friend does is turn on the lights, open the window, and remind us that there are a whole lot of ways to tell the same story." -- Shauna Niequist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641983-if-you-own-this-story-you-get-to-write-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:08:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641983-if-you-own-this-story-you-get-to-write-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you own this story you get to write the ending." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122072-storytellers-are-a-threat-they-threaten-all-champions-of-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:09:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Chinua Achebe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122072-storytellers-are-a-threat-they-threaten-all-champions-of-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Storytellers are a threat. They threaten all champions of control, they frighten usurpers of the right-to-freedom of the human spirit -- in state, in church or mosque, in party congress, in the university or wherever." -- Chinua Achebe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233569-my-story-is-important-not-because-it-is-mine-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:10:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233569-my-story-is-important-not-because-it-is-mine-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My story is important not because it is mine, God knows, but because if I tell it anything like right, the chances are you will recognize that in many ways it is also yours… it is precisely through these stories in all their particularity, as I have long believed and often said, that God makes himself known to each of us more powerfully and personally. If this is true, it means that to lose track of our stories is to be profoundly impoverished not only humanly but also spiritually." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327512-the-story-of-any-one-of-us-is-in-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:10:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327512-the-story-of-any-one-of-us-is-in-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the story of any one of us is in some measure the story of us all" -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140448-the-place-god-calls-you-to-is-the-place-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:11:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140448-the-place-god-calls-you-to-is-the-place-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place God calls you to is the place where your deep gladness and the world’s deep hunger meet." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158523-listen-to-your-life-see-it-for-the-fathomless-mystery</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:12:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158523-listen-to-your-life-see-it-for-the-fathomless-mystery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to your life. See it for the fathomless mystery it is. In the boredom and pain of it, no less than in the excitement and gladness: touch, taste, smell your way to the holy and hidden heart of it, because in the last analysis all moments are key moments, and life itself is grace." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33456-to-be-commanded-to-love-god-at-all-let-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33456-to-be-commanded-to-love-god-at-all-let-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be commanded to love God at all, let alone in the wilderness, is like being commanded to be well when we are sick, to sing for joy when we are dying of thirst, to run when our legs are broken. But this is the first and great commandment nonetheless. Even in the wilderness - especially in the wilderness - you shall love him." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206031-the-original-shimmering-self-gets-buried-so-deep-that-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:13:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206031-the-original-shimmering-self-gets-buried-so-deep-that-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The original, shimmering self gets buried so deep that most of us end up hardly living out of it at all.  Instead we live out all the other selves, which we are constantly putting on and taking off like coats and hats against the world’s weather" -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 11:13:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a world of magic and mystery, of deep darkness and flickering starlight. It is a world where terrible things happen and wonderful things too. It is a world where goodness is pitted against evil, love against hate, order against chaos, in a great struggle where often it is hard to be sure who belongs to which side because appearances are endlessly deceptive. Yet for all its confusion and wildness, it is a world where the battle goes ultimately to the good, who live happily ever after, and where in the long run everybody, good and evil alike, becomes known by his true name....That is the fairy tale of the Gospel with, of course, one crucial difference from all other fairy tales, which is that the claim made for it is that it is true, that it not only happened once upon a time but has kept on happening ever since and is happening still." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382960-when-you-remember-me-it-means-that-you-have-carried</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 11:16:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382960-when-you-remember-me-it-means-that-you-have-carried]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you remember me, it means that you have carried something of who I am with you, that I have left some mark of who I am on who you are. It means that you can summon me back to your mind even though countless years and miles may stand between us. It means that if we meet again, you will know me. It means that even after I die, you can still see my face and hear my voice and speak to me in your heart.
For as long as you remember me, I am never entirely lost. When I'm feeling most ghost-like, it is your remembering me that helps remind me that I actually exist. When I'm feeling sad, it's my consolation. When I'm feeling happy, it's part of why I feel that way.
If you forget me, one of the ways I remember who I am will be gone. If you forget, part of who I am will be gone." -- Frederick Buechner ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607582-unbelief-is-as-much-of-a-choice-as-belief-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 11:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tammy add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607582-unbelief-is-as-much-of-a-choice-as-belief-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unbelief is as much of a choice as belief is. What makes it in many ways more appealing is that whereas to believe in something requires some measure of understanding and effort, not to believe doesn't require much of anything at all." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
