<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/684092-seth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/684092-seth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 12:56:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5408-i-have-no-enemies-but-my-friends-don-t-like-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 12:56:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5408-i-have-no-enemies-but-my-friends-don-t-like-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no enemies.  But my friends don't like me." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5410-i-wouldn-t-mind-seeing-china-if-i-could-come-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 12:58:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5410-i-wouldn-t-mind-seeing-china-if-i-could-come-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wouldn't mind seeing China if I could come back the same day." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5412-you-have-to-distinguish-between-things-that-seemed-odd-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:01:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5412-you-have-to-distinguish-between-things-that-seemed-odd-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to distinguish between things that seemed odd when they were new but are now quite familiar, such as Ibsen and Wagner, and things that seemed crazy when they were new and seem crazy now, like 'Finnegans Wake' and Picasso." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5414-a-great-deal-of-intelligence-can-be-invested-in-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:03:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5414-a-great-deal-of-intelligence-can-be-invested-in-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A great deal of intelligence can be invested in ignorance when the need for illusion is deep." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5416-an-ideological-movement-is-a-collection-of-people-many-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:05:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Kenneth Minogue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5416-an-ideological-movement-is-a-collection-of-people-many-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An ideological movement is a collection of people many of whom could hardly bake a cake, fix a car, sustain a friendship or a marriage, or even do a quadratic equation, yet they believe they know how to rule the world.  The university, in which it is possible to combine theoretical pretension with comprehensive ineptitude, has become the natural habitat of the ideological enthusiast.  A kind of adventure playground, carefully insulated from reality in order to prevent absent-minded professors from bumping into things as they explore transcendental realms, has become the institutional base for civilizational self-hatred." -- Kenneth Minogue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5418-pray-always-for-all-the-learned-the-oblique-the-delicate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:05:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5418-pray-always-for-all-the-learned-the-oblique-the-delicate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pray always for all the learned, the oblique, the delicate. Let them not be  quite forgotten at the throne of God when the simple come into their kingdom." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5419-animistic-savages-prostrating-themselves-before-a-painted-stone-have-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:10:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5419-animistic-savages-prostrating-themselves-before-a-painted-stone-have-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Animistic savages prostrating themselves before a painted stone have always seemed to me to be nearer the truth than any Einstein or Bertrand Russell.  As it might be pigs in a crowded sty, jostling and shoving to bury their snouts in the trough; until one of them momentarily lifts his snout upwards in the air, in so doing expressing the hope of all enlightenment to come; breaking off from his guzzling to point with his lifted snout to where the angels and archangels gather round God's throne." -- Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5420-as-well-as-the-league-of-nations-delegates-themselves-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:11:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5420-as-well-as-the-league-of-nations-delegates-themselves-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As well as the [League of Nations] delegates themselves and their suites, there were innumerable campaigners of one sort and another, male and female, clerical and lay, young and old; all with some notion to publicise, some pet solution to offer, some organisation to promote.  They gathered in droves, fanning out through the city, and settling in hotels and pensions, from the Lakeside ones down to tiny obscure back-street establishments.  Ferocious ladies with moustaches, clergymen with black leather patches on the elbows of their jackets or cassocks and smelling of tobacco smoke, mad admirals who knew where to find the lost tribes of Israel, and scarcely saner generals who deduced prophetic warnings from the measurement of the pyramids; but one and all believers in the League's historic role to deliver mankind painlessly and inexpensively from the curse of war to the great advantage of all concerned." -- Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5421-perhaps-i-should-have-been-one-some-sort-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:12:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5421-perhaps-i-should-have-been-one-some-sort-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps I should have been one [some sort of a professional religious]; I like to think a monk notable for his austerities, the voice of one crying in the wilderness; but more probably a tiresome Unitarian in Walsall who writes incessantly to the local paper." -- Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5422-i-have-never-forgotten-these-visitors-or-ceased-to-marvel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5422-i-have-never-forgotten-these-visitors-or-ceased-to-marvel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never forgotten these visitors, or ceased to marvel at them, at how they have gone on from strength to strength, continuing to lighten our darkness, and to guide, counsel and instruct us; on occasion, momentarily abashed, but always ready to pick themselves up, put on their cardboard helmets, mount Rosinante, and go galloping off on yet another foray on behalf of the down-trodden and oppressed.  They are unquestionably one of the wonders of the age, and I shall treasure till I die as a blessed memory the spectacle of them travelling with radiant optimism through a famished countryside, wandering in happy bands about squalid, over-crowded towns, listening with unshakeable faith to the fatuous patter of carefully trained and indoctrinated guides, repeating like schoolchildren a multiplication table, the bogus statistics and mindless slogans endlessly intoned to them.  There, I would think, an earnest office-holder in some local branch of the League of Nations Union, there a godly Quaker who once had tea with Gandhi, there an inveigher against the Means Test and the Blasphemy Laws, there a staunch upholder of free speech and human rights, there an indomitable preventer of cruelty to animals; there scarred and worthy veterans of a hundred battles for truth, freedom and justice--all, all chanting the praises of Stalin and his Dictatorship of the Proletariat.  It was as though a vegetarian society had come out with a passionate plea for cannibalism, or Hitler had been nominated posthumously for the Nobel Peace Prize." -- Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5425-it-was-a-cold-still-afternoon-with-a-hard-steely</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:18:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Kenneth Grahame]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5425-it-was-a-cold-still-afternoon-with-a-hard-steely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a cold still afternoon with a hard steely sky overhead, when he slipped out of the warm parlour into the open air.  The country lay bare and entirely leafless around him, and he thought that he had never seen so far and intimately into the insides of things as on that winter day when Nature was deep in her annual slumber and seemed to have kicked the clothes off.  Copses, dells, quarries and all hidden places, which had been mysterious mines for exploration in leafy summer, now exposed themselves and their secrets pathetically, and seemed to ask him to overlook their shabby poverty for a while, til they could riot in rich masquerade as before, and trick and entice him with the old deceptions.  It was pitiful in a way, and yet cheering-even exhilarating.  He was glad that he liked the country undecorated, hard, and stripped of its finery.  He had got down to the bare bones of it, and they were fine and strong and simple.  He did not want the warm clover and the play of seeding grasses; the screens of quickset, the billowy drapery of beech and elm seemed best away; and with great cheerfulness of spirit he pushed on towards the Wild Wood, which lay before him  low and threatening, like a black reef in some still southern sea." -- Kenneth Grahame]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5430-the-catholic-novelist-in-the-south-will-see-many-distorted</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:22:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5430-the-catholic-novelist-in-the-south-will-see-many-distorted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Catholic novelist in the South will see many distorted images of Christ, but he will certainly feel that a distorted image of Christ is better than no image at all. I think he will feel a good deal more kinship with backwoods prophets and shouting fundamentalists than he will with those politer elements for whom the supernatural is an embarrassment and for whom religion has become a department of sociology or culture or personality development." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5434-reason-excludes-faith-alessandro-responded-watching-the-blood-red-mite-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:26:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5434-reason-excludes-faith-alessandro-responded-watching-the-blood-red-mite-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reason excludes faith,&quot; Alessandro responded, watching the blood-red mite as it made a dash for the rim. &quot;It's deliberately limited. It won't function with the materials of religion. You can come close to proving the existence of God by reason, but you can't do it absolutely. That's because you can't do anything absolutely by reason. That's because reason depends on postulates. Postulates defy proof and yet they are essential to reason. God is a postulate. I don't think God is interested in the verification of His existence, and, therefore, neither am I.  Anyway, I have professional reasons to believe. Nature and art pivot faithfully around God. Even dogs know that." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5435-an-enormous-emotion-beat-on-him-it-was-like-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:27:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5435-an-enormous-emotion-beat-on-him-it-was-like-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An enormous emotion beat on him; it was like something trying to get in, the pressure of gigantic wings against the glass.  Dona nobis pacem.  He withstood it, with all the bitter force of the school bench, the cement playground, the St. Pancras waiting room, Dallow's and Judy's secret lust, and the cold and unhappy moment on the pier.  If the glass broke, if the beast--whatever it was--got in, God knows what it would do.  He had a sense of huge havoc--the confession, the penance, and the sacrament--an awful distraction, and he drove blind into the rain." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5438-he-was-talking-very-excitedly-to-me-said-the-vicar</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:31:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5438-he-was-talking-very-excitedly-to-me-said-the-vicar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was talking very excitedly to me,&quot; said the Vicar, &quot;about some apparatus for warming a church in Worthing and about the Apostolic Claims of the Church of Abyssinia. I confess I could not follow him clearly. He seems deeply interested in Church matters. Are you quite sure he is right in the head? I have noticed again and again since I have been in the Church that lay interest in ecclesiastical matters is often a prelude to insanity." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5439-ten-men-of-revolting-appearance-were-approaching-from-the-drive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:32:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5439-ten-men-of-revolting-appearance-were-approaching-from-the-drive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ten men of revolting appearance were approaching from the drive. They were low of brow, crafty of eye, and crooked of limb. They advanced huddled together with the loping tread of wolves, peering about them furtively as they came, as though in constant terror of ambush; they slavered at their mouths, which hung loosely over the receding chins, while each clutched under his ape-like arm a burden of curious and unaccountable shape. On seeing the Doctor they halted and edged back, those behind squinting and moulting over the companions' shoulders." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5440-from-the-earliest-times-the-welsh-have-been-looked-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2007 13:33:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5440-from-the-earliest-times-the-welsh-have-been-looked-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the earliest times the Welsh have been looked upon as an unclean people. It is thus that they have preserved their racial integrity. Their sons and daughters rarely mate with humankind except their own blood relations." -- Evelyn Waugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14079-i-can-t-understand-these-chaps-who-go-round-american-universities</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 18:10:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14079-i-can-t-understand-these-chaps-who-go-round-american-universities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't understand these chaps who go round American universities explaining how they write poems: It's like going round explaining how you sleep with your wife." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14081-for-what-in-actual-practice-should-the-critical-mature-modernist</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 18:16:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Anne Roche Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14081-for-what-in-actual-practice-should-the-critical-mature-modernist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For what, in actual practice, should the critical, mature modernist Christian do when, for instance, he gathers his children around him to celebrate Christmas? Should he read Luke's Christmas Gospel and sing the Christmas carols as if they were true, even though he believes them to be crude and primitive theology? After all, the rest of his society has no scruples about doing this, the pagans and the department stores. Or if this seems too cynical, too dishonest, ought he rather, in the manner of early socialist Sunday schools, to devise a passionately rationalist catechesis, swap German for German, chant a passage from Bultmann instead of 'Joy to the World!'; ought he rather to gather his little ones about the Crib, light the candles, and read Raymond Brown instead of St. Luke on the virginal conception of Jesus: 'My judgment in conclusion is that the totality of the scientifically controllable evidence leaves an unresolved problem.' How their eyes will shine, how their little hearts will burn within them as they hear these holy words! How touched they will all be as the littlest child reverently places a shining question mark in the empty manger. And how they will rejoice when they find their stockings, which they have hung up to a Protestant parody of a Catholic bishop, stuffed with subscriptions to 'Concilium,' 'Catholic Update,' 'National Catholic Reporter,' and 'The Tablet." -- Anne Roche Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14089-all-this-was-only-in-my-father-s-estimation-a-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 18:28:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14089-all-this-was-only-in-my-father-s-estimation-a-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All this was only, in my father's estimation, a means; the end was the Earthly Paradise, the translation of William Morris's 'News from Nowhere' into 'News from Somewhere.'  Then Whitman's sense of abounding joy in his own and all creation's sensuality would sweep away the paltry backwaters of bourgeois morality; the horrors of industrial ugliness which Ruskin so eloquently denounced would dissolve, and die forgotten as a dream (phrases from hymns still washed about in my father's mind) as slums were transformed into garden cities, and the belching smoke of hateful furnaces into the cool elegance of electric power.  As for the ferocious ravings of my namesake, Carlyle, about the pettifogging nature of modern industrial man's pursuits and expectations -- all that would be corrected as he was induced to spend ever more of his increasing leisure in cultural and craft activities; in the enjoyment of music, literature and art.

It was pefectly true -- a point that Will Straughan was liable to bring up at the Saturday evening gatherings -- that on the present form the new citizenry might be expected to have a marked preference for dog-racing over chamber music or readings from 'Paradise Lost,' but, my father would loftily point out, education would change all that.  Education was, in fact, the lynchpin of the whole operation; the means whereby the Old Adam of the Saturday night booze-up, and fondness for Marie Lloyd in preference to Beatrice Webb, would be cast off, and the New Man be born as potential fodder for third Programmes yet to come." -- Malcolm Muggeridge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16961-tall-nettles-tall-nettles-cover-up-as-they-have-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 13:12:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Edward Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16961-tall-nettles-tall-nettles-cover-up-as-they-have-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tall  Nettles

Tall nettles cover up, as they have done
These many springs, the rusty harrow, the plough
Long worn out, and the roller made of stone :
Only the elm butt tops the nettles now.

This corner of the farmyard I like most:
As well as any bloom upon a flower
I like the dust on the nettles, never lost
Except to prove the sweetness of a shower." -- Edward Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16970-a-new-voice-haild-me-of-an-old-friend-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 13:15:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Charles Montagu Doughty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16970-a-new-voice-haild-me-of-an-old-friend-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A new voice haild me of an old friend when, first returned from the Peninsula, I paced again in that long street of Damascus which is called Straight; and suddenly taking me wondering by the hand, 'Tell me (said he), since thou art here again in the peace and assurance of Ullah, and whilst we walk, as in the former years, toward the new blossoming orchards, full of the sweet spring as the garden of God, what moved thee, or how couldst thou take such journeys into the fanatic Arabia?" -- Charles Montagu Doughty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16974-screen-d-is-this-nook-o-er-the-high-half-reap-d-field-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 13:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Matthew Arnold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16974-screen-d-is-this-nook-o-er-the-high-half-reap-d-field-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Screen'd is this nook o'er the high, half-reap'd field,
  And here till sundown, Shepherd, will I be.
    Through the thick corn the scarlet poppies peep,
  And round green roots and yellowing stalks I see
    Pale blue convolvulus in tendrils creep:
      And air-swept lindens yield
  Their scent, and rustle down their perfumed showers
    Of bloom on the bent grass where I am laid,
    And bower me from the August sun with shade;
  And the eye travels down to Oxford's towers..." -- Matthew Arnold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16977-i-have-tried-imagining-that-the-single-peacock-i-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 13:34:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16977-i-have-tried-imagining-that-the-single-peacock-i-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have tried imagining that the single peacock I see before me is the only one I have, but then one comes to join him, another flies off the roof, four or five crash out of the crepe-myrtle hedge; from the pond one screams and from the barn I hear the dairyman denouncing another that has got into the cow-feed. My kin are given to such phrases as, 'Let's face it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
