<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/68530-ashley-gresh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/68530-ashley-gresh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 15:39:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16999-run-mad-as-often-as-you-choose-but-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 15:39:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16999-run-mad-as-often-as-you-choose-but-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Run mad as often as you choose, but do not faint!" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 16:00:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 16:00:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 16:00:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 16:03:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150222-i-have-loved-to-the-point-of-madness-that-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 05:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Francois Sagon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150222-i-have-loved-to-the-point-of-madness-that-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have loved to the point of madness; that which is called madness, that which to me, is the only sensible way to love." -- Francois Sagon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345512-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-he-lived</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 09:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345512-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-he-lived]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time, there was a boy. He lived in a village that no longer exists, in a house that no longer exists, on the edge of a field that no longer exists, where everything was discovered, and everything was possible. A stick could be a sword, a pebble could be a diamond, a tree, a castle. Once upon a time, there was a boy who lived in a house across the field, from a girl who no longer exists. They made up a thousand games. She was queen and he was king. In the autumn light her hair shone like a crown. They collected the world in small handfuls, and when the sky grew dark, and they parted with leaves in their hair.

Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101870-though-she-be-but-little-she-is-fierce</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 11:43:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101870-though-she-be-but-little-she-is-fierce]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though she be but little, she is fierce!" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 12:24:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashley add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
