<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/685338-mtoddm84]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/685338-mtoddm84" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:23:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:23:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:26:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:46:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38963-the-earth-is-a-very-small-stage-in-a-vast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that in glory and in triumph they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of the dot on scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner of the dot. How frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds. Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity -- in all this vastness -- there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves. It is up to us. It's been said that astronomy is a humbling, and I might add, a character-building experience. To my mind, there is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly and compassionately with one another and to preserve and cherish that pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73908-if-you-imagine-the-4-500-bilion-odd-years-of-earth-s-history-compressed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:49:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73908-if-you-imagine-the-4-500-bilion-odd-years-of-earth-s-history-compressed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you imagine the 4,500-bilion-odd years of Earth's history compressed into a normal earthly day, then life begins very early, about 4 A.M., with the rise of the first simple, single-celled organisms, but then advances no further for the next sixteen hours. Not until almost 8:30 in the evening, with the day five-sixths over, has Earth anything to show the universe but a restless skin of microbes. Then, finally, the first sea plants appear, followed twenty minutes later by the first jellyfish and the enigmatic Ediacaran fauna first seen by Reginald Sprigg in Australia. At 9:04 P.M. trilobites swim onto the scene, followed more or less immediately by the shapely creatures of the Burgess Shale. Just before 10 P.M. plants begin to pop up on the land. Soon after, with less than two hours left in the day, the first land creatures follow. 

Thanks to ten minutes or so of balmy weather, by 10:24 the Earth is covered in the great carboniferous forests whose residues give us all our coal, and the first winged insects are evident. Dinosaurs plod onto the scene just before 11 P.M. and hold sway for about three-quarters of an hour. At twenty-one minutes to midnight they vanish and the age of mammals begins. Humans emerge one minute and seventeen seconds before midnight. The whole of our recorded history, on this scale, would be no more than a few seconds, a single human lifetime barely an instant. Throughout this greatly speeded-up day continents slide about and bang together at a clip that seems positively reckless. Mountains rise and melt away, ocean basins come and go, ice sheets advance and withdraw. And throughout the whole, about three times every minute, somewhere on the planet there is a flash-bulb pop of light marking the impact of a Manson-sized meteor or one even larger. It's a wonder that anything at all can survive in such a pummeled and unsettled environment. In fact, not many things do for long." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 19:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153827-science-has-carried-us-to-the-gateway-to-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 20:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Ann Druyan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153827-science-has-carried-us-to-the-gateway-to-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science has carried us to the gateway to the universe. And yet our conception of our surroundings remains the disproportionate view of the still-small child. We are spiritually and culturally paralyzed, unable to face the vastness, to embrace our lack of centrality and find our actual place in the fabric of nature. We batter this planet as if we had someplace else to go. That we even do science is a hopeful glimmer of mental health. However, it's not enough merely to accept these insights intellectually while we cling to a spiritual ideology that is not only rootless in nature but also, in many ways, contemptuous of what is natural." -- Ann Druyan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 20:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 20:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who imagines that bliss is normal is going to waste a lot of time running around shouting that he has been robbed. The fact is that most putts don’t drop, most beef is tough, most children grow up to be just like people, most successful marriages require a high degree of mutual toleration, and most jobs are more often dull than otherwise. Life is just like an old time rail journey ... delays, sidetracks, smoke, dust, cinders, and jolts, interspersed only occasionally by beautiful vistas and thrilling bursts of speed. The trick is to thank the Lord for letting you have the ride." -- Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43538-to-waste-to-destroy-our-natural-resources-to-skin-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 19:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43538-to-waste-to-destroy-our-natural-resources-to-skin-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To waste, to destroy our natural resources, to skin and exhaust the land instead of using it so as to increase its usefulness, will result in undermining in the days of our children the very prosperity which we ought by right to hand down to them amplified and developed." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196452-here-is-your-country-cherish-these-natural-wonders-cherish-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 19:47:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196452-here-is-your-country-cherish-these-natural-wonders-cherish-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is your country. Cherish these natural wonders, cherish the natural resources, cherish the history and romance as a sacred heritage, for your children and your children's children. Do not let selfish men or greedy interests skin your country of its beauty, its riches or its romance." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259749-the-angry-men-know-that-this-golden-age-of-fossil</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 19:50:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by George Monbiot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259749-the-angry-men-know-that-this-golden-age-of-fossil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The angry men know that this golden age (of fossil fuels) has gone; but they cannot find the words for the constraints they hate. Clutching their copies of Atlas Shrugged, they flail around, accusing those who would impede them of communism, fascism, religiosity, misanthropy, but knowing at heart that these restrictions are driven by something far more repulsive to the unrestrained man: the decencies we owe to other human beings." -- George Monbiot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313769-the-recipe-for-perpetual-ignorance-is-be-satisfied-with-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 20:02:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313769-the-recipe-for-perpetual-ignorance-is-be-satisfied-with-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The recipe for perpetual ignorance is: Be satisfied with your opinions and content with your knowledge." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7886-never-explain-your-friends-do-not-need-it-and-your-enemies</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 20:02:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mtoddm84 add a quote by Elbert Hubbard ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7886-never-explain-your-friends-do-not-need-it-and-your-enemies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never explain―your friends do not need it and your enemies will not believe you anyway." -- Elbert Hubbard ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
