<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687087-gina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687087-gina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 18:03:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621076-her-name-is-brienne-jaime-said-brienne-the-maid-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 18:03:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/621076-her-name-is-brienne-jaime-said-brienne-the-maid-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her name is Brienne,&quot; Jaime said. &quot;Brienne, the maid of Tarth. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; still maiden, I hope?&quot;

Her broad homely face turned red. &quot;Yes.&quot;

&quot;Oh, good,&quot; Jaime said. &quot;I only rescue maidens." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 06:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless someone like you cares a whole awful lot,
Nothing is going to get better. It's not." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 06:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person's a person, no matter how small." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23148-ah-said-dumbledore-gently-yes-i-thought-we-might-hit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 12:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23148-ah-said-dumbledore-gently-yes-i-thought-we-might-hit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah&quot; said Dumbledore gently, &quot;Yes I thought we might hit that little snag!&quot;
&quot;Snag?&quot; said Fudge, his voice still vibrating with joy. &quot;I see no snag, Dumbledore!&quot;
&quot;Well,&quot; said Dumbledore apologetically, &quot;I'm afraid I do.&quot;
&quot;Oh, really?&quot;
&quot;Well it's just that you seem to be labouring under the delusion that I am going to -- come quietly. I am afraid I am not going to come quietly at all, Cornelius. I have absolutely no intention of being sent to Azkaban. I could break out, of course -- but what a waste of time, and frankly, I can think of a whole host of things I would rather be doing." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55043-so-will-i-turn-her-virtue-into-pitch-and-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 13:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55043-so-will-i-turn-her-virtue-into-pitch-and-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So will I turn her virtue into pitch,
And out of her own goodness make the net
That shall enmesh them all. " -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61846-did-you-say-the-stars-were-worlds-tess-yes-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 13:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61846-did-you-say-the-stars-were-worlds-tess-yes-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you say the stars were worlds, Tess?&quot;
&quot;Yes.&quot;
&quot;All like ours?&quot;
&quot;I don't know, but I think so. They sometimes seem to be like the apples on our stubbard-tree. Most of them splendid and sound - a few blighted.&quot;
&quot;Which do we live on - a splendid one or a blighted one?&quot;
&quot;A blighted one." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 07:11:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470-it-is-a-far-far-better-thing-that-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69332-for-you-and-for-any-dear-to-you-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 07:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69332-for-you-and-for-any-dear-to-you-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For you, and for any dear to you, I would do anything. If my career were of that better kind that there was any opportunity or capacity of sacrifice in it, I would embrace any sacrifice for you and for those dear to you. Try to hold me in your mind, at some quiet times, as ardent and sincere in this one thing. The time will come, the time will not be long in coming, when new ties will be formed about you--ties that will bind you yet more tenderly and strongly to the home you so adorn--the dearest ties that will ever grace and gladden you. O Miss Manette, when the little picture of a happy father's face looks up in yours, when you see your own bright beauty springing up anew at your feet, think now and then that there is a man who would give his life, to keep a life you love beside you!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78924-before-i-go-he-said-and-paused----i-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 07:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78924-before-i-go-he-said-and-paused----i-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I go,&quot; he said, and paused -- &quot;I may kiss her?&quot;

It was remembered afterwards that when he bent down and touched her face with his lips, he murmured some words. The child, who was nearest to him, told them afterwards, and told her grandchildren when she was a handsome old lady, that she heard him say, &quot;A life you love." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:29:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7989-of-course-it-is-happening-inside-your-head-harry-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:30:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7989-of-course-it-is-happening-inside-your-head-harry-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course it is happening inside your head, Harry, but why on earth should that mean that it is not real?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18284-it-was-he-thought-the-difference-between-being-dragged-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:34:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18284-it-was-he-thought-the-difference-between-being-dragged-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was, he thought, the difference between being dragged into the arena to face a battle to the death and walking into the arena with your head held high. Some people, perhaps, would say that there was little to choose between the two ways, but Dumbledore knew - and so do I, thought Harry, with a rush of fierce pride, and so did my parents - that there was all the difference in the world." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132594-i-begin-to-think-said-estella-in-a-musing-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:43:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132594-i-begin-to-think-said-estella-in-a-musing-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I begin to think,' said Estella, in a musing way, after another moment of calm wonder, 'that I almost understand how this comes about. If you had brought up your adopted daughter wholly in the dark confinement of these rooms, and had never let her know that there was such a thing as the daylight by which she has never once seen your face―if you had done that, and then, for a purpose, had wanted her to understand the daylight and know all about it, you would have been disappointed and angry? . . .'
Or,' said Estella, '―which is a nearer case―if you had taught her, from the dawn of her intelligence, with your utmost energy and might, that there was such a thing as daylight, but that it was made to be her enemy and destroyer, and she must always turn against it, for it had blighted you and would else blight her―if you had done this, and then, for a purpose, had wanted her to take naturally to the daylight and she could not do it, you would have been disappointed and angry? . . .'
So,' said Estella, 'I must be taken as I have been made. The success is not mine, the failure is not mine, but the two together make me." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328250-japanese-owned-cargo-ship-tsimtsum-flying-panamanian-flag-sank-july-2nd</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:46:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328250-japanese-owned-cargo-ship-tsimtsum-flying-panamanian-flag-sank-july-2nd]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Japanese-owned cargo ship Tsimtsum, flying Panamanian flag, sank July 2nd, 1977, in Pacific, four days out of Manila. Am in lifeboat. Pi Patel my name. Have some food, some water, but Bengal tiger a serious problem. Please advise family in Winnepeg, Canada. Any help very much appreciated.  Thank you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54481-far-out-in-the-uncharted-backwaters-of-the-unfashionable-end</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 07:48:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54481-far-out-in-the-uncharted-backwaters-of-the-unfashionable-end]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Far out in the uncharted backwaters of the unfashionable end of the western spiral arm of the Galaxy lies a small unregarded yellow sun. Orbiting this at a distance of roughly ninety-two million miles is an utterly insignificant little blue green planet whose ape-descended life forms are so amazingly primitive that they still think digital watches are a pretty neat idea." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487666-i-ve-lost-a-hand-a-father-a-son-a-sister</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 19:20:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487666-i-ve-lost-a-hand-a-father-a-son-a-sister]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've lost a hand, a father, a son, a sister, and a lover, and soon enough I will lose a brother. And yet they keep telling me House Lannister won this war." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
