<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687174-sarah-hannan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687174-sarah-hannan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:22:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842127-because-whatever-has-happened-to-humanity-whatever-is-currently-happening</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:22:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842127-because-whatever-has-happened-to-humanity-whatever-is-currently-happening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because whatever has happened to humanity, whatever is currently happening to humanity, it is happening to all of us. No matter how hidden the cruelty, no matter how far off the screams of pain and terror, we live in one world. We are one people. My illness proved that. As well as my understanding that Generose's lost daughter belongs to all of us. It is up to all of us to find her; it is up to us to do our best to make her whole again. There is only one daughter, one father, one mother, one son, one aunt or uncle, one dog, one cat, donkey, monkey, or goat in the universe, after all: the one right in front of you." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842129-all-i-wanted-to-do-was-get-back-to-africa</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:24:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842129-all-i-wanted-to-do-was-get-back-to-africa]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I wanted to do was get back to Africa. We had not left it, yet, but when I would wake in the night I would lie, listening, homesick for it already. Now, looking out the tunnel of trees over the ravine at the sky with white clouds moving across in the wind, I loved the country so that I was happy as you are after you have been with a woman that you really love, when, empty, you feel it welling up again and there it is and you can never have it all and yet what there is, now, you can have, and you want more and more, to have, and be, and live in, to possess now again for always, for that long sudden-ended always; making time stand still, sometimes so very still that afterwards you wait to hear it move, and it is slow in starting. But you are not alone because if you have every really loved her happy and untragic, she loves you always; no matter whom she loves nor where she goes she loves you more." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842132-if-the-heart-of-africa-remained-elusive-my-search-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 07:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842132-if-the-heart-of-africa-remained-elusive-my-search-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the heart of Africa remained elusive, my search for it had brought me closer to understanding myself and other human beings. The ache for home lives in all of us, the safe place where we can go as we are and not be questioned. It impels mighty ambitions and dangerous capers. We amass great fortunes at the cost of our souls, or risk our lives in drug dens from London’s Soho, to San Francisco’s Haight-Ashbury. We shout in Baptist churches, wear yarmulkes and wigs and argue even the tiniest points in the Torah, or worship the sun and refuse to kill cows for the starving. Hoping that by doing these things, home will find us acceptable or failing that, that we will forget our awful yearning for it." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 07:36:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58751-i-wanted-to-tell-the-book-thief-many-things-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted to tell the book thief many things, about beauty and brutality.  But what could I tell her about those things that she didn't already know?  I wanted to explain that I am constantly overestimating and underestimating the human race-that rarely do I ever simply estimate it.  I wanted to ask her how the same thing could be so ugly and so glorious, and its words and stories so damning and brilliant." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 09:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842113-i-m-dying-of-aids-but-i-m-dying-by-accident-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:05:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Gil Courtemanche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/842113-i-m-dying-of-aids-but-i-m-dying-by-accident-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm dying of AIDS, but I'm dying by accident. I didn't choose, it was a mistake. I thought it was a white's or homosexual's or monkey's or druggie's sickness. I was born a Tutsi, it's written on my identity card, but I'm a Tutsi by accident. I didn't choose, that was a mistake too. My great-grandfather learned from the whites that the Tutsis were superior to the Hutus. He was Hutu. He did everything possible so his children and grandchildren would become Tutsis. So here I am, a Hutu-Tutsi and victim of AIDS, possessor of all the sicknesses that are going to destroy us. Look at me, I'm your mirror, your double who's rotting from the inside. I'm dying a bit earlier than you, that's all." -- Gil Courtemanche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97673-how-wrong-to-have-been-so-negative-how-wrong-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:10:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97673-how-wrong-to-have-been-so-negative-how-wrong-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wrong to have been so negative, how wrong to have been so gloomy, how wrong to have run away from life, how wrong to have said no, again and again, instead of yes." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2013 07:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think and think and think, I‘ve thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518986-she-told-me-about-a-group-of-people-in-guinea</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518986-she-told-me-about-a-group-of-people-in-guinea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She told me about a group of people in Guinea who carry the sky on their heads. They are the people of Creation. Strong, tall, and mighty people who can bear anything. Their Maker, she said, gives them the sky to carry because they are strong. These people do not know who they are, but if you see a lot of trouble in your life, it is because you were chosen to carry part of the sky on your head." -- Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280757-you-must-never-behave-as-if-your-life-belongs-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280757-you-must-never-behave-as-if-your-life-belongs-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must never behave as if your life belongs to a man. Do you hear me?' Aunty Ifeka said. 'Your life belongs to you and you alone." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416777-misery-won-t-touch-you-gentle-it-always-leaves-its-thumbprints</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416777-misery-won-t-touch-you-gentle-it-always-leaves-its-thumbprints]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Misery won't touch you gentle. It always leaves its thumbprints on you; sometimes it leaves them for others to see, sometimes for nobody but you to know of." -- Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937913-the-truth-about-my-family-was-that-we-disappointed-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 14:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Monique Truong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937913-the-truth-about-my-family-was-that-we-disappointed-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about my family was that we disappointed one another.  When I heard the word 'disappoint,' I tasted toast, slightly burned.  But when I saw the word written, I thought of it first and foremost as the combining or the collapsing together of the words 'disappear' and 'point,' as in how something in us ceased to exist the moment someone let us down.  Small children understood this better than adults, this irreparable diminution of the self that occurred at each instance, large and small, of someone forgetting a promise, arriving late, losing interest, leaving too soon, and otherwise making us feel like a fool.  That was why children, in the face of disappointments, large and small, were so quick to cry and scream, often throwing their bodies to the ground as if their tiny limbs were on fire.  That was a good instinct.  We, the adults or the survivors of our youth, traded in instinct for a societal norm.  We stayed calm.  We swallowed the hurt.  We forgave the infraction.  We ignored that our skin was on fire.  We became our own fools.  Sometimes, when we were very successful, we forgot entirely the memory of the disappointment.  The loss that resulted, of course, could not be undone. What was gone was gone.  We just could no longer remember how we ended up with so much less of our selves.  Why we expected nothing, why we deserved so little, and why we brought strangers into our lives to fill the void." -- Monique Truong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920512-light-like-this-does-not-exist-but-we-wish-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 18:52:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920512-light-like-this-does-not-exist-but-we-wish-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Light like this does not exist, but we wish it did. We wish the sun could make us young and beautiful, we wish our clothes could glisten and ripple against our skins, most of all, we wish that everyone we knew could be brightened simply by our looking at them, as are the maid with the letter and the soldier with the hat." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536237-you-see-each-country-has-a-colour-a-smell-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Gil Courtemanche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/536237-you-see-each-country-has-a-colour-a-smell-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, each country has a colour, a smell, and also a contagious sickness. In my country the sickness is complacency. In France it's arrogance, and in the United States it's ignorance.&quot; 

&quot;What about Rwanda?&quot;

&quot;Easy power and impunity. Here, there's total disorder. To someone who has a little money or powere, everything that seems forbidden elsewhere looks permissible and possible. All it takes is to dare it. Someone who's simply a liar in my country can be a fraud artist here, and the fraud artist gets to be a big-time thief. Chaos and most of all poverty give him powers he wouldn't have elsewhere." -- Gil Courtemanche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1038063-stories-matter-stories-are-how-we-make-sense-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 12:27:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Laurie Penny]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1038063-stories-matter-stories-are-how-we-make-sense-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories matter. Stories are how we make sense of the world, which doesn't mean that those stories can't be stupid and simplistic and full of lies. Stories can exaggerate and offend and they always, always matter." -- Laurie Penny]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150586-i-love-seeing-the-bookshops-and-meeting-the-booksellers---booksellers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 08:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mary Ann Shaffer and Annie Barrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150586-i-love-seeing-the-bookshops-and-meeting-the-booksellers---booksellers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love seeing the bookshops and meeting the booksellers-- booksellers really are a special breed. No one in their right mind would take up clerking in a bookstore for the salary, and no one in his right mind would want to own one-- the margin of profit is too small. So, it has to be a love of readers and reading that makes them do it-- along with first dibs on the new books." -- Mary Ann Shaffer and Annie Barrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146472-depression-presents-itself-as-a-realism-regarding-the-rottenness-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146472-depression-presents-itself-as-a-realism-regarding-the-rottenness-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Depression presents itself as a realism regarding the rottenness of the world in general and the rottenness of your life in particular. But the realism is merely a mask for depression's actual essence, which is an overwhelming estrangement from humanity. The more persuaded you are of your unique access to the rottenness, the more afraid you become of engaging with the world; and the less you engage with the world, the more perfidiously happy-faced the rest of humanity seems for continuing to engage with it." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419450-peux-ce-que-veux-allons-y</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 09:54:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Roméo Dallaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419450-peux-ce-que-veux-allons-y]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peux ce que veux. Allons-y." -- Roméo Dallaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530428-i-also-know-there-are-timeless-waters-endless-seas-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530428-i-also-know-there-are-timeless-waters-endless-seas-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I also know there are timeless waters, endless seas, and lots of people in this world whose names don't matter to anyone but themselves. I look up at the sky and I see you there." -- Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920434-jephthah-called-together-the-men-of-gilead-and-fought-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 16:15:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920434-jephthah-called-together-the-men-of-gilead-and-fought-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jephthah called together the men of Gilead and fought against Ephraim. The Gileadites captured the fords of the Jordan leading to Ephraim, and whenever a survivor of Ephraim said, 'Let me cross over,' the men of Gilead asked him, 'Are you an Ephraimite?' If he replied, 'No,' they said, 'All right, say Shibboleth.' If he said, 'Sibboleth,' because he could not pronounce the word correctly, they seized and killed him at the fords of the Jordan. Fourty-thousand were killed at the time.

- Judges 12:4-6" -- Edwidge Danticat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144910-what-goes-on-inside-is-just-too-fast-and-huge</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 14:45:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144910-what-goes-on-inside-is-just-too-fast-and-huge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What goes on inside is just too fast and huge and all interconnected for words to do more than barely sketch the outlines of at most one tiny little part of it at any given instant." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138080-they-had-nothing-to-say-to-each-other-a-five-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138080-they-had-nothing-to-say-to-each-other-a-five-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They had nothing to say to each other.  A five-year age gap between siblings is like a garden that needs constant attention.  Even three months apart allows the weeds to grow up between you." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208780-then-you-begin-to-give-up-the-very-idea-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208780-then-you-begin-to-give-up-the-very-idea-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then you begin to give up the very idea of belonging. Suddenly this thing, this belonging,it seems like some long, dirty lie ... and I begin to believe that birthplaces are accidents, that everything is an accident. But if you believe that, where do you go? What do you do? What does anything matter?" -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297210-there-are-some-things-that-are-so-unforgivable-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297210-there-are-some-things-that-are-so-unforgivable-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some things that are so unforgivable that they make other things easily forgivable." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/961913-when-i-was-a-baby-child-they-put-the-jinx</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 01:07:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bill Cheng]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/961913-when-i-was-a-baby-child-they-put-the-jinx]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a baby child, they put the jinx on me.  It was in my drink and food and milk.  And when I ran, it heavied in my bones and when I sang, it stopped up my throat and when I loved, it let from me, hot and poisonous.  I saw it in my daddy, the hard lines of his face, that uneasy lope - how in his years he didn't lift his feet, but slid them, soles across this gritted earth.  It settled in my mama, trembled her voice and blanked her eyes.  My brother, Billy, locked it inside him and it carried him low into that deep earth, silting then into the river and dew and air, in the moths and bee catchers, borne skyward and, as will be, lowed again, into earth again.  It's dusking.  There goes the sun.  There goes sky and cloud and light, taken into that black horizon.  And I know I am bad crossed.  I see its line.  It reaches up, arcs.  It cuts through me.  It draws me on and dogs me down to that place where I am bound.  And when it is I borne down, my eyes and mouth stitched with gut, when they take my balls and brain and heart, and that deeper black claims me wholly, then let me meet that sumbitch at his eye, for I know my name's been writ - Robert Lee Chatham - in his Book." -- Bill Cheng]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27180-right-i-look-fine-except-i-don-t-said-zora-tugging</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 14:34:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27180-right-i-look-fine-except-i-don-t-said-zora-tugging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Right.  I look fine. Except I don't,' said Zora, tugging sadly at her man's nightshirt.  This was why Kiki had dreaded having girls: she knew she wouldn't be able to protect them from self-disgust.  To that end she had tried banning television in the early years, and never had a lipstick or a woman's magazine crossed the threshold of the Belsey home to Kiki's knowledge, but these and other precautionary measures had made no difference.  It was in the air, or so it seemed to Kiki, this hatred of women and their bodies-- it seeped in with every draught in the house; people brought it home on their shoes, they breathed it in off their newspapers.  There was no way to control it." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376387-we-did-that-often-asking-each-other-questions-whose-answers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 16:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376387-we-did-that-often-asking-each-other-questions-whose-answers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We did that often, asking each other questions whose answers we already knew. Perhaps it was so that we would not ask the other questions, the ones whose answers we did not want to know." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417471-he-was-making-her-feel-small-and-absurdly-petulant-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 16:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417471-he-was-making-her-feel-small-and-absurdly-petulant-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was making her feel small and absurdly petulant and, worse yet, she suspected he was right. She always suspected he was right. For a brief irrational moment, she wished she could walk away from him. Then she wished, more rationally, that she could love him without needing him. Need gave him power without his trying; need was the choicelessness she often felt around him." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605265-there-s-something-very-lazy-about-the-way-you-have-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 16:30:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605265-there-s-something-very-lazy-about-the-way-you-have-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's something very lazy about the way you have loved him blindly for so long without ever criticizing him.  You've never even accepted that the man is ugly,' Kainene said.  There was a small smile on her face and then she was laughing, and Olanna could not help but laugh too, because it was not what she had wanted to hear and because hearing it had made her feel better." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
