<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687234-abby]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687234-abby" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 17:45:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19364-it-was-as-if-that-great-rush-of-anger-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 17:45:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19364-it-was-as-if-that-great-rush-of-anger-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was as if that great rush of anger had washed me clean, emptied me of hope, and, gazing up at the dark sky spangled with its signs and stars, for the first time, the first, I laid my heart open to the benign indifference of the universe.
To feel it so like myself, indeed, so brotherly, made me realize that I'd been happy, and that I was happy still. For all to be accomplished, for me to feel less lonely, all that remained to hope was that on the day of my execution there should be a huge crowd of spectators and that they should greet me with howls of execration." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54353-you-must-feel-a-certain-lack-of-excitement-in-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 17:48:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by B. F. Skinner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54353-you-must-feel-a-certain-lack-of-excitement-in-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must feel a certain lack of excitement in these accouncements.  No garish posters, no bright lights, none of the paraphernalia with which the entertainment industry whips up a jaded public.  But in a day or so these simple notices will begin to take on all the excitement of the shimmering marquee.  When there are no signs ten feet high, five feet will do.  When there are none five feet high, one foot serves well enough. It isn't the color or brightness or size of a poster which makes it exciting.  It's the experiences which have accompanied similar posters in the past.  The excitement is a conditioned reflex.  Our bulletin board is our Great White Way, and we're dazzled by it." -- B. F. Skinner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 12:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
