<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687720-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687720-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:48:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:48:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:48:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:48:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:49:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14304-it-is-better-to-be-hated-for-what-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:51:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Andre Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14304-it-is-better-to-be-hated-for-what-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not." -- Andre Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:52:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:52:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:52:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:55:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3202-life-is-an-opportunity-benefit-from-it-life-is-beauty</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:56:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3202-life-is-an-opportunity-benefit-from-it-life-is-beauty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is an opportunity, benefit from it.
Life is beauty, admire it.
Life is a dream, realize it.
Life is a challenge, meet it.
Life is a duty, complete it.
Life is a game, play it.
Life is a promise, fulfill it.
Life is sorrow, overcome it.
Life is a song, sing it.
Life is a struggle, accept it.
Life is a tragedy, confront it.
Life is an adventure, dare it.
Life is luck, make it.
Life is too precious, do not destroy it.
Life is life, fight for it." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:55:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103-be-not-afraid-of-greatness-some-are-born-great-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:55:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103-be-not-afraid-of-greatness-some-are-born-great-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be not afraid of greatness. Some are born great, some achieve greatness, and others have greatness thrust upon them." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:59:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:58:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you'll go." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2528-keep-away-from-people-who-try-to-belittle-your-ambitions</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 01:59:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2528-keep-away-from-people-who-try-to-belittle-your-ambitions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep away from people who try to belittle your ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really great make you feel that you, too, can become great." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58559-it-s-better-to-be-unhappy-alone-than-unhappy-with-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 02:00:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58559-it-s-better-to-be-unhappy-alone-than-unhappy-with-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's better to be unhappy alone than unhappy with someone." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25106-do-one-thing-every-day-that-scares-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 02:00:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25106-do-one-thing-every-day-that-scares-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do one thing every day that scares you." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 02:00:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Sam Levenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Attractive lips, speak words of kindness.
&amp;emsp;For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people.
&amp;emsp;For a slim figure, share your food with the hungry.
&amp;emsp;For beautiful hair, let a child run their fingers through it once a day.
&amp;emsp;For poise, walk with the knowledge that you never walk alone. 
&amp;emsp;People, more than things, have to be restored, renewed, revived, reclaimed, and redeemed. Remember, if you ever need a helping hand, you will find one at the end of each of your arms.
&amp;emsp;As you grow older, you will discover that you have two hands, one for helping yourself and the other for helping others." -- Sam Levenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 02:01:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41050-i-don-t-believe-in-people-just-hoping-we-work-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 18:13:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41050-i-don-t-believe-in-people-just-hoping-we-work-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in people just hoping. We work for what we want. I always say that one has no right to hope without
endeavor, so we work to try and bring about the situation that is necessary for the country, and we are confident that we will get to the negotiation table at one time or another." -- Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586622-please-use-your-liberty-to-promote-ours</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 18:14:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/586622-please-use-your-liberty-to-promote-ours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Please use your liberty to promote ours" -- Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403182-to-view-the-opposition-as-dangerous-is-to-misunderstand-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 18:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403182-to-view-the-opposition-as-dangerous-is-to-misunderstand-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To view the opposition as dangerous is to misunderstand the basic concepts of democracy. To oppress the opposition is to assault the very foundation of democracy." -- Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
