<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687791-lia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/687791-lia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 20:31:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16674-nobody-can-claim-the-name-of-pedro-nobody-is-rosa</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 20:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lia add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16674-nobody-can-claim-the-name-of-pedro-nobody-is-rosa]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody can claim the name of Pedro,
nobody is Rosa or Mar&amp;iacute;a,
all of us are dust or sand,
all of us are rain under rain.
They have spoken to me of Venezuelas,
of Chiles and Paraguays;
I have no idea what they are saying.
I know only the skin of the earth
and I know it has no name." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539456-insofar-as-the-theorist-wins-therefore-by-constructing-an-increasingly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 21:08:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lia add a quote by Fredric Jameson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539456-insofar-as-the-theorist-wins-therefore-by-constructing-an-increasingly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insofar as the theorist wins, therefore, by constructing an increasingly closed and terrifying machine, to that very degree he loses, since the critical capacity of his work is thereby paralysed, and the impulses of negation and revolt, not to speak of those of social transformation, are increasingly perceived as vain and trivial in the face of the model itself." -- Fredric Jameson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287750-i-am-reduced-to-a-thing-that-wants-virginia-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 21:59:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lia add a quote by Vita Sackville-West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287750-i-am-reduced-to-a-thing-that-wants-virginia-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am reduced to a thing that wants Virginia. I composed a beautiful letter to you in the sleepless nightmare hours of the night, and it has all gone: I just miss you, in a quite simple desperate human way. You, with all your un-dumb letters, would never write so elementary a phrase as that; perhaps you wouldn’t even feel it. And yet I believe you’ll be sensible of a little gap. But you’d clothe it in so exquisite a phrase that it would lose a little of its reality. Whereas with me it is quite stark: I miss you even more than I could have believed; and I was prepared to miss you a good deal. So this letter is just really a squeal of pain. It is incredible how essential to me you have become. I suppose you are accustomed to people saying these things. Damn you, spoilt creature; I shan’t make you love me any the more by giving myself away like this —But oh my dear, I can’t be clever and stand-offish with you: I love you too much for that. Too truly. You have no idea how stand-offish I can be with people I don’t love. I have brought it to a fine art. But you have broken down my defences. And I don’t really resent it." -- Vita Sackville-West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630961-you-don-t-owe-prettiness-to-anyone-not-to-your-boyfriend-spouse-partner</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 08:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lia add a quote by Erin McKean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630961-you-don-t-owe-prettiness-to-anyone-not-to-your-boyfriend-spouse-partner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t owe prettiness to anyone. Not to your boyfriend/spouse/partner, not to your co-workers, especially not to random men on the street. You don’t owe it to your mother, you don’t owe it to your children, you don’t owe it to civilization in general. Prettiness is not a rent you pay for occupying a space marked ‘female’." -- Erin McKean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169989-he-was-having-an-odd-paternal-rush-a-blood-surge</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 20:18:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lia add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169989-he-was-having-an-odd-paternal-rush-a-blood-surge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was having an odd paternal rush, a blood surge that was also &lt;i&gt;about&lt;/i&gt; blood and was presently hunting through Howard's expansive intelligence to find words that would more effectively express something like &lt;i&gt;don't walk in front of cars take care and be good and don't hurt or be hurt and don't live in a way that makes you feel dead and don't betray anybody or yourself and take care of what matters and please don't and please remember and make sure&lt;/i&gt;" -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
