<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/688655-esdoubleu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/688655-esdoubleu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 05:51:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63142-anyone-who-falls-in-love-is-searching-for-the-missing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 05:51:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esdoubleu add a quote by Murakami, Haruki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63142-anyone-who-falls-in-love-is-searching-for-the-missing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who falls in love is searching for the missing pieces of themselves. So anyone who's in love gets sad when they think of their lover. It's like stepping back inside a room you have fond memories of, one you haven't seen in a long time." -- Murakami, Haruki]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 05:51:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esdoubleu add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1977-it-s-like-tolstoy-said-happiness-is-an-allegory-unhappiness-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's like Tolstoy said. Happiness is an allegory, unhappiness a &lt;i&gt;story&lt;/i&gt;." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 05:51:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esdoubleu add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when I look at you, I feel I'm gazing at a distant star. 
It's dazzling, but the light is from tens of thousands of years ago.
Maybe the star doesn't even exist any more. Yet sometimes that light seems more real to me than anything." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 02:49:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esdoubleu add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91562-why-do-people-have-to-be-this-lonely-what-s-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 02:49:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esdoubleu add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91562-why-do-people-have-to-be-this-lonely-what-s-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do people have to be this lonely? What's the point of it all? Millions of people in this world, all of them yearning, looking to others to satisfy them, yet isolating themselves. Why? Was the earth put here just to nourish human loneliness?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
