<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/688937-elena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/688937-elena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 17:48:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324416-all-things-are-true-god-s-an-astronaut-oz-is-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 17:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elena add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324416-all-things-are-true-god-s-an-astronaut-oz-is-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All things are true. God's an Astronaut. Oz is Over the Rainbow, and Midian is where the monsters live.&quot; - Peloquin" -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66725-remember-if-people-talk-behind-your-back-it-only-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 07:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elena add a quote by Fannie Flagg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66725-remember-if-people-talk-behind-your-back-it-only-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember if people talk behind your back, it only means you are two steps ahead." -- Fannie Flagg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634293-it-s-funny-when-you-re-a-child-you-think-time-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 08:00:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elena add a quote by Fannie Flagg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/634293-it-s-funny-when-you-re-a-child-you-think-time-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's funny, when you're a child you think time will never go by, but when you hit about twenty, time passes like you're on the fast train to Memphis. I guess life just slips up on everybody. It sure did on me." -- Fannie Flagg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329152-lately-it-had-been-an-endless-procession-of-long-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 08:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elena add a quote by Fannie Flagg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329152-lately-it-had-been-an-endless-procession-of-long-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lately, it had been an endless procession of long, black nights and gray mornings, when her sense of failure swept over her like a five-hundred-pound wave; and she was scared. But it wasn't death that she feared. She had looked down into that black pit of death and had wanted to jump in, once too often. As a matter of fact, the thought began to appeal to her more and more.

She even knew how she would kill herself. It would be with a silver bullet. As round and as smooth as an ice-cold blue martini. She would place the gun in the freezer for a few hours before she did it, so it would feel frosty and cold against her head. She could almost feel the ice-cold bullet shooting through her hot, troubled brain, freezing the pain for good. The sound of the gun blast would be the last sound she would ever hear. And then... nothing. Maybe just the silent sound that a bird might hear, flying in the clean, cool air, high above the earth. The sweet, pure air of freedom.

No, it wasn't death she was afraid of. It was this life of hers that was beginning to remind her of that gray intensive care waiting room." -- Fannie Flagg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
