<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/691338-jessica-seymour]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/691338-jessica-seymour" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 05:51:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13856-if-you-believe-in-peace-act-peacefully-if-you-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 05:51:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13856-if-you-believe-in-peace-act-peacefully-if-you-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you believe in peace, act peacefully; if you believe in love, acting lovingly; if you believe every which way, then act every which way, that's perfectly valid - but don't go out trying to sell your beliefs to the system. You end up contradicting what you profess to believe in, and you set a bum example. If you want to change the world, change yourself." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13861-people-tend-the-take-everything-too-seriously-especially-themselves-yep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 06:04:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13861-people-tend-the-take-everything-too-seriously-especially-themselves-yep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People tend the take everything too seriously. Especially themselves. Yep. And that's probably what makes 'em scared and hurt so much of the time. Life is too serious to take that seriously." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13863-perhaps-a-person-gains-by-accumulating-obstacles-the-more-obstacles</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 06:11:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13863-perhaps-a-person-gains-by-accumulating-obstacles-the-more-obstacles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps a person gains by accumulating obstacles. The more obstacles set up to prevent happiness from appearing, the greater the shock when it does appear, just as the rebound of a spring will be all the more powerful the greater the pressure that has been exerted to compress it. Care must be taken, however, to select large obstacles, for only those of sufficient scope and scale have the capacity to lift us out of context and force life to appear in an entirely new and unexpected light.

For example, should you litter the floor and tabletops of your room with small objects, they constitute little more than a nuisance, an inconvenient clutter that frustrates you and leaves you irritable; the petty is mean. Cursing, you step around the objects, pick them up, knock them aside.

Should you, on the other hand, encounter in your room a nine thousand pound granite boulder, the surprise it evokes, the extreme steps that must be taken to deal with it, compel you to see with new eyes. Difficulties illuminate existence, but they must be fresh and of high quality." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13864-so-you-think-that-you-re-a-failure-do-you-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 06:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13864-so-you-think-that-you-re-a-failure-do-you-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you think that you're a failure, do you? Well, you probably are. What's wrong with that? In the first place, if you've any sense at all you must have learned by now that we pay just as dearly for our triumphs as we do for our defeats. Go ahead and fail. But fail with wit, fail with grace, fail with style. A mediocre failure is as insufferable as a mediocre success. Embrace failure! Seek it out. Learn to love it. That may be the only way any of us will ever be free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
