<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/69168-mary-beth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/69168-mary-beth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 09:20:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179969-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2012 09:20:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179969-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is not a relationship between the healer and the wounded. It's a relationship between equals. Only when we know our own darkness well can we be present with the darkness of others. Compassion becomes real when we recognize our shared humanity." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476366-if-it-had-been-a-heart-attack-the-newspaper-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:51:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Nick Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476366-if-it-had-been-a-heart-attack-the-newspaper-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If it had been a heart attack, the newspaper
might have used the word &lt;i&gt;massive&lt;/i&gt;,
as if a mountain range had opened
inside her, but instead

it used the word &lt;i&gt;suddenly&lt;/i&gt;, a light coming on

in an empty room. The telephone

fell from my shoulder, a black parrot repeating
&lt;i&gt;something happened, something awful&lt;/i&gt;

a sunday, dusky. If it had been

&lt;i&gt;terminal&lt;/i&gt;, we could have cradled her
as she grew smaller, wiped her mouth,

said good-bye. But it was &lt;i&gt;sudden&lt;/i&gt;,

how overnight we could be orphaned
&amp; the world became a bell we'd crawl inside
&amp; the ringing all we'd eat." -- Nick Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:52:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me, what is it you plan to do 
with your one wild and precious life?" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62038-instructions-for-living-a-life-pay-attention-be-astonished-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:51:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62038-instructions-for-living-a-life-pay-attention-be-astonished-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instructions for living a life. 
Pay attention. 
Be astonished. 
Tell about it." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313718-someone-i-loved-once-gave-me-a-box-full-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:52:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313718-someone-i-loved-once-gave-me-a-box-full-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone I loved once gave me a box full of darkness. It took me years to understand that this too, was a gift." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3398-i-will-arise-and-go-now-and-go-to-innisfree</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:53:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3398-i-will-arise-and-go-now-and-go-to-innisfree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will arise and go now,
And go to Innisfree,
And a small cabin build there,
Of clay and wattles made;
Nine bean rows will I have there,
A hive for the honey bee,
And live alone in the bee-loud glade.

And I shall have some peace there,
For peace comes dropping slow,
Dropping from the veils of the morning
To where the cricket sings;
There midnight's all a glimmer,
And noon a purple glow,
And evening full of the linnet's wings

I will arise and go now,
For always night and day
I hear lake water lapping
With low sounds by the shore;
While I stand on the roadway
Or on the pavements gray,
I hear it in the deep heart's core." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102636-down-the-hall-came-the-wife-she-was-glorious-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:54:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102636-down-the-hall-came-the-wife-she-was-glorious-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Down the hall came the wife. She was glorious, burning. She didn't know yet that her husband was dead. We knew. That's what gave her such power over us. The doctor took her into a room with a desk at the end of the hall, and from under the closed door a slab of brilliance radiated as if, by some stupendous process, diamonds were being incinerated in there. What a pair of lungs! She shrieked as I imagined an eagle would shriek. It felt wonderful to be alive to hear it! I've gone looking for that feeling everywhere." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5028-there-s-so-much-goop-inside-of-us-man-he-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:54:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5028-there-s-so-much-goop-inside-of-us-man-he-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's so much goop inside of us, man,&quot; he said, &quot;and it all just wants to get out." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54971-but-when-the-thing-that-is-scaring-you-is-already</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:57:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54971-but-when-the-thing-that-is-scaring-you-is-already]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But when the thing that is scaring you is already Jesus, who are you supposed to pray to?" -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402689-what-if-she-stepped-on-a-needle-and-it-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:58:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402689-what-if-she-stepped-on-a-needle-and-it-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if she stepped on a needle and it went right into her foot and Roberta would not feel it and the needle would rise and rise and rise through the veins leading up to the heart and then the needle would STAB HER IN THE HEART and Roberta would DIE and it would be VERY PAINFUL this according to nurse mother a medical expert on Freaky Ways to Croak... The mother shouted that she knew several people who died from the Rising Stab of the Unfelt Needle or RSUN she has seen cases of it many times and not ONE PERSON HAS SURVIVED IT." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36862-i-think-of-the-chimp-the-one-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36862-i-think-of-the-chimp-the-one-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  I think of the chimp, the one with the talking hands.
  In the course of the experiment, that chimp had a baby.  Imagine how her trainers must have thrilled when the mother, without prompting, began to sign her newborn.
  Baby, drink milk.
  Baby, play ball.
  And when the baby died, the mother stood over the body, her wrinkled hands moving with animal grace, forming again and again the words:  Baby, come hug, Baby come hug, fluent now in the language of grief." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513621-it-was-like-that-class-at-school-where-the-teacher</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:01:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513621-it-was-like-that-class-at-school-where-the-teacher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was like that class at school where the teacher talks about Realization, about how you could realize something big in a commonplace thing. The example he gave--and the liar said it really happened--was that once while drinking orange juice, he'd realized he would be dead someday. He wondered if we, his students, had had similar 'realizations.'
Is he kidding? I thought.
Once I cashed a paycheck and I realized it wasn't enough.
Once I had food poisoning, and realized I was trapped inside my body." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250142-it-was-the-day-of-the-worms-that-first-almost-warm</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250142-it-was-the-day-of-the-worms-that-first-almost-warm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the day of the worms. That first almost-warm, after-the-rainy-night day in April, when you bolt from your house to find yourself in a world of worms. They were as numerous here in the East End as they had been in the West. The sidewalks, the streets. The very places where they didn't belong. Forlorn, marooned on concrete and asphalt, no place to burrow, April's orphans." -- Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5444-love-is-a-decision-it-is-a-judgment-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:04:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Erich Fromm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5444-love-is-a-decision-it-is-a-judgment-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a decision, it is a judgment, it is a promise. If love were only a feeling, there would be no basis for the promise to love each other forever. A feeling comes and it may go. How can I judge that it will stay forever, when my act does not involve judgment and decision." -- Erich Fromm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255912-i-do-not-say-what-i-feel-and-people-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:06:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Amy Bloom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255912-i-do-not-say-what-i-feel-and-people-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not say what I feel, and people often take that for shyness, even kindness." -- Amy Bloom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:07:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually adult males who are unable to make emotional connections with the women they choose to be intimate with are frozen in time, unable to allow themselves to love for fear that the loved one will abandon them.  If the first woman they passionately loved, the mother, was not true to her bond of love, then how can they trust that their partner will be true to love. Often in their adult relationships these men act out again and again to test their partner's love. While the rejected adolescent boy imagines that he can no longer receive his mother's love because he is not worthy, as a grown man he may act out in ways that are unworthy and yet demand of the woman in his life that she offer him unconditional love. This testing does not heal the wound of the past, it merely reenacts it, for ultimately the woman will become weary of being tested and end the relationship, thus reenacting the abandonment.  This drama confirms for many men that they cannot put their trust in love. They decide that it is better to put their faith in being powerful, in being dominant." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219536-love-is-a-combination-of-care-commitment-knowledge-responsibility-respect</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:07:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219536-love-is-a-combination-of-care-commitment-knowledge-responsibility-respect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a combination of care, commitment, knowledge, responsibility, respect and trust." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295257-often-men-who-have-been-emotionally-neglected-and-abused-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295257-often-men-who-have-been-emotionally-neglected-and-abused-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often men who have been emotionally neglected and abused as children by dominating mothers bond with assertive women, only to have their childhood feelings of being engulfed surface.  While they could not 'smash their mommy' and still receive love, they find that they can engage in intimate violence with partners who respond to their acting out by trying harder to connect with them emotionally, hoping that the love offered in the present will heal the wounds of the past.  If only one party in the relationship is working to create love, to create the space of emotional connection, the dominator model remains in place and the relationship just becomes a site for continuous power struggle." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291578-love-is-an-action-never-simply-a-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:08:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291578-love-is-an-action-never-simply-a-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is an action, never simply a feeling." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497691-the-wounded-child-inside-many-males-is-a-boy-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:10:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497691-the-wounded-child-inside-many-males-is-a-boy-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the wounded child inside many males is a boy who, when he first spoke his truths, was silenced by paternal sadism, by a patriarchal world that did not want him to claim his true feelings.  The wounded child inside many females is a girl who was taught from early childhood that she must become something other than herself, deny her true feelings, in order to attract and please others.  When men and women punish each other for truth telling, we reinforce the notion that lies are better.  To be loving we willingly hear the other’s truth, and most important, we affirm the value of truth telling.  Lies may make people feel better, but they do not help them to know love." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497690-schools-for-love-do-not-exist-everyone-assumes-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:11:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497690-schools-for-love-do-not-exist-everyone-assumes-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["schools for love do not exist.  everyone assumes that we will know how to love instinctively.
despite overwhelming evidence to the contrary, we still accept that the family is the primary school for love.
those of us who do not learn how to love among family are expected to experience love in romantic relationships.  however this love often eludes us." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:12:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516826-it-still-took-years-for-me-to-let-go-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It still took years for me to let go of learned pattern's of behavior that negated my capacity to give and receive love.  One pattern that made the practice of love especially difficult was my constantly choosing to be with men who were emotionally wounded, who were not that interested in loving, even though they desired to be loved.  I wanted to know love but was afraid to be intimate.  By choosing men who were not interested in being loving, I was able to practice giving love but always within an unfufilling context.  Naturally, my need to receive love was not met. I got what I was accustomed to getting. Care and affection, usually mingled with a degree of unkindness, neglect, and on some occasions, out right cruelty." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35512-i-believe-that-when-people-die-they-go-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:13:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary Beth add a quote by Dara Horn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35512-i-believe-that-when-people-die-they-go-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that when people die, they go to the same place as all the people who haven’t yet been born.  That’s why it’s called the world to come, because that’s where they make the new souls for the future.  And the reward when good people die” – her mother paused, swallowed, paused again – “the reward when good people die is that they get to help make the people in their families who haven’t been born yet.  They pick out what kinds of traits they want the new people to have – they give them all the raw material of their souls, like their talents and their brains and their potential.  Of course it’s up to the new ones, once they’re born, what they’ll use and what they won’t, but that’s what everyone who dies is doing, I think.  They get to decide what kind of people the new ones might be able to become." -- Dara Horn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
