<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/691711-heather]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/691711-heather" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 18:48:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429043-but-those-who-seek-only-reassurance-from-life-will-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 18:48:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Simon Van Booy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429043-but-those-who-seek-only-reassurance-from-life-will-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But those who seek only reassurance from life will never be more than tourists—seeing everything and trying to possess what can only be felt.
Beauty is the shadow of imperfection." -- Simon Van Booy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76939-there-are-those-wonderful-moments-of-clarity-in-life-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 18:49:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Paula Poundstone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76939-there-are-those-wonderful-moments-of-clarity-in-life-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those wonderful moments of clarity in life when one is reminded how irreparably flawed we humans are. Once, when I was nineteen, on the subway in Boston I lost my balance slightly and bumped into an elderly woman. I quickly apologized and she replied, &quot;Well, hold on to something, stupid.&quot; There it is. That's it. That's it in a nutshell. I don't want to sound negative, but I think every fetus should be shown a film of that incident, maybe projected up on the uterine wall, and then asked if it wants to come out. I am a strong believer in a woman's right to choose, but I also think that in the last trimester, the kid should be given every opportunity to back out." -- Paula Poundstone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163365-life-is-a-comedy-to-those-who-think-a-tragedy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:31:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Jean Racine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163365-life-is-a-comedy-to-those-who-think-a-tragedy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a comedy to those who think, a tragedy to those who feel." -- Jean Racine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339165-about-a-month-ago-i-got-a-cactus-a-week</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:42:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Demetri Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339165-about-a-month-ago-i-got-a-cactus-a-week]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["About a month ago I got a cactus. A week later, it died. I was really depressed because I was like, 'Damn! I am less nurturing than a desert." -- Demetri Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:46:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people say, “Never let them see you cry.” I say, if you’re so mad you could just cry, then cry. It terrifies everyone." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426470-t-he-definition-of-crazy-in-show-business-is-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:55:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426470-t-he-definition-of-crazy-in-show-business-is-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[T]he definition of 'crazy' in show business is a woman who keeps talking even after no one wants to fuck her anymore." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435196-amy-poehler-made-it-clear-that-she-wasn-t-there-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:56:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435196-amy-poehler-made-it-clear-that-she-wasn-t-there-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Amy [Poehler] made it clear that she wasn’t there to be cute. She wasn’t there to play wives and girlfriends in the boys’ scenes. She was there to do what she wanted to do and she did not fucking care if you like it." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378312-most-photographers-have-some-kind-of-verbal-patter-going-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:57:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378312-most-photographers-have-some-kind-of-verbal-patter-going-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most photographers have some kind of verbal patter going on when they shoot: &quot;Great. Turn to me. Big smile. Less shark eyes. Have fun with it. Not like that.&quot; Some photographers are compulsively effusive. &quot;Beautiful. Amazing. Gorgeous! Ugh, so gorgeous!&quot; they yell at shutter speed. If you are anything less than insane, you will realize this is not sincere. It's hard to take because it's more positive feedback than you've received in your entire life thrown at you in fifteen seconds. It would be like going jogging while someone rode next to you in a slow-moving car, yelling, &quot;Yes! You are Carl Lewis! You're breaking a world record right now. Amazing! You are fast. You're going very fast, yes!" -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445395-whenever-someone-says-to-me-jerry-lewis-says-women-aren-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 12:58:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445395-whenever-someone-says-to-me-jerry-lewis-says-women-aren-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Whenever someone says to me, 'Jerry Lewis says women aren't funny,' or 'Christopher Hitchens says women aren't funny,' or 'Rick Fenderman says women aren't funny... Do you have anything to say to that?'

Yes. We don't fucking care if you like it.

I don't say it out loud, of course, because Jerry Lewis is a great philanthropist, Hitchens is very sick, and the third guy I made up." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445397-there-was-an-assumption-that-i-was-personally-attacking-sarah</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 13:03:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445397-there-was-an-assumption-that-i-was-personally-attacking-sarah]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there was an assumption that I was personally attacking Sarah Palin by impersonating her on TV. No one ever said it was 'mean' when Chevy Chase played Gerald Ford falling down all the time. No one ever accused Dana Carvey or Darrell Hammond or Dan Aykroyd of 'going too far' in their political impressions. You see what I'm getting at here. I am not mean and Mrs. Palin is not fragile. To imply otherwise is a disservice to us both." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581474-i-want-to-go-to-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 13:07:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/581474-i-want-to-go-to-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to go to there." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394313-a-tv-show-comprises-many-departments-costumes-props-talent-graphics-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 13:12:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394313-a-tv-show-comprises-many-departments-costumes-props-talent-graphics-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A TV show comprises many departments—Costumes, Props, Talent, Graphics, Set Dressing, Transportation. Everyone in every department wants to show off their skills and contribute creatively to the show, which is a blessing. You’re grateful to work with people who are talented and enthusiastic about their jobs. You would think that as a producer, your job would be to churn up creativity, but mostly your job is to police enthusiasm. You may have an occasion where the script calls for a bran muffin on a white plate and the Props Department shows up with a bran cake in the shape of Santa Claus sitting on a silver platter that says “Welcome to Denmark.” “We just thought it would be funny.” And you have to find a polite way to explain that the character is Jewish, so her eating Santa’s face might have negative connotations, and the silver tray, while beautiful, is giving a weird glare on camera and maybe let’s go with the bran muffin on the white plate. And then sometimes Actors have what they call “ideas.” Usually it involves them talking more, or, in the case of more experienced actors, sitting more. When Actors have ideas it’s very important to get to the core reason behind their idea." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733669-that-night-s-show-was-watched-by-ten-million-people-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 13:13:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/733669-that-night-s-show-was-watched-by-ten-million-people-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That night's show was watched by ten million people, so I guess that director at The Second City who said the audience &quot;didn't want to see a sketch with two women&quot; can go shit in his hat." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
