<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/693788-gemini]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/693788-gemini" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 15:21:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501308-i-don-t-like-anything-here-at-all-said-frodo-step</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 15:21:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Tolkien John Ronald Reuel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/501308-i-don-t-like-anything-here-at-all-said-frodo-step]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t like anything here at all.” said Frodo, “step or stone, breath or bone. Earth, air and water all seem accursed. But so our path is laid.”

“Yes, that’s so,” said Sam, “And we shouldn’t be here at all, if we’d known more about it before we started. But I suppose it’s often that way. The brave things in the old tales and songs, Mr. Frodo, adventures, as I used to call them. I used to think that they were things the wonderful folk of the stories went out and
looked for, because they wanted them, because they were exciting and life was a bit dull, a kind of a sport, as you might say. But that’s not the way of it with the tales that really mattered, or the ones that stay in the mind. Folk seem to have been just landed in them, usually their paths were laid that way, as you put it. But I expect they had lots of chances, like us, of turning back, only they didn’t. And if they had, we shouldn’t know, because they’d have been forgotten. We hear about those as just went on, and not all to a good end, mind you; at least not to what folk inside a story and not outside it call a good end. You know, coming home, and finding things all right, though not quite the same; like old Mr Bilbo. But those aren’t always the best tales to hear, though they may be the best tales to get landed in! I wonder what sort of a tale we’ve fallen into?”

“I wonder,” said Frodo, “But I don’t know. And that’s the way of a real tale. Take any one that you’re fond of. You may know, or guess, what kind of a tale it is, happy-ending or sad-ending, but the people in it don’t know. And you don’t want them to." -- Tolkien John Ronald Reuel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750676-there-are-two-sacred-causes-in-this-world-he-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 18:11:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Rachel Hartman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750676-there-are-two-sacred-causes-in-this-world-he-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two sacred causes in this world,” he said, holding up his pinkie and ring ringer. “Chance and necessity. By chance I was there to help when you had need." -- Rachel Hartman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126510-i-am-convinced-that-most-people-do-not-grow-up-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 18:03:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126510-i-am-convinced-that-most-people-do-not-grow-up-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am convinced that most people do not grow up...We marry and dare to have children and call that growing up. I think what we do is mostly grow old. We carry accumulation of years in our bodies, and on our faces, but generally our real selves, the children inside, are innocent and shy as magnolias." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8860-try-not-to-become-a-man-of-success-rather-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2013 18:03:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8860-try-not-to-become-a-man-of-success-rather-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try not to become a man of success. Rather become a man of value." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 18:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m not laughing.” I was actually crying. “And please don’t laugh at me now, but I think the reason it’s so hard for me to get over this guy is because I seriously believed David was my soul mate. ”He probably was. Your problem is you don’t understand what that word means. People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that’s what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that’s holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life. A true soul mate is probably the most important person you’ll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake. But to live with a soul mate forever? Nah. Too painful. Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then they leave. And thank God for it. Your problem is, you just can’t let this one go. It’s over, Groceries. David’s purpose was to shake you up, drive you out of your marriage that you needed to leave, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light could get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you had to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master and beat it. That was his job, and he did great, but now it’s over. Problem is, you can’t accept that his relationship had a real short shelf life. You’re like a dog at the dump, baby – you’re just lickin’ at the empty tin can, trying to get more nutrition out of it. And if you’re not careful, that can’s gonna get stuck on your snout forever and make your life miserable. So drop it.“But I love him.”
“So love him.” “But I miss him.” “So miss him. Send him some love and light every time you think about him, then drop it. You’re just afraid to let go of the last bits of David because then you’ll be really alone, and Liz Gilbert is scared to death of what will happen if she’s really alone. But here’s what you gotta understand, Groceries. If you clear out all that space in your mind that you’re using right now to obsess about this guy, you’ll have a vacuum there, an open spot – a doorway. And guess what the universe will do with the doorway? It will rush in – God will rush in – and fill you with more love than you ever dreamed. So stop using David to block that door. Let it go." -- Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105784-the-life-of-every-man-is-a-diary-in-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:33:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105784-the-life-of-every-man-is-a-diary-in-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The life of every man is a diary in which he means to write one story, and writes another; and his humblest hour is when he compares the volume as it is with what he vowed to make it." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215709-keep-in-mind-eragon-that-no-one-thinks-himself-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 19:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Christopher Paolini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215709-keep-in-mind-eragon-that-no-one-thinks-himself-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep in mind, Eragon, that no one thinks himself a villain, and few make decisions they think are wrong.  A person may dislike his choice, but he will stand by it because, even in the worst circumstances, he believes that it was the best option available to him at the time." -- Christopher Paolini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322447-i-ll-fight-when-needed-revel-when-there-s-an-occasion-mourn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 19:52:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Christopher Paolini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322447-i-ll-fight-when-needed-revel-when-there-s-an-occasion-mourn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll fight when needed, revel when there's an occasion, mourn when there is greif and die if my time comes...But I will not let anyone use me against my will." -- Christopher Paolini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458358-that-s-the-secret-to-performance-conviction-the-right-note-played</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 18:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Rachel Hartman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/458358-that-s-the-secret-to-performance-conviction-the-right-note-played]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s the secret to performance: conviction.  The right note played tentatively still misses its mark, but play boldly and no one will question you.  If one believes there is truth in art – and I do – then it’s troubling how similar the skill of performing is to lying.  Maybe lying is itself a kind of art.  I think about that more than I should." -- Rachel Hartman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286105-but-there-is-one-thing-you-must-remember-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 20:24:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Juliet Marillier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286105-but-there-is-one-thing-you-must-remember-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there is one thing you must remember, if you forget all else. There is no good or evil, save in the way you see the world. There is no dark or light save in your own vision. All changes in the blink of an eyelid; yet all remains the same." -- Juliet Marillier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5908-what-difference-does-it-make-to-the-dead-the-orphans</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 15:56:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5908-what-difference-does-it-make-to-the-dead-the-orphans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What difference does it make to the dead, the orphans and the homeless, whether the mad destruction is wrought under the name of totalitarianism or in the holy name of liberty or democracy?" -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811666-the-dark-breaks-wide-in-fragile-rays-dawn-on-ithiss-tor</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 19:35:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Ann Aguirre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811666-the-dark-breaks-wide-in-fragile-rays-dawn-on-ithiss-tor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dark breaks wide in fragile rays.  Dawn on Ithiss-Tor is more subtle than other sunrises.  I have lost count of the worlds where I have stood and watched the light rise, peeling away the sky, sometimes in quiet colors, and sometimes in raw, violent slashes, as if the goddess I don't believe in has cut her veins.  And sometimes, as on Gehenna, the sky changes not at all, just endless night, or endless brilliance--and after a time, the constant uniformity makes you feel as if you are the thing that must give way." -- Ann Aguirre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640483-i-had-felt-the-shot-coming-i-hadn-t-realized-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 18:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Rachel Hartman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640483-i-had-felt-the-shot-coming-i-hadn-t-realized-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had felt the shot coming; I hadn’t realized the bow was loaded with this very quarrel, perfectly calibrated to hit him hardest. What part of me had been studying him, stockpiling knowledge as ammunition?" -- Rachel Hartman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192309-the-road-that-is-built-in-hope-is-more-pleasant</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 19:10:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Marion Zimmer Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192309-the-road-that-is-built-in-hope-is-more-pleasant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road that is built in hope is more pleasant to the traveler than the road built in despair, even though they both lead to the same destination." -- Marion Zimmer Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412068-it-would-have-been-funny-if-i-had-been-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 20:07:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Sherwood Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412068-it-would-have-been-funny-if-i-had-been-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would have been funny if I had been an observer and not a participant, an idea that gave me a disconcerting insight into gossip. As I walked beside the silent Tamara, I realized that despite how entertaining certain stories were, at the bottom of every item of gossip there was someone getting hurt." -- Sherwood Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246298-whether-you-approach-your-dreams-on-soft-feet-or-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 12:29:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Devon Monk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246298-whether-you-approach-your-dreams-on-soft-feet-or-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether you approach your dreams on soft feet or in a breathless run, just so long as you acknowledge that your dreams are valuable and worthy of pursuing, then you’ve made it." -- Devon Monk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151093-is-this-the-part-where-you-say-if-i-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:09:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151093-is-this-the-part-where-you-say-if-i-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is this the part where you say if I hurt her, you'll kill me?&quot;
&quot;No&quot; Simon said, &quot;If you hurt Clary she's quite capable of killing you herself. Possibly with a variety of weapons." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/927609-you-can-live-without-me-i-don-t-want-to-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 19:35:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Ann Aguirre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/927609-you-can-live-without-me-i-don-t-want-to-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can live without me.&quot;

&quot;I don't want to.&quot;

I feared a love like this - that made us incomplete without each other. It was beautiful but treacherous, like snow that looked white and pure and lovely from the safety of your window, but when you stepped out to touch the softness, the cold first stole your breath, and then your will to move, until you could just lay down in it and let the numbness take you. yet I didn't want to be without him either, so I didn't chide him for the statement." -- Ann Aguirre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598381-temper-is-a-weapon-that-we-hold-by-the-blade</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:20:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598381-temper-is-a-weapon-that-we-hold-by-the-blade]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Temper is a weapon that we hold by the blade." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148223-not-everything-is-about-you-clary-said-furiously-possibly-jace</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:09:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148223-not-everything-is-about-you-clary-said-furiously-possibly-jace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not everything is about you,&quot; Clary said furiously.
&quot;Possibly,&quot; Jace said, &quot;but you do have to admit that the majority of things are." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682911-she-was-not-a-little-girl-heart-broken-about-him-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 17:26:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682911-she-was-not-a-little-girl-heart-broken-about-him-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎&quot;She was not a little girl heart-broken about him; she was a grown woman smiling at it all, but they were wet smiles." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533514-what-the-hell-i-muttered-then-i-realized-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 20:12:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Devon Monk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533514-what-the-hell-i-muttered-then-i-realized-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What the hell?” I muttered. Then I realized it was Jack Quinn’s car. Jack was a Hound and Bea’s boyfriend. The left blinker flashed on for just a second, and then Jack drove at speed again.

“Zayvion, I’m sorry to tell you I think I have a crush on another man.”

“Who is this unfortunate and soon-to-be-dead fool?” he asked.

“Jack. That’s his car. He must have been waiting for us, or maybe he followed us.”

“Jack Quinn has been following us?” Shame said.

“And now he’s taking us to Collins, I think.”

“Or a trap,” Shame said.

“He’s a Hound, Shame.”

“My statement stands.”

“You still don’t get it, do you?” I turned left, following the car. “Hounds are loyal. Jack and Bea told me they’d help me if they could. They’re not going to turn against me while I’m in trouble.”

“What happens when you’re not in trouble?” Shame asked.

“Don’t know. It’s never happened." -- Devon Monk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116279-don-t-tell-me-jace-said-simon-s-turned-himself-into-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:09:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116279-don-t-tell-me-jace-said-simon-s-turned-himself-into-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't tell me,&quot; Jace said, &quot;Simon's turned himself into an ocelot and you want me to do something about it before Isabelle makes him into a stole. Well, you'll have have to wait till tomorrow. I'm out of commission.&quot; He pointed at himself - he was wearing blue pajamas with a hole in the sleeve. &quot;Look. Jammies.&quot;
&quot;Jace,&quot; Clary said, &quot;this is important.&quot;
&quot;Don't tell me,&quot; he said. &quot;You've got a drawing emergency. You need a nude model. Well, I'm not in the mood. You could always ask Hodge,&quot; he said as an afterthought. &quot;I hear he'll do anything for a -&quot;
&quot;JACE!&quot; she interrupted him, her voice rising to a scream. &quot;JUST SHUT UP FOR A SECOND AND LISTEN, WILL YOU?" -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129803-never-doubt-my-weaseling-abilities-shadowhunter-for-they-are-epic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:10:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129803-never-doubt-my-weaseling-abilities-shadowhunter-for-they-are-epic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never doubt my weaseling abilities, Shadowhunter, for they are epic and memorable in their scope." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134516-so-when-the-moon-s-only-partly-full-you-only-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:10:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134516-so-when-the-moon-s-only-partly-full-you-only-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So when the moon's only partly full, you only feel a little wolfy?&quot; 
&quot;You could say that.&quot;
&quot;Well, you can go ahead and hang your head out the car window if you feel like it.&quot;
&quot;I'm a werewolf, not a golden retriever." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116252-let-me-put-it-this-way-my-father-believed-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:11:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Jace from Cassandra Clare's City of Bones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116252-let-me-put-it-this-way-my-father-believed-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me put it this way, my father believed in a righteous God. Deus volt, that was his motto- 'because God wills it.' It was the Crusaders' motto, and they went into battle and were slaughtered just like my father. And when I saw him lying dead in a pool of his own blood, I knew then that I hadn't stopped believing in God. I'd just stopped believing God cared. There might be a God, Clary, and there might not, but I don't think it matters. Either way we're on our own." -- Jace from Cassandra Clare's City of Bones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42158-he-d-felt-like-a-jack-o-lantern-for-the-past-few-days</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42158-he-d-felt-like-a-jack-o-lantern-for-the-past-few-days]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He'd felt like a jack-o-lantern for the past few days, as if his guts had been yanked out with a fork and dumped in a heap while a grinning smile stayed plastered on his face." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148339-there-is-no-pretending-jace-said-with-absolute-clarity-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:11:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148339-there-is-no-pretending-jace-said-with-absolute-clarity-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no pretending,&quot; Jace said with absolute clarity. &quot;I love you, and I will love you until I die, and if there is life after that, I'll love you then." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134515-jesus-luke-exclaimed-actually-it-s-just-me-said-simon-although</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:11:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134515-jesus-luke-exclaimed-actually-it-s-just-me-said-simon-although]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus!&quot; Luke exclaimed.
&quot;Actually, it's just me,&quot; said Simon. &quot;Although I've been told the resemblance is startling." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85108-we-came-to-see-jace-is-he-alright-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 13:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gemini add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85108-we-came-to-see-jace-is-he-alright-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We came to see Jace. Is he alright?&quot;
&quot;I don't know,&quot; Magnus said. &quot;Does he normally just lie on the floor like that without moving?" -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
