<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/693832-kit]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/693832-kit" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 19:07:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60256-i-do-think-that-women-could-make-politics-irrelevant-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 19:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kit add a quote by Germaine Greer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60256-i-do-think-that-women-could-make-politics-irrelevant-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do think that women could make politics irrelevant; by a kind of spontaneous cooperative action the like of which we have never seen; which is so far from people’s ideas of state structure or viable social structure that it seems to them like total anarchy — when what it really is, is very subtle forms of interrelation that do not follow some heirarchal pattern which is fundamentally patriarchal. The opposite to patriarchy is not matriarchy but fraternity, yet I think it’s women who are going to have to break this spiral of power and find the trick of cooperation." -- Germaine Greer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 16:49:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kit add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ideally, what should be said to every child, repeatedly, throughout his or her school life is something like this: 'You are in the process of being indoctrinated. We have not yet evolved a system of education that is not a system of indoctrination. We are sorry, but it is the best we can do. What you are being taught here is an amalgam of current prejudice and the choices of this particular culture. The slightest look at history will show how impermanent these must be. You are being taught by people who have been able to accommodate themselves to a regime of thought laid down by their predecessors. It is a self-perpetuating system. Those of you who are more robust and individual than others will be encouraged to leave and find ways of educating yourself — educating your own judgements. Those that stay must remember, always, and all the time, that they are being moulded and patterned to fit into the narrow and particular needs of this particular society." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
