<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/695452-bridget]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/695452-bridget" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 08:37:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59550-when-i-was-in-school-i-studied-biology-i-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 08:37:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59550-when-i-was-in-school-i-studied-biology-i-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was in school I studied biology. I learned that in making their experiments scientists will take some group--bacteria, mice, people--and subject that group to certain conditions. They compare the results with a second group which has not been disturbed. This second group is called the control group. It is the control group which enables the scientist gauge the effect of his experiment. To judge the significance of what has occurred. In history there are no control groups. There is no one to tell us what might have been. We weep over the might have been, but there is no might have been. There never was. It is supposed to be true that those who o not know history are condemned to repeat it. I don't believe knowing can save us. What is constant in history is greed and foolishness and a love of blood and this is a thing that even God--who knows all that can be known--seems powerless to change." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523158-near-the-end-of-love-s-labor-eva-feder-kittay-1999</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 10:12:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Cynthia Lewiecki-Wilson and Jen Cellio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523158-near-the-end-of-love-s-labor-eva-feder-kittay-1999]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Near the end of &lt;i&gt;Love's Labor&lt;/i&gt;, Eva Feder Kittay (1999, 154) writes that a fundamental aspect of a just society is related to the conditions and limits of mothering. In a just society, women with disabilities can mother because there is adequate emotional and material support for them to do so, and given a context of support and approval to reproduce, they can also choose not to bear children. In a just society, mothers of children with disability can mother, and they, their children, and other needed caregivers will be adequately supported.&quot; (15)" -- Cynthia Lewiecki-Wilson and Jen Cellio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598522-robert-was-concerned-with-how-to-make-the-photograph-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 13:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Patti Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598522-robert-was-concerned-with-how-to-make-the-photograph-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Robert was concerned with how to make the photograph, and I with how to be the photograph." -- Patti Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612707-because-mothers-make-us-because-they-map-our-emotional-terrain</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 10:20:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Rebecca Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612707-because-mothers-make-us-because-they-map-our-emotional-terrain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because mothers make us, because they map our emotional terrain before we even know we are capable of having an emotional terrain, they know just where to stick the dynamite. With a few small power plays - a skeptical comment, the withholding of approval or praise - a mother can devastate a daughter. Decades of subtle undermining can stunt a daughter, or so monopolize her energy that she in effect stunts herself. Muted, fearful, riddled with self-doubt, she can remain trapped in daughterhood forever, the one place she feels confident she knows the rules." -- Rebecca Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151867-what-wouldn-t-i-give-now-for-a-never-changing-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 13:03:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151867-what-wouldn-t-i-give-now-for-a-never-changing-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What wouldn't I give now for a never-changing map of the ever-constant ineffable? To possess, as it were, an atlas of clouds." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760202-what-three-things-can-never-be-done-forget-keep-silent</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 06:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Muriel Rukeyser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/760202-what-three-things-can-never-be-done-forget-keep-silent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What three things can never be done?
Forget. Keep silent. Stand alone.
The hill of glass, the fatal brilliant plain." -- Muriel Rukeyser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 10:09:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the effect of her being on those around her was incalculably diffusive: for the growing good of the world is partly dependent on unhistoric acts; and that things are not so ill with you and me as they might have been, is half owing to the number who lived faithfully a hidden life, and rest in unvisited tombs." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500581-true-nervous-very-very-dreadfully-nervous-i-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 13:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500581-true-nervous-very-very-dreadfully-nervous-i-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TRUE! – nervous – very, very dreadfully nervous I had been and am; but why will you say that I am mad? The disease had sharpened my senses – not destroyed – not dulled them. Above all was the sense of hearing acute. I heard all things in the heaven and in the earth. I heard many things in hell. How, then, am I mad? Hearken! and observe how healthily – how calmly I can tell you the whole story." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625910-why-is-this-the-new-feminism-and-not-what-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 12:33:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Ariel Levy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625910-why-is-this-the-new-feminism-and-not-what-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is this the 'new feminism' and not what it looks like: the old objectification?" -- Ariel Levy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 07:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as a thief loves a gallery and as a crow loves a murder, as a cloud loves bats and as a range loves braes. I will love you as misfortune loves orphans, as fire loves innocence and as justice loves to sit and watch while everything goes wrong. I will love you as a battlefield loves young men and as peppermints love your allergies, and I will love you as the banana peel loves the shoe of a man who was just struck by a shingle falling off a house. I will love you as a volunteer fire department loves rushing into burning buildings and as burning buildings love to chase them back out, and as a parachute loves to leave a blimp and as a blimp operator loves to chase after it.
I will love you as a dagger loves a certain person’s back, and as a certain person loves to wear dagger proof tunics, and as a dagger proof tunic loves to go to a certain dry cleaning facility, and how a certain employee of a dry cleaning facility loves to stay up late with a pair of binoculars, watching a dagger factory for hours in the hopes of catching a burglar, and as a burglar loves sneaking up behind people with binoculars, suddenly realizing that she has left her dagger at home. I will love you as a drawer loves a secret compartment, and as a secret compartment loves a secret, and as a secret loves to make a person gasp, and as a gasping person loves a glass of brandy to calm their nerves, and as a glass of brandy loves to shatter on the floor, and as the noise of glass shattering loves to make someone else gasp, and as someone else gasping loves a nearby desk to lean against, even if leaning against it presses a lever that loves to open a drawer and reveal a secret compartment. I will love you until all such compartments are discovered and opened, and until all the secrets have gone gasping into the world. I will love you until all the codes and hearts have been broken and until every anagram and egg has been unscrambled.
I will love you until every fire is extinguised and until every home is rebuilt from the handsomest and most susceptible of woods, and until every criminal is handcuffed by the laziest of policemen. I will love until M. hates snakes and J. hates grammar, and I will love you until C. realizes S. is not worthy of his love and N. realizes he is not worthy of the V. I will love you until the bird hates a nest and the worm hates an apple, and until the apple hates a tree and the tree hates a nest, and until a bird hates a tree and an apple hates a nest, although honestly I cannot imagine that last occurrence no matter how hard I try. I will love you as we grow older, which has just happened, and has happened again, and happened several days ago, continuously, and then several years before that, and will continue to happen as the spinning hands of every clock and the flipping pages of every calendar mark the passage of time, except for the clocks that people have forgotten to wind and the calendars that people have forgotten to place in a highly visible area. I will love you as we find ourselves farther and farther from one another, where we once we were so close that we could slip the curved straw, and the long, slender spoon, between our lips and fingers respectively.
I will love you until the chances of us running into one another slip from slim to zero, and until your face is fogged by distant memory, and your memory faced by distant fog, and your fog memorized by a distant face, and your distance distanced by the memorized memory of a foggy fog. I will love you no matter where you go and who you see, no matter where you avoid and who you don’t see, and no matter who sees you avoiding where you go. I will love you no matter what happens to you, and no matter how I discover what happens to you, and no matter what happens to me as I discover this, and now matter how I am discovered after what happens to me as I am discovering this." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/891013-are-we-not-witnessing-a-strange-tableau-of-survival-whenever</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 08:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Annalee Newitz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/891013-are-we-not-witnessing-a-strange-tableau-of-survival-whenever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are we not witnessing a strange tableau of survival whenever a bird alights on the head of a crocodile, bringing together the evolutionary offspring of Triassic and Jurassic?" -- Annalee Newitz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278644-i-will-remember-the-kisses-our-lips-raw-with-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278644-i-will-remember-the-kisses-our-lips-raw-with-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will remember the kisses 
our lips raw with love 
and how you gave me 
everything you had 
and how I 
offered you what was left of 
me, 
and I will remember your small room 
the feel of you 
the light in the window 
your records 
your books 
our morning coffee 
our noons our nights 
our bodies spilled together 
sleeping 
the tiny flowing currents 
immediate and forever 
your leg my leg 
your arm my arm 
your smile and the warmth 
of you 
who made me laugh 
again." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/891913-i-know-a-woman-who-keeps-buying-puzzles-chinese-puzzles</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 11:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/891913-i-know-a-woman-who-keeps-buying-puzzles-chinese-puzzles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know a woman
who keeps buying puzzles
chinese
puzzles
blocks
wires
pieces that finally fit
into some order.
she works it out
mathmatically
she solves all her
puzzles
lives down by the sea
puts sugar out for the ants
and believes
ultimately
in a better world.
her hair is white
she seldom combs it
her teeth are snaggled
and she wears loose shapeless
coveralls over a body most
women would wish they had.
for many years she irritated me
with what I considered her
eccentricities-
like soaking eggshells in water
(to feed the plants so that
they'd get calcium).
but finally when I think of her
life
and compare it to other lives
more dazzling, original
and beautiful
I realize that she has hurt fewer
people than anybody I know
(and by hurt I simply mean hurt).
she has had some terrible times,
times when maybe I should have
helped her more
for she is the mother of my only
child
and we were once great lovers,
but she has come through
like I said
she has hurt fewer people than
anybody I know,
and if you look at it like that,
well,
she has created a better world.
she has won.
Frances, this poem is for
you." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982340-utah-s-mountains-are-not-the-himalayas-but-by-one-standard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 08:34:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Michael Weibel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982340-utah-s-mountains-are-not-the-himalayas-but-by-one-standard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Utah's mountains are not the Himalayas, but by one standard they are the highest in the country. According to a series of stories in the The Salt Lake Tribune, the average elevation of Utah's tallest peaks in each county is roughly 11,222 feet. Colorado ranks second, with an average county high peak elevation of 10,791 feet, followed by Nevada (10,764) and Wyoming (10,179). Alaska, home to the country's highest peak - the 20,320-foot Denali - ranks only sixth, with an average county high peak elevation of 9,280 feet." -- Michael Weibel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982342-you-ve-called-your-carelessness-love-and-made-a-virtue-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 08:35:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/982342-you-ve-called-your-carelessness-love-and-made-a-virtue-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've called your carelessness love and made a virtue of irresponsibility." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/989873-i-turn-on-my-computer-to-search-craigslist-for-apartment</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 10:04:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Jonathan Goldstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/989873-i-turn-on-my-computer-to-search-craigslist-for-apartment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I turn on my computer to search Craigslist for apartment listings. The wireless window pops up, and I realize with some regret that all I know about my neighbours is their wireless network names: Krypton, Space balls, Couscous, and Scarlet. From this I can tell little else than that they're fans of Superman, Mel Brooks, Middle Eastern cuisine, and the colour red. I look out my window, wondering whose house is whose and what private food and entertainment consumption occurs in each and how I will never get to know." -- Jonathan Goldstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 16:49:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188039-men-are-afraid-that-women-will-laugh-at-them-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men are afraid that women will laugh at them. Women are afraid that men will kill them." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
