<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696233-leslie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696233-leslie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 10:10:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 10:10:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodbye,&quot; said the fox. &quot;And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48418-so-the-little-prince-tamed-the-fox-and-when-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:50:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48418-so-the-little-prince-tamed-the-fox-and-when-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So the little prince tamed the fox. And when the hour of his departure drew near--

Ah,&quot; said the fox, &quot;I shall cry.&quot;

It is your own fault,&quot; said the little prince. &quot;I never wished you any sort of harm; but you wanted me to tame you . . .&quot;

Yes, that is so,&quot; said the fox.

But now you are going to cry!&quot; said the little prince.

Yes, that is so,&quot; said the fox.

Then it has done you no good at all!&quot;

It has done me good,&quot; said the fox, &quot;because of the color of the wheat fields." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5882-it-is-a-truth-universally-acknowledged-that-a-single-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:52:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5882-it-is-a-truth-universally-acknowledged-that-a-single-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a truth universally acknowledged, that a single man in possession of a good fortune, must be in want of a wife." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:53:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted you to see what real courage is, instead of getting the idea that courage is a man with a gun in his hand. It's when you know you're licked before you begin, but you begin anyway and see it through no matter what.
- Atticus Finch" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12619-atticus-said-to-jem-one-day-i-d-rather-you-shot</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:53:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12619-atticus-said-to-jem-one-day-i-d-rather-you-shot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Atticus said to Jem one day, &quot;I’d rather you shot at tin cans in the backyard, but I know you’ll go after birds.  Shoot all the blue jays you want, if you can hit ‘em, but remember it’s a sin to kill a mockingbird.&quot;  That was the only time I ever heard Atticus say it was a sin to do something, and I asked Miss Maudie about it.  &quot;Your father’s right,&quot; she said.  &quot;Mockingbirds don’t do one thing except make music for us to enjoy.  They don’t eat up people’s gardens, don’t nest in corn cribs, they don’t do one thing but sing their hearts out for us.  That’s why it’s a sin to kill a mockingbird." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28188-i-had-found-a-new-friend-the-surprising-thing-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Lloyd Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28188-i-had-found-a-new-friend-the-surprising-thing-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had found a new friend. The surprising thing is where I’d found him – not up a tree or sulking in the shade, or splashing around in one of the hill streams, but in a book. No one had told us kids to look there for a friend. Or that you could slip inside the skin of another. Or travel to another place with marshes, and where, to our ears, the bad people spoke like pirates. " -- Lloyd Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108511-in-that-macondo-forgotten-even-by-the-birds-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2009 11:55:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Leslie add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108511-in-that-macondo-forgotten-even-by-the-birds-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In that Macondo forgotten even by the birds, where the dust and the heat had become so strong that it was difficult to breathe, secluded by solitude and love and by the solitude of love in a house where it was almost impossible to sleep because of the noise of the red ants, Aureliano, and Amaranta Úrsula were the only happy beings, and the most happy on the face of the earth." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
