<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696878-evan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696878-evan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 17:34:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6293-just-that-you-do-the-right-thing-the-rest-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 17:34:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6293-just-that-you-do-the-right-thing-the-rest-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just that you do the right thing. The rest doesn't matter. Cold or warm. Tired or well-rested. Despised or honored. Dying...or busy with other assignments. Because dying, too, is one of our assignments in life. There as well: &quot;To do what needs doing.&quot; Look inward. Don't let the true nature of anything elude you. Before long, all existing things will be transformed, to rise like smoke (assuming all things become one), or be dispersed in fragments...to move from one unselfish act to another with God in mind. Only there, delight and stillness...when jarred, unavoidably, by circumstances, revert at once to yourself, and don't lose the rhythm more than you can help. You'll have a better grasp of the harmony if you keep going back to it." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31339-so-this-is-hell-i-d-never-have-believed-it-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 17:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31339-so-this-is-hell-i-d-never-have-believed-it-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So this is hell. I'd never have believed it. You remember all we were told about the torture-chambers, the fire and brimstone, the &quot;burning marl.&quot; Old wives' tales! There's no need for red-hot pokers. Hell is—other people!" -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6295-when-the-short-days-of-winter-came-dusk-fell-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2007 17:45:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Evan add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6295-when-the-short-days-of-winter-came-dusk-fell-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the short days of winter came, dusk fell before we had well eaten our dinners. When we met in the street the houses had grown sombre. The space of sky above us was the colour of ever-changing violet and towards it the lamps of the street lifted their feeble lanterns. The cold air stung us and we played till our bodies glowed. Our shouts echoed in the silent street." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
