<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696935-anemia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/696935-anemia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 05:32:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244136-and-i-imagine-with-great-pleasure-all-the-horrible-stirrings</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 05:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Alexandro Jodorowsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244136-and-i-imagine-with-great-pleasure-all-the-horrible-stirrings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I imagine... with great pleasure... all the horrible stirrings of the nonmanifested to bring forth the scream which creates the universe.  Maybe one day I'll see you trembling, and you'll go into convulsion and grow larger and smaller until your mouth opens and the world will come from your mouth, escaping through the window like a river, and it will flood the city.  And then we'll begin to live. " -- Alexandro Jodorowsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333993-what-i-am-trying-to-do-when-i-use-symbols</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 05:32:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Alejandro Jodorowsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333993-what-i-am-trying-to-do-when-i-use-symbols]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I am trying to do when I use symbols is to awaken in your unconscious some reaction. I am very conscious of what I am using because symbols can be very dangerous. When we use normal language we can defend ourselves because our society is a linguistic society, a semantic society. But when you start to speak, not with words, but only with images, the people cannot defend themselves." -- Alejandro Jodorowsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:00:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18883-you-do-not-need-to-leave-your-room-remain-sitting</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18883-you-do-not-need-to-leave-your-room-remain-sitting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not need to leave your room. Remain sitting at your table and listen. Do not even listen, simply wait, be quiet, still and solitary. The world will freely offer itself to you to be unmasked, it has no choice, it will roll in ecstasy at your feet." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:03:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we ought to read only the kind of books that wound or stab us. If the book we're reading doesn't wake us up with a blow to the head, what are we reading for? So that it will make us happy, as you write? Good Lord, we would be happy precisely if we had no books, and the kind of books that make us happy are the kind we could write ourselves if we had to. But we need books that affect us like a disaster, that grieve us deeply, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, like being banished into forests far from everyone, like a suicide. A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us. That is my belief." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209433-i-need-solitude-for-my-writing-not-like-a-hermit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 17:05:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209433-i-need-solitude-for-my-writing-not-like-a-hermit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I need solitude for my writing; not 'like a hermit' - that wouldn't be enough - but like a dead man." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355176-i-spell-god-with-two-o-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 07:44:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Jon Shculberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355176-i-spell-god-with-two-o-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I spell God with two o's." -- Jon Shculberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/687225-i-was-in-the-winter-of-my-life--and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2013 19:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Lana Del Rey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/687225-i-was-in-the-winter-of-my-life--and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was in the winter of my life- and the men I met along the road were my only summer. At night I fell sleep with visions of myself dancing and laughing and crying with them. Three years down the line of being on an endless world tour and memories of them were the only things that sustained me, and my only real happy times. I was a singer, not a very popular one, who once had dreams of becoming a beautiful poet- but upon an unfortunate series of events saw those dreams dashed and divided like a million stars in the night sky that I wished on over and over again- sparkling and broken. But I really didn’t mind because I knew that it takes getting everything you ever wanted and then losing it to know what true freedom is.

When the people I used to know found out what I had been doing, how I had been living- they asked me why. But there’s no use in talking to people who have a home, they have no idea what its like to seek safety in other people, for home to be wherever you lay your head.

I was always an unusual girl, my mother told me that I had a chameleon soul. No moral compass pointing me due north, no fixed personality. Just an inner indecisiveness that was as wide as wavering as the ocean. And if I said that I didn't plan for it to turn out this way I’d be lying- because I was born to be the other woman. I belonged to no one- who belonged to everyone, who had nothing- who wanted everything with a fire for every experience and an obsession for freedom that terrified me to the point that I couldn’t even talk about- and pushed me to a nomadic point of madness that both dazzled and dizzied me.

Every night I used to pray that I’d find my people- and finally I did- on the open road. We have nothing to lose, nothing to gain, nothing we desired anymore- except to make our lives into a work of art." -- Lana Del Rey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106280-i-will-not-wait-to-love-as-best-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 09:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106280-i-will-not-wait-to-love-as-best-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not wait to love as best as I can. We thought we were young and that there would be time to love well sometime in the future. This is a terrible way to think. It is no way to live, to wait to love." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:07:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What passes for hip cynical transcendence of sentiment is really some kind of fear of being really human, since to be really human [...] is probably to be unavoidably sentimental and naïve and goo-prone and generally pathetic." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 19:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2061-life-shrinks-or-expands-in-proportion-to-one-s-courage</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 19:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2061-life-shrinks-or-expands-in-proportion-to-one-s-courage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515108-dada-is-not-modern-at-all-it-is-rather-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 06:58:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Tristan Tzara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515108-dada-is-not-modern-at-all-it-is-rather-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dada is not modern at all, it is rather a return to a quasi-Buddhist religion of indifference. Dada puts an artificial sweetness onto things, a snow of butterflies coming out of a conjurer's skull. Dada is stillness and does not understand the passions." -- Tristan Tzara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182397-what-kind-of-idea-are-you-are-you-the-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 17:03:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[anemia add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182397-what-kind-of-idea-are-you-are-you-the-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What kind of idea are you? Are you the kind that compromises, does deals, accomodates itself to society, aims to find a niche, to survive; or are you the cussed, bloody-minded, ramrod-backed type of damnfool notion that would rather break than sway with the breeze? – The kind that will almost certainly, ninety-nine times out of hundred, be smashed to bits; but, the hundredth time, will change the world." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
