<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/699001-zach]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/699001-zach" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 12:31:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83303-we-are-going-to-die-and-that-makes-us-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 12:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zach add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83303-we-are-going-to-die-and-that-makes-us-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are going to die, and that makes us the lucky ones. Most people are never going to die because they are never going to be born. The potential people who could have been here in my place but who will in fact never see the light of day outnumber the sand grains of Arabia. Certainly those unborn ghosts include greater poets than Keats, scientists greater than Newton. We know this because the set of possible people allowed by our DNA so massively exceeds the set of actual people. In the teeth of these stupefying odds it is you and I, in our ordinariness, that are here.We privileged few, who won the lottery of birth against all odds, how dare we whine at our inevitable return to that prior state from which the vast majority have never stirred?" -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77428-bush-and-bin-laden-are-really-on-the-same-side</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 12:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zach add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77428-bush-and-bin-laden-are-really-on-the-same-side]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bush and bin Laden are really on the same side: the side of faith and violence against the side of reason and discussion. Both have implacable faith that they are right and the other is evil. Each believes that when he dies he is going to heaven. Each believes that if he could kill the other, his path to paradise in the next world would be even swifter. The delusional &quot;next world&quot; is welcome to both of them. This world would be a much better place without either of them. " -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
