<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700282-kirstie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700282-kirstie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 19:46:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347747-decadence-is-the-total-loss-of-unconsciousness-which-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 19:46:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/347747-decadence-is-the-total-loss-of-unconsciousness-which-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Decadence is the total loss of unconsciousness, which is the very basis of life. Could it think, the heart would stop beating." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348104-pg-9-in-my-heart-there-s-a-peaceful-anguish-and-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 20:29:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348104-pg-9-in-my-heart-there-s-a-peaceful-anguish-and-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["pg.9 &quot;In my heart there's a peaceful anguish, and my calm is made of resignation." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348519-pg-9-the-consciousness-of-life-s-unconsciousness-is-the-oldest</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 18:37:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/348519-pg-9-the-consciousness-of-life-s-unconsciousness-is-the-oldest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["pg 9, &quot;The consciousness of life's unconsciousness is the oldest tax levied on the intelligence." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525817-history-knew-the-truth-history-was-the-most-inhuman-product</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2012 19:35:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Yukio Mishima]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525817-history-knew-the-truth-history-was-the-most-inhuman-product]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History knew the truth.  History was the most inhuman product of humanity.It scooped up the whole of human will and, like the goddess Kali in Calcutta, dripped blood from its mouth as it bit and crunched." -- Yukio Mishima]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542602-he-seemed-to-savor-telling-the-story-as-if-he-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 20:23:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542602-he-seemed-to-savor-telling-the-story-as-if-he-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He seemed to savor telling the story, as if he'd memorized its details especially for her: how three or four days after she and Lulu had left the general's redoubt, the photographers began showing up, first one or two whom the soldiers ferreted out of the jungle and imprisoned, then more, too many to capture or even count-they were superb hiders, crouching like monkeys in the trees, burying themselves i shallow pits camouflaging inside bunches of leaves.  Assassins has never managed to locate the general with any precision, but the photographers made it look easy: scores of them surging across the border without visas, curled in baskets and wine casks, rolled up in rugs, juddering over unpaved roads in the backs of trucks and eventually surrounding the general's enclave, which he didn't dare leave." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553994-it-s-so-heartbreaking-violence-when-it-s-in-a-house-like-seeing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 19:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553994-it-s-so-heartbreaking-violence-when-it-s-in-a-house-like-seeing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so heartbreaking, violence, when it's in a house-like seeing the clothes in a tree after an explosion.  You may be prepared to see death but not the clothes in the tree." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611097-i-wish-it-were-different-i-wish-that-we-privileged</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 20:54:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611097-i-wish-it-were-different-i-wish-that-we-privileged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish it were different. I wish that we privileged knowledge in politicians, that the ones who know things didn't have to hide it behind brown pants, and that the know-not-enoughs were laughed all the way to the Maine border on their first New Hampshire meet and greet. I wish that in order to secure his party's nomination, a presidential candidate would be required to point at the sky and name all the stars; have the periodic table of the elements memorized; rattle off the kings and queens of Spain; define the significance of the Gatling gun; joke around in Latin; interpret the symbolism in seventeenth-century Dutch painting; explain photosynthesis to a six-year-old; recite Emily Dickinson; bake a perfect popover; build a shortwave radio out of a coconut; and know all the words to Hoagy Carmichael's &quot;Two Sleepy People,&quot; Johnny Cash's &quot;Five Feet High and Rising,&quot; and &quot;You Got the Silver&quot; by the Rolling Stones. After all, the United States is the greatest country on earth dealing with the most complicated problems in the history of the world--poverty, pollution, justice, Jerusalem. What we need is a president who is at least twelve kinds of nerd, a nerd messiah to come along every four years, acquire the Secret Service code name Poindexter, install a Revenge of the Nerds screen saver on the Oval Office computer, and one by one decrypt our woes." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54701-i-am-a-cage-in-search-of-a-bird</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 20:14:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54701-i-am-a-cage-in-search-of-a-bird]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a cage, in search of a bird." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2012 20:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirstie add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we ought to read only the kind of books that wound or stab us. If the book we're reading doesn't wake us up with a blow to the head, what are we reading for? So that it will make us happy, as you write? Good Lord, we would be happy precisely if we had no books, and the kind of books that make us happy are the kind we could write ourselves if we had to. But we need books that affect us like a disaster, that grieve us deeply, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, like being banished into forests far from everyone, like a suicide. A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us. That is my belief." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
