<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700797-kirsten]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700797-kirsten" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 11:33:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 11:33:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51320-he-took-a-sip-of-my-father-s-weak-coffee-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He took a sip of my father’s weak coffee and spit it back into the mug. &quot;This shit’s like making love in a canoe.&quot;
&quot;Excuse me?&quot;
&quot;It’s fucking near water." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281540-yes-he-said-that-s-it-they-d-kick-him-and-beat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 11:38:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281540-yes-he-said-that-s-it-they-d-kick-him-and-beat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes,' he said. 'That's it. They'd kick him and beat him with a switch. Then if the youngster was really bad, they'd put him in a sack and take him back to Spain.'
'Saint Nicholas would kick you?'
'Well, not anymore,' Oscar said. 'Now he just pretends to kick you.'
He considered this to be progressive, but in a way I think it's almost more preverse than the original punishment.'I'm going to hurt you but not really.' How many times have we fallen for that line? The fake slap invariably makes contact, adding the elements of shock and betrayal to what had previously been plain old-fashioned fear. What kind of a Santa spends his time pretending to kick people before stuffing them into a canvas sack? Then, of course, you've got the six to eight former slaves who could potentially go off at any moment. This, I think, is the greatest difference between us and the Dutch. While a certain segment of our population might be perfectly happy with the arrangement, if you told the average white American that six to eight nameless black men would be sneaking into his house in the middle of the night, he would barricade the doors and arm himself with whatever he could get his hands on.
'Six to eight, did you say?" -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425062-listen-you-might-want-to-pack-a-few-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 11:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kirsten add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425062-listen-you-might-want-to-pack-a-few-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen, you might want to pack a few of your things together before going to bed. The former bishop of Turkey will be coming tonight along with six to eight black men. They might put some candy in your shoes, they might stuff you into a sack and take you to Spain, or they might just pretend to kick you. We don't know for sure, but we want you to be prepared.&quot; 
This was the reward for living in the Netherlands. As a child you get to hear this story, and as an adult you get to turn around and repeat it." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
