<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700937-holly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/700937-holly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:23:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:23:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:24:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:24:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:24:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:25:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:43:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:43:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:43:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16949-a-friend-is-someone-who-knows-all-about-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is someone who knows all about you and still loves you." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:44:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:44:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:46:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:48:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself any direction you choose. You're on your own. And you know what you know. And YOU are the one who'll decide where to go..." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353-for-every-minute-you-are-angry-you-lose-sixty-seconds</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353-for-every-minute-you-are-angry-you-lose-sixty-seconds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 17:51:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 18:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 18:52:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’s not perfect. You aren’t either, and the two of you will never be perfect. But if he can make you laugh at least once, causes you to think twice, and if he admits to being human and making mistakes, hold onto him and give him the most you can. He isn’t going to quote poetry, he’s not thinking about you every moment, but he will give you a part of him that he knows you could break. Don’t hurt him, don’t change him, and don’t expect for more than he can give. Don’t analyze. Smile when he makes you happy, yell when he makes you mad, and miss him when he’s not there. Love hard when there is love to be had. Because perfect guys don’t exist, but there’s always one guy that is perfect for you." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4963-where-is-human-nature-so-weak-as-in-the-bookstore</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 19:12:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Henry Ward Beecherr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4963-where-is-human-nature-so-weak-as-in-the-bookstore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where is human nature so weak as in the bookstore?" -- Henry Ward Beecherr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 19:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Holly add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
