<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/702467-kurt-keefner]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/702467-kurt-keefner" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 21:05:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436437-the-straight-brows-fell-low-over-the-over-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 21:05:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436437-the-straight-brows-fell-low-over-the-over-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["… the straight brows fell low over the over the clear, deep-set, earnest eyes, which, without being unpleasantly sharp, seemed intent enough to penetrate into the very heart and core of what he was looking at.  The lines in the face were few but firm, as if they were carved in marble, and lay principally about the lips, which were slightly compressed over a set of teeth so faultless and beautiful as to give the effect of sudden sunlight when the rare, bright smile, coming in an instant and shining out of the eyes, changed the whole look from the severe and resolved expression of a man ready to do and dare anything, to the keen, honest enjoyment of the moment, which is seldom shown so fearlessly and instantaneously, except by children." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16384-no-plan-survives-contact-with-the-enemy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 17:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Erwin Rommel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16384-no-plan-survives-contact-with-the-enemy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No plan survives contact with the enemy" -- Erwin Rommel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143-i-choose-to-believe-that-i-owe-my-very-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:24:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1143-i-choose-to-believe-that-i-owe-my-very-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I choose to believe that I owe my very
life to you--ay--smile, and think it an exaggeration if you will.
I believe it, because it adds a value to that life to think--oh,
Miss Hale!' continued he, lowering his voice to such a tender
intensity of passion that she shivered and trembled before him,
'to think circumstance so wrought, that whenever I exult in
existence henceforward, I may say to myself, &quot;All this gladness
in life, all honest pride in doing my work in the world, all this
keen sense of being, I owe to her!&quot; And it doubles the gladness,
it makes the pride glow, it sharpens the sense of existence till
I hardly know if it is pain or pleasure, to think that I owe it
to one--nay, you must, you shall hear'--said he, stepping
forwards with stern determination--'to one whom I love, as I do
not believe man ever loved woman before.' He held her hand tight
in his. He panted as he listened for what should come. " -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28542-a-wise-parent-humors-the-desire-for-independent-action-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28542-a-wise-parent-humors-the-desire-for-independent-action-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wise parent humors the desire for independent action, so as to become the friend and advisor when his absolute rule shall cease." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311523-he-could-not-forget-the-touch-of-her-arms-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:30:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311523-he-could-not-forget-the-touch-of-her-arms-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He could not forget the touch of her arms around his neck, impatiently felt as it had been at the time; but now the recollection of her clinging defence of him, seemed to thrill him through and through,—to melt away every resolution, all power of self-control, as if it were wax before a fire." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267863-i-take-it-that-gentleman-is-a-term-that-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267863-i-take-it-that-gentleman-is-a-term-that-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I take it that “gentleman” is a term that only describes a person in his relation to others; but when we speak of him as “a man” , we consider him not merely with regard to his fellow men, but in relation to himself, - to life – to time – to eternity. A cast-away lonely as Robinson Crusoe- a prisoner immured in a dungeon for life – nay, even a saint in Patmos, has his endurance, his strength, his faith, best described by being spoken of as “a man”. I am rather weary of this word “ gentlemanly” which seems to me to be often inappropriately used, and often too with such exaggerated distortion of meaning, while the full simplicity of the noun “man”, and the adjective “manly” are unacknowledged." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396802-take-care--if-you-do-not-speak--i-shall-claim</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:32:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396802-take-care--if-you-do-not-speak--i-shall-claim]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take care. -If you do not speak- I shall claim you as my own in some presumptuous way. -Send me away at once, if I must go; -Margaret!-" -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378992-thinking-has-many-a-time-made-me-sad-darling-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:32:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378992-thinking-has-many-a-time-made-me-sad-darling-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thinking has, many a time, made me sad, darling; but doing never did in all my life....My precept is, do something, my sister, do good if you can; but at any rate, do something." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378989-oh-dear-a-drunken-infidel-weaver-said-mr-hale-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 22:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378989-oh-dear-a-drunken-infidel-weaver-said-mr-hale-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh dear! A drunken infidel weaver! said Mr. Hale to himself." -- Elizabeth Gaskell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75265-some-prisoners-spent-more-than-ten-years-buried-in-solitary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 17:48:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kurt add a quote by Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75265-some-prisoners-spent-more-than-ten-years-buried-in-solitary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some prisoners spent more than ten years buried in solitary cells the size of coffins, hearing nothing but clanging bars or footsteps in the corridors. . .[they] survived because they could talk to each other by tapping on the wall. In that way they told of dreams and memories, fallings in and out of love; they discussed, embraced, fought; they shared beliefs and beauties, doubts and guilts, and those questions that have no answers. 
When it is genuine, when it is born of the need to speak, no one can stop the human voice. When denied a mouth, it speaks with the hands or the eyes, or the pores, or anything at all. Because every single one of us has something to say to the others, something that deserves to be celebrated or forgiven by others. " -- Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
