<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70268-anna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70268-anna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 17:45:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184403-as-long-as-people-have-been-on-this-earth-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 17:45:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184403-as-long-as-people-have-been-on-this-earth-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as people have been on this earth, the moon has been a mystery to us.  Think about it.  She is strong enough to pull the oceans, and when she dies away, she always comes back again.  My mama used to tell me Our Lady lived on the moon and that I should dance when her face was bright and hibernate when it was dark." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233535-the-train-passed-through-a-series-of-tunnels-because-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 00:41:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Robert D. Kaplan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233535-the-train-passed-through-a-series-of-tunnels-because-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The train passed through a series of tunnels.  Because the overhead light fixtures had no bulbs in them, some people lit candles inside the tunnels, which dramatically illuminated their black, liquid eyes.  There was a solemn, almost devotional cynicism to these eyes, reflecting, as though by a genetic process, all of the horrors witnessed by generation upon generation of forebears." -- Robert D. Kaplan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 12:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Eleanor Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349942-she-remembered-one-of-her-boyfriends-asking-offhandedly-how-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She remembered one of her boyfriends asking, offhandedly, how many books she read in a year. &quot;A few hundred,&quot; she said.
&quot;How do you have the time?&quot; he asked, gobsmacked.
She narrowed her eyes and considered the array of potential answers in front of her. Because I don't spend hours flipping through cable complaining there's nothing on? Because my entire Sunday is not eaten up with pre-game, in-game, and post-game talking heads? Because I do not spend every night drinking overpriced beer and engaging in dick-swinging contests with the other financirati? Because when I am waiting in line, at the gym, on the train, eating lunch, I am not complaining about the wait/staring into space/admiring myself in reflective surfaces? I am reading!
&quot;I don't know,&quot; she said, shrugging." -- Eleanor Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417360-but-unvented---ahh-one-un-vents-something-one-unearths-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 09:10:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Elizabeth Zimmermann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417360-but-unvented---ahh-one-un-vents-something-one-unearths-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But unvented - ahh! One un-vents something; one unearths it; one digs it up, one runs it down in whatever recesses of the eternal consciousness it has gone to ground.  I very much doubt if anything is really new when one works in the prehistoric medium of wool with needles.  The products of science and technology may be new, and some of them are quite horrid, but knitting?  In knitting there are ancient possibilities; the earth is enriched with the dust of the millions of knitters who have held wool and needles since the beginning of sheep.  Seamless sweaters and one-row buttonholes; knitted hems and phoney seams - it is unthinkable that these have, in mankind's history, remained undiscovered and unknitted.  One likes to believe that there is memory in the fingers; memory undeveloped, but still alive." -- Elizabeth Zimmermann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394742-now-when-t-rin-learnt-from-finduilas-of-what-had-passed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 08:18:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394742-now-when-t-rin-learnt-from-finduilas-of-what-had-passed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now when Túrin learnt from Finduilas of what had passed, he was wrathful, and he said to Gwindor: 'In love I hold you for your rescue and sake-keeping. But now you have done ill to me, friend, to betray my right name, and call my doom upon me, from which I would lie hid.'
But Gwindor answered: 'The doom lies in yourself, not in your name." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
