<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/703695-howard]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/703695-howard" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 17:49:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6700-the-policy-of-the-emperors-and-the-senate-as-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2007 17:49:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Edward Gibbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6700-the-policy-of-the-emperors-and-the-senate-as-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The policy of the emperors and the senate, as far as it concerned religion, was happily seconded by the reflections of the enlightened, and by the habits of the superstitious, part of their subjects.  The various modes of worship, which prevailed in the Roman world, were all considered by the people, as equally true; by the philosopher, as equally false; and by the magistrate, as equally useful.  And thus toleration produced not only mutual indulgence, but even religious concord." -- Edward Gibbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7174-it-was-a-subtle-refinement-of-god-to-learn-greek</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 21:35:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7174-it-was-a-subtle-refinement-of-god-to-learn-greek]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a subtle refinement of God to learn Greek when he wished to write a book – and that he did not learn it better." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7336-i-m-really-very-sorry-for-you-all-but-it-s-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 13:27:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by W.S. Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7336-i-m-really-very-sorry-for-you-all-but-it-s-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm really very sorry for you all, but it's an unjust world, and virtue is triumphant only in theatrical performances." -- W.S. Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5882-it-is-a-truth-universally-acknowledged-that-a-single-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:02:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5882-it-is-a-truth-universally-acknowledged-that-a-single-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a truth universally acknowledged, that a single man in possession of a good fortune, must be in want of a wife." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7582-the-whole-of-the-targum-deserves-study-as-shewing-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 08:15:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Edwin A. Abbott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7582-the-whole-of-the-targum-deserves-study-as-shewing-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole of the Targum deserves study as shewing how textual ambiguity or corruption may combine with doctrinal prepossession to modify tradition;
Chapter II, Section 2, Paragraph 1171" -- Edwin A. Abbott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7681-mrs-howe-julia-ward-wife-of-dr-howe-of-boston-famous</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2007 10:56:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Howard K. Beale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7681-mrs-howe-julia-ward-wife-of-dr-howe-of-boston-famous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mrs. HOWE (Julia Ward)–Wife of Dr. Howe, of Boston, famous as a teacher of the deaf and dumb.  This lady is here, 
giving a course of private lectures, on quaint subjects—e. g. “moral triganometry [sic]” alias “practical ethics.”
I dined with her, by special invitation, at Mr. Eames’—She is a smart, educated, traveled lady, a little touched, ‘tis thought, with strong-mindedness.  Complacent, and well satisfied with her peculiar theories." -- Howard K. Beale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8078-henry-leave-me-out-of-it-they-don-t-count-maybe</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 19:43:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8078-henry-leave-me-out-of-it-they-don-t-count-maybe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HENRY:
Leave me out of it.  They don’t count.  Maybe Brodie got a raw deal, maybe he didn’t.  I don’t know.  It doesn’t count.  He’s a lout with language.  I can’t help somebody who thinks, or thinks he thinks, that editing a newspaper is censorship, or that throwing bricks is a demonstration while building tower blocks is social violence, or that unpalatable statement is provocation while disrupting the speaker is the exercise of free speech…Words don’t deserve that kind of malarkey.  They’re innocent, neutral, precise, standing for this, describing that, meaning the other, so if you look after them you can build bridges across incomprehension and chaos.  But when they get their corners knocked off, they’re no good any more, and Brodie knocks their corners off.  I don’t think writers are sacred, but words are.  They deserve respect.  If you get the right ones in the right order, you can nudge the world a little or make a poem which children will speak for you when you’re dead.
Act II, Scene 5, HENRY and ANNIE" -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8306-mr-2nd-comptroller-cutts-came-into-my-office-to-shew</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 18:30:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Howard K. Beale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8306-mr-2nd-comptroller-cutts-came-into-my-office-to-shew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. 2nd Comptroller Cutts came into my office to shew me the papers in the case of the late Purser Josiah Tatnal, Jr.  (I had asked him for copy of the bond).
That done, he stated, at cruel length, his difficulty with the Q.[uarter] M.[aster] Genl’s office...
He is a polite man, and I think means well, but [is] excessively dull and vain.  I really pity him.  It is a great misfortune to any gentleman to have no sense." -- Howard K. Beale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8458-nor-could-i-fail-to-recall-my-friendship-with-howard</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2007 09:39:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by John Hope Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8458-nor-could-i-fail-to-recall-my-friendship-with-howard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor could I fail to recall my friendship with Howard K. Beale, professor of American History at the University of North Carolina.  There he was, one day in 1940, standing just outside my room in the men’s dormitory at St. Augustine’s, in his chesterfield topcoat, white silk scarf, and bowler hat, with his calling card in hand, perhaps looking for a silver tray in which to drop it.  Paul Buck, whom he knew at Harvard, had told him to look me up.  He wanted to invite me to his home in Chapel Hill to have lunch or dinner and to meet his family.  From that point on we saw each other regularly.
After I moved to Durham, he invited me each year to give a lecture on “The Negro in American Social Thought” in one of his classes.  One day when I was en route to Beale’s class, I encountered one of his colleagues, who greeted me and inquired where I was going.  I returned the greeting and told him that I was going to Howard Beale’s class to give a lecture.  After I began the lecture I noticed that Howard was called out of the class.  He returned shortly, and I did not give it another thought.  Some years later, after we both had left North Carolina, Howard told me that he had been called out to answer a long-distance phone call from a trustee of the university who had heard that a Negro was lecturing in his class.  The trustee ordered Beale to remove me immediately.  In recounting this story, Beale told me that he had said that he was not in the habit of letting trustees plan his courses, and he promptly hung up.  Within a few years Howard accepted a professorship at the University of Wisconsin.  A favorite comment from Chapel Hill was that upon his departure from North Carolina, blood pressures went down all over the state." -- John Hope Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8970-the-point-i-would-make-is-that-the-novelist-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 13:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Shelby Foote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8970-the-point-i-would-make-is-that-the-novelist-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point I would make is that the novelist and the historian are seeking the same thing:  the truth – not a different truth:  the same truth – only they reach it, or try to reach it, by different routes.  Whether the event took place in a world now gone to dust, preserved by documents and evaluated by scholarship, or in the imagination, preserved by memory and distilled by the creative process, they both want to tell us how it was:  to re-create it, by their separate methods, and make it live again in the world around them." -- Shelby Foote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9834-all-of-creation-s-a-farce-man-was-born-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2008 18:24:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9834-all-of-creation-s-a-farce-man-was-born-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of Creation’s a farce.
Man was born as a joke.
In his head his reason is buffeted
Like wind-blown smoke.
Life is a game.
Everyone ridicules everyone else.
But he who has the last laugh
Laughs longest." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27818-there-has-always-been-a-temptation-to-classify-economic-goods</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 16:23:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Alfred Marshall]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27818-there-has-always-been-a-temptation-to-classify-economic-goods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There has always been a temptation to classify economic goods in clearly defined groups, about which a number of short and sharp propositions could be made, to gratify at once the student’s desire for logical precision, and the popular liking for dogmas that have the air of being profound and are yet easily handled.  But great mischief seems to have been done by yielding to this temptation, and drawing broad artificial lines of division where Nature has made none.  The more simple and absolute an economic doctrine is, the greater will be the confusion which it brings into attempts to apply economic doctrines to practice, if the dividing lines to which it refers cannot be found in real life.  There is not in real life a clear line of division between things that are and are not Capital, or that are and are not Necessaries, or again between labour that is and is not Productive." -- Alfred Marshall]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27823-one-who-though-he-never-digress-to-read-a-lecture</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 16:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Thomas Hobbes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27823-one-who-though-he-never-digress-to-read-a-lecture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["one who, though he never digress to read a Lecture, Moral or Political, upon his own Text, nor enter into men’s hearts, further than the Actions themselves evidently guide him…filleth his Narrations with that choice of matter, and ordereth them with that Judgement, and with such perspicuity and efficacy expresseth himself that (as Plutarch saith) he maketh his Auditor a Spectator.  For he setteth his Reader in the Assemblies of the People, and in their Senates, at their debating; in the Streets, at their Seditions; and in the Field, at their Battels.

Quoted by Shelby Foote in his The Civil War:  A Narrative – Volume 2:  Fredericksburg to Meridian, Bibliographical Note, from Thomas Hobbes’ Forward to Hobbes’ translation of The Peloponnesian War by Thucydides" -- Thomas Hobbes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27826-i-give-you-this-charge-that-you-shall-be-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 16:28:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Queen Elizabeth I]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27826-i-give-you-this-charge-that-you-shall-be-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I give you this charge, that you shall be of my Privy Council and content yourself to take pains for me and my realm.  This judgement I have of you, that you will not be corrupted with any manner of gift and that you will be faithful to the State, and that without respect of my private will, you will give me that counsel that you think best: and, if you shall know anything necessary to be declared to me of secrecy, you shall show it to myself only and assure yourself I will not fail to keep taciturnity therein.  And therefore herewith I charge you.

Administering the oath of office to William Cecil as Secretary of State, November 20, 1558, as quoted in Elizabeth I:  The Word of a Prince, A Life from Contemporary Documents, by Maria Perry, Chapter V, Section: To make a good account to Almighty God" -- Queen Elizabeth I]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35978-burnside-left-even-sooner-hard-on-the-heels-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 11:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Shelby Foote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35978-burnside-left-even-sooner-hard-on-the-heels-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Burnside left even sooner, hard on the heels of a violent argument with Meade, an exchange of recriminations which a staff observer said “went far toward confirming one’s belief in the wealth and flexibility of the English language as a medium of personal dispute.”
The Civil War: A Narrative, Volume III:  Red River to Appomattox, War is Cruelty" -- Shelby Foote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112238-mr-bates-comments-on-the-description-of-robespierre-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2008 10:31:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Howard add a quote by Edward Bates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112238-mr-bates-comments-on-the-description-of-robespierre-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" [Mr. Bates comments on the description of Robespierre in History of the French Revolution by M. J. L. Adolphe Thiers]
He was a living proof that[,] in civil troubles, obstinate mediocrity is more powerful than the irregularity of genius.  It is not only in civil troubles but in all the affairs of life, that obstinate mediocrity triumphs over irregular genius, and enjoys the fruits of victory.
The Diary of Edward Bates, Entry for March 7, 1865, Edited by Howard K. Beale
" -- Edward Bates]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
