<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70425-mckinley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70425-mckinley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 09:42:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13751-quite-simply-i-was-in-love-with-new-york-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 09:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[McKinley add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13751-quite-simply-i-was-in-love-with-new-york-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...quite simply, I was in love with New York. I do not mean “love” in any colloquial way, I mean that I was in love with the city, the way you love the first person who ever touches you and you never love anyone quite that way again. I remember walking across Sixty-second Street one twilight that first spring, or the second spring, they were all alike for a while. I was late to meet someone but I stopped at Lexington Avenue and bought a peach and stood on the corner eating it and knew that I had come out out of the West and reached the mirage." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26196-people-who-believe-in-politics-are-like-people-who-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2008 19:50:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[McKinley add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26196-people-who-believe-in-politics-are-like-people-who-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who believe in politics are like people who believe in God: they are sucking wind through bent straws." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122943-although-i-have-felt-compelled-to-write-things-down-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 18:14:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[McKinley add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122943-although-i-have-felt-compelled-to-write-things-down-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although I have felt compelled to write things down since I was five years old, I doubt that my daughter ever will, for she is a singularly blessed and accepting child, delighted with life exactly as life presents itself to her, unafraid to go to sleep and unafraid to wake up.  Keepers of private notebooks are a different breed altogether, lonely and resistant rearrangers of things, anxious malcontents, children afflicted apparently at birth with some presentiment of loss." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130850-i-know-something-about-dread-myself-and-appreciate-the-elaborate</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 18:16:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[McKinley add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130850-i-know-something-about-dread-myself-and-appreciate-the-elaborate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know something about dread myself, and appreciate the elaborate systems with which some people fill the void, appreciate all the opiates of the people, whether they are as accessible as alcohol and heroin and promiscuity or as hard to come by as faith in God or History." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35178-but-the-fact-of-it-was-that-i-liked-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 18:17:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[McKinley add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35178-but-the-fact-of-it-was-that-i-liked-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the fact of it was that I liked it out there, a ruin devoid of human vanities, clean of human illusions, an empty place reclaimed by the weather where a woman plays an organ to stop the wind's whining and an old man plays ball with a dog named Duke.  I could tell you that I came back because I had promises to keep, but maybe it was because nobody asked me to stay. " -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
