<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/704300-elle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/704300-elle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 17:06:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6917-clemenza-s-overriding-responsibility-is-to-his-family-he-takes-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2007 17:06:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elle add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6917-clemenza-s-overriding-responsibility-is-to-his-family-he-takes-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clemenza's overriding responsibility is to his family. He takes a moment out of his routine madness to remember that he had promised his wife that he would bring dessert home. His instruction to his partner in crime is an entire moral manifesto in six little words: 'Leave the gun. Take the cannoli." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12424-i-will-tell-you-what-i-will-do-and-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 08:00:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elle add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12424-i-will-tell-you-what-i-will-do-and-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will tell you what I will do and what I will not do.  I will not serve that in which I no longer believe, whether it calls itself my home, my fatherland, or my church: and I will try to express myself in some mode of life or art as freely as I can and as wholly as I can, using for my defense the only arms I allow myself to use -- silence, exile, and cunning." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47209-normally-i-didn-t-see-a-great-deal-i-didn-t-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 18:49:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elle add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47209-normally-i-didn-t-see-a-great-deal-i-didn-t-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Normally I didn’t see a great deal. I didn’t hear a great deal either. I didn’t pay attention. Strictly speaking I wasn’t there. Strictly speaking I believe I’ve never been anywhere." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 21:07:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elle add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's face it. We're undone by each other. And if we're not, we're missing something. If this seems so clearly the case with grief, it is only because it was already the case with desire. One does not always stay intact. It may be that one wants to, or does, but it may also be that despite one's best efforts, one is undone, in the face of the other, by the touch, by the scent, by the feel, by the prospect of the touch, by the memory of the feel. And so when we speak about my sexuality or my gender, as we do (and as we must), we mean something complicated by it. Neither of these is precisely a possession, but both are to be understood as modes of being dispossessed, ways of being for another, or, indeed, by virtue of another." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
