<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/704851-veronika]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/704851-veronika" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 08:58:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201816-don-t-bend-don-t-water-it-down-don-t-try-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 08:58:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201816-don-t-bend-don-t-water-it-down-don-t-try-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't bend; don't water it down; don't try to make it logical; don't edit your own soul according to the fashion. Rather, follow your most intense obsessions mercilessly." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275483-the-advice-i-like-to-give-young-artists-or-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:01:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Chuck Close]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275483-the-advice-i-like-to-give-young-artists-or-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The advice I like to give young artists, or really anybody who'll listen to me, is not to wait around for inspiration. Inspiration is for amateurs; the rest of us just show up and get to work. If you wait around for the clouds to part and a bolt of lightning to strike you in the brain, you are not going to make an awful lot of work. All the best ideas come out of the process; they come out of the work itself. Things occur to you. If you're sitting around trying to dream up a great art idea, you can sit there a long time before anything happens. But if you just get to work, something will occur to you and something else will occur to you and something else that you reject will push you in another direction. Inspiration is absolutely unnecessary and somehow deceptive. You feel like you need this great idea before you can get down to work, and I find that's almost never the case." -- Chuck Close]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92194-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 12:34:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92194-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which were frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you. But you know you must never allow yourself to be awed, that among them there extend for acres and acres the Books You Needn't Read, the Books Made For Purposes Other Than Reading, Books Read Even Before You Open Them Since They Belong To The Category Of Books Read Before Being Written. And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of the Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out In Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. Eluding these assaults, you come up beneath the towers of the fortress, where other troops are holding out:

the Books You've Been Planning To Read For Ages,

the Books You've Been Hunting For Years Without Success,

the Books Dealing With Something You're Working On At The Moment,

the Books You Want To Own So They'll Be Handy Just In Case,

the Books You Could Put Aside Maybe To Read This Summer,

the Books You Need To Go With Other Books On Your Shelves,

the Books That Fill You With Sudden, Inexplicable Curiosity, Not Easily Justified,

Now you have been able to reduce the countless embattled troops to an array that is, to be sure, very large but still calculable in a finite number; but this relative relief is then undermined by the ambush of the Books Read Long Ago Which It's Now Time To Reread and the Books You've Always Pretended To Have Read And Now It's Time To Sit Down And Really Read Them." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466068-croyez-ceux-qui-cherchent-la-v-rit-doutez-de-ceux-qui</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:02:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by André Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/466068-croyez-ceux-qui-cherchent-la-v-rit-doutez-de-ceux-qui]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Croyez ceux qui cherchent la vérité, doutez de ceux qui la trouvent." -- André Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8756-when-people-are-finding-meaning-in-things----beware</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:01:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Edward Gorey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8756-when-people-are-finding-meaning-in-things----beware]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When people are finding meaning in things -- beware." -- Edward Gorey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:02:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My name is Mary Katherine Blackwood. I am eighteen years old, and I live with my sister Constance. I have often thought that with any luck at all, I could have been born a werewolf, because the two middle fingers on both my hands are the same length, but I have had to be content with what I had. I dislike washing myself, and dogs, and noise. I like my sister Constance, and Richard Plantagenet, and Amanita phalloides, the death-cup mushroom. Everyone else in our family is dead." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:02:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46503-the-day-of-battle-dawned-pink-as-the-fresh-bitten-thigh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:02:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Roger Zelazny]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46503-the-day-of-battle-dawned-pink-as-the-fresh-bitten-thigh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The day of battle dawned pink as the fresh-bitten thigh of a maiden." -- Roger Zelazny]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80121-he-invented-the-fuse-box-dwarf-a-little-man-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:02:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by John Bellairs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80121-he-invented-the-fuse-box-dwarf-a-little-man-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He invented the Fuse Box Dwarf, a little man who popped out at you from behind the paint cans in the cellarway and screamed, &quot;Dreeb!  Dreeb!  I am the Fuse Box Dwarf!&quot;  Lewis was not scared by the little man, and he felt that those who scream &quot;Dreeb&quot; are more to be pitied than censured." -- John Bellairs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36656-jette-mon-livre-dis-toi-bien-que-ce-n-est-l-qu-une</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:03:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by André Gide]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36656-jette-mon-livre-dis-toi-bien-que-ce-n-est-l-qu-une]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jette mon livre; dis-toi bien que ce n'est là &lt;i&gt;qu'une&lt;/i&gt; des mille postures possibles en face de la vie. Cherche la tienne. Ce qu'un autre aurait aussi bien fait que toi, ne le fais pas. Ce qu'un autre aurait aussi bien dit que toi, ne le dis pas, -- aussi bien écrit que toi, ne l'écris pas. Ne t'attache en toi qu'à ce que tu sens qui n'est nulle part ailleurs qu'en toi-même, et crée de toi, impatiemment ou patiemment, ah! le plus irremplaçable des êtres." -- André Gide]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179787-consciousness-unprovable-by-scientific-standards-is-forever-then-the-impossible</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 09:03:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179787-consciousness-unprovable-by-scientific-standards-is-forever-then-the-impossible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consciousness, unprovable by scientific standards, is forever, then, the impossible phantom in the predictable biologic machine, and your every thought a genuine supernatural event. Your every thought is a ghost, dancing." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107434-much-of-magic-as-i-understand-it-in-the-western</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 10:32:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107434-much-of-magic-as-i-understand-it-in-the-western]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Much of magic as I understand it in the Western occult tradition is the search for the Self, with a capital S.  This is understood as being the Great Work, as being the gold the alchemists sought, as being the Will, the Soul, the thing we have inside us that is behind the intellect, the body, the dreams.  The inner dynamo of us, if you like.  Now this is the single most important thing that we can ever attain, the knowledge of our own Self.  And yet there are a frightening amount of people who seem to have the urge not just to ignore the Self, but actually seem to have the urge to obliterate themselves.  This is horrific, but you can almost understand the desire to simply wipe out that awareness, because it’s too much of a responsibility to actually posses such a thing as a soul, such a precious thing.  What if you break it?  What if you lose it?  Mightn’t it be best to anesthetize it, to deaden it, to destroy it, to not have to live with the pain of struggling towards it and trying to keep it pure?  I think that the way that people immerse themselves in alcohol, in drugs, in television, in any of the addictions that our culture throws up, can be seen as a deliberate attempt to destroy any connection between themselves and the responsibility of accepting and owning a higher Self and then having to maintain it." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136177-in-order-to-be-able-to-make-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 10:33:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136177-in-order-to-be-able-to-make-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to be able to make it, you have to put aside the fear of failing and the desire of succeeding. You have to do these things completely and purely without fear, without desire. Because things that we do without lust of result are the purest actions we shall ever take." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148685-to-me-all-creativity-is-magic-ideas-start-out-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 10:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148685-to-me-all-creativity-is-magic-ideas-start-out-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me, all creativity is magic. Ideas start out in the empty void of your head - and they end up as a material thing, like a book you can hold in your hand. That is the magical process. It's an alchemical thing. Yes, we do get the gold out of it but that's not the most important thing. It's the work itself." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30296-inspiration-exists-but-it-has-to-find-you-working</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 10:35:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30296-inspiration-exists-but-it-has-to-find-you-working]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inspiration exists, but it has to find you working." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/610973-the-test-of-a-vocation-is-the-love-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 12:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Logan Pearsall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/610973-the-test-of-a-vocation-is-the-love-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The test of a vocation is the love of the drudgery it involves." -- Logan Pearsall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62846-i-m-not-so-sure-he-s-mad-father-just-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 14:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Veronika add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62846-i-m-not-so-sure-he-s-mad-father-just-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not so sure he's mad, Father. Just a little devious in his sanity." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
