<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/705629-kelley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/705629-kelley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 11:51:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136464-so-everything-lets-us-down-including-curiosity-and-honesty-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 11:51:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelley add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136464-so-everything-lets-us-down-including-curiosity-and-honesty-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything lets us down, including curiosity and honesty and what we love best. Yes, said the voice, but cheer up, it's fun in the end." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33846-utopia-lies-at-the-horizon-when-i-draw-nearer-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 11:52:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelley add a quote by Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33846-utopia-lies-at-the-horizon-when-i-draw-nearer-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Utopia lies at the horizon.
When I draw nearer by two steps,
it retreats two steps.
If I proceed ten steps forward, it
swiftly slips ten steps ahead.
No matter how far I go, I can never reach it.
What, then, is the purpose of utopia?
It is to cause us to advance." -- Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231660-sometimes-i-have-the-feeling-that-what-takes-place-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 16:15:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelley add a quote by Javier Marías]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231660-sometimes-i-have-the-feeling-that-what-takes-place-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I have the feeling that what takes place is identical to what doesn't take place, what we dismiss or allow to slip by us identical to what we accept and seize, what we experience identical to what we never try, and yet we spend our lives in a process of choosing and rejecting and selecting, in drawing a line to separate these identical things and make of our story a unique story that we can remember and that can be recounted, either now or at the end of time, and this be erased or swept away, the annulment of everything we are and do. We pour all our intelligence and our feelings and our enthusiasm into the task of discriminating between things that will all be made equal, if they haven't already been, and that's why we're so full of regrets and lost opportunities, of confirmations and reaffirmations and opportunities grasped, when the truth is that nothing is affirmed and everything is constantly in the process of being lost." -- Javier Marías]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1045541-no-soy-un-nacionalista-exacerbado-sin-embargo-siento-un-amor</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 20:36:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelley add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1045541-no-soy-un-nacionalista-exacerbado-sin-embargo-siento-un-amor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["«No soy un nacionalista exacerbado, sin embargo siento un amor auténtico por mi país. Chile, Chile. ¿Cómo has podido cambiar tanto?, le decía a veces, asomado a mi ventana abierta, mirando el reverbero de Santiago en la lejanía. ¿Qué te han hecho? ¿Se han vuelto locos los chilenos? ¿Quién tiene la culpa? Y otras veces, mientras caminaba por los pasillos del colegio o por los pasillos del periódico, le decía: ¿Hasta cuándo piensas seguir así, Chile? ¿Es que te vas a convertir en otra cosa? ¿En un monstruo que ya nadie reconocerá?»." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396807-the-sadness-of-the-world-has-different-ways-of-getting</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 19:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelley add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396807-the-sadness-of-the-world-has-different-ways-of-getting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sadness of the world has different ways of getting to people, but it seems to succeed almost every time." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
