<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/705729-sara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/705729-sara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:31:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8261-man-should-not-be-in-the-service-of-society-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:31:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8261-man-should-not-be-in-the-service-of-society-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man should not be in the service of society, society should be in the service of man. When man is in the service of society, you have a monster state, and that's what is threatening the world at this minute. ...Certainly Star Wars has a valid mythological perspective. It shows the state as a machine and asks, &quot;Is the machine going to crush humanity or serve humanity?&quot; Humanity comes not from the machine but from the heart. What I see in Star Wars is the same problem that Faust gives us: Mephistopheles, the machine man, can provide us with all the means, and is thus likely to determine the aims of life as well. But of course the characteristic of Faust, which makes him eligible to be saved, is that he seeks aims that are not those of the machine. Now, when Luke Skywalker unmasks his father, he is taking off the machine role that the father has played. The father was the uniform. That is power, the state role." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9227-time-for-you-and-time-for-me-and-time-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 14:35:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9227-time-for-you-and-time-for-me-and-time-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time for you and time for me,	
And time yet for a hundred indecisions,	
And for a hundred visions and revisions,	
Before the taking of a toast and tea." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
