<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706378-cameron]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706378-cameron" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 11:56:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26627-because-this-law-could-mean-so-much-or-so-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 11:56:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by John Frohnmayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26627-because-this-law-could-mean-so-much-or-so-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because this law could mean so much or so little, it held potential for causing great mischief in the world of art and politics.  We needed to reduce its uncertainty, and the best way to do that, I believed, was to force a court to interpret it, which would either void or narrow the law.  To make it as broad a target as possible and to assure that someone would sue us, I reproduced the Helms amendment verbatim in the terms and conditions for grant recipients.  It could not be ignored there, and if it was to be declared unconstitutional, it had to appear where the courts could not ignore it either." -- John Frohnmayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29210-the-white-house-usually-followed-the-seagull-theory-of-management</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by John Frohnmayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29210-the-white-house-usually-followed-the-seagull-theory-of-management]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The White House usually followed the seagull theory of management: fly in, squawk and flap and shit, and fly away." -- John Frohnmayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29211-an-apocryphal-story-recounts-the-dilhemma-of-a-man-during</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:12:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by John Frohnmayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29211-an-apocryphal-story-recounts-the-dilhemma-of-a-man-during]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An apocryphal story recounts the dilhemma of a man during the Civil War who could not decide whether to join the Confederate or Union forces.  Finally he put on a gray coat and blue pants, and both sides shot him." -- John Frohnmayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34031-during-my-tenure-at-the-endowment-i-often-found-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 10:13:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by John Frohnmayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34031-during-my-tenure-at-the-endowment-i-often-found-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During my tenure at the Endowment, I often found that those who did us the most damage did so under the justification of helping us by 'preventing worse language.'  In the military it would be called friendly fire.  One ends up just as dead." -- John Frohnmayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42294-the-science-of-government-it-is-my-duty-to-study</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 11:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42294-the-science-of-government-it-is-my-duty-to-study]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The science of government it is my duty to study, more than all other sciences; the arts of legislation and administration and negotiation ought to take the place of, indeed exclude, in a manner, all other arts. I must study politics and war, that our sons may have liberty to study mathematics and philosophy. Our sons ought to study mathematics and philosophy, geography, natural history and naval architecture, navigation, commerce and agriculture in order to give their children a right to study painting, poetry, music, architecture, statuary, tapestry and porcelain." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81867-for-a-successful-technology-reality-must-take-precedence-over-public</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 12:34:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81867-for-a-successful-technology-reality-must-take-precedence-over-public]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a successful technology, reality must take precedence over public relations, for nature cannot be fooled." -- Richard P. Feynman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84382-i-handed-them-a-script-and-they-turned-it-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 09:05:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cameron add a quote by Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84382-i-handed-them-a-script-and-they-turned-it-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I handed them a script and they turned it down.  It was too controversial. It talked about concepts like, 'Who is God?' The Enterprise meets God in space; God is a life form, and I wanted to suggest that there may have been, at one time in the human beginning, an alien entity that early man believed was God, and kept those legends. But I also wanted to suggest that it might have been as much the Devil as it was God. After all, what kind of god would throw humans out of Paradise for eating the fruit of the Tree of Knowledge. One of the Vulcans on board, in a very logical way, says, '&lt;b&gt;If this is your God, he's not very impressive. He's got so many psychological problems; he's so insecure. He demands worship every seven days. He goes out and creates faulty humans and then blames them for his own mistakes. He's a pretty poor excuse for a supreme being&lt;/b&gt;." -- Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
