<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706650-phil]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706650-phil" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 10:30:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/914814-there-is-a-serious-discrepancy-between-what-we-really-wants</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 10:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/914814-there-is-a-serious-discrepancy-between-what-we-really-wants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a serious discrepancy between what we really wants, and what we usually do to get what we think we want. What we really want is to fill the hole inside and become complete, and what we do is look for success and growth outside." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6935-from-the-twelve-enlightenments-observe-your-own-body-it-breathes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 10:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6935-from-the-twelve-enlightenments-observe-your-own-body-it-breathes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From The Twelve Enlightenments

Observe your own body.  It breathes.  You breathe when you are asleep, when you are no longer conscious of your own ideas of self-identity.  Who, then, is breathing?  The collection of information that you mistakenly think it’s you is not the main protagonist in this drama called the breath.  In fact, you are not breathing; breath is naturally happening to you.  You can purposely end your own life, but you cannot purposely keep your own life going.  The expression, “My life” is actually an oxymoron, a result of ignorance and mistaken assumption.  You don’t posses life; life expresses itself through you.  Your body is a flower that life let bloom, a phenomenon created by life." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916907-change-is-the-very-nature-of-nature-if-there-s-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 11:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916907-change-is-the-very-nature-of-nature-if-there-s-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Change is the very nature of Nature. if there's one thing that doesn't change, it is the fact that everything changes. In the Korean tradition of Tao, this is called impermanence. The teaching about impermanence can be summarized like this: Anything that has a beginning must have an end. Anything that is created will change. Impermanence is the very nature of things. Realizing that nothing is permanent is the true beginning of enlightenment. Suffering comes from attachment that wants to hold something permanently that is not permanent in its intrinsic nature. Awakening to the truth of impermanence frees you from attachment." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52241-whoever-you-are-or-whatever-it-is-that-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 14:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52241-whoever-you-are-or-whatever-it-is-that-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever you are, or whatever it is that you do, when you really want something, it's because that desire originated in the soul of the universe. It's your mission on earth." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/917083-i-define-vulnerability-as-uncertainty-risk-and-emotional-exposure-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 14:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/917083-i-define-vulnerability-as-uncertainty-risk-and-emotional-exposure-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I define vulnerability as uncertainty, risk and emotional exposure. With that definition in mind, let’s think about love. Waking up every day and loving someone who may or may not love us back, whose safety we can’t ensure, who may stay in our lives or may leave without a moment’s notice, who may be loyal to the day they die or betray us tomorrow—that’s vulnerability." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 14:38:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919500-dreams-are-reality-that-has-not-become-true-however-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 10:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919500-dreams-are-reality-that-has-not-become-true-however-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dreams are reality that has not become true. However, in the hearts of some people, they have already come true. People whose dreams are already achieved in their hearts, and who can see that as they boldly throw themselves into it, have true courage." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920978-if-you-allow-your-consciousness-to-drift-toward-your-lower</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 15:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920978-if-you-allow-your-consciousness-to-drift-toward-your-lower]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you allow your consciousness to drift toward your lower abdomen during breathing, then your breath will naturally delve deeper within you. If you allow your consciousness to experiencce the gratitude and joy of breathing, then your breath will naturally become light. Your breathing will naturally achieve a deep lightness as you consider inhaling as an expression of thanks to your body and exhaling as an expression of thanks to the Heavens above. Then you can lose yourself in your breath. You can follow your breath within and without your body, losing yourself until you become the breath itself." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922848-even-when-we-have-realized-oneness-and-nothingness-we-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 14:32:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922848-even-when-we-have-realized-oneness-and-nothingness-we-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even when we have realized oneness and nothingness, we still have our personal lives to manage, bodies to take care of, and mouths to feed, and you will know which one is yours and which ones are others', so you won't put food into another person's mouth when you are hungry. Also you won't kiss a rattlesnake or hug a cactus no matter how strong an affinity you feel toward them. But at the same time, we know these apparent separations are functional, not fundamental, and should be recognized as such without mistaking one for the other. I would call this apparent separation &quot;functional ego,&quot; or you can call it your &quot;character,&quot; which is the collection of your beliefs, habits, and other people's expectations." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924035-the-energy-of-life-entering-and-leaving-your-body-flows</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 14:39:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924035-the-energy-of-life-entering-and-leaving-your-body-flows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The energy of life entering and leaving your body flows evenly throughout the universe. With that current, the mind of the cosmos communicates with all things." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925866-we-have-the-noble-desire-to-help-others-and-benefit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 13:14:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/925866-we-have-the-noble-desire-to-help-others-and-benefit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have the Noble Desire to help others and benefit the world, without expecting any return or recognition. What makes us great is not our knowledge, skill, money, or power. What makes us great is not our knowledge, skill, money, or power. What makes us truly great is this noble desire, this passion that transcends all separation, goes beyond one's limitations, and wants to hug others and embrace the whole world. This is not something that we need to learn, because we already have it. It just needs to be acknowledged and awakened." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951488-for-the-person-who-is-grounded-in-the-timeless-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 09:18:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951488-for-the-person-who-is-grounded-in-the-timeless-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the person who is grounded in the timeless truth of the universe, there is no life and no death. He or she can experience eternal joy without being limited by the definitions of good and evil. The essence of Oneness always exists within us." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955038-your-mind-creates-everything-your-conscious-mind-has-much-greater</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 07:55:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955038-your-mind-creates-everything-your-conscious-mind-has-much-greater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your mind creates everything. Your conscious mind has much greater power than you can ever imagine. Your mind can create blessings or disasters, can heal or harm, can bring abundance or absence. It is up to your mind whether the world looks hopeful or hopeless." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958403-this-is-a-beautiful-and-hopeful-time-to-be-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 16:50:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958403-this-is-a-beautiful-and-hopeful-time-to-be-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is a beautiful and hopeful time to be alive. We are at a turning point, and your contribution to the world is needed more than ever. All of your struggles, all the struggles of your ancestors, all the struggles of all life have led to this moment right now. You are the culmination of life's great yearning; you are the hope of the world." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511614-i-existed-before-i-received-this-body-i-am-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 16:51:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511614-i-existed-before-i-received-this-body-i-am-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I existed before I received this body. I am the external and fundamental life energy of the universe." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921721-our-exclusive-dependence-on-rational-thought-and-language-has-obscured</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 07:46:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921721-our-exclusive-dependence-on-rational-thought-and-language-has-obscured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our exclusive dependence on rational thought and language has obscured our natural ability to sense the flow of energy." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922445-if-you-close-your-eyes-and-begin</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 07:46:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/922445-if-you-close-your-eyes-and-begin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . if you close your eyes and begin to feel your breath, it will instantly become deeper and slower, and your mind will become calmer. Then gradually you'll become aware of your body, or more precisely the subtle sense of energy inside and around your body. At that moment, you exist as Energy-Consciousness, not as names, jobs, duties, roles, desires, and so on." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921719-choice-is-the-doorway-to-our-creative-power-to-unleash</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 07:46:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921719-choice-is-the-doorway-to-our-creative-power-to-unleash]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Choice is the doorway to our creative power. To unleash this power, we must begin from the state of beingness." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921725-now-the-choices-you-make-are-not-about-finding-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 07:46:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921725-now-the-choices-you-make-are-not-about-finding-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now the choices you make are not about finding your path. Rather, they are choices to open the path you have found." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/959150-i-don-t-believe-in-greatness-that-is-bestowed-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 12:59:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/959150-i-don-t-believe-in-greatness-that-is-bestowed-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in greatness that is bestowed as a rare gift to a few lucky ones. Rather, I think all people have greatness inside them. It is just a matter of persistence--sticking to what you have envisioned until it is reality. I have a deep conviction that everyone, including you, has been given exactly the right set of gifts to fulfill some magnificent purpose in life. Greatness must simply be chosen. And if you choose it, it will happen." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960248-devotion-is-a-spiritual-act-of-egoless-surrender-when-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 21:12:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by anodea judith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960248-devotion-is-a-spiritual-act-of-egoless-surrender-when-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Devotion is a spiritual act of egoless surrender. When the Self blinds the spirit too tightly, then devotion expands the blinding by lifting us beyond ourselves. We get the powerful lesson that the Self survives even without constant attention." -- anodea judith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960512-meditation-is-earnest-prayer-and-when-prayer-progresses-it-becomes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 07:38:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960512-meditation-is-earnest-prayer-and-when-prayer-progresses-it-becomes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Meditation is earnest prayer,  and when prayer progresses,  it becomes true meditation." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960518-i-believe-in-the-goodness-of-fellow-human-beings-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 07:39:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960518-i-believe-in-the-goodness-of-fellow-human-beings-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in the goodness of fellow human beings. We have a true desire for greatness and genuine good intention to be helpful to others. That's enough. Change is possible." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960525-now-is-a-time-for-change-a-time-to-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 07:39:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/960525-now-is-a-time-for-change-a-time-to-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now is a time for change, a time to become the greatest version of yourself. And a time to to make your grandest vision of the world ." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/961217-nothing-is-the-universe-s-great-storehouse-and-power-plant-laws</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 15:13:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/961217-nothing-is-the-universe-s-great-storehouse-and-power-plant-laws]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is the universe's great storehouse and power plant. Laws give the universe order and stability, while possibilities give the universe dynamic creativity and change. Through the balance of these, the universe maintains its eternal dynamic harmony that provides all beings with the environment in which they can realize their potential value." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967919-we-are-here-on-earth-and-such-and-such-shape</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 10:58:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967919-we-are-here-on-earth-and-such-and-such-shape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are here on earth and such and such shape, form, and mind to strive for the completion of our spiritual selves, not only as individuals but as the whole of humanity. We are here to heal our souls and come closer to recovering the divine nature – our spiritual nature – through the physical and mental tools that we've been given.

Healing Society" -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970102-when-you-honestly-face-the-fact-that-the-time-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 15:57:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970102-when-you-honestly-face-the-fact-that-the-time-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you honestly face the fact that the time you will have in this body and this lifetime is limited, you begin to ask yourself important questions about how you will use that time. What legacy, what gift do you wish to leave behind for others? How would you like to be remembered after you have left this life?" -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971812-who-am-i-what-is-the-purpose-of-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 09:07:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971812-who-am-i-what-is-the-purpose-of-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who am I?&quot; &quot;What is the purpose of my life?&quot; These questions arise spontaneously throughout our lives, either unbidden or through conscious intent. Anyone who wishes to live an authentic life must answer these questions, regardless of whether they believe in the existence of the soul or practice a religion. If these queries remain unanswered, life will more than likely remain superficial and empty, in spite of any material abundance. If you wish to make the soul's journey, then I suggest you ask yourself these questions relentlessly and ruthlessly, and listen carefully." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981502-a-more-truthful-perception-may-be-seen-from-the-perspective</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 17:23:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981502-a-more-truthful-perception-may-be-seen-from-the-perspective]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A more truthful perception may be seen from the perspective of the whole - what we really are, beyond names, roles, education, religion and other information added to our true nature." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981731-when-you-are-stressed-if-you-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 17:26:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Phil add a quote by Ilchi Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981731-when-you-are-stressed-if-you-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . when you are stressed, if you take three deep breaths before you say or do anything, this will help prevent you from making choices you might regret later." -- Ilchi Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
