<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706942-victoria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/706942-victoria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 10:02:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7887-and-those-who-were-seen-dancing-were-thought-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 10:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7887-and-those-who-were-seen-dancing-were-thought-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And those who were seen dancing were thought to be insane by those who could not hear the music." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451171-when-you-quit-drinking-you-stop-waiting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 14:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Caroline Knapp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/451171-when-you-quit-drinking-you-stop-waiting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you quit drinking you stop waiting." -- Caroline Knapp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507658-to-a-drinker-the-sensation-is-real-and-pure-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 14:39:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Caroline Knapp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507658-to-a-drinker-the-sensation-is-real-and-pure-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To a drinker the sensation is real and pure and akin to something spiritual: you seek; in the bottle, you find." -- Caroline Knapp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445612-women-have-less-direct-relationship-to-anger-when-a-woman-bites</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 08:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Louann Brizendine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445612-women-have-less-direct-relationship-to-anger-when-a-woman-bites]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women have less direct relationship to anger...When a woman &quot;bites&quot; her tongue to avoid expressing anger, its not at all socialization. A lot of it is brain circuitry. Even if a woman wanted to express her anger right away, often her brain circuits would attempt to hijack this response, to reflect on it first out of fear and anticipation of retaliation. Also, the female brain has a tremendous aversion to conflict, which is set up by fear of angering the other person and losing the relationship. Instead of triggering a quick action response in the brain, as it does in males, anger in girls and women moves through the brain's gut feeling, conflict-pain anticipation, and verbal circuits. 
Scientists speculate that though a woman is slower to act out of anger, once her faster verbal circuits get going, they can cause her to unleash a barrage of angry words that a man cant match.
Typical men speak fewer words and have less verbal fluency than women, so they may be handicapped in angry exchanges with women. 
Often when I see a couple who are not communicating well, the problem I see is that the man's brain's circuits push him frequently and quickly to an angry, aggressive reaction, and the woman feels frightened and shuts down." -- Louann Brizendine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160097-love-is-like-a-precious-plant-you-can-t-just-accept</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 07:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160097-love-is-like-a-precious-plant-you-can-t-just-accept]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is like a precious plant. You can't just accept it and leave it in the cupboard or just think it's going to get on by itself. You've got to keep on watering it. You've got to really look after it and nurture it." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417396-we-cultivate-love-when-we-allow-our-most-vulnerable-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 20:12:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417396-we-cultivate-love-when-we-allow-our-most-vulnerable-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cultivate love when we allow our most vulnerable and powerful selves to be deeply seen and known, and when we honor the spiritual connection that grows from that offering with trust, respect, kindness and affection.

Love is not something we give or get; it is something that we nurture and grow, a connection that can only be cultivated between two people when it exists within each one of them – we can only love others as much as we love ourselves.

Shame, blame, disrespect, betrayal, and the withholding of affection damage the roots from which love grows. Love can only survive these injuries if they are acknowledged, healed and rare." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
