<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708000-liberty]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708000-liberty" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:34:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63960-should-i-kill-myself-or-have-a-cup-of-coffee</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:34:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63960-should-i-kill-myself-or-have-a-cup-of-coffee]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Should I kill myself, or have a cup of coffee?" -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13908-innocence-ends-when-one-is-stripped-of-the-delusion-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:34:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13908-innocence-ends-when-one-is-stripped-of-the-delusion-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Innocence ends when one is stripped of the delusion that one likes oneself." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:34:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205828-my-only-advantage-as-a-reporter-is-that-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 07:34:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205828-my-only-advantage-as-a-reporter-is-that-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My only advantage as a reporter is that I am so physically small, so temperamentally unobtrustive, and so neurotically inarticulate that people tend to forget that my presence runs counter to their best interests.  And it always does.  That is one last thing to remember: writers are always selling somebody out." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187913-above-all-she-is-the-girl-who-feels-things-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 07:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187913-above-all-she-is-the-girl-who-feels-things-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, she is the girl who 'feels' things, who has hung on to the freshness and pain of adolescence, the girl ever wounded, ever young.  Now, at an age when the wounds begin to heal whether one wants them to or not, Joan Baez rarely leaves the Carmel Valley." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253292-to-have-that-sense-of-one-s-intrinsic-worth-which-constitutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 07:35:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253292-to-have-that-sense-of-one-s-intrinsic-worth-which-constitutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To have that sense of one's intrinsic worth which constitutes self-respect is potentially to have everything: the ability to discriminate, to love and to remain indifferent. To lack it is to be locked within oneself, paradoxically incapable of either love or indifference." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293066-we-are-not-idealized-wild-things-we-are-imperfect-mortal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 07:36:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293066-we-are-not-idealized-wild-things-we-are-imperfect-mortal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not idealized wild things.
We are imperfect mortal beings, aware of that mortality even as we push it away, failed by our very complication, so wired that when we mourn our losses we also mourn, for better or for worse, ourselves. As we were. As we are no longer. As we will one day not be at all." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29449-time-you-enjoy-wasting-is-not-wasted-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 01:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Marthe Troly-Curtin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29449-time-you-enjoy-wasting-is-not-wasted-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time." -- Marthe Troly-Curtin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 02:34:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7147-you-must-have-chaos-within-you-to-give-birth-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must have chaos within you to give birth to a dancing star." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82820-every-deep-thinker-is-more-afraid-of-being-understood-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 02:35:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Friedrich Neitzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82820-every-deep-thinker-is-more-afraid-of-being-understood-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every deep thinker is more afraid of being understood than of being misunderstood." -- Friedrich Neitzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39958-ah-women-they-make-the-highs-higher-and-the-lows</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 02:35:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39958-ah-women-they-make-the-highs-higher-and-the-lows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, women. They make the highs higher and the lows more frequent." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2012 02:42:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Neil Postman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40581-we-were-keeping-our-eye-on-1984-when-the-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were keeping our eye on 1984. When the year came and the prophecy didn't, thoughtful Americans sang softly in praise of themselves. The roots of liberal democracy had held. Wherever else the terror had happened, we, at least, had not been visited by [author:Orwellian|3706] nightmares.

But we had forgotten that alongside [author:Orwell|3706]'s dark vision, there was another - slightly older, slightly less well known, equally chilling: [author:Aldous Huxley|3487]'s Brave New World. Contrary to common belief even among the educated, [author:Huxley|3487] and [author:Orwell|3706] did not prophesy the same thing. [author:Orwell|3706] warns that we will be overcome by an externally imposed oppression. But in [author:Huxley|3487]'s vision, no Big Brother is required to deprive people of their autonomy, maturity and history. As he saw it, people will come to love their oppression, to adore the technologies that undo their capacities to think.

What [author:Orwell|3706] feared were those who would ban books. What [author:Huxley|3487] feared was that there would be no reason to ban a book, for there would be no one who wanted to read one. [author:Orwell|3706] feared those who would deprive us of information. [author:Huxley|3487] feared those who would give us so much that we would be reduced to passivity and egoism. [author:Orwell|3706] feared that the truth would be concealed from us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared the truth would be drowned in a sea of irrelevance. [author:Orwell|3706] feared we would become a captive culture. [author:Huxley|3487] feared we would become a trivial culture, preoccupied with some equivalent of the feelies, the orgy porgy, and the centrifugal bumblepuppy. As [author:Huxley|3487] remarked in Brave New World Revisited, the civil libertarians and rationalists who are ever on the alert to oppose tyranny &quot;&lt;i&gt;failed to take into account man's almost infinite appetite for distractions&lt;/i&gt;.&quot; In 1984, [author:Orwell|3706] added, people are controlled by inflicting pain. In Brave New World, they are controlled by inflicting pleasure. In short, [author:Orwell|3706] feared that what we fear will ruin us. [author:Huxley|3487] feared that what we desire will ruin us.

This book is about the possibility that [author:Huxley|3487], not [author:Orwell|3706], was right." -- Neil Postman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514430-is-not-this-a-true-autumn-day-just-the-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:33:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/514430-is-not-this-a-true-autumn-day-just-the-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is not this a true autumn day? Just the still melancholy that I love - that makes life and nature harmonise. The birds are consulting about their migrations, the trees are putting on the hectic or the pallid hues of decay, and begin to strew the ground, that one's very footsteps may not disturb the repose of earth and air, while they give us a scent that is a perfect anodyne to the restless spirit. Delicious autumn! My very soul is wedded to it, and if I were a bird I would fly about the earth seeking the successive autumns.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Miss Eliot&lt;/i&gt;, Oct. 1, 1841]" -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32925-autumn-is-a-second-spring-when-every-leaf-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:35:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32925-autumn-is-a-second-spring-when-every-leaf-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Autumn is a second spring when every leaf is a flower." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:35:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You expected to be sad in the fall. Part of you died each year when the leaves fell from the trees and their branches were bare against the wind and the cold, wintery light. But you knew there would always be the spring, as you knew the river would flow again after it was frozen. When the cold rains kept on and killed the spring, it was as though a young person died for no reason." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267033-my-heart-is-drumming-in-my-chest-so-hard-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:35:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Lauren Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267033-my-heart-is-drumming-in-my-chest-so-hard-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My heart is drumming in my chest so hard it aches, but it's the good kind of ache, like the feeling you get on the first real day of autumn, when the air is crisp and the leaves are all flaring at the edges and the wind smells just vaguely of smoke - like the end and the beginning of something all at once." -- Lauren Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22840-climb-the-mountains-and-get-their-good-tidings-nature-s-peace</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:36:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by John Muir]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22840-climb-the-mountains-and-get-their-good-tidings-nature-s-peace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Climb the mountains and get their good tidings. Nature's peace will flow into you as sunshine flows into trees. The winds will blow their own freshness into you, and the storms their energy, while cares will drop away from you like the leaves of Autumn." -- John Muir]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153726-aprils-have-never-meant-much-to-me-autumns-seem-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:37:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153726-aprils-have-never-meant-much-to-me-autumns-seem-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aprils have never meant much to me, autumns seem that season of beginning, spring." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54406-at-no-other-time-than-autumn-does-the-earth-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:37:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54406-at-no-other-time-than-autumn-does-the-earth-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At no other time (than autumn) does the earth let itself be inhaled in one smell, the ripe earth; in a smell that is in no way inferior to the smell of the sea, bitter where it borders on taste, and more honeysweet where you feel it touching the first sounds.  Containing depth within itself, darkness, something of the grave almost." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60641-your-heart-bessie-is-an-autumn-garage</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:39:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60641-your-heart-bessie-is-an-autumn-garage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your heart, Bessie, is an autumn garage." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85563-the-law-presides-over-things-of-this-world-finally-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 06:40:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85563-the-law-presides-over-things-of-this-world-finally-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The law presides over things of this world, finally. The world where shadow is shadow and light is light, yin is yin and yang is yang, I'm me and he's him. 'I am me and / He is him/ Autumn eve.' But you don't belong to that world, sonny. The world you belong to is above that or below that.&quot;

Which is better?&quot; I asked, out of simple curiosity. &quot;Above or below?&quot;

It's not that either one is better,&quot; he said. After a brief coughing fit, he spat a glob of phlegm onto a tissue and studied it closely before crumpling the tissue and throwing it into a wastebasket. &quot;It's not a question of better or worse. The point is, not to resist the flow. You go up when you're supposed to go up and down when you're supposed to go down. When you're supposed to go up, find the highest tower and climb to the top. When you're supposed to go down, find the deepest well and go down to the bottom. When there is no flow, stay still. If you resist the flow, everything dries up. If everything dries up, the world is darkness. 'I am he and/ He is me:/ Spring nightfall.' Abandon the self, and there you are." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233610-now-you-ve-said-it-the-hopeless-emptiness-hell-plenty-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 10:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Richard Yates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233610-now-you-ve-said-it-the-hopeless-emptiness-hell-plenty-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now you’ve said it. The hopeless emptiness. Hell, plenty of people are on to the emptiness part; out where I used to work, on the Coast, that’s all we ever talked about. We’d sit around talking about emptiness all night. Nobody ever said ‘hopeless,’ though; that’s where we’d chicken out. Because maybe it does take a certain amount of guts to see the emptiness, but it takes a whole hell of a lot more to see the hopelessness. And I guess when you do see the hopelessness, that’s when there’s nothing to do but take off. If you can" -- Richard Yates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65823-karma-repair-kit-items-1-4-1-get-enough-food-to-eat</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 19:30:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liberty add a quote by Richard Brautigan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65823-karma-repair-kit-items-1-4-1-get-enough-food-to-eat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Karma Repair Kit  Items 1-4.

1.Get enough food to eat,
and eat it.

2.Find a place to sleep where it is quiet,
and sleep there.

3.Reduce intellectual and emotional noise
until you arrive at the silence of yourself,
and listen to it.

4." -- Richard Brautigan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
