<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708262-oli]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708262-oli" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 17:00:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92364-thus-the-task-is-not-so-much-to-see-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 17:00:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92364-thus-the-task-is-not-so-much-to-see-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, the task is not so much to see what no one yet has seen, but to think what nobody yet has thought about that which everybody sees." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70868-out-of-the-night-that-covers-me-black-as-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 05:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by William Ernest Henley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70868-out-of-the-night-that-covers-me-black-as-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of the night that covers me, 
Black as the Pit from pole to pole, 
I thank whatever gods may be 
For my unconquerable soul.

In the fell clutch of circumstance 
I have not winced nor cried aloud. 
Under the bludgeonings of chance 
My head is bloody, but unbowed.

Beyond this place of wrath and tears 
Looms but the Horror of the shade, 
And yet the menace of the years 
Finds, and shall find, me unafraid.

It matters not how strait the gate, 
How charged with punishments the scroll, 
I am the master of my fate: 
I am the captain of my soul." -- William Ernest Henley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27229-confidence-is-what-you-have-before-you-understand-the-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 16:59:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27229-confidence-is-what-you-have-before-you-understand-the-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Confidence is what you have before you understand the problem." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2378-enjoy-when-you-can-and-endure-when-you-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 05:13:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2378-enjoy-when-you-can-and-endure-when-you-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enjoy when you can, and endure when you must." -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113639-it-is-not-worth-the-bother-of-killing-yourself-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 17:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113639-it-is-not-worth-the-bother-of-killing-yourself-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not worth the bother of killing yourself, since you always kill yourself too late." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2194-every-man-takes-the-limits-of-his-own-field-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 05:13:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2194-every-man-takes-the-limits-of-his-own-field-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every man takes the limits of his own field of vision for the limits of the world." -- Arthur Schopenhauer ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12588-death-therefore-the-most-awful-of-evils-is-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 05:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Epicurus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12588-death-therefore-the-most-awful-of-evils-is-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death, therefore, the most awful of evils, is nothing to us, seeing that, when we are, death is not come, and, when death is come, we are not." -- Epicurus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250942-mostly-it-is-loss-which-teaches-us-about-the-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 16:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250942-mostly-it-is-loss-which-teaches-us-about-the-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mostly it is loss which teaches us about the worth of things." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8634-may-you-live-every-day-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2012 16:38:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Jonathan Swift]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8634-may-you-live-every-day-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May you live every day of your life." -- Jonathan Swift]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 06:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36609-as-a-writer-you-should-not-judge-you-should-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 06:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36609-as-a-writer-you-should-not-judge-you-should-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a writer, you should not judge, you should understand." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84190-sometimes-i-write-drunk-and-revise-sober-and-sometimes-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2009 06:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Peter De Vries]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84190-sometimes-i-write-drunk-and-revise-sober-and-sometimes-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I write drunk and revise sober, and sometimes I write sober and revise drunk. But you have to have both elements in creation — the Apollonian and the Dionysian, or spontaneity and restraint, emotion and discipline." -- Peter De Vries]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14306-almost-nobody-dances-sober-unless-they-happen-to-be-insane</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 15:19:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14306-almost-nobody-dances-sober-unless-they-happen-to-be-insane]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almost nobody dances sober, unless they happen to be insane." -- Howard Phillips Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33242-if-you-treat-an-individual-as-he-is-he-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 15:30:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33242-if-you-treat-an-individual-as-he-is-he-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you treat an individual as he is, he will remain how he is. But if you treat him as if he were what he ought to be and could be, he will become what he ought to be and could be." -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15355-words-do-not-express-thoughts-very-well-they-always-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 15:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15355-words-do-not-express-thoughts-very-well-they-always-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words do not express thoughts very well. They always become a little different immediately after they are expressed, a little distorted, a little foolish." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 15:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 14:47:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fear of death follows from the fear of life. A man who lives fully is prepared to die at any time." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18213-why-do-you-have-to-be-a-nonconformist-like-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 05:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by James Thurber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18213-why-do-you-have-to-be-a-nonconformist-like-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you have to be a nonconformist like everybody else?" -- James Thurber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15558-it-is-better-to-know-some-of-the-questions-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 05:41:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by James Thurber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15558-it-is-better-to-know-some-of-the-questions-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to know some of the questions than all of the answers." -- James Thurber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6693-independence-is-my-happiness-and-i-view-things-as-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2012 15:12:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by thomas paine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6693-independence-is-my-happiness-and-i-view-things-as-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Independence is my happiness, and I view things as they are, without regard to place or person; my country is the world, and my religion is to do good." -- thomas paine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136069-be-the-flame-not-the-moth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 17:23:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Giacomo Casanova ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136069-be-the-flame-not-the-moth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the flame, not the moth." -- Giacomo Casanova ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5035-eighty-percent-of-success-is-showing-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 15:58:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5035-eighty-percent-of-success-is-showing-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eighty percent of success is showing up." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44252-what-if-everything-is-an-illusion-and-nothing-exists-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 15:59:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44252-what-if-everything-is-an-illusion-and-nothing-exists-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if everything is an illusion and nothing exists? In that case, I definitely overpaid for my carpet." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109388-warning-if-you-are-reading-this-then-this-warning-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 03:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109388-warning-if-you-are-reading-this-then-this-warning-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Warning: If you are reading this then this warning is for you. Every word you read of this useless fine print is another second off your life. Don't you have other things to do? Is your life so empty that you honestly can't think of a better way to spend these moments? Or are you so impressed with authority that you give respect and credence to all that claim it? Do you read everything you're supposed to read? Do you think every thing you're supposed to think? Buy what you're told to want? Get out of your apartment. Meet a member of the opposite sex. Stop the excessive shopping and masturbation. Quit your job. Start a fight. Prove you're alive. If you don't claim your humanity you will become a statistic. You have been warned." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43459-we-cannot-change-the-cards-we-are-dealt-just-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 16:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43459-we-cannot-change-the-cards-we-are-dealt-just-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot change the cards we are dealt, just how we play the hand." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 16:23:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then I felt sad because I realized that once people are broken in certain ways, they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one. You wonder when your turn is going to be, or if it's already happened." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118705-i-m-a-pessimist-because-of-intelligence-but-an-optimist-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 10:33:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Antonio Gramsci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118705-i-m-a-pessimist-because-of-intelligence-but-an-optimist-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a pessimist because of intelligence, but an optimist because of will." -- Antonio Gramsci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 16:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8-talent-hits-a-target-no-one-else-can-hit-genius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent hits a target no one else can hit. Genius hits a target no one else can see." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304403-a-man-can-be-himself-only-so-long-as-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 16:56:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304403-a-man-can-be-himself-only-so-long-as-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can be himself only so long as he is alone; and if he does not love solitude, he will not love freedom; for it is only when he is alone that he is really free." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176216-they-tell-us-that-suicide-is-the-greatest-piece-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 16:57:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oli add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176216-they-tell-us-that-suicide-is-the-greatest-piece-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They tell us that Suicide is the greatest piece of Cowardice... That Suicide is wrong; when it is quite obvious that there is nothing in this world to which every man has a more unassailable title than to his own life and person." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
