<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708733-michael-mcleod]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708733-michael-mcleod" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 03:54:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677949-not-one-of-your-pertinent-ancestors-was-squashed-devoured-drowned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 03:54:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677949-not-one-of-your-pertinent-ancestors-was-squashed-devoured-drowned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not one of your pertinent ancestors was squashed, devoured, drowned, starved, stranded, stuck fast, untimely wounded, or otherwise deflected from its life's quest of delivering a tiny charge of genetic material to the right partner at the right moment in order to perpetuate the only possible sequence of hereditary combinations that could result -- eventually, astoundingly, and all too briefly -- in you." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7523-but-that-s-the-glory-of-foreign-travel-as-far-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 03:54:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7523-but-that-s-the-glory-of-foreign-travel-as-far-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But that's the glory of foreign travel, as far as I am concerned. I don't want to know what people are talking about. I can't think of anything that excites a greater sense of childlike wonder than to be in a country where you are ignorant of almost everything. Suddenly you are five years old again. You can't read anything, you have only the most rudimentary sense of how things work, you can't even reliably cross a street without endangering your life. Your whole existence becomes a series of interesting guesses." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18373-tune-your-television-to-any-channel-it-doesn-t-receive-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 03:55:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18373-tune-your-television-to-any-channel-it-doesn-t-receive-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tune your television to any channel it doesn't receive and about 1 percent of the dancing static you see is accounted for by this ancient remnant of the Big Bang. The next time you complain that there is nothing on, remember that you can always watch the birth of the universe." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256355-consider-the-fact-that-for-3-8-billion-years-a-period</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 04:01:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256355-consider-the-fact-that-for-3-8-billion-years-a-period]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider the fact that for 3.8 billion years, a period of time older than the Earth's mountains and rivers and oceans, every one of your forebears on both sides has been attractive enough to find a mate, healthy enough to reproduce, and sufficiently blessed by fate and circumstances to live long enough to do so. Not one of your pertinent ancestors was squashed, devoured, drowned, starved, stranded, stuck fast, untimely wounded, or otherwise deflected from its life's quest of delivering a tiny charge of genetic material to the right partner at the right moment in order to perpetuate the only possible sequence of hereditary combinations that could result -- eventually, astoundingly, and all too briefly -- in you." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84739-i-glanced-at-my-watch---it-was-two-minutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 04:09:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84739-i-glanced-at-my-watch---it-was-two-minutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I glanced at my watch - it was two minutes to eleven; just right for lunch when and if we ever got to the godforsaken lodge - and took some comfort from the thought that at least I still had my wits about me. Or at least I felt as if I did. Presumably, a confused person would be too addled to recognize that he was confused. Ergo, if you know that you are not confused then you are not confused. Unless, it suddenly occurred to me - and here was an arresting notion - unless persuading yourself that you are not confused is merely a cruel, early symptom of confusion. Or even an advanced symptom. Who could tell? For all I knew I could be stumbling into some kind of helpless preconfusional state characterized by the fear on the part of the sufferer that he may be stumbling into some kind of helpless preconfusional state. That's the trouble with losing your mind; by the time it's gone, it's too late to get it back." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333572-and-i-find-chopsticks-frankly-distressing-am-i-alone-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2012 04:11:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333572-and-i-find-chopsticks-frankly-distressing-am-i-alone-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I find chopsticks frankly distressing. Am I alone in thinking it odd that a people ingenious enough to invent paper, gunpowder, kites and any number of other useful objects, and who have a noble history extending back 3,000 years haven't yet worked out that a pair of knitting needles is no way to capture food?" -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 18:45:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766026-for-man-is-essentially-alone-and-one-should-pity-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 18:45:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Halldór Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/766026-for-man-is-essentially-alone-and-one-should-pity-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For man is essentially alone, and one should pity him and love him and grieve with him." -- Halldór Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56194-all-happiness-depends-on-courage-and-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 18:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56194-all-happiness-depends-on-courage-and-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All happiness depends on courage and work." -- Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393041-if-books-could-have-more-give-more-be-more-show</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2013 23:07:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Gary Paulsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393041-if-books-could-have-more-give-more-be-more-show]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If books could have more, give more, be more, show more, they would still need readers who bring to them sound and smell and light and all the rest that can’t be in books.
	The book needs you." -- Gary Paulsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/863624-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 21:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/863624-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately..." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81130-in-the-world-i-am-always-a-stranger-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 20:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Bei Dao]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81130-in-the-world-i-am-always-a-stranger-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the world I am
Always a stranger
I do not understand its language
It does not understand my silence" -- Bei Dao]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2013 06:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Kent M. Keith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6396-the-paradoxical-commandments-people-are-illogical-unreasonable-and-self-centered-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Paradoxical Commandments

People are illogical, unreasonable, and self-centered.
Love them anyway.

If you do good, people will accuse you of selfish ulterior motives.
Do good anyway.

If you are successful, you will win false friends and true enemies.
Succeed anyway.

The good you do today will be forgotten tomorrow.
Do good anyway.

Honesty and frankness make you vulnerable.
Be honest and frank anyway.

The biggest men and women with the biggest ideas can be shot down by the smallest men and women with the smallest minds.
Think big anyway.

People favor underdogs but follow only top dogs.
Fight for a few underdogs anyway.

What you spend years building may be destroyed overnight.
Build anyway.

People really need help but may attack you if you do help them.
Help people anyway.

Give the world the best you have and you'll get kicked in the teeth.
Give the world the best you have anyway." -- Kent M. Keith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22524-we-are-just-an-advanced-breed-of-monkeys-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 21:32:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by Stephen Hawking]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22524-we-are-just-an-advanced-breed-of-monkeys-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are just an advanced breed of monkeys on a minor planet of a very average star. But we can understand the Universe. That makes us something very special." -- Stephen Hawking]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
