<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708858-john]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708858-john" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 13:12:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79207-the-death-of-god-left-the-angels-in-a-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2008 13:12:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Donald Barthelme]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79207-the-death-of-god-left-the-angels-in-a-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The death of God left the angels in a strange position." -- Donald Barthelme]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127942-ineluctable-modality-of-the-visible-at-least-that-if-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:22:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127942-ineluctable-modality-of-the-visible-at-least-that-if-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ineluctable modality of the visible: at least that if no more, thought through my eyes. Signatures of all things I am here to read, seaspawn and seawrack, the nearing tide, that rusty boot. Snotgreen, bluesilver, rust: coloured signs. Limits of the diaphane. But he adds: in bodies." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32998-we-work-in-the-dark---we-do-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:24:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32998-we-work-in-the-dark---we-do-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We work in the dark - we do what we can - we give what we have. Our doubt is our passion, and our passion is our task. The rest is the madness of art." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189262-whether-there-is-such-a-thing-as-reality-of-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2009 08:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189262-whether-there-is-such-a-thing-as-reality-of-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether there is such a thing as Reality, of which the various levels are only partial aspects, or whether there are only levels, is something that literature cannot decide. Literature recognizes rather the *reality of the levels.* " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75130-let-all-of-life-be-an-unfettered-howl</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 11:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75130-let-all-of-life-be-an-unfettered-howl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let all of life be an unfettered howl." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 11:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our imagination flies -- we are its shadow on the earth." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83743-i-have-been-writing-my-heart-out-all-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 07:38:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83743-i-have-been-writing-my-heart-out-all-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been writing my heart out all my life, but only getting a living out of it now, and the attacks are coming in thick. A lot of people are mad and jealous and bitter and I only hope they also can be heard by an expanding publishing program the size of Russia's. Because it's not a question of the merit of art, but a question of spontaneity and sincerity and joy I say. I would like everybody in the world to tell his full life confession and tell it HIS OWN WAY and then we'd have something to read in our old age, instead of the hesitations and cavilings of 'men of letters' with blear faces who only alter words that the Angel brought them." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69191-know-all-the-questions-but-not-the-answers-look-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 12:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Zilpha Keatley Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69191-know-all-the-questions-but-not-the-answers-look-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Know all the Questions, but not the Answers
Look for the Different, instead of the Same
Never Walk where there's room for Running
Don't do anything that can't be a Game" -- Zilpha Keatley Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117849-death-speaks-there-was-a-merchant-in-bagdad-who-sent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 09:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117849-death-speaks-there-was-a-merchant-in-bagdad-who-sent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death speaks: There was a merchant in Bagdad who sent his servant to market to buy provisions and in a little while the servant came back, white and trembling and said, Master, just now when I was in the market-place I was jostled by a woman in the crowd and when I turned I saw it was Death that jostled me. She looked at me and made a threatening gesture; now, lend me your horse, and I will ride away from this city and avoid my fate. I will go to Samarra and there Death will not find me. The merchant lent him his horse, and the servant mounted it, and he dug his spurs in its flanks and as fast as the horse could gallop he went. Then the merchant went down to the market-place and he saw me standing in the crowd and he came to me and said, Why did you make a threatening gesture to my servant when you saw him this morning? That was not a threatening gesture, I said, it was only a start of surprise. I was astonished to see him in Bagdad, for I had an appointment with him tonight in Samarra." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
