<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708965-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/708965-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 12:50:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11861-no-my-advocates-my-angels-with-sadist-eyes-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 12:50:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11861-no-my-advocates-my-angels-with-sadist-eyes-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, my advocates, my angels with sadist eyes, this is the beginning of my life, or the end. So I lean affirmation across the cafe table, and surrender my fifty years away with an easy smile. But the surety of my love is not dismayed by any eventuality which prudence or pity can conjure up, and in the end all that we can do is to sit at the table over which our hands cross, listening to tunes from the wurlitzer, with love huge and simple between us, and nothing more to be said." -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11862-how-can-i-be-kind-how-can-i-find-bird-relief</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 12:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11862-how-can-i-be-kind-how-can-i-find-bird-relief]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can I be kind? How can I find bird-relief in the nest-building of day-to-day? Necessity supplies no velvet wing with which to escape. I am indeed and mortally pierced with the seeds of love." -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13107-and-i-don-t-know-it-is-one-thing-to-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 14:45:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13107-and-i-don-t-know-it-is-one-thing-to-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I don't know, it is one thing to look out a window, but when you are Out, actually Out, that is something very powerful, and how embarrassing was that, because I could not help it, I went down flat on my gut checking out those flowers, and the feeling of the one I chose was like the silk on that Hermes jacket I could never seem to get Reserved because Vance was always hogging it, except the flower was even better, it being very smooth and built in like layers? With the outside layer being yellow, and inside that a white thing like a bell, and inside the white bell-like thing were fifteen (I counted) smaller bell-like red things, and inside each red thing was an even smaller orange two-dingly-thing combo." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13108-in-the-town-where-i-live-i-have-frequently-observed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 14:46:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13108-in-the-town-where-i-live-i-have-frequently-observed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the town where I live, I have frequently observed a phenomenon I have come to think of as Samish-Sex Marriage." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13110-a-hip-looking-teen-watches-an-elderly-woman-hobble-across-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 14:49:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13110-a-hip-looking-teen-watches-an-elderly-woman-hobble-across-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A hip-looking teen watches an elderly woman hobble across the street on a walker.
&quot;Grammy's here!&quot; he shouts.
He puts some MacAttack Mac&amp;Cheese in the microwave and dons headphones and takes out a video game so he won't be bored during the forty seconds it takes his lunch to cook. A truck comes around the corner and hits Grammy, sending her flying over the roof into the backyard, where luckily she lands on a trampoline. Unluckily, she bounces back over the roof, into the front yard, landing on a rosebush." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13111-she-said-america-was-a-spoiled-child-ignorant-of-grief</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 14:50:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13111-she-said-america-was-a-spoiled-child-ignorant-of-grief]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She said America was a spoiled child ignorant of grief." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13591-in-1951-we-were-also-told-that-the-russians-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 08:40:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13591-in-1951-we-were-also-told-that-the-russians-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[In 1951] we were also told that the Russians could be parachuting from planes over our town at any time. These were the same Russians that my uncles had fought alongside only a few years earlier. Now they had become monsters who were coming to slit our throats and incinerate us. It seemed peculiar. Living under a cloud of fear like this robs a child of his spirit. It's one thing to be afraid when someone's holding a shotgun on you, but it's another thing to be afraid of something that's just not quite real." -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13592-wagon-train-was-on-it-seemed-to-be-beaming-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 08:45:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13592-wagon-train-was-on-it-seemed-to-be-beaming-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;Wagon Train&lt;/i&gt; was on. It seemed to be beaming in from some foreign country. I shut that off, too, and went into another room, a windowless one with a painted door--a dark cavern with a floor-to-ceiling library. I switched on the lamps. The place had an overpowering presence of literature and you couldn't help but lose your passion for dumbness." -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13595-they-waited-the-door-did-not-open-the-rain-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 08:48:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Timothy Findley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13595-they-waited-the-door-did-not-open-the-rain-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They waited.
The door did not open.
The rain did not stop.
The darkness made a tent and covered them completely." -- Timothy Findley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13599-with-every-new-manoeuvre-the-light-was-growing-dimmer--fading-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2008 08:53:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Timothy Findley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13599-with-every-new-manoeuvre-the-light-was-growing-dimmer--fading-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...with every new manoeuvre, the light was growing dimmer--fading by numbers as well as strength--and the sound could no longer be heard, but only the pulse of it--seen going out in the darkness--losing its edges--caving in at its centre--webbing, now, as if a spider was spinning against the rain--until the last few strands of brightness fell--and were extinguished--silenced and removed from life and from all that lives forever.
And the bell tolled--but the ark, as ever, was adamant. Its shape had taken on a voice. And the voice said: no." -- Timothy Findley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16846-april-19-and-now-it-is-spring-birds-are-singing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:01:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16846-april-19-and-now-it-is-spring-birds-are-singing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["April 19
And now it is spring. Birds are singing. Wistful notes and jubilant. And bare streets and no need for coats, and skipping ropes and bicycles and a thin new moon." -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16847-work-is-the-only-only-only-remedy-for-life-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:03:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16847-work-is-the-only-only-only-remedy-for-life-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work is the only only only remedy for life: for happiness, for interest, for stability, for security. Hard, willed work. Oh work!" -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16850-man-is-without-doubt-the-defacer-the-destroyer-but-spending</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16850-man-is-without-doubt-the-defacer-the-destroyer-but-spending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is, without doubt, the defacer, the destroyer. But spending at least the last three years in trying to understand the enemy has almost seduced me to his side." -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16852-the-temperament-of-a-dandelion-or-cosmic-preservation-where-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:13:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16852-the-temperament-of-a-dandelion-or-cosmic-preservation-where-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The temperament of a dandelion or cosmic preservation. Where does wonder begin?" -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16856-if-i-had-my-wilderness-nature-could-be-my-lover</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2008 09:15:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16856-if-i-had-my-wilderness-nature-could-be-my-lover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had my wilderness, nature could be my  lover. What can I do in the paved streets for my thirsty roots? I waste time. I encourage fools. I slip the vital hours into penny slot machines -- to pass time, to start my stuck wheels only love can oil." -- Elizabeth Smart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20247-all-of-us-humans-have-myriad-other-species-to-thank</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 10:51:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alan Weisman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20247-all-of-us-humans-have-myriad-other-species-to-thank]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of us humans have myriad other species to thank. Without them, we couldn't exist. It's that simple, and we can't afford to ignore them, anymore than I can afford to neglect my precious wife--nor the sweet mother Earth that births and holds us all. 

Without us, Earth will abide and endure; without her, however, we could not even be." -- Alan Weisman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20248-when-you-examine-societies-just-as-self-confident-as-ours-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 10:54:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Arthur Demarest]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20248-when-you-examine-societies-just-as-self-confident-as-ours-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you examine societies just as self-confident as ours that unraveled and were eventually swallowed by the jungle...you see that the balance between ecology and society is exquisitely delicate. If something throws that off, it all can end.

...Two thousand years later, someone will be squinting over the fragments, trying to find our what went wrong." -- Arthur Demarest]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23032-our-modern-civilization-returns-exceedingly-little-of-what-it-borrows</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 15:47:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23032-our-modern-civilization-returns-exceedingly-little-of-what-it-borrows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...our modern civilization returns exceedingly little of what it borrows.&quot; -Martin Renner" -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18508-eat-food-not-too-much-mostly-plants</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 09:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18508-eat-food-not-too-much-mostly-plants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eat food.  Not too much.  Mostly plants." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23041-for-most-people-in-the-jewish-ghetto-of-warsaw-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 15:55:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Diane Ackerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23041-for-most-people-in-the-jewish-ghetto-of-warsaw-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...for most people in the [Jewish] Ghetto [of Warsaw] nature lived only in memory -- no parks, birds, or greenery existed in the Ghetto -- and they suffered the loss of nature like a phantom-limb pain, an amputation that scrambled the body's rhythms, starved the senses, and made basic ideas about the world impossible for children to fathom." -- Diane Ackerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23042-as-zookeepers-the-zabinskis-understood-both-vigilance-and-predators-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 15:57:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Diane Ackerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23042-as-zookeepers-the-zabinskis-understood-both-vigilance-and-predators-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...as zookeepers, the Zabinskis understood both vigilance and predators; in a swamp of vipers, one planned every footstep. Shaped by the gravity of wartime, it wasn't always clear who or what could be considered outside or inside, loyal or turncoat, predator or prey." -- Diane Ackerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23922-what-was-a-face-on-television-but-a-code-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:11:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Lydia Millet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23922-what-was-a-face-on-television-but-a-code-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What was a face on television but a code, and what was the difference between these faces but a realignment of line and color to shift among signals? If he grasped deeply this language of symbols, grasped it beneath the surface, he could course through the currents of authority as they coursed through him like heat or the tremble of cold." -- Lydia Millet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23925-david-had-been-photographing-endangered-species-in-the-hawaiian-rainforest</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:16:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23925-david-had-been-photographing-endangered-species-in-the-hawaiian-rainforest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["David had been photographing endangered species in the Hawaiian rainforest and elsewhere for years, and his collections of photographs and Suzie's tarot cards seemed somehow related. Because species disappear when their habitat does, he photographed them against the nowhere of a black backdrop (which sometimes meant propping up a black velvet cloth in the most unlikely places and discouraging climates), and so each creature, each plant, stood as though for a formal portrait alone against the darkness. The photographs looked like cards too, card from the deck of the world in which each creature describes a history, a way of being in the world, a set of possibilities, a deck from which cards are being thrown away, one after another. Plants and animals are a language, even in our reduced, domesticated English, where children grow like weeds or come out smelling like roses, the market is made up of bulls and bears, politics of hawks and doves. Like cards, flora and fauna could be read again and again, not only alone but in combination, in the endlessly shifting combinations of a nature that tells its own stories and colors ours, a nature we are losing without even knowing the extent of that loss." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23929-i-grew-up-with-landscape-as-a-recourse-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:20:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23929-i-grew-up-with-landscape-as-a-recourse-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I grew up with landscape as a recourse, with the possibility of exiting the horizontal realm of social relations for a vertical alignment with earth and sky, matter and spirit. Vast open spaces speak best to this craving, the spaces I myself first found in the desert and then in the western grasslands." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23932-eduardo-galeano-notes-that-america-was-conquered-but-not-discovered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:22:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23932-eduardo-galeano-notes-that-america-was-conquered-but-not-discovered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eduardo Galeano notes that America was conquered, but not discovered, that the men who arrived with a religion to impose and dreams of gold never really knew where they were, and that this discovery is still taking place in our time." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23933-cabeza-de-vaca-ceased-to-be-lost-not-by-returning</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:24:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23933-cabeza-de-vaca-ceased-to-be-lost-not-by-returning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[Cabeza de Vaca] ceased to be lost not by returning but by turning into something else." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23934-in-her-novel-regeneration-pat-barker-writes-of-a-doctor</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23934-in-her-novel-regeneration-pat-barker-writes-of-a-doctor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In her novel Regeneration, Pat Barker writes of a doctor who 'knew only too well how often the early stages of change or cure may mimic deterioration. Cut a chrysalis open, and you will find a rotting caterpillar. What you will never find is that mythical creature, half caterpillar, half butterfly, a fit emblem of the human soul, for those whose cast of mind leads them to seek such emblems. No, the process of transformation consists almost entirely of decay." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23935-when-someone-doesn-t-show-up-the-people-who-wait-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:30:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23935-when-someone-doesn-t-show-up-the-people-who-wait-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone doesn't show up, the people who wait sometimes tell stories about what might have happened and come to half believe the desertion, the abduction, the accident. Worry is a way to pretend that you have knowledge or control over what you don't--and it surprises me, even in myself, how much we prefer ugly scenarios to the pure unknown. Perhaps fantasy is what you fill up maps with rather than saying that they too contain the unknown." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23936-they-are-all-beasts-of-burden-in-a-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:32:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23936-they-are-all-beasts-of-burden-in-a-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They are all beasts of burden in a sense, ' Thoreau once remarked of animals, 'made to carry some portion of our thoughts.' Animals are the old language of the imagination; one of the ten thousand tragedies of their disappearance would be a silencing of this speech." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19355-there-s-no-place-you-can-go-on-the-prairie-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 11:35:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Diane Ackerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19355-there-s-no-place-you-can-go-on-the-prairie-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no place you can go on the prairie that you don't hear the white noise of the wind, steady and rough as surf curling along a non-existant shore." -- Diane Ackerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
