<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70913-deb]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/70913-deb" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 16:08:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 16:08:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The covers of this book are too far apart." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515964-the-dr-nuts-seemed-only-as-an-acid-gurgling-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 14:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deb add a quote by John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515964-the-dr-nuts-seemed-only-as-an-acid-gurgling-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Dr. Nuts seemed only as an acid gurgling down into his intestine.  He filled with gas, the sealed valve trapping it just as one pinches the mouth of a balloon.  Great eructations rose from his throat and bounced upward toward the refuse-laden bowl of the milk glass chandelier.  Once a person was asked to step into this brutal century, anything could happen.  Everywhere there lurked pitfalls like Abelman, the insipid Crusaders for Moorish Dignity, the Mancuso cretin, Dorian Greene, newspaper reporters, stripteasers, birds, photography, juvenile delinquents, Nazi pornographers.  And especially Myrna Minkoff.  The musky minx must be dealt with.  Somehow.  Someday.  She must pay.  Whatever happened, he must attend to her even if the revenge took years and he had to stalk her through decades from one coffee shop to another, from one folksinging orgy to another, from subway train to pad to cotton field to demonstration.  Ignatius invoked an elaborate Elizabethan curse upon Myrna and, rolling over, frantically abused the glove once more." -- John Kennedy Toole]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
