<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/709129-ramiro-de-la-garza]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/709129-ramiro-de-la-garza" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 14:12:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10086-brevity-is-the-soul-of-wit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 14:12:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ramiro  add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10086-brevity-is-the-soul-of-wit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brevity is the soul of wit." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10089-these-said-conrad-knew-the-world-by-systematic-examination-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 14:16:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ramiro  add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10089-these-said-conrad-knew-the-world-by-systematic-examination-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These, said Conrad, knew the world by systematic examination. To begin with the artist had only himself; he descended within himself and in the lonely regions to which he descended, he found &quot;the terms of his appeal&quot;. He appealed, said Conrad, &quot;to that part of our being which is a gift, not an acquisition, to the capacity for delight and wonder... our sense of pity and pain, to the latent feeling of fellowship with all creation - and to the subtle but invincible conviction of solidarity that knits together the loneliness of innumerable hearts... which binds together all humanity - the dead to the living and the living to the unborn." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10100-in-this-pilgrimage-in-search-of-modernity-i-lost-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2008 14:30:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ramiro  add a quote by Octavio Paz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10100-in-this-pilgrimage-in-search-of-modernity-i-lost-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this pilgrimage in search of modernity I lost my way at many points only to find myself again. I returned to the source and discovered that modernity is not outside but within us. It is today and the most ancient antiquity; it is tomorrow and the beginning of the world; it is a thousand years old and yet newborn. It speaks in Nahuatl, draws Chinese ideograms from the 9th century, and appears on the television screen. This intact present, recently unearthed, shakes off the dust of centuries, smiles and suddenly starts to fly, disappearing through the window. A simultaneous plurality of time and presence: modernity breaks with the immediate past only to recover an age-old past and transform a tiny fertility figure from the neolithic into our contemporary. We pursue modernity in her incessant metamorphoses yet we never manage to trap her. She always escapes: each encounter ends in flight. We embrace her and she disappears immediately: it was just a little air. It is the instant, that bird that is everywhere and nowhere. We want to trap it alive but it flaps its wings and vanishes in the form of a handful of syllables. We are left empty-handed. Then the doors of perception open slightly and the other time appears, the real one we were searching for without knowing it: the present, the presence." -- Octavio Paz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
