<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/710075-laurelei]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/710075-laurelei" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 05:31:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12227-how-often-since-then-has-she-wondered-what-might-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 05:31:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12227-how-often-since-then-has-she-wondered-what-might-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How often since then has she wondered what might have happened if she'd tried to remain with him; if she’d returned Richards kiss on the corner of Bleeker and McDougal, gone off somewhere (where?) with him, never bought the packet of incense or the alpaca coat with rose-shaped buttons. Couldn’t they have discovered something larger and stranger than what they've got. It is impossible not to imagine that other future, that rejected future, as taking place in Italy or France, among big sunny rooms and gardens; as being full of infidelities and great battles; as a vast and enduring romance laid over friendship so searing and profound it would accompany them to the grave and possibly even beyond. She could, she thinks, have entered another world. She could have had a life as potent and dangerous as literature itself.

Or then again maybe not, Clarissa tells herself. That's who I was. This is who I am--a decent woman with a good apartment, with a stable and affectionate marriage, giving a party. Venture too far for love, she tells herself, and you renounce citizenship in the country you've made for yourself. You end up just sailing from port to port.

Still, there is this sense of missed opportunity. Maybe there is nothing, ever, that can equal the recollection of having been young together. Maybe its as simple as that. Richard was the person Clarissa loved at her most optimistic moment. Richard had stood beside her at the ponds edge at dusk, wearing cut-off jeans and rubber sandals. Richard had called her Mrs. Dalloway, and they had kissed. His mouth had opened to hers; (exciting and utterly familiar, she'd never forget it) had worked its way shyly inside until she met its own. They'd kissed and walked around the pond together.

It had seemed like the beginning of happiness, and Clarissa is still sometimes shocked, more than thirty years later to realize that it was happiness; that the entire experience lay in a kiss and a walk. The anticipation of dinner and a book. The dinner is by now forgotten; Lessing has been long overshadowed by other writers. What lives undimmed in Clarissa's mind more than three decades later is a kiss at dusk on a patch of dead grass, and a walk around a pond as mosquitoes droned in the darkening air. There is still that singular perfection, and its perfect in part because it seemed, at the time, so clearly to promise more. Now she knows: That was the moment, right then. There has been no other." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 13:01:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now tequila may be the favored beverage of outlaws but that doesn't mean it gives them preferential treatment. In fact, tequila probably has betrayed as many outlaws as has the central nervous system and dissatisfied wives. Tequila, scorpion honey, harsh dew of the doglands, essence of Aztec, crema de cacti; tequila, oily and thermal like the sun in solution; tequila, liquid geometry of passion; Tequila, the buzzard god who copulates in midair with the ascending souls of dying virgins; tequila, firebug in the house of good taste; O tequila, savage water of sorcery, what confusion and mischief your sly, rebellious drops do generate!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7516-i-am-beginning-to-understand-said-the-little-prince-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 13:04:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7516-i-am-beginning-to-understand-said-the-little-prince-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am beginning to understand,&quot; said the little prince. &quot;There is a flower... I think that she has tamed me..." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2008 22:10:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7518-since-feeling-is-first-who-pays-any-attention-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 13:27:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7518-since-feeling-is-first-who-pays-any-attention-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["since feeling is first
who pays any attention
to the syntax of things
will never wholly kiss you;

wholly to be a fool
while Spring is in the world

my blood approves,
and kisses are a far better fate
than wisdom
lady i swear by all flowers. Don't cry
--the best gesture of my brain is less than
your eyelids' flutter which says

we are for eachother: then
laugh, leaning back in my arms
for life's not a paragraph

And death i think is no parenthesis" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 09:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn't quite make out. I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn't make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 09:22:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7038-kiss-me-and-you-will-see-how-important-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kiss me, and you will see how important I am." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11769-conversation-between-a-princess-and-an-outlaw-if-i-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 07:48:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11769-conversation-between-a-princess-and-an-outlaw-if-i-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conversation between a princess and an outlaw: 
&quot;If I stand for fairy-tale balls and dragon bait--dragon bait--what do you stand for?&quot;
&quot;Me? I stand for uncertainty, insecurity, bad taste, fun, and things that go boom in the night.&quot;
&quot;Franky, it seems to me that you've turned yourself into a stereotype.&quot;
&quot;You may be right. I don't care. As any car freak will tell you, the old models are the most beautiful, even if they aren't the most efficient. People who sacrifice beauty for efficiency get what they deserve.&quot;
&quot;Well, you may get off on being a beautiful stereotype, regardless of the social consequences, but my conscience won't allow it.&quot; 
&quot;And I goddamn refuse to be dragon bait. I'm as capable of rescuing you as you are of rescuing me.&quot;
&quot;I'm an outlaw, not a hero. I never intended to rescue you. We're our own dragons as well as our own heroes, and we have to rescue ourselves from ourselves." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11771-why-are-women-so-much-more-interesting-to-men-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 07:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11771-why-are-women-so-much-more-interesting-to-men-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why are women... so much more interesting to men than men are to women?" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68325-yes-my-consuming-desire-is-to-mingle-with-road-crews</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 09:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68325-yes-my-consuming-desire-is-to-mingle-with-road-crews]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, my consuming desire is to mingle with road crews, sailors and soldiers, barroom regulars—to be a part of a scene, anonymous, listening, recording—all this is spoiled by the fact that I am a girl, a female always supposedly in danger of assault and battery. My consuming interest in men and their lives is often misconstrued as a desire to seduce them, or as an invitation to intimacy. Yes, God, I want to talk to everybody as deeply as I can. I want to be able to sleep in an open field, to travel west, to walk freely at night..." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230058-though-blessed-with-the-enviable-properties-of-a-mink-coat-graceful</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 05:33:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230058-though-blessed-with-the-enviable-properties-of-a-mink-coat-graceful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though blessed with the enviable properties of a mink coat—graceful, unreasonable, and impractical no matter what she was draped over—she was nevertheless one of those people whose personality proved to be the bane of modern mathematicians. She was neither a flat nor solid shape. She showed no symmetry at all. Trigonometry, Calculus and Statistics all proved useless. Her Pie Chart was a muddle of arbitrary wedges, her Line Graph, the silhouette of the Alps. And just when one listed her under Chaos Theory—Butterfly Effects, Weather Predictions, Fractals, Bifurcation diagrams and whatnot—she showed up as an equilateral triangle, sometimes even a square." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230060-i-first-met-winston-churchill-in-the-early-summer-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 05:38:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Violet Bonham Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230060-i-first-met-winston-churchill-in-the-early-summer-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I first met Winston Churchill in the early summer of 1906 at a dinner party to which I went as a very young girl. Our hostess was Lady Wemyss and I remember that Arthur Balfour, George Wyndman, Hilaire Belloc and Charles Whibley were among the guests…

I found myself sitting next to this young man who seemed to me quite different from any other young man I had ever met. For a long time he seemed sunk in abstraction. Then he appeared to become suddenly aware of my existence. He turned on me a lowering gaze and asked me abruptly how old I was. I replied that I was nineteen. “And I,” he said despairingly, “am thirty-two already. Younger than anyone else who counts, though, “he added, as if to comfort himself. Then savagely: “Curse ruthless time! Curse our mortality. How cruelly short is this allotted span for all we must cram into it!” And he burst forth into an eloquent diatribe on the shortness of human life, the immensity of possible human accomplishment—a theme so well exploited by the poets, prophets, and philosophers of all ages that it might seem difficult to invest it with new and startling significance. Yet for me he did so, in a torrent of magnificent language which appeared to be both effortless and inexhaustible and ended up with the words I shall always remember: “We are all worms. But I do believe that I am a glow worm.”

By this time I was convinced of it—and my conviction remained unshaken throughout the years that followed. Later he asked me whether I thought that words had a magic and music quite independent of their meaning. I said I certainly thought so, and I quoted as a classic though familiar instance the first lines that came into my head.

Charm’d magic casements, opening on the foam
Of perilous seas, in faery lands forlorn.

His eyes blazed with excitement. “Say that again,” he said, “say it again—it is marvelous!” “But I objected, “You know these lines. You know the ‘Ode to a Nightengale.’ ” He had apparently never read or heard of it before (I must, however, add that next time I met him he had not learned not merely this but all of the odes to Keats by heart—and he recited them quite mercilessly from start to finish, not sparing me a syllable).

Finding that he liked poetry, I quoted to him from one of my own favorite poets, Blake. He listened avidly, repeating some lines to himself with varying emphases and stresses, then added meditatively: “I never knew that old Admiral had found so much time to write such good poetry.” I was astounded that he, with his acute susceptibility to words and power of using them, should have left such tracts of English literature entirely unexplored. But however it happened he had lost nothing by it, when he approached books it was “with a hungry, empty mind and with fairly srong jaws, and what I got I *bit*.” And his ear for the beauty of language needed no tuning fork.

Until the end of dinner I listened to him spellbound. I can remember thinking: This is what people mean when they talk of seeing stars. That is what I am doing now. I do not to this day know who was on my other side. Good manners, social obligation, duty—all had gone with the wind. I was transfixed, transported into a new element. I knew only that I had seen a great light. I recognized it as the light of genius…

I cannot attempt to analyze, still less transmit, the light of genius. But I will try to set down, as I remember them, some of the differences which struck me between him and all the others, young and old, whom I have known.

First and foremost he was incalculable. He ran true to no form. There lurked in his every thought and world the ambush of the unexpected. I felt also that the impact of life, ideas and even words upon his mind, was not only vivid and immediate, but direct. Between him and them there was no shock absorber of vicarious thought or precedent gleaned either from books or other minds. His relationship wit" -- Violet Bonham Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7575-i-thought-how-unpleasant-it-is-to-be-locked-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 06:53:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7575-i-thought-how-unpleasant-it-is-to-be-locked-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought how unpleasant it is to be locked out; and I thought how it is worse, perhaps, to be locked in." -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1863-women-have-served-all-these-centuries-as-looking-glasses-possessing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 06:53:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1863-women-have-served-all-these-centuries-as-looking-glasses-possessing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women have served all these centuries as looking glasses possessing the magic and delicious power of reflecting the figure of man at twice its natural size." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4732-i-don-t-believe-in-aging-i-believe-in-forever-altering</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 06:53:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4732-i-don-t-believe-in-aging-i-believe-in-forever-altering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in aging. I believe in forever altering one's aspect to the sun. " -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18873-i-meant-to-write-about-death-only-life-came-breaking</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 06:53:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18873-i-meant-to-write-about-death-only-life-came-breaking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I meant to write about death, only life came breaking in as usual" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6338-literature-is-strewn-with-the-wreckage-of-those-who-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 06:54:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6338-literature-is-strewn-with-the-wreckage-of-those-who-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature is strewn with the wreckage of those who have minded beyond reason the opinion of others." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:13:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ll get over it…” It’s the clichés that cause the trouble. To lose someone you love is to alter your life for ever. You don’t get over it because ‘it” is the person you loved. The pain stops, there are new people, but the gap never closes. How could it? The particularness of someone who mattered enough to grieve over is not made anodyne by death. This hole in my heart is in the shape of you and no-one else can fit it. Why would I want them to?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80787-why-is-the-measure-of-love-loss</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80787-why-is-the-measure-of-love-loss]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why is the measure of love loss?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371743-many-waters-cannot-quench-love-neither-can-floods-drown-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:14:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371743-many-waters-cannot-quench-love-neither-can-floods-drown-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many waters cannot quench love, neither can floods drown it. What then kills love? Only this: Neglect. Not to see you when you stand before me. Not to think of you in the little things. Not to make the road wide for you, the table spread for you. To choose you out of habit not desire, to pass the flower seller without a thought. To leave the dishes unwashed, the bed unmade, to ignore you in the mornings, make use of you at night. To crave another while pecking your cheek. To say your name without hearing it, to assume it is mine to call." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53711-i-don-t-know-how-to-answer-i-know-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:15:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53711-i-don-t-know-how-to-answer-i-know-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know how to answer. I know what I think, but words in the head are like voices underwater. They are distorted." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158882-in-the-library-i-felt-better-words-you-could-trust</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:16:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158882-in-the-library-i-felt-better-words-you-could-trust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the library I felt better, words you could trust and look at till you understood them, they couldn't change half way through a sentence like people, so it was easier to spot a lie." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147741-she-must-find-a-boat-and-sail-in-it-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:16:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147741-she-must-find-a-boat-and-sail-in-it-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She must find a boat and sail in it.  No guarantee of shore.  Only a conviction that what she wanted could exist, if she dared to find it." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182570-love-demands-expression-it-will-not-stay-still-stay-silent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:16:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182570-love-demands-expression-it-will-not-stay-still-stay-silent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love demands expression.  It will not stay still, stay silent, be good, be modest, be seen and not heard, no.  It will break out in tongues of praise, the high note that smashes the glass and spills the liquid." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110979-what-a-strange-world-this-is-when-you-can-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:16:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110979-what-a-strange-world-this-is-when-you-can-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a strange world this is when you can have as much sex as you like but love is taboo." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127783-i-was-happy-but-happy-is-an-adult-word-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:17:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127783-i-was-happy-but-happy-is-an-adult-word-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was happy but happy is an adult word. You don't have to ask a child about happy, you see it. They are or they are not. Adults talk about being happy because largely they are not. Talking about it is the same as trying to catch the wind. Much easier to let it blow all over you." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120861-what-it-means-to-be-human-is-to-bring-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:18:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120861-what-it-means-to-be-human-is-to-bring-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What it means to be human is to bring up your children in safety, educate them, keep them healthy, teach them how to care for themselves and others, allow them to develop in their own way among adults who are sane and responsibile, who know the value of the world and not its economic potential. It means art, it means time, it means all the invisibles never counted by the GDP and the census figures. It means knowing that life has an inside as well as an outside. And I think it means love." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179955-but-where-was-god-now-with-heaven-full-of-astronauts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:19:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179955-but-where-was-god-now-with-heaven-full-of-astronauts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But where was God now, with heaven full of astronauts, and the Lord overthrown? I miss God. I miss the company of someone utterly loyal. I still don't think of God as my betrayer. The servants of God, yes, but servants by their very nature betray. I miss God who was my friend. I don't even know if God exists, but I do know that if God is your emotional role model, very few human relationships will match up to it. I have an idea that one day it might be possible, I thought once it had become possible, and that glimpse has set me wandering, trying to find the balance between earth and sky. If the servants hadn't rushed in and parted us, I might have been disappointed, might have snatched off the white samite to find a bowl of soup. 

As it is, I can't settle, I want someone who is fierce and will love me until death and know that love is as strong as death, and be on my side for ever and ever. I want someone who will destroy and be destroyed by me. There are many forms of love and affection, some people can spend their whole lives together without knowing each other's names. Naming is a difficult and time-consuming process; it concerns essences, and it means power. But on the wild nights who can call you home? Only the one who knows your name. Romantic love has been diluted into paperback form and has sold thousands and millions of copies. Somewhere it is still in the original, written on tablets of stone. I would cross seas and suffer sunstroke and give away all I have, but not for a man, because they want to be the destroyer and never the destroyed." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303601-i-find-pieces-of-myself-everywhere-and-i-cut-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:20:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303601-i-find-pieces-of-myself-everywhere-and-i-cut-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find pieces of myself everywhere, and I cut myself handling them." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198173-i-say-i-m-in-love-with-her-what-does-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2013 04:20:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurelei add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198173-i-say-i-m-in-love-with-her-what-does-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I say I'm in love with her. What does that mean? 

It means I review my future and my past in the light of this feeling. It is as though I wrote in a foreign language that I am suddenly able to read. Wordlessly, she explains me to myself. LIke genius she is ignorant of what she does." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
