<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/711637-erin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/711637-erin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 19:10:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30375-first-of-all-don-t-mix-your-hairpins-up-with-mine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 19:10:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Jean Genet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30375-first-of-all-don-t-mix-your-hairpins-up-with-mine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, don't mix your hairpins up with mine! You .... Oh! All right, mix your muck with mine. Mix it! Mix your rags with my tatters! Mix it all up. ..." -- Jean Genet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33383-what-gosta-he-said-to-himself-can-you-no-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 13:03:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Selma Lagerlöf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33383-what-gosta-he-said-to-himself-can-you-no-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What Gosta,' he said to himself, 'can you no longer endure? You have been hardened in poverty all of your life; you have heard every tree in the forest, every tuft in the meadows preach to you of sacrifice and patience. You, brought up in a country where the winter is severe, and the summer joy is very short, have you forgotten the art of bearing your trials? 
     'Oh Gosta, a man must bear all that life gives him with a courageous heart and a smile on his lips, else he is no man. Sorrow as much as you will. If you love your beloved, let your conscience burn and chafe within you, but show yourself a man and a Varmlander. Let your glances beam with joy, and meet your friends with a gay word on your lips! Life and nature are hard. They bring forth courage and joy as a counterweight against their own hardness, or no one could endure them..." -- Selma Lagerlöf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39962-how-i-have-tried-and-tried-to-be-a-splendid</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 00:10:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erin add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39962-how-i-have-tried-and-tried-to-be-a-splendid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How I have tried and tried to be a splendid woman, and how destiny has been against me!  ...I do not deserve my lot! ...O, the cruelty of putting me into this ill-conceived world! I was capable of much; but I have been injured and blighted and crushed by things beyond my control! O, how hard it is of Heaven to devise such tortures for me, who have done no harm to heaven at all!" -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
