<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/714431-roger]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/714431-roger" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:30:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66262-for-there-either-was-some-tristero-beyond-the-appearance-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:30:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66262-for-there-either-was-some-tristero-beyond-the-appearance-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For there either was some Tristero beyond the appearance of the legacy America, or there was just America, and if there was just America then it seemed the only way she could continue, and manage to be at all relevant to it, was as an alien, unfurrowed, assumed full circle into some paranoia." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:31:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41336-such-a-captive-maiden-having-plenty-of-time-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such a captive maiden, having plenty of time to think, soon realizes that her tower, its height and architecture, are like her ego only incidental: that what really keeps her where she is is magic, anonymous and malignant, visited on her from outside and for no reason at all. Having no apparatus except gut fear and female cunning to examine this formless magic, to understand how it works, how to measure its field strength, count its lines of force, she may fall back on superstition, or take up a useful hobby like embroidery, or go mad, or marry a disk jockey. If the tower is everywhere and the knight of deliverance no proof against its magic, what else?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66264-a-wild-angel-had-appeared-to-him-the-angel-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66264-a-wild-angel-had-appeared-to-him-the-angel-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wild angel had appeared to him, the angel of mortal youth and beauty, an envoy from the fair courts of life, to throw open before him in an instant of ecstasy the gates of all the ways of error and glory." -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35760-an-event-may-be-small-and-insignificant-in-its-origin</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:37:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Bruno Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35760-an-event-may-be-small-and-insignificant-in-its-origin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An event may be small and insignificant in its origin , and yet, when drawn close to one’s eye, it may open in its center an infinite and radiant perspective because a higher order of being is trying to express itself in it and irradiates it violently." -- Bruno Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14145-can-you-understand-asked-my-father-the-deep-meaning-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 17:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Bruno Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14145-can-you-understand-asked-my-father-the-deep-meaning-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can you understand,' asked my father, 'the deep meaning of that weakness, that passion for colored tissue, for papier-mache, for distemper, for oakum and sawdust? This is,' he continued with a pained smile, 'the proof of our love for matter as such, for its fluffiness or porosity, for its unique mystical consistency. Demiurge, that great master and artist, made matter invisible, made it disappear under the surface of life. We, on the contrary, love its creaking, its resistance, its clumsiness. We like to see behind each gesture, behind each move, its inertia, its heavy effort, its bearlike awkwardness." -- Bruno Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68736-did-i-say-that-the-world-had-never-had-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 15:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68736-did-i-say-that-the-world-had-never-had-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did I say that the world had never had better color? I left something out of account, a limping, crippled consideration which seems to lose ground as you reach beauty and Orizaba flowers, but soon you find it has preceded you." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93974-but-it-is-a-curve-each-of-them-feels-unmistakably</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2008 18:46:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Roger add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93974-but-it-is-a-curve-each-of-them-feels-unmistakably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it is a curve each of them feels, unmistakably. It is the parabola. They must have guessed, once or twice -- guessed and refused to believe -- that everything, always, collectively, had been moving toward that purified shape latent in the sky, that shape of no surprise, no second chance, no return. Yet they do move forever under it, reserved for its own black-and-white bad news certainly as if it were the rainbow, and they its children. . . ." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
