<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/71608-saira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/71608-saira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 12:06:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632649-to-grow-up-steeped-in-these-tellings-was-to-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 12:06:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[saira add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632649-to-grow-up-steeped-in-these-tellings-was-to-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To grow up steeped in these tellings was to learn two unforgettable lessons: first, that stories were not true (there were no &quot;real&quot; genies in bottles or flying carpets or wonderful lamps), but by being untrue they could make him feel and know truths that the truth could not tell him, and second, that they all belonged to him, just as they belonged to his father, Anis, and to everyone else, they were all his, as they were hsi father's, bright stories and dark stories, sacred stories and profane, his to alter and renew and discard and pick up again as and when he pleased, his to laugh at and rejoice in and live in and with and by, to give the stories life by loving them and to be given life in return. Man was the storytelling animal, the only creature on earth that told itself stories to understand what kind of creature it was. The story was his birthright, and nobody could take it away." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524581-when-trying-to-find-the-words-to-tell-her-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 15:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[saira add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524581-when-trying-to-find-the-words-to-tell-her-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When trying to find the words to tell her how much I loved her, I stumbled across the ingredients for grilled cheese sandwiches. That’s when I realized she was the melted cheese to my toast. And the guy she’s currently seeing, the guy she left me for, well, I guess he is the tomato soup. " -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
