<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716774-zoe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716774-zoe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 12:11:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2008 12:11:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoe add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["April is the cruelest month, T.S. Eliot wrote, by which I think he meant (among other things) that springtime makes people crazy. We expect too much, the world burgeons with promises it can't keep, all passion is really a setup, and we're doomed to get our hearts broken yet again. I agree, and would further add: Who cares? Every spring I go out there anyway, around the bend, unconditionally. ... Come the end of the dark days, I am more than joyful. I'm nuts. " -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64208-64-surprising-and-distressing-things-while-one-is-cleaning</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 12:19:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoe add a quote by Sei Shonagon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64208-64-surprising-and-distressing-things-while-one-is-cleaning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  64. Surprising and Distressing Things
  While one is cleaning a decorative comb, something catches in the teeth and the comb breaks.
  A carriage overturns. One would have imagined that such a solid, bulky object would remain forever on its wheels. It all seems like a dream -- astonishing and senseless.
  A child or grown-up blurts out something that is bound to make people uncomfortable.
  All night long one has been waiting for a man who one thought was sure to arrive. At dawn, just when one has forgotten about him for a moment and dozed off, a crow caws loudly. One wakes up with a start and sees that it is daytime -- most astonishing.
  One of the bowmen in an archery contest stands trembling for a long time before shooting; when finally he does release his arrow, it goes in the wrong direction." -- Sei Shonagon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64211-134-letters-are-commonplace-letters-are-commonplace-enough-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2008 12:23:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoe add a quote by Sei Shonagon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64211-134-letters-are-commonplace-letters-are-commonplace-enough-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  134. Letters are Commonplace
  Letters are commonplace enough, yet what splendid things they are! When someone is in a distant province and one is worried about him, and then a letter suddenly arrives, one feels as though one were seeing him face to face. Again, it is a great comfort to have expressed one's feelings in a letter even though one knows it cannot yet have arrived. If letters did not exist, what dark depressions would come over one! When one has been worrying about something and wants to tell a certain person about it, what a relief it is to put it all down in a letter! Still greater is one's joy when a reply arrives. At that moment a letter really seems like an elixir of life." -- Sei Shonagon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121015-new-england-with-its-humid-continental-climate-its-cool-short</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 01:32:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zoe add a quote by Loyal Durand, Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121015-new-england-with-its-humid-continental-climate-its-cool-short]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New England, with its Humid Continental climate, its cool, short summers and stony, glaciated crystalline land...." -- Loyal Durand, Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
