<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716894-alex]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716894-alex" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:46:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 17:46:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1323-here-s-what-i-think-mr-wind-up-bird-said-may-kasahara]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's what I think, Mr. Wind-Up Bird,&quot; said May Kasahara. &quot;Everybody's born with some different thing at the core of their existence. And that thing, whatever it is, becomes like a heat source that runs each person from the inside. I have one too, of course. Like everybody else. But sometimes it gets out of hand. It swells or shrinks inside me, and it shakes me up. What I'd really like to do is find a way to communicate that feeling to another person. But I can't seem to do it. They just don't get it. Of course, the problem could be that I'm not explaining it very well, but I think it's because they're not listening very well. They pretend to be listening, but they're not, really. So I get worked up sometimes, and I do some crazy things." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2543-i-believe-in-looking-reality-straight-in-the-eye-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 07:12:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2543-i-believe-in-looking-reality-straight-in-the-eye-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in looking reality straight in the eye and denying it. " -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6696-you-get-old-and-you-realize-there-are-no-answers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 07:12:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6696-you-get-old-and-you-realize-there-are-no-answers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get old and you realize there are no answers, just stories." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195849-i-can-see-how-i-could-write-a-bold-account</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 19:04:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195849-i-can-see-how-i-could-write-a-bold-account]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can see how I could write a bold account of myself as a passionate man who rose from humble beginnings to cut a wide swath in the world, whose crimes along the way might be written off to extravagance and love and art, and could even almost believe some of it myself on certain days after the sun went down if I’d had a snort or two and was in Los Angeles and it was February and I was twenty-four, but I find a truer account in the Herald-Star, where it says: “Mr. Gary Keillor visited at the home of Al and Florence Crandall on Monday and after lunch returned to St. Paul, where he is currently employed in the radio show business… Lunch was fried chicken with gravy and creamed peas”." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
