<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716985-george]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/716985-george" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:56:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35767-we-have-as-human-beings-a-storytelling-problem-we-re-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35767-we-have-as-human-beings-a-storytelling-problem-we-re-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have, as human beings, a storytelling problem. We're a bit too quick to come up with explanations for things we don't really have an explanation for." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1799-the-world-as-we-have-created-it-is-a-process</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 07:22:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1799-the-world-as-we-have-created-it-is-a-process]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world as we have created it is a process of our thinking. It cannot be changed without changing our thinking." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 14:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10046-there-did-not-have-to-be-a-moral-she-need]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There did not have to be a moral. She need only show separate minds, as alive as her own, struggling with the idea that other minds were equally alive. It wasn't only wickedness and scheming that made people unhappy, it was confusion and misunderstanding, above all, it was the failure to grasp the simple truth that other people are as real as you. And only in a story could you enter these different minds and show how they had an equal value. That was the only moral a story need have." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851-american-men-are-allotted-just-as-many-tears-as-american</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851-american-men-are-allotted-just-as-many-tears-as-american]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["American men are allotted just as many tears as American women. But because we are forbidden to shed them, we die long before women do, with our hearts exploding or our blood pressure rising or our livers eaten away by alcohol because that lake of grief inside us has no outlet. We, men, die because our faces were not watered enough." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12733-he-stepped-down-trying-not-to-look-long-at-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 13:22:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12733-he-stepped-down-trying-not-to-look-long-at-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He stepped down, trying not to look long at her, as if she were the sun, yet he saw her, like the sun, even without looking." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13100-genuine-love-is-volitional-rather-than-emotional-the-person-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 13:36:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by M. Scott Peck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13100-genuine-love-is-volitional-rather-than-emotional-the-person-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genuine love is volitional rather than emotional. The person who truely loves does so because of a decision to love. This person has made a commitment to be loving whether or not the loving feeling is present. ...Conversely, it is not only possible but necessary for a loving person to avoid acting on feelings of love." -- M. Scott Peck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17226-i-will-take-you-down-my-own-avenue-of-remembrance</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 04:46:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17226-i-will-take-you-down-my-own-avenue-of-remembrance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will take you down my own avenue of remembrance, which winds among the hazards and shadows of my single year as a plebe. I cannot come to this story in full voice. I want to speak for the boys who were violated by this school, the ones who left ashamed and broken and dishonored, who departed from the Institute with wounds and bitter grievances. I want also to speak for the triumphant boys who took everything the system could throw at them, endured every torment and excess, and survived the ordeal of the freshman year with a feeling of transformation and achievement that they never had felt before and would never know again with such clarity and elation.
 
   I will speak from my memory- my memory- a memory that is all refracting light slanting through prisms and dreams, a shifting, troubled riot of electrons charged with pain and wonder. My memory often seems like a city of exiled poets afire with the astonishment of language, each believing in the integrity of his own witness, each with a separate version of culture and history, and the divine essentional fire that is poetry itself.
 
   But i will try to isolate that one lonely singer who gathered the fragments of my plebe year and set the screams to music. For many years, I have refused to listen as his obsessive voice narrated the malignant litany of crimes against my boyhood. We isolate those poets who cause us the greatest pain; we silence them in any way we can. I have never allowed this furious dissident the courtesy of my full attention. His poems are songs for the dead to  me. Something dies in me every time I hear his low, courageous voice calling to me from the solitude of his exile. He has always known that someday I would have to listen to his story, that I would have to deal with the truth or falsity of his witness. He has always known that someday I must take full responsibility for his creation and that, in finally listening to him, I would be sounding the darkest fathoms of myself. I will write his stories now as he shouts them to me. I will listen to him and listen to myself. I will get it all down.
 
   Yet the laws of recall are subject to distortion and alienation. Memory is a trick, and I have lied so often to myself about my own role and the role of others that I am not sure I can recognize the truth about those days. But I have come to believe in the unconscious integrity of lies. I want to record even them. Somewhere in the immensity of the lie the truth gleams like the pure, light-glazed bones of an extinct angel. Hidden in the enormous falsity of my story is the truth for all of us who began at the Institute in 1963, and for all who survived to become her sons. I write my own truth, in my own time, in my own way, and take full responsibility for its mistakes and slanders. Even the lies are part of my truth.
 
   I return to the city of memory, to the city of exiled poets. I approach the one whose back is turned to me. He is frail and timorous and angry. His head is shaved and he fears the judgment of regiments. He will always be a victim, always a plebe. I tap him on the shoulder.
   &quot;Begin,&quot; I command.
   &quot;It was the beginning of 1963,&quot; he begins, and I know he will not stop until the story has ended." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22269-human-beings-are-poor-examiners-subject-to-superstition-bias-prejudice</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 19:01:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by M. Scott Peck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22269-human-beings-are-poor-examiners-subject-to-superstition-bias-prejudice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings are poor examiners, subject to superstition, bias, prejudice, and a PROFOUND tendency to see what they want to see rather than what is really there." -- M. Scott Peck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 03:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846-for-you-a-thousand-times-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 15:07:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846-for-you-a-thousand-times-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For you, a thousand times over" -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 17:48:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 15:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233-i-don-t-know-half-of-you-half-as-well-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know half of you half as well as I should like; and I like less than half of you half as well as you deserve." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 15:13:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1337-faithless-is-he-that-says-farewell-when-the-road-darkens</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 15:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1337-faithless-is-he-that-says-farewell-when-the-road-darkens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faithless is he that says farewell when the road darkens." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2008 18:10:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9529-it-may-be-unfair-but-what-happens-in-a-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be unfair, but what happens in a few days, sometimes even a single day, can change the course of a whole lifetime..." -- Khaled Hosseini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9555-inside-us-there-is-something-that-has-no-name-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9555-inside-us-there-is-something-that-has-no-name-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inside us there is something that has no name, that something is what we are." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 18:10:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147677-on-the-surface-an-intelligible-lie-underneath-the-unintelligible-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147677-on-the-surface-an-intelligible-lie-underneath-the-unintelligible-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the surface, an intelligible lie; underneath, the unintelligible truth." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35646-but-what-are-our-stories-if-not-the-mirrors-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35646-but-what-are-our-stories-if-not-the-mirrors-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what are our stories if not the mirrors we hold up to our fears?" -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35647----that-books-were-mirrors-reflective-in-sometimes-unpredictable-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35647----that-books-were-mirrors-reflective-in-sometimes-unpredictable-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["-- that books were mirrors, reflective in sometimes unpredictable ways." -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25052-that-was-the-big-joke-wasn-t-it-the-answer-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25052-that-was-the-big-joke-wasn-t-it-the-answer-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was the big joke, wasn't it? The answer to the riddle: There was no one up there in Heaven, making sure the accounts came out right. I'd solved it, hadn't I? Cracked the code? It was all just a joke. The god inside my brother's head was just his disease. My mother had knelt every night and prayed to her own steepled hands. Your baby died because of ... because of no particular reason at all. Your wife left you because you sucked all the oxygen out of the room, so you pretended she was the one in bed with you while you screwed your girlfriend and her boyfriend hid in the closet, watching." -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4725-have-courage-for-the-great-sorrows-of-life-and-patience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4725-have-courage-for-the-great-sorrows-of-life-and-patience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have courage for the great sorrows of life and patience for the small ones; and when you have laboriously accomplished your daily task, go to sleep in peace. God is awake." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4226-no-man-really-knows-about-other-human-beings-the-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:54:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4226-no-man-really-knows-about-other-human-beings-the-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man really knows about other human beings. The best he can do is to suppose that they are like himself." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120721-feelings-like-disappointment-embarrassment-irritation-resentment-anger-jealousy-and-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…feelings like disappointment, embarrassment, irritation, resentment, anger, jealousy, and fear, instead of being bad news, are actually very clear moments that teach us where it is that we’re holding back. They teach us to perk up and lean in when we feel we’d rather collapse and back away. They’re like messengers that show us, with terrifying clarity, exactly where we’re stuck. This very moment is the perfect teacher, and, lucky for us, it’s with us wherever we are." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43053-the-fact-that-we-often-judge-the-pleasure-of-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Daniel Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43053-the-fact-that-we-often-judge-the-pleasure-of-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that we often judge the pleasure of an experience by its ending can cause us to make some curious choices." -- Daniel Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34844-my-friends-tell-me-that-i-have-a-tendency-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Daniel Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34844-my-friends-tell-me-that-i-have-a-tendency-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My friends tell me that I have a tendency to point out problems without offering solutions, but they never tell me what I should do about it." -- Daniel Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44666-you-forget-what-you-want-to-remember-and-you-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2009 12:44:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[George add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44666-you-forget-what-you-want-to-remember-and-you-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You forget what you want to remember, and you remember what you want to forget." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
