<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/717125-wawa-lie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/717125-wawa-lie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 16:52:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7523-but-that-s-the-glory-of-foreign-travel-as-far-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 16:52:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[wawa add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7523-but-that-s-the-glory-of-foreign-travel-as-far-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But that's the glory of foreign travel, as far as I am concerned. I don't want to know what people are talking about. I can't think of anything that excites a greater sense of childlike wonder than to be in a country where you are ignorant of almost everything. Suddenly you are five years old again. You can't read anything, you have only the most rudimentary sense of how things work, you can't even reliably cross a street without endangering your life. Your whole existence becomes a series of interesting guesses." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802093-success-demands-singleness-of-purpose-you-need-to-be-doing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 08:48:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[wawa add a quote by Gary Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/802093-success-demands-singleness-of-purpose-you-need-to-be-doing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success demands singleness of purpose.

You need to be doing fewer things for more effect instead of doing more things with side effects.

It is those who concentrate on but one thing at a time who advance in this world.

Passion for something leads to disproportionate time practicing or working at it. That time spent eventually translates to skill, and when skill improves, results improve. Better results generally lead to more enjoyment, and more passion and more time is invested. It can be a virtuous cycle all the way to extraordinary results.

The ONE Thing shows up time and again in the lives of the successful because it’s a fundamental truth.

More than anything else, expertise tracks with hours invested.

The pursuit of mastery bears gifts.

When people look back on their lives, it is the things they have not done that generate the greatest regret...People’s actions may be troublesome initially; it is their inactions that plague them most with long-term feelings of regret.

Make sure every day you do what matters most. When you know what matters most, everything makes sense. When you don’t know what matters most, anything makes sense." -- Gary Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
