<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718165-adam-carter]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718165-adam-carter" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:48:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21346-naturally-society-cherished-itself-alone-it-prized-what-everyone-agreed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:48:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21346-naturally-society-cherished-itself-alone-it-prized-what-everyone-agreed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Naturally society cherished itself alone; it prized what everyone agreed was precious, despised what everyone agreed was despicable, and ignored what no one mentioned-all to it's own enhancement, and with the loud view that these bubbles and vapors were eternal and universal. If June had stressed to Mabel that she was going to die, would she have learned to eat with a fork? Society's loyal members, having sacrificed their only lives to it's caprices, hastened to entrap the next generation into agreement, so their follies would not have been in vain and they could all go down together, blind and well turned out. The company, the club, and the party had offered him a position like bait, and he bit. He had embedded himself in the company like a man bricked into a wall, and whirled with the building's maps, files, and desks,senselessly, as the planet spun and death pooled on the cold basement floors. Who could blame him?- when people have always lived so. Now , however, he saw the city lifted away, and the bricks and files vaporized; he saw the preenings of men laid low, and the comforts of family scattered. He was free and loosed on the black beach." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21304-wild-geese-fly-south-creaking-like-anguished-hinges-along-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:42:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21304-wild-geese-fly-south-creaking-like-anguished-hinges-along-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wild geese fly south, creaking like anguished hinges; along the riverbank the candles of the sumacs burn dull red.  It's the first week of October.  Season of woolen garments taken out of mothballs; of nocturnal mists and dew and slippery front steps, and late-blooming slugs; of snapdragons having one last fling; of those frilly ornamental pink-and-purple cabbages that never used to exist, but are all over everywhere now." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21315-it-does-not-pay-to-cherish-symbols-when-the-substance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:48:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21315-it-does-not-pay-to-cherish-symbols-when-the-substance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not pay to cherish symbols when the substance lies so close at hand." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21287-love-makes-you-see-a-place-differently-just-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 14:19:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Anne Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21287-love-makes-you-see-a-place-differently-just-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love makes you see a place differently, just as you hold differently an object that belongs to someone you love.  If you know one landscape well, you will look at all other landscapes differently.  And if you learn to love one place, sometimes you can also learn to love another." -- Anne Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21321-thanks-to-impermanence-everything-is-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21321-thanks-to-impermanence-everything-is-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks to impermanence, everything is possible." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21288-when-we-say-we-re-looking-for-a-spiritual-adviser-we-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 14:22:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Anne Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21288-when-we-say-we-re-looking-for-a-spiritual-adviser-we-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...when we say we're looking for a spiritual adviser, we're really looking for someone to tell us what to do with our bodies.  Decisions of the flesh.  We forget to learn from pleasure as well as pain." -- Anne Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21294-and-then-everything-went-on-very-quietly-for-a-fortnight</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 14:38:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21294-and-then-everything-went-on-very-quietly-for-a-fortnight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then everything went on very quietly for a fortnight, says Dr. Jordan. He is reading aloud from my confession.
Yes Sir, it did, I say. More or less quietly.
What is everything? How did it go on?
I beg your pardon, Sir?
What did you do everyday?
Oh, the usual, Sir, I say. I performed my duties.
You will forgive me, says Dr. Jordan. Of what did those duties consist?
I look at him. He is wearing a yellow cravat with small white squares, he is not making a joke. He really does not know. Men such as him do not have to clean up the messes they make, but we have to clean up our own messes, and theirs into the bargain. In that way they are like children, they do not have to think ahead, or worry about the consequences of what they do. But it's not their fault, it is only how they are brought up." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21311-i-see-that-the-life-of-this-place-is-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:02:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21311-i-see-that-the-life-of-this-place-is-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see that the life of this place is always emerging beyond expectation or prediction or typicality, that it is unique, given to the world minute by minute, only once, never to be repeated. And this is when I see that this life is a miracle, absolutely worth having, absolutely worth saving.  We are alive within mystery, by miracle." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21313-no-one-who-has-ever-lived-through-the-unmasking-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:04:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Joan Timmerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21313-no-one-who-has-ever-lived-through-the-unmasking-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...no one who has ever lived through the unmasking of one ideology, taken uncritically as the truth about human life, will be quite as vulnerable to the absolutizing of another.

-Sexuality and Spiritual Growth" -- Joan Timmerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21319-my-humanity-includes-not-just-what-i-am-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:09:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Joan Timmerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21319-my-humanity-includes-not-just-what-i-am-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My humanity includes not just what I am at the present moment, but what I can be.  I am also my future,  To exclude the potential from the real, and identify the real only with what is already actualized is another form of reductionism.
-Sexuality and Spiritual Growth" -- Joan Timmerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21320-the-sense-of-adventure-and-curiosity-to-see-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:14:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Joan Timmerman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21320-the-sense-of-adventure-and-curiosity-to-see-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sense of adventure and curiosity to see what the future holds is the other side of serenity.  It, too, is a spiritual state most attractive in people in transition, whether entering adulthood or preparing for death.
-Sexuality and Spiritual Growth" -- Joan Timmerman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21333-there-are-times-when-personal-experience-keeps-us-from-reaching</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:50:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21333-there-are-times-when-personal-experience-keeps-us-from-reaching]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are times when personal experience keeps us from reaching the mountain top and so we let it go because the weight of it is too heavy.  And sometimes the mountain top is difficult to reach with all our resources, factual and confessional, so we are just there, collectively grasping, feeling the limitations of knowledge, longing together, yearning for a way to reach that highest point.  Even this yearning is a way to know." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21343-i-think-people-are-very-brave-and-often-are-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Brenda Peterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21343-i-think-people-are-very-brave-and-often-are-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think people are very brave and often are a lot more frightened than they're allowed to admit.  Life is much harder to live for most people than we want to admit.  And so many things take a summoning up of courage.  It makes one's own life a little bit easier when you can acknowledge that.
-Ursula LeGuin, interviewed by" -- Brenda Peterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21338-in-a-culture-where-profit-has-become-the-true-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Starhawk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21338-in-a-culture-where-profit-has-become-the-true-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a culture where profit has become the true God, self-sacrifice can seem incomprehensible rather than noble." -- Starhawk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21280-nihilism-is-a-natural-consequence-of-a-culture-or-civilization</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:46:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21280-nihilism-is-a-natural-consequence-of-a-culture-or-civilization]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nihilism is a natural consequence of a culture (or civilization) ruled and regulated by categories that mask manipulation, mastery and domination of peoples and nature." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21283-prophetic-pragmatism-attempts-to-keep-alive-the-sense-of-alternative</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:46:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21283-prophetic-pragmatism-attempts-to-keep-alive-the-sense-of-alternative]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prophetic pragmatism attempts to keep alive the sense of alternative ways of life and of struggle based on the best of the past.  In this sense, the praxis of prophetic pragmatism is tragic action with revolutionary intent, usually reformist consequences and always visionary outlook." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21284-if-you-suffer-and-make-your-loved-ones-suffer-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:46:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21284-if-you-suffer-and-make-your-loved-ones-suffer-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you suffer and make your loved ones suffer, there is nothing that can justify your desire." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21305-it-is-impossible-to-prefigure-the-salvation-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:46:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21305-it-is-impossible-to-prefigure-the-salvation-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is impossible to prefigure the salvation of the world in the same language by which the world has been dismembered and defaced." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21282-in-a-time-in-which-communist-regimes-have-been-rightfully</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 09:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adam add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21282-in-a-time-in-which-communist-regimes-have-been-rightfully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a time in which Communist regimes have been rightfully discredited and yet alternatives to neoliberal capitalist societies are unwisely dismissed, I defend the fundamental claim of Marxist theory: there must be countervailing forces that defend people's needs against the brutality of profit driven capitalism." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
