<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718298-david]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718298-david" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 07:14:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3388-love-is-a-snowmobile-racing-across-the-tundra-and-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 07:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Matt Groening]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3388-love-is-a-snowmobile-racing-across-the-tundra-and-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a snowmobile racing across the tundra and then suddenly it flips over, pinning you underneath. At night, the ice weasels come." -- Matt Groening]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 08:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is indeed full of peril, and in it there are many dark places; but still there is much that is fair, and though in all lands love is now mingled with grief, it grows perhaps the greater." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14627-war-must-be-while-we-defend-our-lives-against-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 08:20:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14627-war-must-be-while-we-defend-our-lives-against-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War must be, while we defend our lives against a destroyer who would devour all; but I do not love the bright sword for its sharpness, nor the arrow for its swiftness, nor the warrior for his glory. I love only that which they defend." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138526-a-small-but-noteworthy-note-i-ve-seen-so-many-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 12:52:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138526-a-small-but-noteworthy-note-i-ve-seen-so-many-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A small but noteworthy note. I've seen so many young men over the years who think they're running at other young men. They are not. They are running at me." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30540-i-don-t-care-what-is-written-meyer-landsman-says-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 09:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30540-i-don-t-care-what-is-written-meyer-landsman-says-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't care what is written,&quot; Meyer Landsman says. &quot;I don't care what supposedly got promised to some sandal-wearing idiot whose claim to fame is that he was ready to cut his own son's throat for the sake of a hare-brained idea. I don't care about red heifers and patriarchs and locusts. A bunch of old bones in the sand. My homeland is in my hat. It's in my ex-wife's tote bag." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14439-a-book-is-more-than-the-sum-of-its-materials</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 10:10:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14439-a-book-is-more-than-the-sum-of-its-materials]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is more than the sum of its materials. It is an artifact of the human mind and hand." -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143582-to-know-a-man-s-library-is-in-some-measure-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 10:10:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143582-to-know-a-man-s-library-is-in-some-measure-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know a man's library is, in some measure, to know a man's mind." -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237148-a-man-who-has-been-dead-for-a-week-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 06:07:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237148-a-man-who-has-been-dead-for-a-week-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who has been dead for a week in a hot trailer looks more like a man than you would first expect." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132162-there-are-certain-children-who-are-told-they-are-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 06:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Lynda Barry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132162-there-are-certain-children-who-are-told-they-are-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are certain children who are told they are too sensitive, and there are certain adults who believe sensitivity is a problem that can be fixed in the way that crooked teeth can be fixed and made straight. And when these two come together you get a fairytale, a kind of story with hopelessness in it.

I believe there is something in these old stories that does what singing does to words. They have transformational capabilities, in the way melody can transform mood.

They can't transform your actual situation, but they can transform your experience of it. We don't create a fantasy world to escape reality, we create it to be able to stay. I believe we have always done this, used images to stand and understand what otherwise would be intolerable." -- Lynda Barry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 07:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16072-the-unreal-is-more-powerful-than-the-real-because-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unreal is more powerful than the real. Because nothing is as perfect as you can imagine it. Because its only intangible ideas, concepts, beliefs, fantasies that last. Stone crumbles. Wood rots. People, well, they die. But things as fragile as a thought, a dream, a legend, they can go on and on. If you can change the way people think. The way they see themselves. The way they see the world. You can change the way people live their lives. That's the only lasting thing you can create." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 07:08:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111013-the-arc-of-the-moral-universe-is-long-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 05:53:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111013-the-arc-of-the-moral-universe-is-long-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The arc of the moral universe is long, but it bends towards justice." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675767-i-know-the-goliath-fucking-bird-eating-spider-can-t-fly-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 17:09:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Wong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675767-i-know-the-goliath-fucking-bird-eating-spider-can-t-fly-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know the Goliath Fucking Bird-Eating Spider can't fly because if it could, it would have a different name entirely. We would call it &quot;sir&quot; because it would be the dominant species on the planet. None of us would leave the house unless a Goliath Fucking Bird-Eating Spider said it was okay" -- David Wong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432353-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 14:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432353-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until a man is twenty-five, he still thinks, every so often, that under the right circumstances he could be the baddest motherfucker in the world. If I moved to a martial-arts monastery in China and studied real hard for ten years. If my family was wiped out by Colombian drug dealers and I swore myself to revenge. If I got a fatal disease, had one year to live, and devoted it to wiping out street crime. If I just dropped out and devoted my life to being bad.

Hiro used to feel this way, too, but then he ran into Raven. In a way, this was liberating. He no longer has to worry about being the baddest motherfucker in the world. The position is taken." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
