<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718427-luke]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/718427-luke" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 06:46:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162557-it-comes-from-a-very-ancient-democracy-you-see-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2012 06:46:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luke add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162557-it-comes-from-a-very-ancient-democracy-you-see-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It comes from a very ancient democracy, you see...&quot;
&quot;You mean, it comes from a world of lizards?&quot;
&quot;No,&quot; said Ford, who by this time was a little more rational and coherent than he had been, having finally had the coffee forced down him, &quot;nothing so simple. Nothing anything like so straightforward. On its world, the people are people. The leaders are lizards. The people hate the lizards and the lizards rule the people.&quot;
&quot;Odd,&quot; said Arthur, &quot;I thought you said it was a democracy.&quot;
&quot;I did,&quot; said Ford. &quot;It is.&quot;
&quot;So,&quot; said Arthur, hoping he wasn't sounding ridiculously obtuse, &quot;why don't people get rid of the lizards?&quot;
&quot;It honestly doesn't occur to them,&quot; said Ford. &quot;They've all got the vote, so they all pretty much assume that the government they've voted in more or less approximates to the government they want.&quot;
&quot;You mean they actually vote for the lizards?&quot;
&quot;Oh yes,&quot; said Ford with a shrug, &quot;of course.&quot;
&quot;But,&quot; said Arthur, going for the big one again, &quot;why?&quot;
&quot;Because if they didn't vote for a lizard,&quot; said Ford, &quot;the wrong lizard might get in. Got any gin?&quot;
&quot;What?&quot;
&quot;I said,&quot; said Ford, with an increasing air of urgency creeping into his voice, &quot;have you got any gin?&quot;
&quot;I'll look. Tell me about the lizards.&quot;
Ford shrugged again.
&quot;Some people say that the lizards are the best thing that ever happenned to them,&quot; he said. &quot;They're completely wrong of course, completely and utterly wrong, but someone's got to say it.&quot;
&quot;But that's terrible,&quot; said Arthur.
&quot;Listen, bud,&quot; said Ford, &quot;if I had one Altairian dollar for every time I heard one bit of the Universe look at another bit of the Universe and say 'That's terrible' I wouldn't be sitting here like a lemon looking for a gin." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
