<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/71852-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/71852-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 12:31:53 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 12:31:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41534-one-word-ma-am-he-said-coming-back-from-the-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 12:32:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41534-one-word-ma-am-he-said-coming-back-from-the-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One word, Ma'am,&quot; he said, coming back from the fire; limping, because of the pain. &quot;One word. All you've been saying is quite right, I shouldn't wonder. I'm a chap who always liked to know the worst and then put the best face I can on it. So I won't deny any of what you said. But there's one more thing to be said, even so. Suppose we have only dreamed, or made up, all those things-trees and grass and sun and moon and stars and Aslan himself. Suppose we have. Then all I can say is that, in that case, the made-up things seem a good deal more important than the real ones. Suppose this black pit of a kingdom of yours is the only world. Well, it strikes me as a pretty poor one. And that's a funny thing, when you come to think of it. We're just babies making up a game, if you're right. But four babies playing a game can make a play-world which licks your real world hollow. That's why I'm going to stand by the play world. I'm on Aslan's side even if there isn't any Aslan to lead it. I'm going to live as like a Narnian as I can even if there isn't any Narnia. So, thanking you kindly for our supper, if these two gentlemen and the young lady are ready, we're leaving your court at once and setting out in the dark to spend our lives looking for Overland. Not that our lives will be very long, I should think; but that's a small loss if the world's as dull a place as you say." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12070-finally-from-so-little-sleeping-and-so-much-reading-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 13:11:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12070-finally-from-so-little-sleeping-and-so-much-reading-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finally, from so little sleeping and so much reading, his brain dried up and he went completely out of his mind." -- Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49720-to-love-another-person-is-to-see-the-face-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 13:36:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49720-to-love-another-person-is-to-see-the-face-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love another person is to see the face of God." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
