<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/720974-tyagita-silka]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/720974-tyagita-silka" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:05:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He dug so deeply into her sentiments that in search of interest he found love, because by trying to make her love him he ended up falling in love with her. Petra Cotes, for her part, loved him more and more as she felt his love increasing, and that was how in the ripeness of autumn she began to believe once more in the youthful superstition that poverty was the servitude of love. Both looked back then on the wild revelry, the gaudy wealth, and the unbridled fornication as an annoyance and they lamented that it had cost them so much of their lives to find the paradise of shared solitude. Madly in love after so many years of sterile complicity, they enjoyed the miracle of living each other as much at the table as in bed, and they grew to be so happy that even when they were two worn-out people they kept on blooming like little children and playing together like dogs." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14410-it-was-inevitable-the-scent-of-bitter-almonds-always-reminded</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14410-it-was-inevitable-the-scent-of-bitter-almonds-always-reminded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was inevitable: the scent of bitter almonds always reminded him of the fate of unrequited love." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:05:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To him she seemed so beautiful, so seductive, so different from ordinary people, that he could not understand why no one was as disturbed as he by the clicking of her heels on the paving stones, why no one else's heart was wild with the breeze stirred by the sighs of her veils, why everyone did not go mad with the movements of her braid, the flight of her hands, the gold of her laughter. He had not missed a single one of her gestures, not one of the indications of her character, but he did not dare approach her for fear of destroying the spell." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25531-the-problem-with-marriage-is-that-it-ends-every-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:05:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25531-the-problem-with-marriage-is-that-it-ends-every-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with marriage is that it ends every night after making love, and it must be rebuilt every morning before breakfast." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59656-and-the-air-was-full-of-thoughts-and-things-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:10:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59656-and-the-air-was-full-of-thoughts-and-things-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the air was full of Thoughts and Things to Say.  But at times like these, only the Small Things are ever said.  Big Things lurk unsaid inside." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25704-being-with-him-made-her-feel-as-though-her-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:10:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25704-being-with-him-made-her-feel-as-though-her-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being with him made her feel as though her soul had escaped from the narrow confines of her island country into the vast, extravagant spaces of his. He made her feel as though the world belonged to them- as though it lay before them like an opened frog on a dissecting table, begging to be examined." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76443-it-is-after-all-so-easy-to-shatter-a-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:11:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76443-it-is-after-all-so-easy-to-shatter-a-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is after all so easy to shatter a story. To break a chain of thought. To ruin a fragment of a dream being carried around carefully like a piece of porcelain. To let it be, to travel with it, as Velutha did, is much the harder thing to do." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105306-as-estha-stirred-the-thick-jam-he-thought-two-thoughts</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 19:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105306-as-estha-stirred-the-thick-jam-he-thought-two-thoughts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As Estha stirred the thick jam he thought Two Thoughts and the Two Thoughts he thought were these:
a) Anything can happen to anyone.
and
b) It is best to be prepared." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2008-the-tears-of-the-world-are-a-constant-quantity-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 17:27:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2008-the-tears-of-the-world-are-a-constant-quantity-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tears of the world are a constant quantity. For each one who begins to weep somewhere else another stops. The same is true of the laugh." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108501-perhaps-it-s-true-that-things-can-change-in-a-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 17:42:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108501-perhaps-it-s-true-that-things-can-change-in-a-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps it's true that things can change in a day. That a few dozen hours can affect the outcome of whole lifetimes. And that when they do, those few dozen hours, like the salvaged remains of a burned house---the charred clock, the singed photograph, the scorched furniture---must be resurrected from the ruins and examined. Preserved. Accounted for. Little events, ordinary things, smashed and reconstitutred. Imbued with new meaning. Suddenly they become the bleached bones of a story." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125444-when-you-hurt-people-they-begin-to-love-you-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 17:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125444-when-you-hurt-people-they-begin-to-love-you-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you hurt people, they begin to love you less. That's what careless words do. They make people love you a little less." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 02:55:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the secret of the Great Stories is that they &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; no secrets. The Great Stories are the ones you have heard and want to hear again. The ones you can enter anywhere and inhabit comfortably. They don’t deceive you with thrills and trick endings. They don’t surprise you with the unforeseen. They are as familiar as the house you live in. Or the smell of your lover’s skin. You know how they end, yet you listen as though you don’t. In the way that although you know that one day you will die, you live as though you won’t. In the Great Stories you know who lives, who dies, who finds love, who doesn’t. And yet you want to know again.

&lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; is their mystery and their magic." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 02:58:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death must be so beautiful. To lie in the soft brown earth, with the grasses waving above one's head, and listen to silence. To have no yesterday, and no tomorrow. To forget time, to forgive life, to be at peace." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 02:58:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyagita Silka add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
