<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/721515-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/721515-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:15:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never get a cup of tea large enough or a book long enough to suit me." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:17:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51712-we-are-dwellers-in-a-divine-universe-where-no-desires</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:18:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51712-we-are-dwellers-in-a-divine-universe-where-no-desires]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are dwellers in a divine universe where no desires are in vain - if only they be large enough." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51716-those-scenes-of-solitude-from-which-the-hand-of-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:21:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Thomas Cole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51716-those-scenes-of-solitude-from-which-the-hand-of-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those scenes of solitude from which the hand of nature have never been lifted, affect the mind with a more deep-toned emotion than aught which the hand of man has touched. Amid them the consequent associations are of God the Creator, they are His undefiled works; and the mind is cast into contemplation of eternal things." -- Thomas Cole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:23:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51717-and-in-some-of-the-people-of-the-town-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and in some of the people of the town and community surrounding it, one of the characteristic diseases of the twentieth century was making its way: the suspicion that they would be greatly improved if they were somewhere else." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51719-we-are-all-of-us-imaginative-in-some-form-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:26:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51719-we-are-all-of-us-imaginative-in-some-form-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all of us imaginative in some form or other, for images are the brood of desire." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51720-a-rare-objectivity-and-insight-can-be-imparted-regarding-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:27:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Michael D. O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51720-a-rare-objectivity-and-insight-can-be-imparted-regarding-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A rare objectivity and insight can be imparted regarding this world's struggle for spiritual integrity. In the land of Faerie, the reader may see his small battles writ large in the wars of titans or elves and understand for the first time, his own worth." -- Michael D. O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51721-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 09:30:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51721-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The consolation of fairy stories, the joy of the happy ending; or more correctly, the good catastrophe, the sudden, joyous &quot;turn&quot; (for there is no true end to a fairy tale); this joy, which is one of the things that fairy stories can produce supremely well, is not essentially escapist or fugitive. In it's fairy tale or other world setting, it is a sudden and miraculous grace, never to be counted on to reoccur. It does not deny the existence of dyscatastrophe, or sorrow and failure, the possibility of these is necessary to the joy of deliverance. It denies, (in the face of much evidence if you will) universal final defeat and in so far is evangelium, giving a fleeting glimpse of Joy, Joy beyond the walls of the world, poignant as grief." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
