<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72188-pa-t-m]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72188-pa-t-m" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 10:29:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597949-one-extraordinary-thing-happened-as-a-result-of-the-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 10:29:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Graciela Limón]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/597949-one-extraordinary-thing-happened-as-a-result-of-the-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One extraordinary thing happened as a result of the fear caused by your people, and that was that old feuds and envies disappeared. Those among us who had been enemies for generations forgot their grudges and joined one another against the invasion." -- Graciela Limón]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29213-life-is-like-riding-a-bicycle-to-keep-your-balance</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 13:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29213-life-is-like-riding-a-bicycle-to-keep-your-balance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177996-liking-is-probably-the-best-form-of-ownership-and-ownership</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 11:03:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177996-liking-is-probably-the-best-form-of-ownership-and-ownership]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liking is probably the best form of ownership, and ownership the worst form of liking." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:25:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:26:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/362-if-you-don-t-stand-for-something-you-will-fall-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't stand for something you will fall for anything." -- Gordon A. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 14:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 08:51:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The covers of this book are too far apart." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22101-there-s-no-use-going-to-school-unless-your-final-destination</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 09:20:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22101-there-s-no-use-going-to-school-unless-your-final-destination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's no use going to school unless your final destination is the library." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157530-for-human-words-are-like-shadows-and-shadows-are-incapable</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 11:36:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157530-for-human-words-are-like-shadows-and-shadows-are-incapable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...for human words are like shadows, and shadows are incapable of explaining light and between shadow and light there is the opaque body from which words are born.." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24654-pero-quiero-encontrar-la-isla-desconocida-quiero-saber-quien-soy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 11:37:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24654-pero-quiero-encontrar-la-isla-desconocida-quiero-saber-quien-soy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["........pero quiero encontrar la isla desconocida, quiero saber quien soy you cuando este en ella. No lo sabes, Si no sales de ti, no llegas a saber quien eres....." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153645-my-feet-will-want-to-walk-to-where-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 09:53:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153645-my-feet-will-want-to-walk-to-where-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["my feet will want to walk to where you are sleeping
but
I shall go on living." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291122-donde-haya-un-rbol-que-plantar-pl-ntalo-t-donde-haya</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 11:23:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Gabriela Mistral]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291122-donde-haya-un-rbol-que-plantar-pl-ntalo-t-donde-haya]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Donde haya un árbol que plantar, plántalo tú. Donde haya un error que enmendar, enmiéndalo tú. Donde haya un esfuerzo que todos esquivan, hazlo tú. Sé tú el que aparta la piedra del camino." -- Gabriela Mistral]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173174-a-book-being-a-physical-object-engenders-a-certain-respect</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2010 10:30:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Mo Willems]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173174-a-book-being-a-physical-object-engenders-a-certain-respect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book, being a physical object, engenders a certain respect that zipping electrons cannot. Because you cannot turn a book off, because you have to hold it in your hands, because a book sits there, waiting for you, whether you think you want it or not, because of all these things, a book is a friend. It’s not just the content, but the physical being of a book that is there for you always and unconditionally." -- Mo Willems]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 11:41:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134645-lost-opportunities-lost-possibilities-feelings-we-can-never-get-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lost opportunities, lost possibilities, feelings we can never get back.  That's part of what it means to be alive.  But inside our heads - at least that's where I imagine it - there's a little room where we store those memories.  A room like the stacks in this library.  And to understand the workings of our own heart we have to keep on making new reference cards.  We have to dust things off every once in awhile, let in fresh air, change the water in the flower vases.  In other words, you'll live forever in your own private library." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101199-what-does-it-matter-how-cultivated-and-up-to-date-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 12:42:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Gabriel Zaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101199-what-does-it-matter-how-cultivated-and-up-to-date-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does it matter how cultivated and up-to-date we are, or how many thousands of books we’ve read? What matters is how we feel, how we see, what we do after reading; whether the street and the clouds and the existence of others mean anything to us; whether reading makes us, physically, more alive." -- Gabriel Zaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191224-y-para-qu-leer-y-para-qu-escribir-despu-s-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 12:43:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Gabriel Zaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191224-y-para-qu-leer-y-para-qu-escribir-despu-s-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["¿Y para qué leer? ¿Y para qué escribir? Después de leer cien, mil, diez mil libros en la vida, ¿qué se ha leído? Nada. Decir: yo sólo sé que no he leído nada, después de leer miles de libros, no es un acto de fingida modestia: es rigurosamente exacto, hasta la primera decimal de cero por ciento. Pero ¿no es quizá eso, exactamente, socráticamente, lo que los muchos libros deberían enseñarnos? Ser ignorantes a sabiendas, con plena aceptación. Dejar de ser ignorantes, para llegar a ser ignorantes inteligentes. [...] Quizá, por eso, la medida de la lectura no debe ser el número de libros leídos, sino el estado en que nos dejan.
¿Qué demonios importa si uno es culto, está al día o ha leído todos los libros? Lo que importa es cómo se anda, cómo se ve, cómo se actúa, después de leer. Si la calle y las nubes y la existencia de los otros tienen algo que decirnos. Si leer nos hace, físicamente, más reales." -- Gabriel Zaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174153-el-tiempo-barre-con-todo-y-las-costumbres-as-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 10:40:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Fernando Vallejo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174153-el-tiempo-barre-con-todo-y-las-costumbres-as-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…el tiempo barre con todo y las costumbres. Así, de cambio en cambio, paso a paso, van perdiendo las sociedades la cohesión, la identidad, quedan hechas unas colchas deshilachadas de retazos…" -- Fernando Vallejo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 11:04:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371653-first-lord-no-tattoos-may-neither-chinese-symbol-for-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, Lord: No tattoos. May neither Chinese symbol for truth nor Winnie-the-Pooh holding the FSU logo stain her tender haunches.

May she be Beautiful but not Damaged, for it’s the Damage that draws the creepy soccer coach’s eye, not the Beauty.

When the Crystal Meth is offered, May she remember the parents who cut her grapes in half And stick with Beer.

Guide her, protect her

When crossing the street, stepping onto boats, swimming in the ocean, swimming in pools, walking near pools, standing on the subway platform, crossing 86th Street, stepping off of boats, using mall restrooms, getting on and off escalators, driving on country roads while arguing, leaning on large windows, walking in parking lots, riding Ferris wheels, roller-coasters, log flumes, or anything called “Hell Drop,” “Tower of Torture,” or “The Death Spiral Rock ‘N Zero G Roll featuring Aerosmith,” and standing on any kind of balcony ever, anywhere, at any age.

Lead her away from Acting but not all the way to Finance. Something where she can make her own hours but still feel intellectually fulfilled and get outside sometimes And not have to wear high heels.

What would that be, Lord? Architecture? Midwifery? Golf course design? I’m asking You, because if I knew, I’d be doing it, Youdammit.

May she play the Drums to the fiery rhythm of her Own Heart with the sinewy strength of her Own Arms, so she need Not Lie With Drummers.

Grant her a Rough Patch from twelve to seventeen. Let her draw horses and be interested in Barbies for much too long, For childhood is short – a Tiger Flower blooming Magenta for one day – And adulthood is long and dry-humping in cars will wait.

O Lord, break the Internet forever, That she may be spared the misspelled invective of her peers And the online marketing campaign for Rape Hostel V: Girls Just Wanna Get Stabbed.

And when she one day turns on me and calls me a Bitch in front of Hollister, Give me the strength, Lord, to yank her directly into a cab in front of her friends, For I will not have that Shit. I will not have it.

And should she choose to be a Mother one day, be my eyes, Lord, that I may see her, lying on a blanket on the floor at 4:50 A.M., all-at-once exhausted, bored, and in love with the little creature whose poop is leaking up its back.

“My mother did this for me once,” she will realize as she cleans feces off her baby’s neck. “My mother did this for me.” And the delayed gratitude will wash over her as it does each generation and she will make a Mental Note to call me. And she will forget. But I’ll know, because I peeped it with Your God eyes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 09:23:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Audre Lorde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27421-your-silence-will-not-protect-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your silence will not protect you." -- Audre Lorde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184723-la-realidad-no-es-solo-como-se-percibe-en-la</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 12:44:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184723-la-realidad-no-es-solo-como-se-percibe-en-la]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["La realidad no es solo como se percibe en la superficie, también tiene una dimensión mágica y, si a uno se le antoja, es legítimo exagerarla y ponerle color para que el tránsito por esta vida no resulte tan aburrido." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287849-la-memoria-imprime-en-blanco-y-negro-los-grises-se</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2011 12:45:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287849-la-memoria-imprime-en-blanco-y-negro-los-grises-se]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["La memoria imprime en blanco y negro, los grises se pierden por el camino." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 23:06:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 23:06:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98518-i-am-lonely-yet-not-everybody-will-do-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 23:08:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98518-i-am-lonely-yet-not-everybody-will-do-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am lonely, yet not everybody will do. I don't know why, some people fill the gaps and others emphasize my loneliness. In reality those who satisfy me are those who simply allow me to live with my ''idea of them." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65612-music-melts-all-the-separate-parts-of-our-bodies-together</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 23:07:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65612-music-melts-all-the-separate-parts-of-our-bodies-together]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music melts all the separate parts of our bodies together." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:34:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81479-i-write-emotional-algebra</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:46:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81479-i-write-emotional-algebra]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write emotional algebra." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129629-hay-algo-m-s-seductor-y-a-la-vez-m-s-doloroso</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 14:41:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129629-hay-algo-m-s-seductor-y-a-la-vez-m-s-doloroso]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["¿Hay algo más seductor y a la vez más doloroso para el hombre que el libre albedrío?" -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215097-you-have-to-leave-the-island-in-order-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 09:38:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215097-you-have-to-leave-the-island-in-order-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...you have to leave the island in order to see the island, that we can't see ourselves unless we become free of ourselves, Unless we escape from ourselves you mean, No, that's not the same thing." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220583-if-someone-is-not-treating-you-with-love-and-respect</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 11:05:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[pa'tí add a quote by Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220583-if-someone-is-not-treating-you-with-love-and-respect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If someone is not treating you with love and respect, it is a gift if they walk away from you. If that person doesn't walk away, you will surely endure many years of suffering with him or her. Walking away may hurt for a while, but your heart will eventually heal. Then you can choose what you really want. You will find that you don't need to trust others as much as you need to trust yourself to make the right choices." -- Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
