<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/721900-kelly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/721900-kelly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 11:18:30 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 11:18:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Jim MORRISON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most important kind of freedom is to be what you really are. You trade in your reality for a role. You trade in your sense for an act. You give up your ability to feel, and in exchange, put on a mask. There can't be any large-scale revolution until there's a personal revolution, on an individual level. It's got to happen inside first." -- Jim MORRISON]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289279-friendship--my-definition--is-built-on-two-things-respect-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 22:22:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Stieg Larsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289279-friendship--my-definition--is-built-on-two-things-respect-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship- my definition- is built on two things. Respect and trust. Both elements have to be there. And it has to be mutual. You can have respect for someone, but if you don't have trust, the friendship will crumble." -- Stieg Larsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 09:42:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how close we are to another person, few human relationships are as free from strife, disagreement, and frustration as is the relationship you have with a good dog. Few human beings give of themselves to another as a dog gives of itself. I also suspect that we cherish dogs because their unblemished souls make us wish - consciously or unconsciously - that we were as innocent as they are, and make us yearn for a place where innocence is universal and where the meanness, the betrayals, and the cruelties of this world are unknown." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 23:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9809-courage-is-not-the-absence-of-fear-but-rather-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 13:41:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Ambrose Redmoon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9809-courage-is-not-the-absence-of-fear-but-rather-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgement that
something else is more important than fear." -- Ambrose Redmoon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16892-patience-is-bitter-but-its-fruit-is-sweet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 19:04:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16892-patience-is-bitter-but-its-fruit-is-sweet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Patience is bitter, but its fruit is sweet." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233139-courage-is-not-having-the-strength-to-go-on-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 06:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Teddy Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233139-courage-is-not-having-the-strength-to-go-on-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage is not having the strength to go on; it is going on when you don't have the strength." -- Teddy Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270625-if-you-can-t-run-you-crawl-if-you-can-t-crawl--</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 15:55:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270625-if-you-can-t-run-you-crawl-if-you-can-t-crawl--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't run, you crawl. If you can't crawl-- you find someone to carry you." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254464-patience-is-a-virtue-and-the-best-things-in-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 16:43:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Julie Spira]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254464-patience-is-a-virtue-and-the-best-things-in-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Patience is a virtue and the best things in life are worth waiting for." -- Julie Spira]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67507-very-occasionally-if-you-pay-really-close-attention-life-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 18:45:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67507-very-occasionally-if-you-pay-really-close-attention-life-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Very occasionally, if you pay really close attention, life doesn't suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 17:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 21:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 22:43:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1129728-this-i-know-the-mind-left-to-itself-repeats-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 14:59:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Kamal Ravikant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1129728-this-i-know-the-mind-left-to-itself-repeats-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This I know: the mind, left to itself, repeats the same stories, the same loops.  Mostly ones that don't serve us.  So what's practical, what's transformative, is to consciously choose a thought.  Then practice it again and again.  With emotion, with feeling, with acceptance.   Lay down the synaptic pathways until the mind starts playing it automatically.  Do this with enough intensity over time and the mind will have no choice.  That's how it operates.  Where do you think your original loops came from?" -- Kamal Ravikant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708284-i-have-seen-the-best-of-you-and-the-worst</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 15:24:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Sarah Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/708284-i-have-seen-the-best-of-you-and-the-worst]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have seen the best of you, and the worst of you, and I choose both." -- Sarah Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971450-as-you-love-yourself-life-loves-you-back-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 12:05:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Kamal Ravikant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/971450-as-you-love-yourself-life-loves-you-back-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you love yourself, life loves you back.  I don't think it has a choice either.  I can't explain how it works, but I know it to be true." -- Kamal Ravikant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 21:53:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58946-sometimes-when-i-look-at-you-i-feel-i-m-gazing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes when I look at you, I feel I'm gazing at a distant star. 
It's dazzling, but the light is from tens of thousands of years ago.
Maybe the star doesn't even exist any more. Yet sometimes that light seems more real to me than anything." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
