<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722092-j]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722092-j" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 14:20:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 14:20:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need." -- Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53169-we-read-deeply-for-varied-reasons-most-of-them-familiar</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:03:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Harold Bloom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53169-we-read-deeply-for-varied-reasons-most-of-them-familiar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read deeply for varied reasons, most of them familiar: that we cannot know enough people profoundly enough; that we need to know ourselves better; that we require knowledge, not just of self and others, but of the way things are.  Yet the strongest, most authentic motive for deep reading…is the search for a difficult pleasure." -- Harold Bloom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 17:48:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 17:48:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5414-a-great-deal-of-intelligence-can-be-invested-in-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:03:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5414-a-great-deal-of-intelligence-can-be-invested-in-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A great deal of intelligence can be invested in ignorance when the need for illusion is deep." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 14:19:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2150-human-beings-do-not-live-forever-reuven-we-live-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 09:07:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Chaim Potok]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2150-human-beings-do-not-live-forever-reuven-we-live-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings do not live forever, Reuven. We live less than the time it takes to blink an eye, if we measure our lives against eternity. So it may be asked what value is there to a human life.  There is so much pain in the world. What does it mean to have to suffer so much if our lives are nothing more than the blink of an eye? 

I learned a long time ago, Reuven, that a blink of an eye in itself is nothing. But the eye that blinks, that is something. A span of life is nothing. But the man who lives that span, he is something.  He can fill that tiny span with meaning, so its quality is immeasurable though its quantity may be insignificant. Do you understand what I am saying? A man must fill his life with meaning, meaning is not automatically given to life. 

It is hard work to fill one's life with meaning. That I do not think you understand yet. A life filled with meaning is worthy of rest. I want to be worthy of rest when I am no longer here." -- Chaim Potok]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1797-if-henry-adams-whom-you-knew-slightly-could-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:06:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Wallace Stegner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1797-if-henry-adams-whom-you-knew-slightly-could-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Henry Adams, whom you knew slightly, could make a theory of history by applying the second law of thermodynamics to human affairs, I ought to be entitled to base one on the angle of repose, and may yet. There is another physical law that teases me, too: the Doppler Effect. The sound of anything coming at you -- a train, say, or the future -- has a higher pitch than the sound of the same thing going away. If you have perfect pitch and a head for mathematics you can compute the speed of the object by the interval between its arriving and departing sounds. I have neither perfect pitch nor a head for mathematics, and anyway who wants to compute the speed of history? Like all falling bodies, it constantly accelerates. But I would like to hear your life as you heard it, coming at you, instead of hearing it as I do, a sober sound of expectations reduced, desires blunted, hopes deferred or abandoned, chances lost, defeats accepted, griefs borne. I don't find your life uninteresting, as Rodman does. I would like to hear it as it sounded while it was passing. Having no future of my own, why shouldn't I look forward to yours." -- Wallace Stegner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:06:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6287-mientras-la-humanidad-siempre-avanzando-no-sepa-a-do-camina</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 14:06:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Gustavo Adolfo Becquer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6287-mientras-la-humanidad-siempre-avanzando-no-sepa-a-do-camina]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mientras la humanidad siempre avanzando,
No sepa a do camina;
Mientras haya un misterio para el hombre,
¡Habrá poesía! " -- Gustavo Adolfo Becquer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7569-people-can-lose-their-lives-in-libraries-they-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2010 20:29:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7569-people-can-lose-their-lives-in-libraries-they-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People can lose their lives in libraries. They ought to be warned." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109804-there-is-no-surer-foundation-for-a-beautiful-friendship-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 12:03:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109804-there-is-no-surer-foundation-for-a-beautiful-friendship-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no surer foundation for a beautiful friendship than a mutual taste in literature." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119681-a-game-master-or-teacher-who-was-primarily-concerned-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 06:09:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119681-a-game-master-or-teacher-who-was-primarily-concerned-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A game master or teacher who was primarily concerned with being close enough to the &quot;innermost meaning&quot; would be a very bad teacher. To be candid, I myself, for example, have never in my life said a word to my pupils about the &quot;meaning&quot; of music; if there is one it does not need my explanations. On the other hand I have always made a great point of having my pupils count their eighths and sixteenths nicely. Whatever you become, teacher, scholar, or musician, have respect for the &quot;meaning&quot; but do not imagine that it can be taught." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385330-as-many-truths-as-men-occasionally-i-glimpse-a-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 09:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385330-as-many-truths-as-men-occasionally-i-glimpse-a-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As many truths as men.  Occasionally, I glimpse a truer Truth, hiding in imperfect simulacrums of itself, but as I approach, it bestirs itself &amp; moves deeper into the thorny swamp of dissent." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222610-history-says-don-t-hope-on-this-side-of-the-grave</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 22:07:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Seamus Heaney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222610-history-says-don-t-hope-on-this-side-of-the-grave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History says, Don’t hope
On this side of the grave,
But then, once in a lifetime
The longed-for tidal wave
Of justice can rise up,
And hope and history rhyme" -- Seamus Heaney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 21:33:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7810-let-us-be-grateful-to-the-people-who-make-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy; they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 07:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237620-i-think-we-ought-to-read-only-the-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we ought to read only the kind of books that wound or stab us. If the book we're reading doesn't wake us up with a blow to the head, what are we reading for? So that it will make us happy, as you write? Good Lord, we would be happy precisely if we had no books, and the kind of books that make us happy are the kind we could write ourselves if we had to. But we need books that affect us like a disaster, that grieve us deeply, like the death of someone we loved more than ourselves, like being banished into forests far from everyone, like a suicide. A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us. That is my belief." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/808346-wholly-unprepared-we-embark-upon-the-second-half-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 07:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/808346-wholly-unprepared-we-embark-upon-the-second-half-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wholly unprepared, we embark upon the second half of life. Or are there perhaps colleges for forty-year-olds which prepare them for their coming life and its demands as the ordinary colleges introduce our young people to a knowledge of the world? No, thoroughly unprepared we take the step into the afternoon of life; worse still we take this step with the false assumption that our truths and ideals will serve us as hitherto. But we cannot live the afternoon of life according to the program of life's morning; for what was great in the morning will be little at evening, and what in the morning was true will at evening have become a lie." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446925-after-such-knowledge-what-forgiveness-think-now-history-has-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 09:50:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446925-after-such-knowledge-what-forgiveness-think-now-history-has-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After such knowledge, what forgiveness? Think now	
History has many cunning passages, contrived corridors	
And issues, deceives with whispering ambitions,	      
Guides us by vanities. Think now	
She gives when our attention is distracted	
And what she gives, gives with such supple confusions	
That the giving famishes the craving. Gives too late	
What’s not believed in, or if still believed,	       
In memory only, reconsidered passion. Gives too soon	
Into weak hands, what’s thought can be dispensed with	
Till the refusal propagates a fear. Think	
Neither fear nor courage saves us. Unnatural vices	
Are fathered by our heroism. Virtues	       
Are forced upon us by our impudent crimes.	
These tears are shaken from the wrath-bearing tree." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
