<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722291-patty]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722291-patty" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:22:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32122-orr-would-be-crazy-to-fly-more-missions-and-sane</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:22:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32122-orr-would-be-crazy-to-fly-more-missions-and-sane]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Orr would be crazy to fly more missions and sane if he didn't,
but if he was sane he had to fly them.  If he flew them he was crazy and didn't have to; but if he didn't want to he was sane and had to.  That's some catch, that catch-22.
" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32124-love-is-where-you-find-it-i-think-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:24:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32124-love-is-where-you-find-it-i-think-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is where you find it. I think it is foolish to go around looking for it, and I think it can be poisonous. I wish that people who are conventionally supposed to love each other would say to each other, when they fight, 'Please — a little less love, and a little more common decency'." -- Kurt Vonnegut ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32125-later-she-would-remember-these-years-and-realize-with-astonishment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:25:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Marilyn French]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32125-later-she-would-remember-these-years-and-realize-with-astonishment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Later, she would remember these years, and realize with astonishment that she had, by fifteen, decided on most of the assumptions she would carry for the rest of her life: that people were essentially not evil, that perfection was death, that life was better than order and a little chaos good for the soul. Most important, this life was all. Unfortunately, she forgot these things, and had to remember them the hard way." -- Marilyn French]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:26:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it never failed that during the dry years the people forgot about the rich years, and during the wet years they lost all memory of the dry years. It was always that way." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32128-the-history-of-a-city-was-like-the-history-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:27:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32128-the-history-of-a-city-was-like-the-history-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The history of a city was like the history of a family—there is closeness and even affection, but death eventually separates everyone from each other.  It is only the vividness of memory that keeps the dead alive forever; a writer’s job is to imagine everything so personally that the fiction is as vivid as our personal memories.  " -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32130-when-i-was-in-power-i-found-that-experts-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:28:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32130-when-i-was-in-power-i-found-that-experts-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was in power, I found that experts can’t be trusted.  For this simple reason:  unlike tyrants, they are under no delusion that a country, a people is their body.  Under this delusion a tyrant takes everything personally.  An expert takes nothing personally.  Nothing is ever precisely his fault.  If a bridge collapses, or a war miscarries, he has already walked away.  He still has his expertise.  Also,---people imagine that because a thing is big, it has had a great deal of intelligent thought given to it.  This is not true.  A big idea is even more apt to be wrong than a small one, because the scale is inorganic.  The Great Wall, for instance, is extremely stupid.  The two biggest phenomena in the world right now are Maoism and American television, and both are extremely stupid." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9090-too-much-sanity-may-be-madness-and-maddest-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:29:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Dale Wasserman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9090-too-much-sanity-may-be-madness-and-maddest-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Too much sanity may be madness — and maddest of all: to see life as it is, and not as it should be!" -- Dale Wasserman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32137-liberalism-for-every-complicated-problem-there-exists-both-an-intellectual</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:39:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Theodore White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32137-liberalism-for-every-complicated-problem-there-exists-both-an-intellectual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liberalism: for every complicated problem there exists both an intellectual and a moral solution and they coincide." -- Theodore White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32138-i-don-t-actually-take-much-stock-in-the-collapsing-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:40:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32138-i-don-t-actually-take-much-stock-in-the-collapsing-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t actually take much stock in the collapsing culture bit. I’m beginning to see it instead as the conduct of life without input from your soul." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32139-if-a-man-says-but-i-realize-that-my-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:43:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32139-if-a-man-says-but-i-realize-that-my-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a man says: “But I realize that my natural endowments are mediocre—shall I then suffer, be ashamed, have an inferiority complex?” The answer is: “In the basic, crucial sphere, the sphere of morality and action, it is not your endowments that matter, but what you do with them.” It is here that all men are free and equal, regardless of natural gifts. You can be, in your own modest sphere, as good morally as the genius is in his—if you live by the same rules. Find your goal within yourself, in whatever work you are honestly capable of performing. Never make others your prime goal. Demand nothing from others as an unearned gift and grant them nothing unearned. Live by your own rational judgments. Be independent in whatever judgments you hold or actions you undertake, and do not venture beyond your own capacity, into spheres where you’ll have to become a parasite and a second-hander.  You’ll be surprised how decent and wonderful a human being you’ll become, and how much honest, legitimate human affection and appreciation you’ll get from others." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32140-a-good-social-system-is-not-to-be-secured-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:45:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32140-a-good-social-system-is-not-to-be-secured-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good social system is not to be secured by making people unselfish, but, by making their own vital impulses fit in with other peoples.  This is feasible.  Those who have produced stoic philosophies have all had enough to eat and drink.

I feel I shall find the truth on my deathbed and be surrounded by people too stupid to understand—fussing about medicines instead of searching for wisdom.

I hate being all tidy like a book in a library where nobody reads – prison is horribly like that." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204031-it-s-important-in-life-to-conclude-things-properly-only-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 15:28:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204031-it-s-important-in-life-to-conclude-things-properly-only-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's important in life to conclude things properly. Only then can you let go. Otherwise you are left with words you should have said but never did, and your heart is heavy with remorse." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46783-i-didn-t-know-what-to-do-for-my-project-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 15:35:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Brian Regan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46783-i-didn-t-know-what-to-do-for-my-project-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn’t know what to do for my project so I brought in a paper cup filled with dirt just hoping that she’d know I’m an idiot and just walk right on past me just as long as I was holding something. 

“What do you have there, Brian?” 

“It’s a cup of dirt. Just put an ‘F’ on it there and let me go home.” 

“Well, explain it.” 

“Well, it’s a cup with dirt in it. I call it ‘Cup of Dirt.’ You should move on now. Just go ahead and move on. Head on down the line there." -- Brian Regan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39893-the-most-important-things-are-the-hardest-to-say-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 15:39:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patty add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39893-the-most-important-things-are-the-hardest-to-say-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most important things are the hardest to say.  They are the things you get ashamed of, because words diminish them -- words shrink things that seemed limitless when they were in your head to no more than living size when they're brought out.  But it's more than that, isn't it? The most important things lie too close to wherever your secret heart is buried, like landmarks to a treasure your enemies would love to steal away.  And you may make revelations that cost you dearly only to have people look at you in a funny way, not understanding what you've said at all, or why you thought it was so important that you almost cried while you were saying it.  That's the worst, I think.  When the secret stays locked within not for want of a tellar but for want of an understanding ear." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
