<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722481-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722481-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 19:34:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2556-if-you-hate-a-person-you-hate-something-in-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 19:34:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2556-if-you-hate-a-person-you-hate-something-in-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hate a person, you hate something in him that is part of yourself. What isn't part of ourselves doesn't disturb us." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 14:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290767-what-i-need-is-the-dandelion-in-the-spring-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I need is the dandelion in the spring. The bright yellow that means rebirth instead of destruction. The promise that life can go on, no matter how bad our losses. That it can be good again." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56562-he-s-more-myself-than-i-am-whatever-our-souls-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:50:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56562-he-s-more-myself-than-i-am-whatever-our-souls-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's more myself than I am. Whatever our souls are made of, his and mine are the same." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13578-be-with-me-always---take-any-form---drive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13578-be-with-me-always---take-any-form---drive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be with me always - take any form - drive me mad! only do not leave me in this abyss, where I cannot find you! Oh, God! it is unutterable! I can not live without my life! I can not live without my soul!" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100582-catherine-earnshaw-may-you-not-rest-as-long-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100582-catherine-earnshaw-may-you-not-rest-as-long-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Catherine Earnshaw, may you not rest as long as I am living. You said I killed you--haunt me then. The murdered do haunt their murderers. I believe--I know that ghosts have wandered the earth. Be with me always--take any form--drive me mad. Only do not leave me in this abyss, where I cannot find you! Oh, God! It is unutterable! I cannot live without my life! I cannot live without my soul!" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10033-i-cannot-express-it-but-surely-you-and-everybody-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:53:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10033-i-cannot-express-it-but-surely-you-and-everybody-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot express it; but surely you and everybody have a notion that there is or should be an existence of yours beyond you. What were the use of my creation, if I were entirely contained here? My great miseries in this world have been Heathcliff's miseries, and I watched and felt each from the beginning: my great thought in living is himself. If all else perished, and he remained, I should still continue to be; and if all else remained, and he were annihilated, the universe would turn to a mighty stranger: I should not seem a part of it. My love for Linton is like the foliage in the woods: time will change it, I'm well aware, as winter changes the trees. My love for Heathcliff resembles the eternal rocks beneath: a source of little visible delight, but necessary. Nelly, I am Heathcliff! He's always, always in my mind: not as a pleasure, any more than I am always a pleasure to myself, but as my own being." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102207-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:56:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102207-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You teach me now how cruel you've been - cruel and false. Why did you despise me? Why did you betray your own heart, Cathy? I have not one word of comfort. You deserve this. You have killed yourself. Yes, you may kiss me, and cry; and wring out my kisses and tears: they'll blight you - they'll damn you. You loved me - what right had you to leave me? What right - answer me - for the poor fancy you felt for Linton? Because misery, and degradation, and death, and nothing that God or Satan could inflict would have parted us, you, of your own will did it. I have no broken your heart - you have broken it; and in breaking it, you have broken mine. So much the worse for me that I am strong. Do I want to live? What kind of living will it be when you - Oh, God! would you like to lie with your soul in the grave?" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181466-if-you-ever-looked-at-me-once-with-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:58:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181466-if-you-ever-looked-at-me-once-with-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you ever looked at me once with what I know is in you, I would be your slave." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126099-it-is-hard-to-forgive-and-to-look-at-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 21:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126099-it-is-hard-to-forgive-and-to-look-at-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard to forgive, and to look at those eyes, and feel those wasted hands,' he answered. 'Kiss me again; and don’t let me see your eyes! I forgive what you have done to me. I love my murderer—but yours! How can I?" -- Emily Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52514-why-did-you-betray-your-own-heart-cathy-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 22:00:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52514-why-did-you-betray-your-own-heart-cathy-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did you betray your own heart Cathy? I have not one word of comfort. You deserve this. You have killed yourself. ... You loved me - then what right had you to leave me? Because ... nothing God or satan could inflict would have parted us, you, of you own will, did it. I have not broken your heart - you have broken it; and in breaking it, you have broken mine. So much the worse for me that I am strong. Do I want to live? What kind of living will it be when you - oh God! would you like to live with your soul in the grave? [...] I forgive what you have done to me. I love my murderer - but yours! How can I?" -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125256-treachery-and-violence-are-spears-pointed-at-both-ends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 22:01:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125256-treachery-and-violence-are-spears-pointed-at-both-ends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Treachery and violence are spears pointed at both ends; they wound those who resort to them worse than their enemies." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
