<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72252-mark-babcock]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72252-mark-babcock" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:22:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263113-if-you-re-trapped-in-the-dream-of-the-other-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:22:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263113-if-you-re-trapped-in-the-dream-of-the-other-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're trapped in the dream of the Other, you're fucked." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57245-writing-has-nothing-to-do-with-meaning-it-has-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:22:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57245-writing-has-nothing-to-do-with-meaning-it-has-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing has nothing to do with meaning. It has to do with landsurveying and cartography, including the mapping of countries yet to come." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310530-a-concept-is-a-brick-it-can-be-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:23:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310530-a-concept-is-a-brick-it-can-be-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A concept is a brick. It can be used to build a courthouse of reason. Or it can be thrown through the window." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310541-bring-something-incomprehensible-into-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:25:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310541-bring-something-incomprehensible-into-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bring something incomprehensible into the world!" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220912-the-fundamental-problem-of-political-philosophy-is-still-precisely-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:26:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220912-the-fundamental-problem-of-political-philosophy-is-still-precisely-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fundamental problem of political philosophy is still precisely the one that Spinoza saw so clearly (and that Wilhelm Reich rediscovered): Why do men fight for their servitude as stubbornly as though it were their salvation?" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310525-it-is-not-the-slumber-of-reason-that-engenders-monsters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:28:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310525-it-is-not-the-slumber-of-reason-that-engenders-monsters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the slumber of reason that engenders monsters, but vigilant and insomniac rationality." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280040-philosophy-is-not-in-a-state-of-external-reflection-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:29:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280040-philosophy-is-not-in-a-state-of-external-reflection-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Philosophy is not in a state of external reflection on other domains, but in a state of active and internal alliance with them, and it is neither more abstract nor more difficult." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310517-christianity-taught-us-to-see-the-eye-of-the-lord</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:29:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310517-christianity-taught-us-to-see-the-eye-of-the-lord]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christianity taught us to see the eye of the lord looking down upon us. Such forms of knowledge project an image of reality, at the expense of reality itself. They talk figures and icons and signs, but fail to perceive forces and flows. They bind us to other realities, and especially the reality of power as it subjugates us. Their function is to tame, and the result is the fabrication of docile and obedient subjects." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310538-it-is-always-from-the-depths-of-its-impotence-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:31:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310538-it-is-always-from-the-depths-of-its-impotence-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is always from the depths of its impotence that each power center draws its power, hence their extreme maliciousness, and vanity" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310518-d-h-lawrence-had-the-impression-that-psychoanalysis-was-shutting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:34:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310518-d-h-lawrence-had-the-impression-that-psychoanalysis-was-shutting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["D.H. Lawrence had the impression – that psychoanalysis was shutting sexuality up in a bizarre sort of box painted with bourgeois motifs, in a kind of rather repugnant artificial triangle, thereby stifling the whole of sexuality as a production of desire so as to recast it along entirely different lines, making of it a ‘dirty little secret’, a dirty little family secret, a private theater rather than the fantastic factory of nature and production" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310533-language-is-not-made-to-be-believed-but-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:35:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310533-language-is-not-made-to-be-believed-but-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is not made to be believed but to be obeyed, and to compel obedience newspapers, news, proceed by redundancy, in that they tell us what we ‘must’ think, retain, expect, etc. language is neither informational nor communicational. It is not the communication of information but something quite different: the transmission of order-words, either from one statement to another or within each statement, insofar as each statement accomplishes an act and the act is accomplished in the statement" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310539-the-self-is-only-a-threshold-a-door-a-becoming</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:35:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310539-the-self-is-only-a-threshold-a-door-a-becoming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The self is only a threshold, a door, a becoming between two multiplicities" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461157-belief-is-necessarily-something-false-that-diverts-and-suffocates-effective</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 19:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze / Felix Guatari]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461157-belief-is-necessarily-something-false-that-diverts-and-suffocates-effective]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["belief is necessarily something false that diverts and suffocates effective production" -- Gilles Deleuze / Felix Guatari]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310529-state-philosophy-reposes-on-a-double-identity-of-the-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 20:16:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310529-state-philosophy-reposes-on-a-double-identity-of-the-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["State philosophy reposes on a double identity: of the thinking subject, and of the concepts it creates and to which it lends its own presumed attributes of sameness and constancy. The subjects, its concepts, and also the objects in the world to which the concepts are applied have a shared, internal essence: the self-resemblance at the basis of identity. Representational thought is analogical; its concern is to establish a correspondence between these symmetrically structured domains. The faculty of judgment is the policeman of analogy, assuring that each of these terms is honestly itself, and that the proper correspondences obtain. In thought its end is truth, in action justice. The weapons it wields in their pursuit are limitive distribution (the determination of the exclusive set of properties possessed by each term in contradistinction to the others: logos, law) and hierarchical ranking (the measurement of the degree of perfection of a term’s self-resemblance in relation to a supreme standard, man, god, or gold: value, morality). The modus operandi is negation: x = x = not y. Identity, resemblance, truth, justice, and negation. The rational foundation for order. The established order, of course: philosophers have traditionally been employees of the State. The collusion between philosophy and the State was most explicitly enacted in the first decade of the nineteenth century with the foundation of the University of Berlin, which was to become the model of higher learning throughout Europe and in the United States. The goal laid out for it by Wilhelm von Humboldt (based on proposals by Fichte and Schleiermacher) was the ‘spiritual and moral training of the nation,’ to be achieved by ‘deriving everything from an original principle’ (truth), by ‘relating everything to an ideal’ (justice), and by ‘unifying this principle and this ideal to a single Idea’ (the State). The end product would be ‘a fully legitimated subject of knowledge and society’ – each mind an analogously organized mini-State morally unified in the supermind of the State. More insidious than the well-known practical cooperation between university and government (the burgeoning military funding of research) is its philosophical role in the propagation of the form of representational thinking itself, that ‘properly spiritual absolute State’ endlessly reproduced and disseminated at every level of the social fabric." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310540-only-thought-is-capable-of-inventing-the-fiction-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 20:16:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310540-only-thought-is-capable-of-inventing-the-fiction-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only thought is capable of inventing the fiction of a State that is universal by right, of elevation the State to the level of de jure universality" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
