<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722693-mike-caine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722693-mike-caine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 09:08:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37262-vegetarians-and-their-hezbollah-like-splinter-faction-the-vegans-are-a-persistent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 09:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37262-vegetarians-and-their-hezbollah-like-splinter-faction-the-vegans-are-a-persistent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vegetarians, and their Hezbollah-like splinter-faction, the vegans, are a persistent irritant to any chef worth a damn.  

To me, life without veal stock, pork fat, sausage, organ meat, demi-glace, or even stinky cheese is a life not worth living.  

Vegetarians are the enemy of everything good and decent in the human spirit, an affront to all I stand for, the pure enjoyment of food.  The body, these waterheads imagine, is a temple that should not be polluted by animal protein.  It's healthier, they insist, though every vegetarian waiter I've worked with is brought down by any rumor of a cold.  

Oh, I'll accomodate them, I'll rummage around for something to feed them, for a 'vegetarian plate', if called on to do so.  Fourteen dollars for a few slices of grilled eggplant and zucchini suits my food cost fine." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 19:37:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
