<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722721-kim-fuller]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722721-kim-fuller" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:35:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68783-it-may-not-be-nice-to-be-good-little-6655321</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:35:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Anthony Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68783-it-may-not-be-nice-to-be-good-little-6655321]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may not be nice to be good, little 6655321. It may be horrible to be good. And when I say that to you I realize how self-contradictory that sounds. I know I shall have many sleepless nights about this. What does God want? Does God want goodness or the choice of goodness? Is a man who chooses the bad perhaps in some way better than a man who has the good imposed upon him? Deep and hard questions, little 6655321." -- Anthony Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24906-sticking-feathers-up-your-butt-does-not-make-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24906-sticking-feathers-up-your-butt-does-not-make-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sticking feathers up your butt does not make you a chicken!" -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49332-don-t-do-what-you-want-do-what-you-don-t-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49332-don-t-do-what-you-want-do-what-you-don-t-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't do what you want. Do what you don't want. Do what you're trained not to want. Do the things that scare you the most." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 17:57:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:44:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68321-i-need-you-the-reader-to-imagine-us-for-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 03:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Nabokov Vladimi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68321-i-need-you-the-reader-to-imagine-us-for-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I need you, the reader, to imagine us, for we don't really exist if you don't." -- Nabokov Vladimi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2010 19:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2359-harper-in-your-experience-of-the-world-how-do-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 13:03:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2359-harper-in-your-experience-of-the-world-how-do-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Harper: In your experience of the world. How do people change?

Mormon Mother: Well it has something to do with God so it's not very nice.

God splits the skin with a jagged thumbnail from throat to belly and then plunges a huge filthy hand in, he grabs hold of your bloody tubes and they slip to evade his grasp but he squeezes hard, he insists, he pulls and pulls till all your innards are yanked out and the pain! We can't even talk about that. And then he stuffs them back, dirty, tangled and torn. It's up to you to do the stitching. 

Harper: And then up you get. And walk around.

Mormon Mother: Just mangled guts pretending.

Harper: That's how people change." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
