<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722954-tschlesman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/722954-tschlesman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:45:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:45:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851-american-men-are-allotted-just-as-many-tears-as-american</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:46:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/851-american-men-are-allotted-just-as-many-tears-as-american]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["American men are allotted just as many tears as American women. But because we are forbidden to shed them, we die long before women do, with our hearts exploding or our blood pressure rising or our livers eaten away by alcohol because that lake of grief inside us has no outlet. We, men, die because our faces were not watered enough." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16718-no-story-is-a-straight-line-the-geometry-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:46:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16718-no-story-is-a-straight-line-the-geometry-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No story is a straight line.  The geometry of a human life is too imperfect and complex, too distorted by the laughter of time and the bewildering intricacies of fate to admit the straight line into its system of laws." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32412-there-is-such-a-thing-as-too-much-beauty-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:46:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32412-there-is-such-a-thing-as-too-much-beauty-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is such a thing as too much beauty in a woman and it is often a burden as crippling as homeliness and far more dangerous. It takes much luck and integrity to survive the gift of perfect beauty, and its impermanence is its most cunning betrayal." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/852-her-laughter-was-a-shiny-thing-like-pewter-flung-high</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:46:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/852-her-laughter-was-a-shiny-thing-like-pewter-flung-high]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her laughter was a shiny thing, like pewter flung high in the air." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16703-but-no-one-walks-out-of-his-family-without-reprisals</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:47:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16703-but-no-one-walks-out-of-his-family-without-reprisals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But no one walks out of his family without reprisals: a family is too disciplined an army to offer compassion to its deserters." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16696-rape-is-a-crime-against-sleep-and-memory-it-s-afterimage</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:47:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16696-rape-is-a-crime-against-sleep-and-memory-it-s-afterimage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rape is a crime against sleep and memory; it's afterimage imprints itself like an irreversible negative from the camera obscura of dreams." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97208-man-wonders-but-god-decides-when-to-kill-the-prince</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:48:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97208-man-wonders-but-god-decides-when-to-kill-the-prince]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man wonders but God decides
When to kill the Prince of Tides." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198074-my-wound-is-geography-it-is-also-my-anchorage-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:48:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198074-my-wound-is-geography-it-is-also-my-anchorage-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My wound is geography. It is also my anchorage, my port of call." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245203-a-story-is-a-living-thing-it-moves-and-shifts</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:48:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245203-a-story-is-a-living-thing-it-moves-and-shifts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story is a living thing, it moves and shifts..." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263481-what-s-important-is-that-a-story-changes-every-time-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263481-what-s-important-is-that-a-story-changes-every-time-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's important is that a story changes every time you say it out loud. When you put it on paper, it can never change. But the more times you tell it, the more changes will occur. A story is a living thing; it moves and shifts" -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229284-but-as-i-watch-this-film-i-often-think-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:51:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229284-but-as-i-watch-this-film-i-often-think-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, as I watch this film, I often think that the boy did not know what he was really running toward, that it was not the end zone which awaited him. Somewhere in that ten second dash the running boy turned to metaphor and the older man could see it where the boy couldn not. He would be good at running, always good at it, and he would always run away from the things that hurt him, from the people who loved him, and from the friends empowered to save him. But where do we run when there are no crowds, no lights, no end zones? Where does a man run? the coach said, studying the films of himself as a boy. Where can a man run when he has lost the excuse of games? Where can a man run or where can he hide when he looks behind him and sees that he is only pursued by himself?" -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100871-on-writing-aphorisms-and-ten-second-essays-1-a-beginning-ends</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by James Richardson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100871-on-writing-aphorisms-and-ten-second-essays-1-a-beginning-ends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On Writing: Aphorisms and Ten-Second Essays 

1. A beginning ends what an end begins. 

2. The despair of the blank page: it is so full.

3. In the head Art’s not democratic. I wait a long time to be a writer good enough even for myself. 

4. The best time is stolen time.

5. All work is the avoidance of harder work. 

6. When I am trying to write I turn on music so I can hear what is keeping me from hearing.

7. I envy music for being beyond words. But then, every word is beyond music.

8. Why would we write if we’d already heard what we wanted to hear?

9. The poem in the quarterly is sure to fail within two lines: flaccid, rhythmless, hopelessly dutiful. But I read poets from strange languages with freedom and pleasure because I can believe in all that has been lost in translation. Though all works, all acts, all languages are already translation. 

10. Writer: how books read each other.

11. Idolaters of the great need to believe that what they love cannot fail them, adorers of camp, kitsch, trash that they cannot fail what they love. 

12. If I didn’t spend so much time writing, I’d know a lot more. But I wouldn’t know anything.

13. If you’re Larkin or Bishop, one book a decade is enough. If you’re not? More than enough.

14. Writing is like washing windows in the sun. With every attempt to perfect clarity you make a new smear.

15. There are silences harder to take back than words.

16. Opacity gives way. Transparency is the mystery.

17. I need a much greater vocabulary to talk to you than to talk to myself.

18. Only half of writing is saying what you mean. The other half is preventing people from reading what they expected you to mean.

19. Believe stupid praise, deserve stupid criticism.

20. Writing a book is like doing a huge jigsaw puzzle, unendurably slow at first, almost self-propelled at the end. Actually, it’s more like doing a puzzle from a box in which several puzzles have been mixed. Starting out, you can’t tell whether a piece belongs to the puzzle at hand, or one you’ve already done, or will do in ten years, or will never do. 

21. Minds go from intuition to articulation to self-defense, which is what they die of.

22. The dead are still writing. Every morning, somewhere, is a line, a passage, a whole book you are sure wasn’t there yesterday.

23. To feel an end is to discover that there had been a beginning. A parenthesis closes that we hadn’t realized was open).

24. There, all along, was what you wanted to say. But this is not what you wanted, is it, to have said it?" -- James Richardson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95483-step-away-from-the-mean-girls-and-say-bye-bye-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:52:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Oprah Winfrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95483-step-away-from-the-mean-girls-and-say-bye-bye-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Step Away from the Mean Girls…
…and say bye-bye to feeling bad about your looks.
Are you ready to stop colluding with a culture that makes so many of us feel physically inadequate? Say goodbye to your inner critic, and take this pledge to be kinder to yourself and others. 

This is a call to arms. A call to be gentle, to be forgiving, to be generous with yourself. The next time you look into the mirror, try to let go of the story line that says you're too fat or too sallow, too ashy or too old, your eyes are too small or your nose too big; just look into the mirror and see your face. When the criticism drops away, what you will see then is just you, without judgment, and that is the first step toward transforming your experience of the world." -- Oprah Winfrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2275-knowing-can-be-a-curse-on-a-person-s-life-i-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:58:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2275-knowing-can-be-a-curse-on-a-person-s-life-i-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing can be a curse on a person's life. I'd traded in a pack of lies for a pack of truth, and I didn't know which one was heavier. Which one took the most strength to carry around? It was a ridiculous question, though, because once you know the truth, you can't ever go back and pick up your suitcase of lies. Heavier or not, the truth is yours now." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109715-stories-have-to-be-told-or-they-die-and-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109715-stories-have-to-be-told-or-they-die-and-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories have to be told or they die, and when they die, we can't remember who we are or why we're here." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65228-it-is-the-peculiar-nature-of-the-world-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:58:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65228-it-is-the-peculiar-nature-of-the-world-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the peculiar nature of the world to go on spinning no matter what sort of heartbreak is happening." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31723-the-world-will-give-you-that-once-in-awhile-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31723-the-world-will-give-you-that-once-in-awhile-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world will give you that once in awhile, a brief timeout; the boxing bell rings and you go to your corner, where somebody dabs mercy on your beat-up life." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109797-there-s-nothing-like-a-song-about-lost-love-to-remind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:59:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109797-there-s-nothing-like-a-song-about-lost-love-to-remind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing like a song about lost love to remind you how everything precious can slip from the hinges where you've hung it so careful." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106161-i-realized-it-for-the-first-time-in-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 06:59:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106161-i-realized-it-for-the-first-time-in-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I realized it for the first time in my life: there is nothing but mystery in the world, how it hides behind the fabric of our poor, browbeat days, shining brightly, and we don't even know it." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102932-in-a-weird-way-i-must-have-loved-my-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:00:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102932-in-a-weird-way-i-must-have-loved-my-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a weird way I must have loved my little collection of hurts and wounds. They provided me with some real nice sympathy, with the feeling I was exceptional...What a special case I was." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106948-up-until-then-i-d-thought-that-white-people-and-colored</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:01:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106948-up-until-then-i-d-thought-that-white-people-and-colored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Up until then I'd thought that white people and colored people getting along was the big aim, but after that I decided everybody being colorless together was a better plan. I thought of that policeman, Eddie Hazelwurst, saying I'd lowered myself to be in this house of colored women, and for the very life of me I couldn't understand how it had turned out this way, how colored women had become the lowest ones on the totem pole. You only had to look at them to see how special they were, like hidden royalty among us.  Eddie Hazelwurst. What a shitbucket." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157985-i-ll-write-this-all-down-for-you-i-said-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:02:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157985-i-ll-write-this-all-down-for-you-i-said-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll write this all down for you,&quot; I said. &quot;I'll put it in a story.&quot; I don't know if that's what he wanted to ask me, but it's something everybody wants--for someone to see the hurt done to them and set it down like it matters." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86450-we-walked-along-the-river-with-the-words-streaming-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:02:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86450-we-walked-along-the-river-with-the-words-streaming-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We walked along the river with the words streaming behind us like ribbons in the night." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31600-all-that-paddling-around-in-the-alphabet-soup-of-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:04:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31600-all-that-paddling-around-in-the-alphabet-soup-of-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["all that paddling around in the alphabet soup of one's childhood, scooping up letters, hoping to arrange them into enlightening sentences that would explain why things had turned out the way they had. It evoked a certain mutiny in me." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224966-people-who-think-dying-is-the-is-the-worst-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 07:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224966-people-who-think-dying-is-the-is-the-worst-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who think dying is the is the worst thing don't know a thing about life." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229280-every-woman-i-had-ever-met-who-walked-through-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 21:08:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229280-every-woman-i-had-ever-met-who-walked-through-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every woman I had ever met who walked through the world appraised and classified by an extraordinary physicality had also received the keys to an unbearable solitude. It was the coefficient of their beauty, the price they had to pay." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487230-these-are-the-quicksilver-moments-of-my-childhood-i-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 21:11:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487230-these-are-the-quicksilver-moments-of-my-childhood-i-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are the quicksilver moments of my childhood I cannot remember entirely. Irresistible and emblematic, I can recall them only in fragments and shivers of the heart." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32483-i-do-not-have-any-other-way-of-saying-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 21:20:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32483-i-do-not-have-any-other-way-of-saying-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not have any other way of saying it. I think it happens but once and only to the very young when it feels like your skin could ignite at the mere touch of another person. You get to love like that but once." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571632-my-soul-found-ease-and-rest-in-the-companionship-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 21:38:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tschlesman add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571632-my-soul-found-ease-and-rest-in-the-companionship-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My soul found ease and rest in the companionship of books." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
