<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/723283-lor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/723283-lor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 21:20:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9632-sometimes-you-don-t-need-a-goal-in-life-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 21:20:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Sophie Kinsella]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9632-sometimes-you-don-t-need-a-goal-in-life-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sometimes you don't need a goal in life, you don't need to know the big picture. you just need to know what you're going to do next!" -- Sophie Kinsella]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39994-if-it-means-something-take-it-to-heart-if-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 07:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Philippa Gregory]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39994-if-it-means-something-take-it-to-heart-if-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If it means something, take it to heart. If it means nothing, it's nothing. Let it go." -- Philippa Gregory]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 08:04:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6130-a-woman-should-have-enough-money-within-her-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  enough money within her control to move out
  and rent a place of her own even if she never wants
  to or needs to...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  something perfect to wear if the employer or date of her
  dreams wants to see her in an hour...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ...
  a youth she's content to leave behind....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a past juicy enough that she's looking forward to
  retelling it in her old age....
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE .....
  a set of screwdrivers, a cordless drill, and a black
  lace bra...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  one friend who always makes her laugh... and one who
  lets her cry...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a good piece of furniture not previously owned by anyone
  else in her family...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  eight matching plates, wine glasses with stems, and a
  recipe for a meal that will make her guests feel honored...
  A WOMAN SHOULD HAVE ....
  a feeling of control over her destiny...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to fall in love without losing herself..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  HOW TO QUIT A JOB,
  BREAK UP WITH A LOVER,
  AND CONFRONT A FRIEND WITHOUT RUINING THE FRIENDSHIP...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  when to try harder... and WHEN TO WALK AWAY...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that she can't change the length of her calves,
  the width of her hips, or the nature of her parents..
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  that her childhood may not have been perfect...but it's over...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she would and wouldn't do for love or more...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  how to live alone... even if she doesn't like it...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  whom she can trust,
  whom she can't,
  and why she shouldn't
  take it personally...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  where to go...
  be it to her best friend's kitchen table...
  or a charming inn in the woods...
  when her soul needs soothing...
  EVERY WOMAN SHOULD KNOW...
  what she can and can't accomplish in a day...
  a month...and a year..." -- Pamela Redmond Satran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 08:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17849-dance-like-it-hurts-love-like-you-need-money-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 08:51:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Scott Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17849-dance-like-it-hurts-love-like-you-need-money-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dance like it hurts.  Love like you need money.  Work when people are watching. -- Dogbert's Motto" -- Scott Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18064-kind-words-can-be-short-and-easy-to-speak-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 08:51:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18064-kind-words-can-be-short-and-easy-to-speak-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 05:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27574-nobody-loves-me-nobody-cares-nobody-picks-me-peaches-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 09:01:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27574-nobody-loves-me-nobody-cares-nobody-picks-me-peaches-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody loves me, nobody cares,
Nobody picks me peaches and pears.
Nobody offers me candy and Cokes,
Nobody listens and laughs at me jokes.
Nobody helps when I get into a fight,
Nobody does all my homework at night.
Nobody misses me,
Nobody cries,
Nobody thinks I'm a wonderful guy.
So, if you ask me who's my best friend, in a whiz,
I'll stand up and tell you NOBODY is!
But yesterday night I got quite a scare
I woke up and Nobody just WASN'T there!
I called out and reached for Nobody's hand,
In the darkness where Nobody usually stands,
Then I poked through the house, in each cranny and nook,
But I found SOMEBODY each place that I looked.
I seached till I'm tired, and now with the dawn,
There's no doubt about it-
NOBODY'S GONE!!" -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19369-the-best-mirror-is-an-old-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 09:05:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by George Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19369-the-best-mirror-is-an-old-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best mirror is an old friend." -- George Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2659-live-with-intention-walk-to-the-edge-listen-hard-practice</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2659-live-with-intention-walk-to-the-edge-listen-hard-practice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live with intention.
Walk to the edge.
Listen Hard.
Practice wellness.
Play with abandon.
Laugh.
Choose with no regret.
Appreciate your friends.
Continue to learn.
Do what you love.
Live as if this is all there is." -- Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728-i-enjoyed-the-meetings-too-it-was-like-having-friends</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:15:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728-i-enjoyed-the-meetings-too-it-was-like-having-friends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I enjoyed the meetings, too. It was like having friends." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12996-the-trouble-is-not-in-dying-for-a-friend-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:15:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12996-the-trouble-is-not-in-dying-for-a-friend-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is not in dying for a friend, but in finding a friend worth dying for." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3215-silence-is-a-true-friend-who-never-betrays</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:15:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Confucius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3215-silence-is-a-true-friend-who-never-betrays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence is a true friend who never betrays." -- Confucius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17794-do-what-you-will-always-walk-where-you-like-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 06:18:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17794-do-what-you-will-always-walk-where-you-like-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do what you will, 
always
Walk where you like, 
your steps
Do as you please, I'll 
back you up. 

I remember thinking
sometimes we walk
sometimes we run away
But I know
no matter how fast we are running
Somehow we keep
Somehow we keep up with each other." -- Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 02:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 08:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mary Schmich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103606-ladies-and-gentlemen-of-the-class-of-97-wear-sunscreen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ladies and gentlemen of the class of '97:

Wear sunscreen.

If I could offer you only one tip for the future, sunscreen would be it. The long-term benefits of sunscreen have been proved by scientists, whereas the rest of my advice has no basis more reliable than my own meandering experience. I will dispense this advice now.

Enjoy the power and beauty of your youth. Oh, never mind. You will not understand the power and beauty of your youth until they've faded. But trust me, in 20 years, you'll look back at photos of yourself and recall in a way you can't grasp now how much possibility lay before you and how fabulous you really looked. You are not as fat as you imagine.

Don't worry about the future. Or worry, but know that worrying is as effective as trying to solve an algebra equation by chewing bubble gum. The real troubles in your life are apt to be things that never crossed your worried mind, the kind that blindside you at 4 p.m. on some idle Tuesday." -- Mary Schmich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8137-we-are-not-held-back-by-the-love-we-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 08:58:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8137-we-are-not-held-back-by-the-love-we-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not held back by the love we didn't receive in the past, but by the love we're not extending in the present." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106880-this-election-is-about-the-past-vs-the-future-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 09:01:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106880-this-election-is-about-the-past-vs-the-future-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This election is about the past vs. the future. It's about whether we settle for the same divisions and distractions and drama that passes for politics today or whether we reach for a politics of common sense and innovation, a politics of shared sacrifice and shared prosperity. There are those who will continue to tell us that we can't do this, that we can't have what we're looking for, that we can't have what we want, that we're peddling false hopes. But here is what I know. I know that when people say we can't overcome all the big money and influence in Washington, I think of that elderly woman who sent me a contribution the other day, an envelope that had a money order for $3.01 along with a verse of scripture tucked inside the envelope. So don't tell us change isn't possible. That woman knows change is possible. When I hear the cynical talk that blacks and whites and Latinos can't join together and work together, I'm reminded of the Latino brothers and sisters I organized with and stood with and fought with side by side for jobs and justice on the streets of Chicago. So don't tell us change can't happen. When I hear that we'll never overcome the racial divide in our politics, I think about that Republican woman who used to work for Strom Thurmond, who is now devoted to educating inner city-children and who went out into the streets of South Carolina and knocked on doors for this campaign. Don't tell me we can't change. Yes, we can. Yes, we can change. Yes, we can.

Yes, we can heal this nation. Yes, we can seize our future. And as we leave this great state with a new wind at our backs and we take this journey across this great country, a country we love, with the message we carry from the plains of Iowa to the hills of New Hampshire, from the Nevada desert to the South Carolina coast, the same message we had when we were up and when we were down, that out of many, we are one; that while we breathe, we will hope.



And where we are met with cynicism and doubt and fear and those who tell us that we can't, we will respond with that timeless creed that sums up the spirit of the American people in three simple words -- yes, we can." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87699-one-thing-i-do-know-about-intimacy-is-that-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 09:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87699-one-thing-i-do-know-about-intimacy-is-that-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing I do know about intimacy is that there are certain natural laws which govern the sexual experience of two people, and that these laws cannot be budged any more than gravity can be negotiated with.  To feel physically comfortable with someone else's body is not a decision you can make.  It has very little to do with how two people think or act or talk or even look.  The mysterious magnet is either there, buried somewhere deep behind the sternum, or it is not.  When it isn't there (as I have learned in the past, with heartbreaking clarity) you can no more force it to exist than a surgeon can force a patient's body to accept a kidney from the wrong donor.  My friend Annie says it all comes down to one simple question: &quot;Do you want your belly pressed against this person's belly forever --or not?" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14303-writing-is-like-sex-first-you-do-it-for-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 09:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14303-writing-is-like-sex-first-you-do-it-for-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is like sex. First you do it for love, then you do it for your friends, and then you do it for money." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16964-you-know-it-s-never-fifty-fifty-in-a-marriage-it-s-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 09:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16964-you-know-it-s-never-fifty-fifty-in-a-marriage-it-s-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know it's never fifty-fifty in a marriage. It's always seventy-thirty, or sixty-forty. Someone falls in love first. Someone puts someone else up on a pedestal. Someone works very hard to keep things rolling smoothly; someone else sails along for the ride." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2989-i-m-not-afraid-of-death-i-just-don-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 07:57:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2989-i-m-not-afraid-of-death-i-just-don-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not afraid of death; I just don't want to be there when it happens." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9675-i-m-the-one-that-s-got-to-die-when-it-s-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 07:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9675-i-m-the-one-that-s-got-to-die-when-it-s-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the one that's got to die when it's time for me to die, so let me live my life the way I want to." -- Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3345-death-ends-a-life-not-a-relationship</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 07:58:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3345-death-ends-a-life-not-a-relationship]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death ends a life, not a relationship." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 07:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not pity the dead, Harry. Pity the living, and, above all those who live without love." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 08:02:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death must be so beautiful. To lie in the soft brown earth, with the grasses waving above one's head, and listen to silence. To have no yesterday, and no tomorrow. To forget time, to forgive life, to be at peace." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137549-my-father-took-one-hundred-and-thirty-two-minutes-to-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 08:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137549-my-father-took-one-hundred-and-thirty-two-minutes-to-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My father took one hundred and thirty-two minutes to die.

I counted.

It happened on the Jellicoe Road. The prettiest road I’d ever seen, where trees made breezy canopies like a tunnel to Shangri-La. We were going to the ocean, hundreds of miles away, because I wanted to see the ocean and my father said that it was about time the four of us made that journey. I remember asking, 'What’s the difference between a trip and a journey?' and my father said, 'Narnie, my love, when we get there, you’ll understand,' and that was the last thing he ever said." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20123-to-lose-a-brother-is-to-lose-someone-with-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 08:10:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20123-to-lose-a-brother-is-to-lose-someone-with-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To lose a brother is to lose someone with whom you can share the experience of growing old, who is supposed to bring you a sister-in-law and nieces and nephews, creatures who people the tree of your life and give it new branches. To lose your father is to lose the one whose guidance and help you seek, who supports you like a tree trunk supports its branches. To lose your mother, well, that is like losing the sun above you. It is like losing--I'm sorry, I would rather not go on." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198863-years-passed-the-trees-in-our-yard-grew-taller-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 08:20:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Alice Sebold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198863-years-passed-the-trees-in-our-yard-grew-taller-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Years passed. The trees in our yard grew taller. I watched my family and my friends and neighbors, the teachers whom I'd had or imaged having, the high school I had dreamed about. As I sat in the gazebo I would pretend instead that I was sitting on the topmost branch of the maple under which my brother had swallowed a stick and still played hide-and-seek with Nate, or I would perch on the railing of a stairwell in New York and wait for Ruth to pass near. I would study with Ray. Drive the Pacific Coast Highway on a warm afternoon of salty air with my mother. But I would end each day with my father in his den. 

I would lay these photographs down in my mind, those gathered from my constant watching, and I could trace how one thing- my death- connected these images to a single source. No one could have predicted how my loss would change small moments on Earth. But I held on to those moments, hoarded them. None of them were lost as long as I was there." -- Alice Sebold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178654-listen-children-your-father-is-dead-from-his-old-coats</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 08:28:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lor  add a quote by Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178654-listen-children-your-father-is-dead-from-his-old-coats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen, children:
Your father is dead.
From his old coats
I'll make you little jackets;
I'll make you little trousers
From his old pants.
There'll be in his pockets
Things he used to put there,
Keys and pennies
Covered with tobacco;
Dan shall have the pennies
To save in his bank;
Anne shall have the keys
To make a pretty noise with.
Life must go on,
Though good men die;
Anne, eat your breakfast;
Dan, take your medicine;
Life must go on;
I forget just why." -- Edna St. Vincent Millay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
