<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/723583-suzi-conklin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/723583-suzi-conklin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:08:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:08:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:08:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96293-still-despite-all-this-traveling-is-the-great-true-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:12:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96293-still-despite-all-this-traveling-is-the-great-true-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still, despite all this, traveling is the great true love of my life.  I have always felt, ever since I was sixteen years old and first went to Russia with my saved-up babysitting money, that to travel is worth any cost or sacrifice.  I am loyal and constant in my love for travel, as I have not always been loyal and constant in my other loves.  I feel about travel the way a happy new mother feels about her impossible, colicky, restless, newborn baby--I just don't care what it puts me through.  Because I adore it.  Because it's mine.  Because it looks exactly like me.  It can barf all over me if it wants to--I just don't care." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105465-destiny-i-feel-is-also-a-relationship---a-play</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:13:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105465-destiny-i-feel-is-also-a-relationship---a-play]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Destiny, I feel, is also a relationship - a play between divine grace and willful self-effort." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143021-you-have-been-to-hell-ketut-he-smiled-of-course</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:14:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143021-you-have-been-to-hell-ketut-he-smiled-of-course]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been to hell, Ketut?&quot;
He smiled. Of course he's been there.
What's it like in hell?&quot; 
Same like in heaven,&quot; he said.
He saw my confusion and tried to explain. &quot;Universe is a circle, Liss.&quot;
He said. &quot;To up, to down -- all same, at end.&quot;
I remembered an old Christian mystic notion: As above, so below. 
I asked. &quot;Then how can you tell the difference between heaven and hell?&quot;
Because of how you go. Heaven, you go up, through seven happy places. Hell, you go down, through seven sad places. This is why it better for you to go up, Liss.&quot; He laughed.
Same-same,&quot; he said. &quot;Same in end, so better to be happy in journey.&quot;
I said, &quot;So, if heaven is love, then hell is.. &quot; 
Love, too,&quot; he said. 
Ketut laughed again, &quot;Always so difficult for young people to understand this!" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76389-the-great-sufi-poet-and-philosopher-rumi-once-advised-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76389-the-great-sufi-poet-and-philosopher-rumi-once-advised-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great Sufi poet and philosopher Rumi once advised his students to write down the three things they most wanted in life.  If any item on the list clashes with any other item, Rumi warned, you are destined for unhappiness.  Better to live a life of single-pointed focus, he taught.  But what about the benefits of living harmoniously among extremes?  What if you could somehow create an expansive enough life that you could synchronize seemingly incongruous opposites into a worldview that excludes nothing?" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226484-as-i-got-older-i-discovered-that-nothing-within-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:15:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226484-as-i-got-older-i-discovered-that-nothing-within-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I got older, I discovered that nothing within me cried out for a baby.  My womb did not seem to have come equipped with that famously ticking clock.  Unlike so many of my friends, I did not ache with longing whenever I saw an infant. (Though I did ache with longing, it is true, whenever I saw a good used-book shop)" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243857-at-some-point-as-richard-keeps-telling-me-you-gotta</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 11:18:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzi add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243857-at-some-point-as-richard-keeps-telling-me-you-gotta]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point, as Richard keeps telling me, you gotta let go and sit still and allow contentment to come to you.
Letting go, of course, is a scary enterprise for those of us who believe that the world revolves only because it has a handle on the top of it which we personally turn, and that if we were to drop this handle for even a moment, well – that would be the end of the universe. But try dropping it….Sit quietly for now and cease your relentless participation. Watch what happens. The birds do not crash dead out of the sky in mid-flight, after all. The trees do not wither and die, the rivers do not run red with blood. Life continues to go on…. Why are you so sure that your micromanagement of every moment in this whole world is so essential? Why don’t you let it be?" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
