<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/724387-anne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/724387-anne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:18:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Jim MORRISON]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24149-the-most-important-kind-of-freedom-is-to-be-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most important kind of freedom is to be what you really are. You trade in your reality for a role. You trade in your sense for an act. You give up your ability to feel, and in exchange, put on a mask. There can't be any large-scale revolution until there's a personal revolution, on an individual level. It's got to happen inside first." -- Jim MORRISON]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29218-above-all-don-t-lie-to-yourself-the-man-who-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:18:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29218-above-all-don-t-lie-to-yourself-the-man-who-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, don't lie to yourself. The man who lies to himself and listens to his own lie comes to a point that he cannot distinguish the truth within him, or around him, and so loses all respect for himself and for others. And having no respect he ceases to love." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30788-the-only-truth-is-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30788-the-only-truth-is-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only truth is music." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5054-if-you-look-for-truth-you-may-find-comfort-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5054-if-you-look-for-truth-you-may-find-comfort-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you look for truth, you may find comfort in the end; if you look for comfort you will not get either comfort or truth only soft soap and wishful thinking to begin, and in the end, despair." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/767-when-you-are-sorrowful-look-again-in-your-heart-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:19:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/767-when-you-are-sorrowful-look-again-in-your-heart-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are sorrowful look again in your heart, and you shall see that in truth you are weeping for that which has been your delight." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2661-it-is-always-the-false-that-makes-you-suffer-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:20:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Sri Nisargadatta Maharaj]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2661-it-is-always-the-false-that-makes-you-suffer-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is always the false that makes you suffer, the false desires and fears, the false values and ideas, the false relationships between people. Abandon the false and you are free of pain; truth makes happy, truth liberates." -- Sri Nisargadatta Maharaj]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227010-to-be-fully-seen-by-somebody-then-and-be-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:21:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227010-to-be-fully-seen-by-somebody-then-and-be-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be fully seen by somebody, then, and be loved anyhow - this is a human offering that can border on miraculous." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8141-people-think-that-a-liar-gains-a-victory-over-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:22:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8141-people-think-that-a-liar-gains-a-victory-over-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think that a liar gains a victory over his victim. What I’ve learned is that a lie is an act of self-abdication, because one surrenders one’s reality to the person to whom one lies, making that person one’s master, condemning oneself from then on to faking the sort of reality that person’s view requires to be faked…The man who lies to the world, is the world’s slave from then on…There are no white lies, there is only the blackest of destruction, and a white lie is the blackest of all." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241582-i-have-learned-now-that-while-those-who-speak-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:22:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241582-i-have-learned-now-that-while-those-who-speak-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have learned now that while those who speak about one's miseries usually hurt, those who keep silence hurt more." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60592-life-s-as-kind-as-you-let-it-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:24:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60592-life-s-as-kind-as-you-let-it-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's as kind as you let it be." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65474-whatever-satisfies-the-soul-is-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 17:24:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65474-whatever-satisfies-the-soul-is-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever satisfies the soul is truth." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 06:14:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27688-for-me-trees-have-always-been-the-most-penetrating-preachers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, trees have always been the most penetrating preachers. I revere them when they live in tribes and families, in forests and groves. And even more I revere them when they stand alone. They are like lonely persons. Not like hermits who have stolen away out of some weakness, but like great, solitary men, like Beethoven and Nietzsche. In their highest boughs the world rustles, their roots rest in infinity; but they do not lose themselves there, they struggle with all the force of their lives for one thing only: to fulfil themselves according to their own laws, to build up their own form, to represent themselves. Nothing is holier, nothing is more exemplary than a beautiful, strong tree. When a tree is cut down and reveals its naked death-wound to the sun, one can read its whole history in the luminous, inscribed disk of its trunk: in the rings of its years, its scars, all the struggle, all the suffering, all the sickness, all the happiness and prosperity stand truly written, the narrow years and the luxurious years, the attacks withstood, the storms endured. And every young farmboy knows that the hardest and noblest wood has the narrowest rings, that high on the mountains and in continuing danger the most indestructible, the strongest, the ideal trees grow.

     Trees are sanctuaries. Whoever knows how to speak to them, whoever knows how to listen to them, can learn the truth. They do not preach learning and precepts, they preach, undeterred by particulars, the ancient law of life.

     A tree says: A kernel is hidden in me, a spark, a thought, I am life from eternal life. The attempt and the risk that the eternal mother took with me is unique, unique the form and veins of my skin, unique the smallest play of leaves in my branches and the smallest scar on my bark. I was made to form and reveal the eternal in my smallest special detail.

     A tree says: My strength is trust. I know nothing about my fathers, I know nothing about the thousand children that every year spring out of me. I live out the secret of my seed to the very end, and I care for nothing else. I trust that God is in me. I trust that my labor is holy. Out of this trust I live.

     When we are stricken and cannot bear our lives any longer, then a tree has something to say to us: Be still! Be still! Look at me! Life is not easy, life is not difficult. Those are childish thoughts. Let God speak within you, and your thoughts will grow silent. You are anxious because your path leads away from mother and home. But every step and every day lead you back again to the mother. Home is neither here nor there. Home is within you, or home is nowhere at all.

     A longing to wander tears my heart when I hear trees rustling in the wind at evening. If one listens to them silently for a long time, this longing reveals its kernel, its meaning. It is not so much a matter of escaping from one's suffering, though it may seem to be so. It is a longing for home, for a memory of the mother, for new metaphors for life. It leads home. Every path leads homeward, every step is birth, every step is death, every grave is mother.

     So the tree rustles in the evening, when we stand uneasy before our own childish thoughts: Trees have long thoughts, long-breathing and restful, just as they have longer lives than ours. They are wiser than we are, as long as we do not listen to them. But when we have learned how to listen to trees, then the brevity and the quickness and the childlike hastiness of our thoughts achieve an incomparable joy. Whoever has learned how to listen to trees no longer wants to be a tree. He wants to be nothing except what he is. That is home. That is happiness." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286713-happiness-comes-from-within-it-is-not-dependent-on-external</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 06:19:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Brian Weiss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286713-happiness-comes-from-within-it-is-not-dependent-on-external]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness comes from within. It is not dependent on external things or on other people. You become vulnerable and can be easily hurt when your feelings of security and happiness depend on the behavior and actions of other people. Never give your power to anyone else." -- Brian Weiss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105275-with-me-illusions-are-bound-to-be-shattered-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 06:19:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Osho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105275-with-me-illusions-are-bound-to-be-shattered-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With me, illusions are bound to be shattered. I am here to shatter all illusions. Yes, it will irritate you, it will annoy you - that's my way of functioning and working. I will sabotage you from your very roots! Unless you are totally destroyed as a mind, there is no hope for you." -- Osho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143020-at-that-moment-of-realization-that-union-with-god-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 06:19:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anne add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143020-at-that-moment-of-realization-that-union-with-god-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At that moment of realization (that union with God is always present), that's when God let me go, let me slide through His fingers with this last compassionate, unspoken message:

You may return here once you have fully come to understand that you are always here." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
