<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72457-mirae]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/72457-mirae" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:20:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262075-i-ask-you-right-here-please-to-agree-with-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Chris Cleave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262075-i-ask-you-right-here-please-to-agree-with-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ask you right here please to agree with me that a scar is never ugly. That is what the scar makers want us to think. But you and I, we must make an agreement to defy them. We must see all scars as beauty. Okay? This will be our secret. Because take it from me, a scar does not form on the dying. A scar means, &lt;i&gt;I survived&lt;/i&gt;." -- Chris Cleave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16809-god-doesn-t-require-us-to-succeed-he-only-requires-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 09:20:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16809-god-doesn-t-require-us-to-succeed-he-only-requires-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God doesn't require us to succeed, he only requires that you try." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 10:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102209-it-took-me-a-long-time-and-most-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 10:14:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102209-it-took-me-a-long-time-and-most-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It took me a long time and most of the world to learn what I know about love and fate and the choices we make, but the heart of it came to me in an instant, while I was chained to a wall and being tortured. I realised, somehow, through the screaming of my mind, that even in that shackled, bloody helplessness, I was still free: free to hate the men who were torturing me, or to forgive them. It doesn’t sound like much, I know. But in the flinch and bite of the chain, when it’s all you’ve got, that freedom is an universe of possibility. And the choice you make between hating and forgiving, can become the story of your life." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58980-narrow-minds-devoid-of-imagination-intolerance-theories-cut-off-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 10:14:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58980-narrow-minds-devoid-of-imagination-intolerance-theories-cut-off-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Narrow minds devoid of imagination. Intolerance, theories cut off from reality, empty terminology, usurped ideals, inflexible systems. Those are the things that really frighten me. What I absolutely fear and loathe." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53618-which-is-worse-killing-with-hate-or-killing-without-hate</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 10:14:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53618-which-is-worse-killing-with-hate-or-killing-without-hate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Which is worse? Killing with hate or killing without hate?" -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106931-some-feelings-sink-so-deep-into-the-heart-that-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2009 02:08:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106931-some-feelings-sink-so-deep-into-the-heart-that-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some feelings sink so deep into the heart that only loneliness can help you find them again. Some truths are so painful that only shame can help you live with them. Some things are so sad that only your soul can do the crying for them." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33120-just-because-you-re-an-atheist-that-doesn-t-mean-you-wouldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 02:25:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33120-just-because-you-re-an-atheist-that-doesn-t-mean-you-wouldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you're an atheist, that doesn't mean you wouldn't love for things to have reasons for why they are." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116832-i-felt-suddenly-shy-i-was-not-used-to-shy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2010 02:26:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116832-i-felt-suddenly-shy-i-was-not-used-to-shy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt suddenly shy. I was not used to shy. I was used to shame. Shyness is when you turn your head away from something you want. Shame is when you turn your head away from something you do not want." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94221-some-knowledge-is-too-heavy-you-cannot-bear-it-your-father-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2013 06:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirae add a quote by Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94221-some-knowledge-is-too-heavy-you-cannot-bear-it-your-father-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some knowledge is too heavy...you cannot bear it...your Father will carry it until you are able." -- Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
