<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/725498-teeuhh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/725498-teeuhh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:42:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156125-wonder-and-love-and-great-sorrow-shook-schmendrick-the-magician</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Peter S. Beagle ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156125-wonder-and-love-and-great-sorrow-shook-schmendrick-the-magician]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wonder and love and great sorrow shook Schmendrick the Magician then, and came together inside him and filled him, filled him until he felt himself brimming and flowing with something that was none of these. He did not believe it, but it came to him anyway, as it had touched him twice before and left him more barren than he had been. This time, there was too much of it for him to hold; it spilled through his fingers and toes, welled up equally in his eyes and his hair and the hollows of his shoulders. There was too much to hold — too much ever to use; and still he found himself weeping with the pain of his impossible greed. He thought, or said, or sang, I did not know that I was so empty, to be so full." -- Peter S. Beagle ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181244-off-we-skip-like-the-most-heartless-things-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 21:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by J. M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181244-off-we-skip-like-the-most-heartless-things-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Off we skip like the most heartless things in the world, which is what children are, but so attractive; and we have an entirely selfish time, and then when we have need of special attention we nobly return for it, confident that we shall be rewarded instead of smacked." -- J. M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184113-fuck-what-is-written-landsman-says-you-know-what-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2009 07:28:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184113-fuck-what-is-written-landsman-says-you-know-what-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fuck what is written,&quot; Landsman says. “You know what?&quot; All at once he feels weary of ganefs and prophets, guns and sacrifices and the infinite gangster weight of God. He's tired of hearing about the promised land and the inevitable bloodshed required for its redemption. “I don't care what is written. I don't care what supposedly got promised to some sandal-wearing idiot whose claim to fame is that he was ready to cut his own son's throat for the sake of a hare-brained idea. I don't care about red heifers and patriarchs and locusts. A bunch of old bones in the sand. My homeland is in my hat. It's in my ex-wife's tote bag." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 13:31:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, Will,&quot; she said, &quot;What can we do? Whatever can we do? I want to live with you forever. I want to kiss you and lie down with you and wake up with you every day of my life till I die, years and years and years away. I don't want a memory, just a memory...&quot;

&quot;No,&quot; he said. &quot;Memory's a poor thing to have. It's your own real hair and mouth and arms and eyes and hands I want. I didn't know I could ever love anything so much. Oh, Lyra, I wish this night would never end! If only we could stay here like this, and the world could stop turning, and everyone else could fall into a sleep...&quot;

&quot;Everyone except us! And you and I could live here forever and just love each other.&quot;

&quot;I will love you forever; whatever happens. Till I die and after I die, and when I find my way out of the land of the dead, I'll drift about forever, all my atoms, till I find you again...&quot;

&quot;I'll be looking for you, Will, every moment, every single moment. And when we do find each other again, we'll cling together so tight that nothing and no one'll ever tear us apart. Every atom of me and every atom of you...We'll live in birds and flowers and dragonflies and pin trees and in clouds and in those little specks of light you see floating in sunbeams...And when they use our atoms to make new lives, they won't just be able to take one, they'll have to take two, one of you and one of me, we'll be joined so tight...&quot;

They lay side by side, hand in hand, looking at the sky." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127718-and-at-the-word-alone-will-felt-a-great-wave</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 13:32:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127718-and-at-the-word-alone-will-felt-a-great-wave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And at the word alone, Will felt a great wave of rage and despair moving outwards from a place deep within him, as if his mind were an ocean that some profound convulsion had disturbed. All his life he'd been alone, and now he must be alone again, and this infinitely precious blessing that had come to him must be taken away almost at once.He felt the wave build higher and steeper to darken the sky, he felt the crest tremble and begin to spill, he felt the great mass crashing down with the whole weight of the ocean behind it against the iron-bound coast of what had to be. And he felt himself crying aloud with more anger and pain than he had ever felt in his life, and he found Lyra just as helpless in his arms. But as the wave expended its force and the waters withdrew, the bleak rocks remained; there was no arguing with fate; neither his despair nor Lyra's had moved them a single inch." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184811-but-balthamos-couldn-t-tell-he-only-knew-that-half-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2009 13:37:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184811-but-balthamos-couldn-t-tell-he-only-knew-that-half-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But Balthamos couldn't tell; he only knew that half his heart had been extinguished. He couldn't keep still: he flew up again, scouring the sky as if to seek out Baruch in this cloud or that, calling, crying, calling; and then he'd be overcome with guilt, and fly down to urge Will to hide and keep quiet, and promise to watch over him tirelessly; and then the pressure of his grief would crush him to the ground, and he'd remember every instance of kindness and courage that Baruch had ever shown, and there were thousands, and he'd forgotten none of them; and he'd cry that a nature so gracious could ever be snuffed out, and he'd soar into the skies again, casting about in every direction, reckless and wild and stricken, cursing the air, the clouds, the stars." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322730-she-wasn-t-afraid-of-difficulties-what-frightened-her-was-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 21:22:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322730-she-wasn-t-afraid-of-difficulties-what-frightened-her-was-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wasn’t afraid of difficulties; what frightened her was being forced to choose one particular path.
Choosing a path meant having to miss out on others. She had a whole life to live and she was always thinking that, in future, she might regret the choices she made now.
‘I’m afraid of committing myself,’ she thought to herself. She wanted to follow all possible paths and so ended up following none.
Even in that most important area of her life, love, she had failed to commit herself. After her first romantic dissappointment, she had never again given herself entirely. She feared pain, loss and separation. These things were inevitable on the path to love, and the only way of avoiding them was by deciding not to take that path at all. In order not to suffer, you had to renounce love. It was like putting out your own eyes in order not to see the bad things in life." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322731-there-isn-t-any-particular-relationship-between-the-messages-except-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 21:25:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322731-there-isn-t-any-particular-relationship-between-the-messages-except-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There isn’t any particular relationship between the messages, except that the author has chosen them carefully, so that, when seen all at once, they produce an image of life that is beautiful and surprising and deep. There is no beginning, no middle, no end, no suspense, no moral, no causes, no effects. What we love in our books are the depths of many marvelous moments seen all at one time." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299988-does-the-cosmos-contain-keys-for-opening-my-diving-bell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 19:28:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299988-does-the-cosmos-contain-keys-for-opening-my-diving-bell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does the cosmos contain keys for opening my diving bell? A subway line with no terminus? A currency strong enough to buy my freedom back? We must keep looking." -- Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199997-if-i-were-to-be-made-a-knight-said-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 21:03:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199997-if-i-were-to-be-made-a-knight-said-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I were to be made a knight,&quot; said the Wart, staring dreamily into the fire, &quot;I should insist on doing my vigil by myself, as Hob does with his hawks, and I should pray to God to let me encounter all the evil in the world in my own person, so that if I conquered there would be none left, and, if I were defeated, I would be the one to suffer for it.&quot;

&quot;That would be extremely presumptuous of you,&quot; said Merlyn, &quot;and you would be conquered, and you would suffer for it.&quot;

&quot;I shouldn't mind.&quot;

&quot;Wouldn't you?  Wait till it happens and see.&quot;

&quot;Why do people not think, when they are grown up, as I do when I am young?&quot;

&quot;Oh dear,&quot; said Merlyn.  '&quot;You are making me feel confused.  Suppose you wait till you are grown up and know the reason?&quot;

&quot;I don't think that is an answer at all,&quot; replied the Wart, justly.

Merlyn wrung his hands.

&quot;Well, anyway,&quot; he said, &quot;suppose they did not let you stand against all the evil in the world?&quot;

&quot;I could ask,&quot; said the Wart.

&quot;You could ask,&quot; repeated Merlyn.

He thrust the end of his beard into his mouth, stared tragically into the fire, and began to munch it fiercely." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 21:03:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302478-you-could-not-give-up-a-human-heart-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You could not give up a human heart as you could give up drinking. The drink was yours, and you could give it up: but your lover’s soul was not your own: it was not at your disposal; you had a duty towards it." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260675-those-prancing-little-pants-wetters-come-here-to-learn-the-colorful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 21:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Scott Lynch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260675-those-prancing-little-pants-wetters-come-here-to-learn-the-colorful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those prancing little pants-wetters come here to learn the colorful and gentlemanly art of fencing, with its many sporting &lt;i&gt;limitations&lt;/i&gt; and its proscriptions against &lt;i&gt;dishonorable&lt;/i&gt; engagements. You on the other hand, you are going to learn how to &lt;i&gt;kill men with a sword&lt;/i&gt;." -- Scott Lynch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341117-alas-poor-men-their-destiny-when-all-goes-well-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 03:49:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Aeschylus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/341117-alas-poor-men-their-destiny-when-all-goes-well-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alas, poor men, their destiny. When all goes well a shadow will overthrow it. If it be unkind one stroke of a wet sponge wipes all the picture out; and that is far the most unhappy thing of all. 
-Cassandra" -- Aeschylus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108746-you-are-obvious-boy-you-are-difficult-to-miss-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 08:00:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108746-you-are-obvious-boy-you-are-difficult-to-miss-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are obvious, boy.  You are difficult to miss.  If you came to me in company with a purple lion, a green elephant, and a scarlet unicorn astride which was the King of England in his Royal Robes, I do believe that it is you and you alone that people would stare at, dismissing the others as minor irrelevancies." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321402-there-are-no-wrong-turnings-only-paths-we-had-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 21:12:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321402-there-are-no-wrong-turnings-only-paths-we-had-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no wrong turnings. Only paths we had not known we were meant to walk." -- Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215763-when-i-was-young-i-had-to-choose-between-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 17:18:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215763-when-i-was-young-i-had-to-choose-between-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was young, I had to choose between the life of being and the life of doing. And I leapt at the latter like a trout to a fly. But each deed you do, each act, binds you to itself and to its consequences, and makes you act again and yet again. Then very seldom do you come upon a space, a time like this, between act and act, when you may stop and simply be. Or wonder who, after all, you are." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172530-do-you-see-arren-how-an-act-is-not-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 17:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172530-do-you-see-arren-how-an-act-is-not-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you see, Arren, how an act is not, as young men think, like a rock that one picks up and throws, and it hits or misses, and that's the end of it. When that rock is lifted, the earth is lighter; the hand that bears it is heavier. When it is thrown, the circuits of the stars respond, and where it strikes or falls the universe is changed." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60233-does-the-walker-choose-the-path-or-the-path-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 20:59:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Garth Nix]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60233-does-the-walker-choose-the-path-or-the-path-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does the walker choose the path, or the path the walker?" -- Garth Nix]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72312-i-ve-no-surety-that-it-is-i-know-only-parts</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 18:43:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Emma Bull]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72312-i-ve-no-surety-that-it-is-i-know-only-parts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve no surety that it is. I know only parts of what I feel; I may be misnaming the whole. You dwell in my mind like a household spirit. All that I think is followed with, ‘I shall tell that thought to Eddi.’ Whatever I see or hear is colored by what I imagine you will say of it. What is amusing is twice so, if you have laughed at it. There is a way you have of turning your head, quickly with a little tilt, that seems more wonderful to me than the practiced movements of dancers. All this, taken together, I’ve come to think of as love, but it may not be.

It is not a comfortable feeling. But I find that, even so, I would wish the same feeling on you. The possibility that I suffer it alone–that frightens me more than all the host of the Unseelie Court." -- Emma Bull]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49304-could-fulfillment-ever-be-felt-as-deeply-as-loss-romantically</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 20:33:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Kiran Desai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49304-could-fulfillment-ever-be-felt-as-deeply-as-loss-romantically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Could fulfillment ever be felt as deeply as loss? Romantically she decided that love must surely reside in the gap between desire and fulfillment, in the lack, not the contentment. Love was the ache, the anticipation, the retreat, everything around it but the emotion itself." -- Kiran Desai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352437-i-need-to-feel-strongly-to-love-and-admire-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 13:02:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352437-i-need-to-feel-strongly-to-love-and-admire-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I need to feel strongly, to love and admire, just as desperately as I need to breathe." -- Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132311-once-i-was-a-master-at-recycling-leftovers-now-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2012 13:02:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132311-once-i-was-a-master-at-recycling-leftovers-now-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, I was a master at recycling leftovers. Now I cultivate the art of simmering memories." -- Jean-Dominique Bauby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/818089-a-writer-s-brush-is-a-warrior-s-bow-the-letters-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 18:59:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Teeuhh add a quote by Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/818089-a-writer-s-brush-is-a-warrior-s-bow-the-letters-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A writer’s brush is a warrior’s bow, the letters it shapes are arrows that must hit the mark on the page. The calligrapher is an archer, or a general on a battlefield. Someone wrote that long ago. She feels that way this morning. She is at war." -- Guy Gavriel Kay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
