<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/726871-shannon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/726871-shannon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:47:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29225-sometimes-people-are-good-and-they-do-just-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:47:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Mister Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29225-sometimes-people-are-good-and-they-do-just-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes people are good, and they do just what they should. But the very same people who are good sometimes are the very same people who are bad sometimes. It's funny but it's true. Its the same isn't it, for me and . . ." -- Mister Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42308-in-the-reggio-emilia-preschools-however-each-child-is-viewed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 12:20:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Louise Boyd Cadwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42308-in-the-reggio-emilia-preschools-however-each-child-is-viewed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the Reggio Emilia preschools, however, each child is viewed as infinitely capable, creative, and intelligent. The job of the teacher is to support these qualities and to challenge children in appropriate ways so that they develop fully." -- Louise Boyd Cadwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54279-it-would-be-good-thought-prince-andrei-glancing-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2008 12:58:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shannon add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54279-it-would-be-good-thought-prince-andrei-glancing-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be good,&quot; thought Prince Andrei, glancing at the little image that his sister had hung around his neck with such reverence and emotion, &quot;It would be good if everything were as clear and simple as it seems to Princess Marya . How good it would be to know where to seek help in this life, and what to expect after it, beyond the grave! How happy and at peace I should be if I could now say:&quot; Lord have mercy on me!... But to whom should I say this? To some power--- indefinable and incomprehensible, to which I not only cannot appeal, but which I cannot express in words---The Great All or Nothing,&quot; he said to himself, &quot;or to that God who has been sewn into this amulet by Marya? There is nothing certain, nothing except the nothingness of everything that is comprehensible to me, and the greatness of something incomprehensible but all important!" -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
