<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728521-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728521-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:09:43 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8941-i-ve-got-one-more-record-she-said-have-you-heard</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:09:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8941-i-ve-got-one-more-record-she-said-have-you-heard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've got one more record,' she said. 'Have you heard &quot;So Long, Letty&quot;? I suppose you have.'
Honestly, you don't understand--I haven't heard a thing.'
Nor known, nor smelt, nor tasted, he might have added; only hot-cheeked girls in hot secret rooms. The young maidens he had known at New Haven in 1914 had kissed men, saying 'There!', hands at the man's chest to push him away. Now there was this scarcely saved waif of disaster bringing him the essence of a continent..." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8943-one-writes-of-scars-healed-a-loose-parallel-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:13:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8943-one-writes-of-scars-healed-a-loose-parallel-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One writes of scars healed, a loose parallel to the pathology of the skin, but there is no such thing in the life of an individual. There are open wounds, shrunk sometimes to the size of a pin-prick but wounds still. The marks of suffering are more comparable to the loss of a finger, or of the sight of an eye. We may not miss them, either, for one minute in a year, but if we should there is nothing to be done about it." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8945-dick-tried-to-plunge-over-the-alpine-crevasse-between-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:15:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8945-dick-tried-to-plunge-over-the-alpine-crevasse-between-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dick tried to plunge over the Alpine crevasse between the sexes." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9415-she-took-her-hand-and-raised-her-brush-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 06:41:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9415-she-took-her-hand-and-raised-her-brush-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...she took her hand and raised her brush. For a moment it stayed trembling in a painful but exciting ecstacy in the air. Where to begin?--that was the question at what point to make the first mark? One line placed on the canvas committed her to innumerable risks, to frequent and irrevocable decisions. All that in idea seemed simple became in practice immediately complex; as the waves shape themselves symmetrically from the cliff top, but to the swimmer among them are divided by steep gulfs, and foaming crests. Still the risk must run; the mark made." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 06:47:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We die containing a richness of lovers and tribes, tastes we have swallowed, bodies we have plunged into and swum up as if rivers of wisdom, characters we have climbed into as if trees, fears we have hidden in as if caves. 

I wish for all this to be marked on by body when I am dead.  I believe in such cartography - to be marked by nature, not just to label ourselves on a map like the names of rich men and women on buildings.  We are communal histories, communal books.  We are not owned or monogamous in our taste or experience." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9417-we-sleep-to-time-s-hurdy-gurdy-we-wake-if-ever-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2008 06:58:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9417-we-sleep-to-time-s-hurdy-gurdy-we-wake-if-ever-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We sleep to time's hurdy-gurdy; we wake, if ever we wake, to the silence of God. And then, when we wake to the deep shores of time uncreated, then when the dazzling dark breaks over the far slopes of time, then it's time to toss things, like our reason, and our will; then it's time to break our necks for home.
There are no events but thoughts and the heart's hard turning, the heart's slow learning where to love and whom. The rest is merely gossip, and tales for other times." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
