<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728787-robert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728787-robert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 18:30:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23456-the-greatest-hazard-of-all-losing-one-s-self-can-occur</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 18:30:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23456-the-greatest-hazard-of-all-losing-one-s-self-can-occur]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest hazard of all, losing one’s self, can occur very quietly in the world, as if it were nothing at all. No other loss can occur so quietly; any other loss - an arm, a leg, five dollars, a wife, etc. - is sure to be noticed." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62718-i-would-say-about-individuals-a-individual-dies-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 12:26:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62718-i-would-say-about-individuals-a-individual-dies-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would say about individuals, A Individual dies when they cease to to be surprised. I am surprised every morning when I see the sunshine again. When I see an act of evil I don't accomodate, I don't accomodate myself to the violence that goes on everywhere. I am still so surprised! That is why I am against it. We must learn to be surprised." -- Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343028-it-is-my-strong-conviction-that-a-realist-conception-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 08:42:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/343028-it-is-my-strong-conviction-that-a-realist-conception-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is my strong conviction that a realist conception of human nature should be made a servant of an ethic of progressive justice and should not be made into a bastion of conservatism, particularly a conservatism which defends unjust privileges." -- Reinhold Niebuhr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183793-it-is-customary-to-blame-secular-science-and-anti-religious-philosophy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 14:22:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183793-it-is-customary-to-blame-secular-science-and-anti-religious-philosophy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is customary to blame secular science and anti-religious philosophy for the eclipse of religion in modern society. It would be more honest to blame religion for its own defeats. Religion declined not because it was refuted, but because it became irrelevant, dull, oppressive, insipid. When faith is completely replaced by creed, worship by discipline, love by habit; when the crisis of today is ignored because of the splendor of the past; when faith becomes an heirloom rather than a living fountain; when religion speaks only in the name of authority rather than with the voice of compassion--its message becomes meaningless." -- Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325385-i-am-no-friend-of-probability-theory-i-have-hated</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 17:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Erwin Schrödinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325385-i-am-no-friend-of-probability-theory-i-have-hated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am no friend of probability theory, I have hated it from the first moment when our dear friend [author:Max Born|9807] gave it birth. For it could be seen how easy and simple it made everything, in principle, everything ironed and the true problems concealed. Everybody must jump on the bandwagon [Ausweg]. And actually not a year passed before it became an official credo, and it still is." -- Erwin Schrödinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
