<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728855-will]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/728855-will" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:52:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2007 11:52:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/811-for-instance-on-the-planet-earth-man-had-always-assumed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For instance, on the planet Earth, man had always assumed that he was more intelligent than dolphins because he had achieved so much&amp;mdash;the wheel, New York, wars and so on&amp;mdash;whilst all the dolphins had ever done was muck about in the water having a good time. But conversely, the dolphins had always believed that they were far more intelligent than man&amp;mdash;for precisely the same reasons." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242948-i-ve-always-been-a-word-guy-i-like-weird-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 15:56:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242948-i-ve-always-been-a-word-guy-i-like-weird-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve always been a word guy, I like weird words and I like American slang and all that and words that are no longer being used… I like to drag them out of the box and wave them around… this is an interesting one, it’s amazing how in addition to punctuation just a little pause in the wrong place can just completely transform the meaning of something." -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70510-my-kids-are-starting-to-notice-i-m-a-little-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 15:57:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Will add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70510-my-kids-are-starting-to-notice-i-m-a-little-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My kids are starting to notice I'm a little different from the other dads. &quot;Why don't you have a straight job like everyone else?&quot; they asked me the other day. 

I told them this story: 
In the forest, there was a crooked tree and a straight tree. Every day, the straight tree would say to the crooked tree, &quot;Look at me...I'm tall, and I'm straight, and I'm handsome. Look at you...you're all crooked and bent over. No one wants to look at you.&quot; And they grew up in that forest together. And then one day the loggers came, and they saw the crooked tree and the straight tree, and they said, &quot;Just cut the straight trees and leave the rest.&quot; So the loggers turned all the straight trees into lumber and toothpicks and paper. And the crooked tree is still there, growing stronger and stranger every day." -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
