<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/729333-heather]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/729333-heather" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 13:19:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585342-and-if-there-s-anyone-out-here-tonight-that-doesn-t-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 13:19:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Demi Lovato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585342-and-if-there-s-anyone-out-here-tonight-that-doesn-t-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And if there's anyone out here tonight that doesn't feel beautiful enough, or doesn't feel worthy enought... You're wrong. Because you guys are all so incredible. And if you're dealing with any of the issues that I've dealt with, don't be afraid to speak up, because someone will be there for you. And if you think, you're alone, put on my music, because I'm going to be there for you" -- Demi Lovato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4550-there-is-never-a-sudden-revelation-a-complete-and-tidy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 19:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4550-there-is-never-a-sudden-revelation-a-complete-and-tidy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is never a sudden revelation, a complete and tidy explanation for why it happened, or why it ends, or why or who you are. You want one and I want one, but there isn't one. It comes in bits and pieces, and you stitch them together wherever they fit, and when you are done you hold yourself up, and still there are holes and you are a rag doll, invented, imperfect. And yet you are all that you have, so you must be enough. There is no other way." -- Marya Hornbacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125144-it-is-astounding-to-me-and-achingly-sad-that-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 21:18:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Mary Roach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125144-it-is-astounding-to-me-and-achingly-sad-that-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is astounding to me, and achingly sad, that with eighty thousand people on the waiting list for donated hearts and livers and kidneys, with sixteen a day dying there on that list, that more then half of the people in the position H's family was in will say no, will choose to burn those organs or let them rot. We abide the surgeon's scalpel to save our own lives, out loved ones' lives, but not to save a stranger's life. H has no heart, but heartless is the last thing you'd call her." -- Mary Roach]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
