<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/729825-beth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/729825-beth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 08:00:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297596-it-s-never-been-true-not-anywhere-at-any-time-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 08:00:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297596-it-s-never-been-true-not-anywhere-at-any-time-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's never been true, not anywhere at any time, that the value of a soul, of a human spirit, is dependent on a number on a scale.  We are unrepeatable beings of light and space and water who need these physical vehicles to get around.  When we start defining ourselves by that which can be measured or weighed, something deep within us rebels. 

We don't want to EAT hot fudge sundaes as much as we want our lives to BE hot fudge sundaes.  We want to come home to ourselves.  (p. 174-5)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297584-compulsive-eating-is-basically-a-refusal-to-be-fully-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:35:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297584-compulsive-eating-is-basically-a-refusal-to-be-fully-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...compulsive eating is basically a refusal to be fully alive.  No matter what we weigh, those of us who are compulsive eaters have anorexia of the soul.  We refuse to take in what sustains us.  We live lives of deprivation.  And when we can't stand it any longer, we binge.  The way we are able to accomplish all of this is by the simple act of bolting -- of leaving ourselves -- hundreds of times a day." -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297587-hell-is-wanting-to-be-somewhere-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297587-hell-is-wanting-to-be-somewhere-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . hell is wanting to be somewhere different from where you are.  Being one place and wanting to be somewhere else . . . .  Wanting life to be different from what it is.  That's also called leaving without leaving.  Dying before you die.  It's as if there is a part of you that so rails against being shattered by love that you shatter yourself first.  (p. 44)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297588-weight-too-much-or-too-little-is-a-by-product-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:41:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297588-weight-too-much-or-too-little-is-a-by-product-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Weight (too much or too little) is a by-product.  Weight is what happens when you use food to flatten your life.  Even with aching joints, it's not about food.  Even with arthritis, diabetes, high blood pressure.  It's about your desire to flatten your life.  It's about the fact that you've given up without saying so.  It's about your belief that it's not possible to live any other way -- and you're using food to act that out without ever having to admit it. (p. 53)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297590-our-work-is-not-to-change-what-you-do-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:44:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297590-our-work-is-not-to-change-what-you-do-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our work is not to change what you do, but to witness what you do with enough awareness, enough curiosity, enough tenderness that the lies and old decisions upon which the compulsion is based become apparent and fall away.  When you no longer believe that eating will save your life when you feel exhausted or overwhelmed or lonely, you will stop.  When you believe in yourself more than you believe in food, you will stop using food as if it were your only chance at not falling apart.  When the shape of your body no longer matches the shape of your beliefs, the weight disappears. (p. 80-81)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297592-when-you-believe-without-knowing-you-believe-that-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297592-when-you-believe-without-knowing-you-believe-that-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you believe without knowing you believe that you are damaged at your core, you also believe that you need to hide that damage for anyone to love you.  You walk around ashamed of being yourself.  You try hard to make up for the way you look, walk, feel.  Decisions are agonizing because if you, the person who makes the decision, is damaged, then how can you trust what you decide?  You doubt your own impulses so you become masterful at looking outside yourself for comfort.  You become an expert at finding experts and programs, at striving and trying hard and then harder to change yourself, but this process only reaffirms what you already believe about yourself -- that your needs and choices cannot be trusted, and left to your own devices you are out of control (p.82-83)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:48:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not a mistake.  You are not a problem to be solved.  But you won't discover this until you are willing to stop banging your head against the wall of shaming and caging and fearing yourself. (p. 84)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297594-when-you-ignore-your-belly-you-become-homeless-you-spend</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:54:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297594-when-you-ignore-your-belly-you-become-homeless-you-spend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you ignore your belly, you become homeless.  You spend your life trying to erase your own existence.  Apologizing for yourself.  Feeling like a ghost.  Eating to take up space, eating to give yourself the feeling that you have weight here, you belong here, you are allowed to be yourself -- but never quite believing it because you don't sense yourself directly.

. . . I started teaching a simple belly meditation in which I asked people to become aware of sensations in their belly (numbness and emptiness count as sensations).  Every time their mind wandered . . . I asked them to begin counting their breaths so they could anchor their concentration.  Starting with the number one and saying it on the out breath, they'd count to seven and begin again.  If they were able to stay concentrated on the sensations in their belly centers, they didn't need to use counting as a concentration anchor.

. . . you begin the process of bringing yourself back to your body, to your belly, to your breath because they -- not the mind medleys -- are here now.  And it is only here, only now that you can make a decision to eat or not eat.  To occupy your own body or to vacate your arms and your legs while still breathing and go through your days as a walking head.  

. . . Meditation is a tool to shake yourself awake.  A way to discover what you love.  A practice to return yourself to your body when the mind medleys threaten to usurp your sanity." -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297595-freedom-from-obsession-is-not-about-something-you-do-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 07:56:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297595-freedom-from-obsession-is-not-about-something-you-do-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom from obsession is not about something you do; it's about knowing who you are.  It's about recognizing what sustains you and what exhausts you.  What you love and what you think you love because you believe you can't have it.  (p. 163)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474322-for-in-grief-nothing-stays-put-one-keeps-on-emerging</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 06:58:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474322-for-in-grief-nothing-stays-put-one-keeps-on-emerging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For in grief nothing &quot;stays put.&quot;  One keeps on emerging from a phase, but it always recurs.  Round and round.  Everything repeats.  Am I going in circles, or dare I hope I am on a spiral?

But if a spiral, am I going up or down it?

How often -- will it be for always? -- how often will the vast emptiness astonish me like a complete novelty and make me say, &quot;I never realized my loss till this moment&quot;?  The same leg is cut off time after time." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474324-my-idea-of-god-is-not-a-divine-idea-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 07:00:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474324-my-idea-of-god-is-not-a-divine-idea-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My idea of God is not a divine idea.  It has to be shattered time after time.  He shatters it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474325-oh-god-god-why-did-you-take-such-trouble-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 07:47:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474325-oh-god-god-why-did-you-take-such-trouble-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh God, God, why did you take such trouble to force this creature out of its shell if it is now doomed to crawl back -- to be sucked back -- into it?" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474327-her-absence-is-like-the-sky-spread-over-everything-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 07:47:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474327-her-absence-is-like-the-sky-spread-over-everything-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her absence is like the sky, spread over everything.

But no, that is not quite accurate.  There is one place where her absence comes locally home to me, and it is a place I can't avoid.  I mean my own body.  It had such a different importance while it was the body of H.'s lover.  Now it's like an empty house." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474329-if-a-mother-is-mourning-not-for-what-she-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2011 07:07:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474329-if-a-mother-is-mourning-not-for-what-she-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a mother is mourning not for what she has lost but for what her dead child has lost, it is a comfort to believe that the child has not lost the end for which it was created.  And it is a comfort to believe that she herself, in losing her chief or only natural happiness, has not lost a greater thing, that she may still hope to &quot;glorify God and enjoy Him forever.&quot;  A comfort to the God-aimed, eternal spirit within her.  But not to her motherhood.  The specifically maternal happiness must be written off.  Never, in any place or time, will she have her son on her knees, or bathe him, or tell him a story, or plan for his future, or see her grandchild." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477171-i-see-now-that-my-faith-was-becoming-an-ally</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:48:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Jerry Sittser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477171-i-see-now-that-my-faith-was-becoming-an-ally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see now that my faith was becoming an ally rather than an enemy because I could vent anger freely, even toward God, without fearing retribution." -- Jerry Sittser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477172-gifts-of-grace-come-to-all-of-us-but-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:48:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Jerry Sittser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477172-gifts-of-grace-come-to-all-of-us-but-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gifts of grace come to all of us.  But we must be ready to see and willing to receive these gifts.  It will require a kind of sacrifice, the sacrifice of believing that, however painful our losses, life can still be good — good in a different way then before, but nevertheless good.  I will never recover from my loss and I will never got over missing the ones I lost.  But I still cherish life. . . .  I will always want the ones I lost back again.  I long for them with all my soul.  But I still celebrate the life I have found because they are gone.  I have lost, but I have also gained.  I lost the world I loved, but I gained a deeper awareness of grace.  That grace has enabled me to clarify my purpose in life and rediscover the wonder of the present moment." -- Jerry Sittser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37414-i-will-not-say-do-not-weep-for-not-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2011 10:51:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37414-i-will-not-say-do-not-weep-for-not-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will not say, do not weep, for not all tears are an evil." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487988-some-people-say-it-is-a-shame-others-even-imply</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 13:45:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Christine O'Keeffe Lafser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487988-some-people-say-it-is-a-shame-others-even-imply]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people say it is a shame.  Others even imply that it would have been better if the baby had never been created.  But the short time I had with my child is precious to me.  It is painful to me, but I still wouldn't wish it away.  I prayed that God would bless us with a baby.  Each child is a gift, and I am proud that we cooperated with God in the creation of a new soul for all eternity.  Although not with me, my baby lives." -- Christine O'Keeffe Lafser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487991-i-am-not-functioning-very-well-living-with-the-knowledge</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 13:47:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Christine O'Keeffe Lafser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487991-i-am-not-functioning-very-well-living-with-the-knowledge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not functioning very well.  Living with the knowledge that the baby is dead is painful.  I feel so far away from you, God.  I can only try to believe that you are sustaining me and guiding me through this.  Please continue to stand by my side." -- Christine O'Keeffe Lafser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532975-suffering-invites-us-to-place-our-hurts-in-larger-hands</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2012 15:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532975-suffering-invites-us-to-place-our-hurts-in-larger-hands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suffering invites us to place our hurts in larger hands. In Christ we see God suffering – for us. And calling us to share in God’s suffering love for a hurting world. The small and even overpowering pains of our lives are intimately connected with the greater pains of Christ. Our daily sorrows are anchored in a greater sorrow and therefore a larger hope." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:31:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is indeed full of peril, and in it there are many dark places; but still there is much that is fair, and though in all lands love is now mingled with grief, it grows perhaps the greater." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19977-it-s-really-a-wonder-that-i-haven-t-dropped-all-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:31:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19977-it-s-really-a-wonder-that-i-haven-t-dropped-all-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's really a wonder that I haven't dropped all my ideals, because they seem so absurd and impossible to carry out. Yet I keep them, because in spite of everything, I still believe that people are really good at heart." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78209-only-in-the-darkness-can-you-see-the-stars</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:32:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Martin Luther King, Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78209-only-in-the-darkness-can-you-see-the-stars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only in the darkness can you see the stars." -- Martin Luther King, Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5897-for-like-a-shaft-clear-and-cold-the-thought-pierced</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5897-for-like-a-shaft-clear-and-cold-the-thought-pierced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For like a shaft, clear and cold, the thought pierced him that in the end the Shadow was only a small and passing thing: there was light and high beauty for ever beyond its reach." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121683-there-is-some-good-in-this-world-and-it-s-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:33:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121683-there-is-some-good-in-this-world-and-it-s-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is some good in this world, and it's worth fighting for." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16357-little-by-little-one-travels-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:35:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16357-little-by-little-one-travels-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Little by little, one travels far" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37413-i-am-glad-you-are-here-with-me-here-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 21:35:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37413-i-am-glad-you-are-here-with-me-here-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am glad you are here with me. Here at the end of all things, Sam." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580360-at-present-we-are-on-the-outside-the-wrong-side</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:41:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/580360-at-present-we-are-on-the-outside-the-wrong-side]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At present we are on the outside… the wrong side of the door. We discern the freshness and purity of morning, but they do not make us fresh and pure. We cannot mingle with the pleasures we see. But all the pages of the New Testament are rustling with the rumor that it will not always be so. Someday, God willing, we shall get “in”… We will put on glory… that greater glory of which Nature is only the first sketch.

We do not want to merely “see” beauty -- though, God knows, even that is bounty enough. We want something else which can hardly be put into words–to be united with the beauty we see, to pass into it, to receive it into ourselves, to bathe in it, to become part of it." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380195-i-want-to-see-beauty-in-the-ugly-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:48:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Ann Voskamp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/380195-i-want-to-see-beauty-in-the-ugly-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to see beauty. In the ugly, in the sink, in the suffering, in the daily, in all the days before I die, the moments before I sleep." -- Ann Voskamp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457782-the-true-love-dare-to-move-into-his-presence-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 12:51:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beth add a quote by Ann Voskamp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/457782-the-true-love-dare-to-move-into-his-presence-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true Love Dare.  To move into His presence and listen to His love unending and know the grace uncontainable.  This is the vault of the miracles.  The only thing that can change us, the world, is this- all His love." -- Ann Voskamp]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
