<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731141-danielle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731141-danielle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 07:35:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 07:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25238-all-morning-i-struggled-with-the-sensation-of-stray-wisps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All morning I struggled with the sensation of stray wisps of one world seeping through the cracks of another. Do you know the feeling when you start reading a new book before the membrane of the last one has had time to close behind you?  You leave the previous book with ideas and themes -- characters even -- caught in the fibers of your clothes, and when you open the new book, they are still with you." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41293-they-were-all-fitting-into-place-the-jig-saw-pieces-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 07:37:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41293-they-were-all-fitting-into-place-the-jig-saw-pieces-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were all fitting into place, the jig-saw pieces. The odd strained shapes that I had tried to piece together with my fumbling fingers and they had never fitted. Frank's odd manner when  I spoke about Rebecca. Beatrice and her rather diffident negative attitude. The silence that I had always taken for sympathy and regret was a silence born of shame and embarrassment. It seemed incredible to me now that I had never understood. I wondered how many people there were in the world who suffered, and continued to suffer, because they could not break out from their own web of shyness and reserve, and in their blindness and folly built up a great wall in front of them that hid the truth. This was what I had done. I had built up false pictures in my mind and sat before them. I had never had the courage to demand the truth. Had I made one step forward out of my own shyness Maxim would have told these things four months, five months ago." -- Daphne Du Maurier]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
