<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731126-tabitha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731126-tabitha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 09:50:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9146-there-are-girls-lined-along-the-street-girls-in-miniskirts</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 09:50:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tabitha add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9146-there-are-girls-lined-along-the-street-girls-in-miniskirts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there are girls lined along the street, girls in miniskirts, thigh-highs, and halter tops.  The girls stand at the curbs as cars cruise by.  Key-lime Cadillac's, fire-red Tornadoes, wide-mouthed, trolling Lincolns, all in perfect shape.  Chrome glints.  Hubcaps shine.  Not a single rust spot anywhere.  But now the gleaming cars are slowing.  Windows are rolling down and girls are bending to chat with the drivers.  There are calls back and forth, the lifting of already miniscule skirts, and sometimes a flash of breast or an obscene gesture, the girls working it, laughing, high enough by 5am to be numb to the rawness between their legs and the residues of men no amount of perfume can get rid of.  It isn't easy to keep yourself clean on the street, and by this hour each of those young women smells in the places that count like a very ripe, soft French cheese…They're numb, too, to thoughts of babies left at home, six month olds with bad colds lying in used cribs, sucking on pacifiers, and having a hard time breathing…numb to the lingering taste of semen in their mouths along with peppermint gum, most of these girls, no more than 18, this curb on 12th street their first real place of employment, the most the country has to offer in the way of a vocation.  Where are they going to go from here?  They're numb to that, too, except for a couple who have dreams of singing backup or opening up a hair shop..." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
