<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731476-v-lee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/731476-v-lee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:21:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98532-because-once-alone-it-is-impossible-to-believe-that-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:21:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98532-because-once-alone-it-is-impossible-to-believe-that-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because, once alone, it is impossible to believe that one could ever have been otherwise. Loneliness is an absolute discovery." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193041-everybody-knows-if-you-are-too-careful-you-are-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 01:09:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Gertrude Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193041-everybody-knows-if-you-are-too-careful-you-are-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody knows if you are too careful you are so occupied in being careful that you are sure to stumble over something. " -- Gertrude Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399124-men-go-to-far-greater-lengths-to-avoid-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 01:43:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Dan Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399124-men-go-to-far-greater-lengths-to-avoid-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men go to far greater lengths to avoid what they fear than to obtain what they desire." -- Dan Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447517-it-s-important-in-life-to-conclude-things-properly-only-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 01:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447517-it-s-important-in-life-to-conclude-things-properly-only-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s important in life to conclude things properly. Only then can you let go. Otherwise you are left with words you should have said but never did, and your heart is heavy with remorse." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66966-they-fuck-you-up-your-mum-and-dad-they-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 02:02:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66966-they-fuck-you-up-your-mum-and-dad-they-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They fuck you up, your mum and dad.
  They may not mean to, but they do.
They fill you with the faults they had
  And add some extra, just for you.

But they were fucked up in their turn
  By fools in old-style hats and coats,
Who half the time were soppy-stern
  And half at one another's throats.

Man hands on misery to man.
  It deepens like a coastal shelf.
Get out as early as you can,
  And don't have any kids yourself." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7931-i-talk-to-god-but-the-sky-is-empty</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 10:12:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7931-i-talk-to-god-but-the-sky-is-empty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I talk to God but the sky is empty." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250372-this-is-why-we-call-people-exes-i-guess--</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2012 07:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250372-this-is-why-we-call-people-exes-i-guess--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["this is why we call people exes, I guess - because the paths that cross in the middle end up separating at the end. it's too easy to see an X as a cross-out. it's not, because there's no way to cross out something like that. the X is a diagram of two paths." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147184-so-many-things-i-had-thought-forgotten-return-to-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 09:11:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147184-so-many-things-i-had-thought-forgotten-return-to-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many things I had thought forgotten
Return to my mind with stranger pain:
Like letters that arrive addressed to someone
Who left the house so many years ago." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69992-parents-fuck-you-up-they-don-t-mean-to-but-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 09:12:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69992-parents-fuck-you-up-they-don-t-mean-to-but-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parents fuck you up. They don't mean to but they do.   " -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322533-uncontradicting-solitude-supports-me-on-its-giant-palm-and-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 09:12:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322533-uncontradicting-solitude-supports-me-on-its-giant-palm-and-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Uncontradicting solitude
Supports me on its giant palm;
And like a sea-anemone
Or simple snail, there cautiously
Unfolds, emerges, what I am." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505297-seriously-i-think-it-is-a-grave-fault-in-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 09:13:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505297-seriously-i-think-it-is-a-grave-fault-in-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seriously, I think it is a grave fault in life that so much time is wasted in social matters, because it not only takes up time when you might be doing individual private things, but it prevents you storing up the psychic energy that can then be released to create art or whatever it is. It's terrible the way we scotch silence &amp; solitude at every turn, quite suicidal. I can't see how to avoid it, without being very rich or very unpopular, &amp; it does worry me, for time is slipping by , and nothing is done. It isn't as if anything was gained by this social frivolity, It isn't: it's just a waste." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 06:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460624-history-is-that-certainty-produced-at-the-point-where-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History is that certainty produced at the point where the imperfections of memory meet the inadequacies of documentation." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/468626-we-live-in-time---it-holds-us-and-molds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 06:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Julian Barnes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/468626-we-live-in-time---it-holds-us-and-molds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live in time - it holds us and molds us - but I never felt I understood it very well. And I'm not referring to theories about how it bends and doubles back, or may exist elsewhere in parallel versions. No, I mean ordinary, everyday time, which clocks and watches assure us passes regularly: tick-tock, click-clock. Is there anything more plausible than a second hand? And yet it takes only the smallest pleasure or pain to teach us time's malleability. Some emotions speed it up, others slow it down; occasionally, it seems to go missing - until the eventual point when it really does go missing, never to return." -- Julian Barnes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474533-i-certainly-believe-we-all-suffer-damage-one-way-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 06:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Julian Barnes ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/474533-i-certainly-believe-we-all-suffer-damage-one-way-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I certainly believe we all suffer damage, one way or another. How could we not,except in a world of perfect parents, siblings, neighbours, companions? And then  there is the question on which so much depends, of how we react to the damage: whether we admit it or repress it,and how this affects our dealings with others.Some admit the damage, and try to mitigate it;some spend their lives trying to help others who are damaged; and there are those whose main concern is to avoid further damage to themselves, at whatever cost. And those are the ones who are ruthless, and the ones to be careful of." -- Julian Barnes ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2013 00:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You expected to be sad in the fall. Part of you died each year when the leaves fell from the trees and their branches were bare against the wind and the cold, wintery light. But you knew there would always be the spring, as you knew the river would flow again after it was frozen. When the cold rains kept on and killed the spring, it was as though a young person died for no reason." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 08:10:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By then I knew that everything good and bad left an emptiness when it stopped.  But if it was bad, the emptiness filled up by itself.  If it was good you could only fill it by finding something better." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 08:41:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 00:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/862537-there-is-a-world-out-there-so-new-so-random</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 10:22:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by A.M. Homes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/862537-there-is-a-world-out-there-so-new-so-random]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a world out there, so new, so random and disassociated that it puts us all in danger. We talk online, we ‘friend’ each other when we don’t know who we are really talking to – we fuck strangers. We mistake almost anything for a relationship, a community of sorts, and yet, when we are with our families, in our communities, we are clueless, we short-circuit and immediately dive back into the digitized version – it is easier, because we can be both our truer selves and our fantasy selves all at once, with each carrying equal weight." -- A.M. Homes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140515-it-has-been-said-time-heals-all-wounds-i-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 22:53:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Rose Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140515-it-has-been-said-time-heals-all-wounds-i-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said, 'time heals all wounds.' I do not agree. The wounds remain. In time, the mind, protecting its sanity, covers them with scar tissue and the pain lessens. But it is never gone." -- Rose Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121994-i-remember-awakening-one-morning-and-finding-everything-smeared-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121994-i-remember-awakening-one-morning-and-finding-everything-smeared-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember awakening one morning and finding everything smeared with the color of forgotten love." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121997-things-get-bad-for-all-of-us-almost-continually-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 22:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121997-things-get-bad-for-all-of-us-almost-continually-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things get bad for all of us, almost continually, and what we do under the constant stress reveals who/what we are." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121991-there-are-times-when-those-eyes-inside-your-brain-stare</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 22:54:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121991-there-are-times-when-those-eyes-inside-your-brain-stare]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are times when those eyes inside your brain stare back at you." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242925-i-wish-to-weep-but-sorrow-is-stupid-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2014 22:54:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242925-i-wish-to-weep-but-sorrow-is-stupid-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish to weep
but sorrow is
stupid.
I wish to believe
but belief is a
graveyard." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544527-pursuing-happiness-and-i-did-and-still-do-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 04:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544527-pursuing-happiness-and-i-did-and-still-do-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pursuing happiness, and I did, and still do, is not at all the same as being happy- which I think is fleeting, dependent on circumstances, and a bit bovine.

If the sun is shining, stand in it- yes, yes, yes. Happy times are great, but happy times pass- they have to- because time passes.

The pursuit of happiness is more elusive; it is lifelong, and it is not goal-centred.

What you are pursuing is meaning- a meaningful life. There's the hap- the fate, the draw that is yours, and it isn't fixed, but changing the course of the stream, or dealing new cards, whatever metaphor you want to use- that's going to take a lot of energy. There are times when it will go so wrong that you will barely be alive, and times when you realize that being barely alive, on your own terms, is better than living a bloated half-life on someone else's terms." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227358-i-loved-you-so-much-once-i-did-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 10:08:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227358-i-loved-you-so-much-once-i-did-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I loved you so much once. I did. More than anything in the whole wide world. Imagine that. What a laugh that is now. Can you believe it? We were so intimate once upon a time I can't believe it now. The memory of being that intimate with somebody. We were so intimate I could puke. I can't imagine ever being that intimate with somebody else. I haven't been." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111447-it-ought-to-make-us-feel-ashamed-when-we-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 10:08:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[V. Lee add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111447-it-ought-to-make-us-feel-ashamed-when-we-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It ought to make us feel ashamed when we talk like we know what we're talking about when we talk about love." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
