<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732229-sanam]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732229-sanam" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:23:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:23:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485711-my-thoughts-are-stars-i-cannot-fathom-into-constellations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My thoughts are stars I cannot fathom into constellations." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:24:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487705-there-are-infinite-numbers-between-0-and-1-there-s-1</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:24:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487705-there-are-infinite-numbers-between-0-and-1-there-s-1]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are infinite numbers between 0 and 1. There's .1 and .12 and .112 and an infinite collection of others. Of course, there is a bigger infinite set of numbers between 0 and 2, or between 0 and a million. Some infinities are bigger than other infinities. A writer we used to like taught us that. There are days, many of them, when I resent the size of my unbounded set. I want more numbers than I'm likely to get, and God, I want more numbers for Augustus Waters than he got. But, Gus, my love, I cannot tell you how thankful I am for our little infinity. I wouldn't trade it for the world. You gave me a forever within the numbered days, and I'm grateful." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487195-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws-everybody</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:24:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487195-what-a-slut-time-is-she-screws-everybody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a slut time is. She screws everybody." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485844-some-infinities-are-bigger-than-other-infinities</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:24:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485844-some-infinities-are-bigger-than-other-infinities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some infinities are bigger than other infinities." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479964-without-pain-how-could-we-know-joy-this-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:24:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479964-without-pain-how-could-we-know-joy-this-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without pain, how could we know joy?' This is an old argument in the field of thinking about suffering and its stupidity and lack of sophistication could be plumbed for centuries but suffice it to say that the existence of broccoli does not, in any way, affect the taste of chocolate." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490611-the-world-is-not-a-wish-granting-factory</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/490611-the-world-is-not-a-wish-granting-factory]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is not a wish-granting factory." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491534-it-s-a-metaphor-see-you-put-the-killing-thing-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:25:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491534-it-s-a-metaphor-see-you-put-the-killing-thing-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a metaphor, see: You put the killing thing right between your teeth, but you don't give it the power to do its killing." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:16:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:16:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:16:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without music, life would be a mistake." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:16:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:17:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:18:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:19:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292212-when-someone-loves-you-the-way-they-say-your-name</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:22:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Jess C. Scott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292212-when-someone-loves-you-the-way-they-say-your-name]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone loves you, the way they say your name is different. You know that your name is safe in their mouth." -- Jess C. Scott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:24:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197442-if-you-love-somebody-let-them-go-for-if-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 23:25:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197442-if-you-love-somebody-let-them-go-for-if-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love somebody, let them go, for if they return, they were always yours. If they don't, they never were." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369989-so-many-people-are-shut-up-tight-inside-themselves-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 20:22:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sanam add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369989-so-many-people-are-shut-up-tight-inside-themselves-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people are shut up tight inside themselves like boxes, yet they would open up, unfolding quite wonderfully, if only you were interested in them.&quot;

(&lt;i&gt;Initiation&lt;/i&gt;)" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
