<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732395-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732395-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 15:45:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 15:45:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1889-hello-babies-welcome-to-earth-it-s-hot-in-the-summer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hello babies. Welcome to Earth. It's hot in the summer and cold in the winter. It's round and wet and crowded. On the outside, babies, you've got a hundred years here. There's only one rule that I know of, babies-&quot;God damn it, you've got to be kind." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9341-now-behind-the-eyes-and-secrets-of-the-dreamers-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 20:47:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Dylan Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9341-now-behind-the-eyes-and-secrets-of-the-dreamers-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now behind the eyes and secrets of the dreamers in the streets rocked to sleep by the sea, see the titbits and topsyturvies, bobs and buttontops, bags and bones, ash and rind and dandruff and nailparings, saliva and snowflakes and moulted feathers of dreams, the wrecks and sprats and shells and fishbones, whale-juice and moonshine and small salt fry dished up by the hidden sea." -- Dylan Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34574-the-import-is-not-the-kind-of-work-woman-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 06:23:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34574-the-import-is-not-the-kind-of-work-woman-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The import is not the kind of work woman does, but rather the quality of the work she furnishes. She can give suffrage or the ballot no new quality, nor can she receive anything from it that will enhance her own quality.  Her development, her freedom, her independence, must come from and through herself.  First, by asserting herself as a personality, and not as a sex commodity.  Second, by refusing the right to anyone over her body; by refusing to bear children, unless she wants them; by refusing to be a servant to God, the State, society, the husband, the family, etc., by making her life simpler, but deeper and richer.  That is, by trying to learn the meaning and substance of life in all its complexities, by freeing herself from the fear of public opinion and public condemnation.  Only that, and not the ballot, will set woman free, will maker her a force hitherto unknown in the world, a force for real love, for peace, for harmony; a force of divine fire, of life-giving; a creator of free men and women. 

from Woman Suffrage- 1910" -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35090-the-point-is-the-brain-talks-to-itself-and-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2008 19:46:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35090-the-point-is-the-brain-talks-to-itself-and-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point is, the brain talks to itself, and by talking to itself changes its perceptions. To make a new version of the not-entirely-false model, imagine the first interpreter as a foreign correspondent, reporting from the world. The world in this case means everything out- or inside our bodies, including serotonin levels in the brain. The second interpreter is a news analyst, who writes op-ed pieces. They read each other's work. One needs data, the other needs an overview; they influence each other. They get dialogues going.

INTERPRETER ONE: Pain in the left foot, back of heel.
INTERPRETER TWO: I believe that's because the shoe is too tight.
INTERPRETER ONE: Checked that. Took off the shoe. Foot still hurts.
INTERPRETER TWO: Did you look at it?
INTERPRETER ONE: Looking. It's red.
INTERPRETER TWO: No blood?
INTERPRETER ONE: Nope.
INTERPRETER TWO: Forget about it.
INTERPRETER ONE: Okay.

Mental illness seems to be a communication problem between interpreters one and two.

An exemplary piece of confusion.

INTERPRETER ONE: There's a tiger in the corner.
INTERPRETER TWO: No, that's not a tiger- that's a bureau.
INTERPRETER ONE: It's a tiger, it's a tiger!
INTERPRETER TWO: Don't be ridiculous. Let's go look at it.

Then all the dendrites and neurons and serotonin levels and interpreters collect themselves and trot over to the corner.
If you are not crazy, the second interpreter's assertion, that this is a bureau, will be acceptable to the first interpreter. If you are crazy, the first interpreter's viewpoint, the tiger theory, will prevail. 
The trouble here is that the first interpreter actually sees a tiger. The messages sent between neurons are incorrect somehow. The chemicals triggered are the wrong chemicals, or the impulses are going to the wrong connections. Apparently, this happens often, but the second interpreter jumps in to straighten things out." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39403-the-word-fascism-has-now-no-meaning-except-in-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 21:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39403-the-word-fascism-has-now-no-meaning-except-in-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The word Fascism has now no meaning except in so far as it signifies &quot;something not desirable&quot;...In the case of a word like democracy, not only is there no agreed definition, but the attempt to make one is resisted from all sides.  It is almost universally felt that when we call a country democratic we are praising it: consequently the defenders of every kind of regime claim that it is a democracy, and fear that they might have to stop using the word if it were tied down to any one meaning." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39404-in-our-time-political-speech-and-writing-are-largely-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 21:10:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39404-in-our-time-political-speech-and-writing-are-largely-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our time, political speech and writing are largely the defense of the indefensible.  Things like the continuance of British rule in India, the Russian purges and deportations, the dropping of atom bombs on Japan, can indeed be defended, but only by arguments which are too brutal for most people to face, and which do not square with the professed aims of political parties.  Thus political language has to consist largely of euphemism, question-begging and sheer cloudy vagueness.  Defenseless villages are bombarded from the air, the inhabitants driven out into the countryside, the cattle machine-gunned, the huts set on fire with incendiary bullets: this is called pacification.  Millions of peasants are robbed of their farms and sent trudging along the roads with no more than they can carry: this is called transfer of population or rectification of frontiers.  People are imprisoned for years without trial, or shot in the back of the neck or sent to die of scurvy in Arctic lumber camps: this is called elimination of unreliable elements." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 22:28:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Groucho Marx ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find television very educating. Every time somebody turns on the set, I go into the other room and read a book." -- Groucho Marx ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 22:30:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413897-the-surface-of-the-earth-is-the-shore-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:05:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413897-the-surface-of-the-earth-is-the-shore-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The surface of the Earth is the shore of the cosmic ocean. On this shore, we've learned most of what we know. Recently, we've waded a little way out, maybe ankle-deep, and the water seems inviting. Some part of our being knows this is where we came from. We long to return, and we can, because the cosmos is also within us. We're made of star stuff. We are a way for the cosmos to know itself." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9996-i-don-t-know-where-i-m-going-but-i-m-on-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:08:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sandburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9996-i-don-t-know-where-i-m-going-but-i-m-on-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know where I'm going, but I'm on my way." -- Carl Sandburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51841-for-small-creatures-such-as-we-the-vastness-is-bearable</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:08:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51841-for-small-creatures-such-as-we-the-vastness-is-bearable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For small creatures such as we the vastness is bearable only through love." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5855-we-make-our-world-significant-by-the-courage-of-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:08:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5855-we-make-our-world-significant-by-the-courage-of-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we make our world significant by the courage of our questions and the depth of our answers" -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75468-it-s-a-lazy-saturday-afternoon-there-s-a-couple-lying-naked</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:09:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75468-it-s-a-lazy-saturday-afternoon-there-s-a-couple-lying-naked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a lazy Saturday afternoon, there's a couple lying naked in bed reading Encyclopediea Brittannica to each other, and arguing about whether the Andromeda Galaxy is more 'numinous' than the Ressurection. Do they know how to have a good time, or don't they?" -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153824-every-aspect-of-nature-reveals-a-deep-mystery-and-touches</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:11:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153824-every-aspect-of-nature-reveals-a-deep-mystery-and-touches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every aspect of Nature reveals a deep mystery and touches our sense of wonder and awe. Those afraid of the universe as it really is, those who pretend to nonexistent knowledge and envision a Cosmos centered on human beings will prefer the fleeting comforts of superstition. They avoid rather than confront the world. But those with the courage to explore the weave and structure of the Cosmos, even where it differs profoundly from their wishes and prejudices, will penetrate its deepest mysteries." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117586-the-size-and-age-of-the-cosmos-are-beyond-ordinary</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:11:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117586-the-size-and-age-of-the-cosmos-are-beyond-ordinary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The size and age of the Cosmos are beyond ordinary human understanding. Lost somewhere between immensity and eternity is our tiny planetary home. In a cosmic perspective, most human concerns seem insignificant, even petty. And yet our species is young and curious and brave and shows much promise. In the last few millennia we have made the most astonishing and unexpected discoveries about the Cosmos and our place within it, explorations that are exhilarating to consider. They remind us that humans have evolved to wonder, that understanding is a joy, that knowledge is prerequisite to survival. I believe our future depends on how well we know this Cosmos in which we float like a mote of dust in the morning sky." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178439-the-cosmos-is-all-that-is-or-was-or-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178439-the-cosmos-is-all-that-is-or-was-or-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Cosmos is all that is or was or ever will be. Our feeblest contemplations of the Cosmos stir us -- there is a tingling in the spine, a catch in the voice, a faint sensation, as if a distant memory, of falling from a height. We know we are approaching the greatest of mysteries." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:21:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:22:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:23:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267875-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:26:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267875-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there--on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432381-exploration-is-in-our-nature-we-began-as-wanderers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:27:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432381-exploration-is-in-our-nature-we-began-as-wanderers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Exploration is in our nature. We began as wanderers, and we are wanderers still. We have lingered long enough on the shores of the cosmic ocean. We are ready at last to set sail for the stars." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335173-we-make-our-purpose</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:27:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335173-we-make-our-purpose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We make our purpose." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377748-sailors-on-a-becalmed-sea-we-sense-the-stirring-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:27:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377748-sailors-on-a-becalmed-sea-we-sense-the-stirring-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sailors on a becalmed sea, we sense the stirring of a breeze." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460806-what-an-astonishing-thing-a-book-is-it-s-a-flat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:27:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460806-what-an-astonishing-thing-a-book-is-it-s-a-flat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What an astonishing thing a book is. It's a flat object made from a tree with flexible parts on which are imprinted lots of funny dark squiggles. But one glance at it and you're inside the mind of another person, maybe somebody dead for thousands of years. Across the millennia, an author is speaking clearly and silently inside your head, directly to you. Writing is perhaps the greatest of human inventions, binding together people who never knew each other, citizens of distant epochs. Books break the shackles of time. A book is proof that humans are capable of working magic.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Cosmos, Part 11: The Persistence of Memory&lt;/i&gt; (1980)]" -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411824-we-have-begun-to-contemplate-our-origins-starstuff-pondering-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:28:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411824-we-have-begun-to-contemplate-our-origins-starstuff-pondering-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have begun to contemplate our origins: starstuff pondering the stars; organized assemblages of ten billion billion billion atoms considering the evolution of atoms; tracing the long journey by which, here at least, consciousness arose." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389201-it-is-sometimes-said-that-scientists-are-unromantic-that-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:29:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/389201-it-is-sometimes-said-that-scientists-are-unromantic-that-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes said that scientists are unromantic, that their passion to figure out robs the world of beauty and mystery. But is it not stirring to understand how the world actually works — that white light is made of colors, that color is the way we perceive the wavelengths of light, that transparent air reflects light, that in so doing it discriminates among the waves, and that the sky is blue for the same reason that the sunset is red? It does no harm to the romance of the sunset to know a little bit about it." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405773-the-visions-we-offer-our-children-shape-the-future-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:34:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405773-the-visions-we-offer-our-children-shape-the-future-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The visions we offer our children shape the future. It _matters_ what those visions are. Often they become self-fulfilling prophecies. Dreams are maps." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378333-or-consider-a-story-in-the-jewish-talmud-left-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2012 19:41:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378333-or-consider-a-story-in-the-jewish-talmud-left-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Or consider a story in the Jewish Talmud left out of the Book of Genesis. (It is in doubtful accord with the account of the apple, the Tree of Knowledge, the Fall, and the expulsion from Eden.) In The Garden, God tells Eve and Adam that He has intentionally left the Universe unfinished. It is the responsibility of humans, over countless generations, to participate with God in a &quot;glorious&quot; experiment - the &quot;completing of the Creation.&quot; 
     The burden of such a responsibility is heavy, especially on so weak and imperfect a species as ours, one with so unhappy a history. Nothing remotely like &quot;completion&quot; can be attempted without vastly more knowledge than we have today. But, perhaps, if our very existence is at stake, we will find ourselves able to rise to this supreme challenge." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38103-after-all-these-years-i-see-that-i-was-mistaken</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 13:37:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38103-after-all-these-years-i-see-that-i-was-mistaken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all these years, I see that I was mistaken about Eve in the beginning; it is better to live outside the Garden with her than inside it without her." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20100-you-are-an-aperture-through-which-the-universe-is-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 13:39:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alan Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20100-you-are-an-aperture-through-which-the-universe-is-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are an aperture through which the universe is looking at and exploring itself." -- Alan Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
