<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732657-henry-lancaster-iii]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/732657-henry-lancaster-iii" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:41:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:41:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18038-the-world-is-a-tragedy-to-those-who-feel-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:41:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Horace Walpole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18038-the-world-is-a-tragedy-to-those-who-feel-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a tragedy to those who feel, but a comedy to those who think." -- Horace Walpole]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141567-life-could-have-been-different-if-the-meetings-which-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Theodore Zeldin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141567-life-could-have-been-different-if-the-meetings-which-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["life could have been different if the meetings which have decided its course had been less silent, superficial or routine, if more thoughts had been exchanged, if humanity had been more able to show itself in them" -- Theodore Zeldin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you hate people?

I don't hate them...I just feel better when they're not around." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41334-we-cannot-love-something-solely-because-it-has-been-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41334-we-cannot-love-something-solely-because-it-has-been-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot love something solely because it has been ignored. It must also be worthy of our attention. " -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 19:36:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111300-out-of-the-closets-and-into-the-museums-libraries-architectural</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 19:06:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by William Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111300-out-of-the-closets-and-into-the-museums-libraries-architectural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of the closets and into the museums, libraries, architectural monuments, concert halls, bookstores, recording studios and film studios of the world. Everything belongs to the inspired and dedicated thief…. Words, colors, light, sounds, stone, wood, bronze belong to the living artist. They belong to anyone who can use them. Loot the Louvre! A bas l’originalité, the sterile and assertive ego that imprisons us as it creates. Vive le vol-pure, shameless, total. We are not responsible. Steal anything in sight." -- William Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34023-walmart-s-largest-innovation-consists-in-getting-rid-of-the-central</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Steven Shaviro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34023-walmart-s-largest-innovation-consists-in-getting-rid-of-the-central]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Walmart]s largest innovation consists in getting rid of the central Fordist principle of paying the workers enough so that they can afford to buy what they manufacture. Instead, WalMart has pioneered the inverse principle: paying the workers so little that they cannot afford to shop anywhere other than at WalMart. It might even be said, not too hyperbolically, that WalMart has singlehandedly preserved the American economy from total collapse, in that their lowered prices are the only thing that has allowed millions of the “working poor” to retain the status of consumers at all, rather than falling into the “black hole” of total immiseration. WalMart is part and parcel of how the “new economy” has largely been founded upon transferring wealth from the less wealthy to the already-extremely-rich. " -- Steven Shaviro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7834-we-live-in-a-world-where-there-is-more-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 10:49:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Jean Baudrillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7834-we-live-in-a-world-where-there-is-more-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live in a world where there is more and more information, and less and less meaning." -- Jean Baudrillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114988-curiosity-is-insubordination-in-its-purest-form</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2010 22:11:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114988-curiosity-is-insubordination-in-its-purest-form]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Curiosity is insubordination in its purest form." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76028-we-live-together-we-act-on-and-react-to-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 21:34:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76028-we-live-together-we-act-on-and-react-to-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We live together, we act on, and react to, one another; but always and in all circumstances we are by ourselves. The martyrs go hand in hand into the arena; they are crucified alone. Embraced, the lovers desperately try to fuse their insulated ecstasies into a single self-transcendence; in vain. By its very nature every embodied spirit is doomed to suffer and enjoy in solitude. Sensations, feelings, insights, fancies—all these are private and, except through symbols and at second hand, incommunicable. We can pool information about experiences, but never the experiences themselves. From family to nation, every human group is a society of island universes." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122943-although-i-have-felt-compelled-to-write-things-down-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2013 13:30:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Henry add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122943-although-i-have-felt-compelled-to-write-things-down-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although I have felt compelled to write things down since I was five years old, I doubt that my daughter ever will, for she is a singularly blessed and accepting child, delighted with life exactly as life presents itself to her, unafraid to go to sleep and unafraid to wake up.  Keepers of private notebooks are a different breed altogether, lonely and resistant rearrangers of things, anxious malcontents, children afflicted apparently at birth with some presentiment of loss." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
