<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733051-gilly-mcgillicuddy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733051-gilly-mcgillicuddy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:13:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15430-they-were-looking-after-themselves-living-with-rigid-economy-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15430-they-were-looking-after-themselves-living-with-rigid-economy-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were looking after themselves, living with rigid economy; and there was no greater proof of their friendship than the way their harmony withstood their very grave differences in domestic behaviour. In Jack's opinion Stephen was little better than a slut: his papers, odd bits of dry, garlic'd bread, his razors and small-clothes lay on and about his private table in a miserable squalor; and from the appearance of the grizzled wig that was now acting as a tea-cosy for his milk-saucepan, it was clear that he had breakfasted on marmalade.
Jack took off his coat, covered his waistcoat and breeches with an apron, and carried the dishes into the scullery. 'My plate and saucer will serve again,' said Stephen. 'I have blown upon them. I do wish, Jack,' he cried, 'that you would leave that milk-saucepan alone. It is perfectly clean. What more sanitary, what more wholesome, than scalded milk?" -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15433-the-squadron-of-men-of-war-and-transports-was-collected-the-commodore-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:17:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Frederick Marryat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15433-the-squadron-of-men-of-war-and-transports-was-collected-the-commodore-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The squadron of men-of-war and transports was collected, the commodore’s flag hoisted, and the expedition sailed with most secret orders, which, as usual, were as well known to the enemy, and everybody in England, as they were to those by whom they were given. It is the characteristic of our nation, that we scorn to take any unfair advantage, or reap any benefit, by keeping our intentions a secret. We imitate the conduct of that English tar, who, having entered a fort, and meeting a Spanish officer without his sword, being providentially supplied with two cut-lasses himself, immediately offered him one, that they might engage on fair terms.

The idea is generous, but not wise. But I rather imagine that this want of secrecy arises from all matters of importance being arranged by cabinet councils. In the multitude of counsellors there may be wisdom, but there certainly is not secrecy. Twenty men have probably twenty wives, and it is therefore twenty to one but the secret transpires through that channel. Further, twenty men have twenty tongues; and much as we complain of women not keeping secrets, I suspect that men deserve the odium of the charge quite as much, if not more, than women do. On the whole, it is forty to one against secrecy, which, it must be acknowledged, are long odds.

On the arrival of the squadron at the point of attack, a few more days were thrown away,—probably upon the same generous principle of allowing the enemy sufficient time for preparation." -- Frederick Marryat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15435-squeeze-squeeze-squeeze-all-the-morning-long-i-squeezed-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:21:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15435-squeeze-squeeze-squeeze-all-the-morning-long-i-squeezed-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Squeeze! Squeeze! Squeeze! all the morning long; I squeezed that sperm till I myself almost melted into it; I squeezed that sperm till a strange sort of insanity came over me, and I found myself unwittingly squeezing my co-labourers' hands in it, mistaking their hands for the gentle globules. Such an abounding, affectionate, friendly, loving feeling did this avocation beget; that at last I was continually squeezing their hands, and looking up into their eyes sentimentally, as much as to say,—Oh! my dear fellow beings, why should we longer cherish any social acerbities, or know the slightest ill humour or envy! Come; let us squeeze hands all round; nay, let us all squeeze ourselves into each other; let us squeeze ourselves universally into the very milk and sperm of kindness." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15436-it-s-all-along-of-the-unicorn-s-horn-it-s-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15436-it-s-all-along-of-the-unicorn-s-horn-it-s-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s all along of the unicorn’s horn – it’s all along of the glorious hand. Huzzay, three times huzzay for the doctor!’

Lord, how they cheered their surgeon! It was he who had brought the narwhal’s tusk aboard: and the severed hand, the Hand of Glory, was his property: both symbolized (and practically guaranteed) immense good fortune, virility, safety from poison or any disease you chose to name: and both had proved their worth." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15437-he-reflected-on-his-hitherto-reflection-that-soldiers-and-sailors</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:26:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15437-he-reflected-on-his-hitherto-reflection-that-soldiers-and-sailors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He reflected on his hitherto reflection that soldiers and sailors were, upon the whole, quite different creatures. ‘And perhaps they are, too: yet perhaps drink, in very large quantities, may make the difference less evident." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15444-no-man-born-of-woman-has-ever-understood-spoken-portuguese</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:35:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15444-no-man-born-of-woman-has-ever-understood-spoken-portuguese]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man born of woman has ever understood spoken Portuguese." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15456-touch-and-away-jack-asked-stephen-touch-and-away-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 08:12:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15456-touch-and-away-jack-asked-stephen-touch-and-away-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Touch and away, Jack?’ asked Stephen. ‘Touch and away? Do you not recall that I have important business there? Enquiries of the very first interest?’

To do with our enterprise? To do with this voyage?’

Perhaps not quite directly." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15475-go-and-see-whether-the-doctor-is-about-said-jack</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 08:46:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15475-go-and-see-whether-the-doctor-is-about-said-jack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go and see whether the Doctor is about,’ said Jack, ‘and if he is, ask him to look in, when he has a moment.’
Which he is in the fish-market, turning over some old-fashioned lobsters. No. I tell a lie. That is him, falling down the companion-way and cursing in foreign." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16430-you-have-nice-manners-for-a-thief-and-a-liar</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 12:40:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16430-you-have-nice-manners-for-a-thief-and-a-liar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have nice manners for a thief and a liar,&quot; said the dragon." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 06:02:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stephen had been put to sleep in his usual room, far from children and noise, away in that corner of the house which looked down to the orchard and the bowling-green, and in spite of his long absence it was so familiar to him that when he woke at about three he made his way to the window almost as quickly as if dawn had already broken, opened it and walked out onto the balcony. The moon had set: there was barely a star to be seen. The still air was delightfully fresh with falling dew, and a late nightingale, in an indifferent voice, was uttering a routine jug-jug far down in Jack's plantations; closer at hand and more agreeable by far, nightjars churred in the orchard, two of them, or perhaps three, the sound rising and falling, intertwining so that the source could not be made out for sure. There were few birds that he preferred to nightjars, but it was not they that had brought him out of bed: he stood leaning on the balcony rail and presently Jack Aubrey, in a summer-house by the bowling-green, began again, playing very gently in the darkness, improvising wholly for himself, dreaming away on his violin with a mastery that Stephen had never heard equalled, though they had played together for years and years.

Like many other sailors Jack Aubrey had long dreamed of lying in his warm bed all night long; yet although he could now do so with a clear conscience he often rose at unChristian hours, particularly if he were moved by strong emotion, and crept from his bedroom in a watch-coat, to walk about the house or into the stables or to pace the bowling-green. Sometimes he took his fiddle with him. He was in fact a better player than Stephen, and now that he was using his precious Guarnieri rather than a robust sea-going fiddle the difference was still more evident: but the Guarnieri did not account for the whole of it, nor anything like. Jack certainly concealed his excellence when they were playing together, keeping to Stephen's mediocre level: this had become perfectly clear when Stephen's hands were at last recovered from the thumb-screws and other implements applied by French counter-intelligence officers in Minorca; but on reflexion Stephen thought it had been the case much earlier, since quite apart from his delicacy at that period, Jack hated showing away.

Now, in the warm night, there was no one to be comforted, kept in countenance, no one could scorn him for virtuosity, and he could let himself go entirely; and as the grave and subtle music wound on and on, Stephen once more contemplated on the apparent contradiction between the big, cheerful, florid sea-officer whom most people liked on sight but who would have never been described as subtle or capable of subtlety by any one of them (except perhaps his surviving opponents in battle) and the intricate, reflective music he was now creating. So utterly unlike his limited vocabulary in words, at times verging upon the inarticulate.

'My hands have now regained the moderate ability they possessed before I was captured,' observed Maturin, 'but his have gone on to a point I never thought he could reach: his hands and his mind. I am amazed. In his own way he is the secret man of the world." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
