<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733453-darcy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733453-darcy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:08:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50637-each-of-us-is-all-the-sums-he-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:08:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50637-each-of-us-is-all-the-sums-he-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each of us is all the sums he has not counted: subtract us into the nakedness and night again, and you shall see begin in Crete four thousand years ago the love that ended yesterday in Texas." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8525-what-is-that-feeling-when-you-re-driving-away-from-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:08:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8525-what-is-that-feeling-when-you-re-driving-away-from-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is that feeling when you're driving away from people and they recede on the plain till you see their specks dispersing? - it's the too-huge world vaulting us, and it's good-bye. But we lean forward to the next crazy venture beneath the skies." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56032-sometimes-when-we-lose-ourselves-in-fear-and-despair-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Zach Helm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56032-sometimes-when-we-lose-ourselves-in-fear-and-despair-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, when we lose ourselves in fear and despair, in routine and constancy, in hopelessness and tragedy, we can thank God for Bavarian sugar cookies. And, fortunately, when there aren't any cookies, we can still find reassurance in a familiar hand on our skin, or a kind and loving gesture, or subtle encouragement, or a loving embrace, or an offer of comfort, not to mention hospital gurneys and nose plugs, an uneaten Danish, soft-spoken secrets, and Fender Stratocasters, and maybe the occasional piece of fiction. And we must remember that all these things, the nuances, the anomalies, the subtleties, which we assume only accessorize our days, are effective for a much larger and nobler cause. They are here to save our lives. I know the idea seems strange, but I also know that it just so happens to be true." -- Zach Helm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13466-go-then-there-are-other-worlds-than-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 16:08:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13466-go-then-there-are-other-worlds-than-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go then, there are other worlds than these." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242745-world-is-crazier-and-more-of-it-than-we-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 15:21:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Louis MacNeice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242745-world-is-crazier-and-more-of-it-than-we-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["World is crazier and more of it than we think,
Incorrigibly plural. I peel and portion
A tangerine and spit the pips and feel
The drunkenness of things being various." -- Louis MacNeice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85720-show-me-a-man-or-a-woman-alone-and-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 08:48:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Stephen King ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85720-show-me-a-man-or-a-woman-alone-and-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Show me a man or a woman alone and I'll show you a saint. Give me two and they'll fall in love. Give me three and they'll invent the charming thing we call 'society'. Give me four and they'll build a pyramid. Give me five and they'll make one an outcast. Give me six and they'll reinvent prejudice. Give me seven and in seven years they'll reinvent warfare. Man may have been made in the image of God, but human society was made in the image of His opposite number, and is always trying to get back home." -- Stephen King ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 13:19:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 08:13:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many vows... they make you swear and swear. Defend the king. Obey the king. Keep his secrets. Do his bidding. Your life for his. But obey your father. Love your sister. Protect the innocent. Defend the weak. Respect the gods. Obey the laws. It’s too much. No matter what you do, you’re forsaking one vow or the other." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10393-the-true-secret-in-being-a-hero-lies-in-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:48:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10393-the-true-secret-in-being-a-hero-lies-in-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true secret in being a hero lies in knowing the order of things. The swineherd cannot already be wed to the princess when he embarks on his adventures, nor can the boy knock on the witch's door when she is already away on vacation. The wicked uncle cannot be found out and foiled before he does something wicked. Things must happen when it is time for them to happen. Quests may not simply be abandoned; prophecies may not be left to rot like unpicked fruit; unicorns may go unrescued for a very long time, but not forever. The happy ending cannot come in the middle of the story." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34244-when-i-was-alive-i-believed-as-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was alive, I believed — as you do — that time was at least as real and solid as myself, and probably more so. I said 'one o'clock' as though I could see it, and 'Monday' as though I could find it on the map; and I let myself be hurried along from minute to minute, day to day, year to year, as though I were actually moving from one place to another. Like everyone else, I lived in a house bricked up with seconds and minutes, weekends and New Year's Days, and I never went outside until I died, because there was no other door. Now I know that I could have walked through the walls. (...) You can strike your own time, and start the count anywhere. When you understand that — then any time at all will be the right time for you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never put off till tomorrow what may be done day after tomorrow just as well&quot;. 

From: &quot;More Maxims of Mark" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:51:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 16:57:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hide your ignorance, no one will hit you and you'll never learn." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133838-we-do-survive-every-moment-after-all-except-the-last</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 15:11:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133838-we-do-survive-every-moment-after-all-except-the-last]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do survive every moment, after all, except the last one." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235451-souls-cross-ages-like-clouds-cross-skies-an-tho-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2011 09:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235451-souls-cross-ages-like-clouds-cross-skies-an-tho-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Souls cross ages like clouds cross skies, an' tho' a cloud's shape nor hue nor size don't stay the same, it's still a cloud an' so is a soul. Who can say where the cloud's blowed from or who the soul'll be 'morrow? Only Sonmi the east an' the west an' the compass an' the atlas, yay, only the atlas o' clouds." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30600-child-child-have-patience-and-belief-for-life-is-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 10:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30600-child-child-have-patience-and-belief-for-life-is-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Child, child, have patience and belief, for life is many days, and each present hour will pass away. Son, son, you have been mad and drunken, furious and wild, filled with hatred and despair, and all the dark confusions of the soul - but so have we. You found the earth too great for your one life, you found your brain and sinew smaller than the hunger and desire that fed on them - but it has been this way with all men. You have stumbled on in darkness, you have been pulled in opposite directions, you have faltered, you have missed the way, but, child, this is the chronicle of the earth.  And now, because you have known madness and despair, and because you will grow desperate again before you come to evening, we who have stormed the ramparts of the furious earth and been hurled back, we who have been maddened by the unknowable and bitter mystery of love, we who have hungered after fame and savored all of life, the tumult, pain, and frenzy, and now sit quietly by our windows watching all that henceforth never more shall touch us - we call upon you to take heart, for we can swear to you that these things pass." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186721-you-stand-there-braced-cloud-shadows-race-over-the-buff</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 13:07:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Annie Proulx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186721-you-stand-there-braced-cloud-shadows-race-over-the-buff]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You stand there, braced.  Cloud shadows race over the buff rock stacks as a projected film, casting a queasy, mottled ground rash.  The air hisses and it is no local breeze but the great harsh sweep of wind from the turning of the earth.  The wild country--indigo jags of mountain, grassy plain everlasting, tumbled stones like fallen cities, the flaring roll of sky--provokes a spiritual shudder.  It is like a deep note that cannot be heard but is felt, it is like a claw in the gut...
...Other cultures have camped here a while and disappeared.  Only earth and sky matter.  Only the endlessly repeated flood of morning light.  You begin to see that God does not owe us much beyond that." -- Annie Proulx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489084-he-wished-he-was-with-his-mom-in-her-library</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 11:58:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Brian Selznick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/489084-he-wished-he-was-with-his-mom-in-her-library]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wished he was with his mom in her library, where everything was safe and numbered and organized by the Dewey decimal system.  Ben wished the world was organized by the Dewey decimal system.  That way you'd be able to find whatever you were looking for, like the meaning of your dream, or your dad." -- Brian Selznick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31631-we-are-not-enemies-but-friends-we-must-not-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 12:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31631-we-are-not-enemies-but-friends-we-must-not-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not enemies, but friends. We must not be enemies. Though passion may have strained, it must not break our bonds of affection. The mystic chords of memory will swell when again touched, as surely they will be, by the better angels of our nature." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511729-the-place-was-packed-as-we-flooded-in-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 10:27:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Craig Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/511729-the-place-was-packed-as-we-flooded-in-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place was packed as we flooded in, all the patrons freezing at the sight of an armed sheriff, two deputies, an Indian, and a construction worker; we probably looked like the Village People." -- Craig Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565982-what-do-you-think-dignity-s-all-about-the-directness-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 15:41:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565982-what-do-you-think-dignity-s-all-about-the-directness-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do you think dignity's all about?'

The directness of the inquiry did, I admit, take me rather by surprise. 'It's rather a hard thing to explain in a few words, sir,' I said. 'But I suspect it comes down to not removing one's clothing in public." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50163-there-are-things-known-and-there-are-things-unknown-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 15:28:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50163-there-are-things-known-and-there-are-things-unknown-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are things known and there are things unknown, and in between are the doors of perception." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488976-here-it-s--can-i-say-it-s-like-the-song-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 08:54:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Patrick Ness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488976-here-it-s--can-i-say-it-s-like-the-song-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HERE
It’s-
Can I say?
It’s like the song of a family where everything’s always all right, it’s a song of belonging that makes you belong just by hearing it, it’s a song that’ll always take care of you and never leave you. If you have a heart, it breaks, if you have a heart that’s broken, it fixes." -- Patrick Ness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336809-above-all-do-not-lose-your-desire-to-walk-everyday</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 12:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336809-above-all-do-not-lose-your-desire-to-walk-everyday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, do not lose your desire to walk.  Everyday, I walk myself into a state of well-being &amp; walk away from every illness.  I have walked myself into my best thoughts, and I know of no thought so burdensome that one cannot walk away from it.  But by sitting still, &amp; the more one sits still, the closer one comes to feeling ill.  Thus if one just keeps on walking, everything will be all right." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779582-to-multiply-the-years-and-divide-by-the-desire-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 15:38:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Peter Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779582-to-multiply-the-years-and-divide-by-the-desire-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To multiply the years and divide by the desire to live is a kind of false accounting." -- Peter Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212610-when-the-dark-comes-rising-six-shall-turn-it-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 10:25:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212610-when-the-dark-comes-rising-six-shall-turn-it-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the Dark comes rising six shall turn it back;
Three from the circle, three from the track;
Wood, bronze, iron; Water, fire, stone;
Five will return and one go alone.

Iron for the birthday; bronze carried long;
Wood from the burning; stone out of song;
Fire in the candle ring; water from the thaw;
Six signs the circle and the grail gone before.

Fire on the mountain shall find the harp of gold
Played to wake the sleepers, oldest of old.
Power from the Green Witch, lost beneath the sea.
All shall find the Light at last, silver on the tree." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480046-suddenness-he-says-you-do-not-prepare-you-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 15:37:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Téa Obreht]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480046-suddenness-he-says-you-do-not-prepare-you-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suddenness,&quot; he says.  &quot; You do not prepare, you do not explain, you do not apologize.  Suddenly, you go.  And with you, you take all contemplation, all consideration of your own departure.  All the suffering that would have come from knowing comes after you are gone, and you are not a part of it." -- Téa Obreht]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673387-i-know-it-s-not-thematically-in-tune-with-my-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2013 09:48:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darcy add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/673387-i-know-it-s-not-thematically-in-tune-with-my-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it's not thematically in tune with my new job and all, but I find it effective. Build a man a fire and he's warm for a day,&quot; I say. &quot;But set a man on fire and he's warm for the rest of his life. Tao of Pratchett. I live by it." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
