<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733974-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/733974-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 10:15:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48871-dear-me-how-i-love-a-library</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 10:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48871-dear-me-how-i-love-a-library]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear me, how I love a library." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 10:16:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4352-how-do-people-like-not-curse-how-is-it-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do people, like, not curse? How is it possible? There are these gaps in speech where you just have to put a &quot;fuck.&quot; I'll tell you who the most admirable people in the world are: newscasters. If that was me, I'd be like, &quot;And the motherfuckers flew the fucking plane right into the Twin Towers.&quot; How could you not, if you're a human being? Maybe they're not so admirable. Maybe they're robot zombies." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65012-that-s-the-thing-with-the-young-these-days-isn-t-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 10:17:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65012-that-s-the-thing-with-the-young-these-days-isn-t-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s the thing with the young these days, isn’t it? They watch too many happy endings. Everything has to be wrapped up, with a smile and a tear and a wave. Everyone has learned, found love, seen the error of their ways, discovered the joys of monogamy, or fatherhood, or filial duty, or life itself. In my day, people got shot at the end of films, after learning only that life is hollow, dismal, brutish, and short." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528710-what-s-not-so-great-is-that-all-this-technology-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 17:14:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ellen DeGeneres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528710-what-s-not-so-great-is-that-all-this-technology-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What’s not so great is that all this technology is destroying our social skills. Not only have we given up on writing letters to each other, we barely even talk to each other. People have become so accustomed to texting that they’re actually startled when the phone rings. It’s like we suddenly all have Batphones. If it rings, there must be danger. 

Now we answer, “What happened? Is someone tied up in the old sawmill?”

“No, it’s Becky. I just called to say hi.”

“Well you scared me half to death. You can’t just pick up the phone and try to talk to me like that. Don’t the tips of your fingers work?" -- Ellen DeGeneres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 12:51:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tampon commercial, detergent commercial, maxi pad commercial, windex commercial - you'd think all women do is clean and bleed." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/930506-from-the-author-q-a-q-after-you-wrote-the-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 13:37:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/930506-from-the-author-q-a-q-after-you-wrote-the-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(from the author Q&amp;A)

Q. After you wrote the book, however much time has passed, do you think back and wish you could write more, or that you could somehow create more of their world?


A. I never wish I could go back and write more, no. I spent a long, long time trying to write the book that became The Fault in Our Stars and to be completely honest with you, I am entirely happy that the story is no longer my problem and is now your problem." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
