<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/735461-alan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/735461-alan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 09:22:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194-life-s-hard-it-s-even-harder-when-you-re-stupid</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 09:22:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by John Wayne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1194-life-s-hard-it-s-even-harder-when-you-re-stupid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's hard. It's even harder when you're stupid." -- John Wayne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 14:32:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167028-we-must-see-all-scars-as-beauty-okay-this-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 11:55:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Chris Cleave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167028-we-must-see-all-scars-as-beauty-okay-this-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must see all scars as beauty. Okay? This will be our secret. Because take it from me, a scar does not form on the dying. A scar means, 'I survived'." -- Chris Cleave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284084-ray-people-will-come-ray-they-ll-come-to-iowa-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 21:44:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by James Earl Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284084-ray-people-will-come-ray-they-ll-come-to-iowa-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ray. People will come, Ray. They'll come to Iowa for reasons they can't even fathom. They'll turn up your driveway not knowing for sure why they're doing it. They'll arrive at your door as innocent as children, longing for the past. &quot;Of course, we won't mind if you look around&quot;, you'll say, &quot;It's only $20 per person&quot;. They'll pass over the money without even thinking about it: for it is money they have and peace they lack. And they'll walk out to the bleachers; sit in shirtsleeves on a perfect afternoon. They'll find they have reserved seats somewhere along one of the baselines, where they sat when they were children and cheered their heroes. And they'll watch the game and it'll be as if they dipped themselves in magic waters. The memories will be so thick they'll have to brush them away from their faces.  People will come Ray.  The one constant through all the years, Ray, has been baseball. America has rolled by like an army of steamrollers. It has been erased like a blackboard, rebuilt and erased again. But baseball has marked the time. This field, this game: it's a part of our past, Ray. It reminds us of all that once was good and that could be again. Oh...people will come Ray. People will most definitely come." -- James Earl Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656903-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 12:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Will Schwalbe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656903-one-of-the-many-things-i-love-about-bound-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the many things I love about bound books is their sheer physicality. Electronic books live out of sight and out of mind. But printed books have body, presence. ... I often seek electronic books, but they never come after me. They may make me feel, but I can't feel them. They are all soul with no flesh, no texture, and no weight." -- Will Schwalbe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/965240-liquor-is-more-powerful-than-a-peace-treaty</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2013 20:22:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alan add a quote by Jim Leahy &quot;Trailer Park Boys&quot; Season 7]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/965240-liquor-is-more-powerful-than-a-peace-treaty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liquor is more powerful than a peace treaty." -- Jim Leahy &quot;Trailer Park Boys&quot; Season 7]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
