<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/73616-meredith]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/73616-meredith" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 14:50:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 14:50:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[meredith add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2012 14:51:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[meredith add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22842-you-have-brains-in-your-head-you-have-feet-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself any direction you choose. You're on your own. And you know what you know. And YOU are the one who'll decide where to go..." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264229-the-systems-of-stereotypes-may-be-the-core-of-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 12:33:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[meredith add a quote by Walter Lippmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264229-the-systems-of-stereotypes-may-be-the-core-of-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The systems of stereotypes may be the core of our personal tradition, the defenses of our position in society. They are an ordered more or less consistent picture of the world, to which our habits, our tastes, our capacities, our comforts and our hopes have adjusted themselves. They may not be a complete picture of the world, but they are a picture of a possible world to which we are adapted. In that world, people and things have their well-known places, and do certain expected things. We feel at home there. We fit in. We are members.

[...]

It is not merely a short cut. It is all these things and something more. It is the guarantee of our self-respect; it is the projection upon the world of our own sense or our own value, our own position, and our own rights. [...] They are the fortress of our traditions, and behind its defenses we can continue to feel ourselves safe in the position we occupy." -- Walter Lippmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
