<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/736507-audra-pavon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/736507-audra-pavon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 06:17:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59274-some-things-have-to-be-believed-to-be-seen</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 06:17:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Audra add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59274-some-things-have-to-be-believed-to-be-seen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some things have to be believed to be seen." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41455-i-m-apt-to-get-drunk-on-words-ontology-the-word-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 06:19:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Audra add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41455-i-m-apt-to-get-drunk-on-words-ontology-the-word-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm apt to get drunk on words...Ontology: the word about the essence of things; the word about being." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361948-listen-to-your-life-all-moments-are-key-moments</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 05:34:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Audra add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361948-listen-to-your-life-all-moments-are-key-moments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to your life.  All moments are key moments." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 09:44:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Audra add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293637-it-is-a-world-of-magic-and-mystery-of-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a world of magic and mystery, of deep darkness and flickering starlight. It is a world where terrible things happen and wonderful things too. It is a world where goodness is pitted against evil, love against hate, order against chaos, in a great struggle where often it is hard to be sure who belongs to which side because appearances are endlessly deceptive. Yet for all its confusion and wildness, it is a world where the battle goes ultimately to the good, who live happily ever after, and where in the long run everybody, good and evil alike, becomes known by his true name....That is the fairy tale of the Gospel with, of course, one crucial difference from all other fairy tales, which is that the claim made for it is that it is true, that it not only happened once upon a time but has kept on happening ever since and is happening still." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679794-you-wake-up-on-a-winter-morning-and-pull-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 09:53:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Audra add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/679794-you-wake-up-on-a-winter-morning-and-pull-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wake up on a winter morning and pull up the shade, and what lay there the evening before is no longer there--the sodden gray yard, the dog droppings, the tire tracks in the frozen mud, the broken lawn chair you forgot to take in last fall. All this has disappeared overnight, and what you look out on is not the snow of Narnia but the snow of home, which is no less shimmering and white as it falls. The earth is covered with it, and it is falling still in silence so deep that you can hear its silence. It is snow to be shoveled, to make driving even worse than usual, snow to be joked about and cursed at, but unless the child in you is entirely dead, it is snow, too, that can make the heart beat faster when it catches you by surprise that way, before your defenses are up. It is snow that can awaken memories of things more wonderful than anything you ever knew or dreamed." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
