<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/736501-curtis-billau]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/736501-curtis-billau" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:15:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274988-but-remember-sinner-it-is-not-thy-hold-of-christ</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:15:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by Charles Spurgeon August 24 1856.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274988-but-remember-sinner-it-is-not-thy-hold-of-christ]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But remember, sinner, it is not thy hold of Christ that saves thee-its is Christ; it is not thy joy in Christ that saves thee-it is Christ; it is not even faith in Christ, though that is the instrument-it is Christ's blood and merits; therefore, look not so much to thy hand with which thou art grasping Christ, as to Christ; look not to thy hope, but to Christ, the source of thy hope; look not to thy faith, but to Christ, the author and finisher of they faith; and if thou dost that, ten thousand devils cannot throw thee down, but as long as thou lookest at thyself, the meanest of those evil spirits may tread thee beneath his feet... it is not faith, it is not our doings, it is not our feelings upon which we must rest, but apon Christ and on Christ alone." -- Charles Spurgeon August 24 1856.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11409-a-man-can-no-more-diminish-god-s-glory-by-refusing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:17:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11409-a-man-can-no-more-diminish-god-s-glory-by-refusing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can no more diminish God's glory by refusing to worship Him than a lunatic can put out the sun by scribbling the word 'darkness' on the walls of his cell." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274992-all-that-you-ve-loved-is-all-you-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:20:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/274992-all-that-you-ve-loved-is-all-you-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that you've loved is all you own" -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4872-atheism-turns-out-to-be-too-simple-if-the-whole</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:18:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4872-atheism-turns-out-to-be-too-simple-if-the-whole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Atheism turns out to be too simple. If the whole universe has no meaning, we should never have found out that it has no meaning..." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:18:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8912-i-am-fond-of-pigs-dogs-look-up-to-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 07:19:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Curtis add a quote by Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8912-i-am-fond-of-pigs-dogs-look-up-to-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am fond of pigs. Dogs look up to us. Cats look down on us. Pigs treat us as equals." -- Winston S. Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
