<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/7389-scott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/7389-scott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 05:42:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219820-i-look-upon-it-that-a-man-who-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 05:42:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219820-i-look-upon-it-that-a-man-who-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I look upon it that a man who does not mind his stomach would hardly mind anything else." -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:29:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's been a prevalent notion. Fallen sparks. Fragments of vessels broken at the Creation. And someday, somehow, before the end, a gathering back to home. A messenger from the Kingdom, arriving at the last moment. But I tell you there is no such message, no such home -- only the millions of last moments . . . nothing more. Our history is an aggregate of last moments." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24803-why-should-things-be-easy-to-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:29:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24803-why-should-things-be-easy-to-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why should things be easy to understand?" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39513-some-typewriters-in-whitehall-in-the-pentagon-killed-more-civilians</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:30:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39513-some-typewriters-in-whitehall-in-the-pentagon-killed-more-civilians]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some typewriters in Whitehall, in the Pentagon, killed more civilians than our little A4 could have ever hoped to." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77049-perhaps-history-this-century-thought-eigenvalue-is-rippled-with-gathers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:30:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77049-perhaps-history-this-century-thought-eigenvalue-is-rippled-with-gathers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps history this century, thought Eigenvalue, is rippled with gathers in its fabric such that if we are situated, as Stencil seemed to be, at the bottom of a fold, it's impossible to determine warp, woof, or pattern anywhere else. By virtue, however, of existing in one gather it is assumed there are others, compartmented off into sinuous cycles each of which had come to assume greater importance than the weave itself and destroy any continuity. Thus it is that we are charmed by the funny-looking automobiles of the '30's, the curious fashions of the '20's, the particular moral habits of our grandparents. We produce and attend musical comedies about them and are conned into a false memory, a phony nostalgia about what they were. We are accordingly lost to any sense of continuous tradition. Perhaps if we lived on a crest, things would be different. We could at least see." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104910-but-on-the-way-home-tonight-you-wish-you-d-picked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:32:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104910-but-on-the-way-home-tonight-you-wish-you-d-picked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But on the way home tonight, you wish you'd picked him up, held him a bit. Just held him, very close to your heart, his cheek by the hollow of your shoulder, full of sleep. As it it were you who could, somehow, save him. For the moment not caring who you're supposed to be registered as. For the moment, anyway, no longer who the Caesars say you are." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179519-every-weirdo-in-the-world-is-on-my-wavelength</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 17:38:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179519-every-weirdo-in-the-world-is-on-my-wavelength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every weirdo in the world is on my wavelength." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43660-there-is-a-time-for-many-words-and-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 19:51:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Homer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43660-there-is-a-time-for-many-words-and-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a time for many words, and there is also a time for sleep." -- Homer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18857-a-man-who-has-been-through-bitter-experiences-and-travelled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 19:51:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Homer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18857-a-man-who-has-been-through-bitter-experiences-and-travelled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who has been through bitter experiences and travelled far enjoys even his sufferings after a time" -- Homer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160885-the-difficulty-is-not-so-great-to-die-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 19:57:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Homer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160885-the-difficulty-is-not-so-great-to-die-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difficulty is not so great to die for a friend as to find a friend worth dying for." -- Homer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 06:47:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111069-there-is-a-whirlwind-in-southern-morocco-the-aajej-against</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 06:52:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111069-there-is-a-whirlwind-in-southern-morocco-the-aajej-against]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a whirlwind in southern Morocco, the &lt;i&gt;aajej&lt;/i&gt;, against which the fellahin defend themselves with knives. There is the &lt;i&gt;africo&lt;/i&gt;, which has at times reached into the city of Rome. The &lt;i&gt;alm&lt;/i&gt;, a fall wind out of Yugoslavia. The &lt;i&gt;arifi&lt;/i&gt;, also christened &lt;i&gt;aref&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;rifi&lt;/i&gt;, which scorches with numerous tongues. These are permanent winds that live in the present tense.
There are other, less constant winds that change direction, that can knock down horse and rider and realign themselves anticlockwise. The &lt;i&gt;bist roz&lt;/i&gt; leaps into Afghanistan for 170 days--burying villages. There is the hot, dry &lt;i&gt;ghibli&lt;/i&gt; from Tunis, which rolls and rolls and produces a nervous condition. The &lt;i&gt;haboob&lt;/i&gt;--a Sudan dust storm that dresses in bright yellow walls a thousand metres high and is followed by rain. The &lt;i&gt;harmattan&lt;/i&gt;, which blows and eventually drowns itself into the Atlantic. &lt;i&gt;Imbat&lt;/i&gt;, a sea breeze in North Africa. Some winds that just sigh towards the sky. Night dust storms that come with the cold. The &lt;i&gt;khamsin&lt;/i&gt;, a dust in Egypt from March to May, named after the Arabic word for 'fifty,' blooming for fifty days--the ninth plague of Egypt. The &lt;i&gt;datoo&lt;/i&gt; out of Gibraltar, which carries fragrance.
There is also the ------, the secret wind of the desert, whose name was erased by a king after his son died within it. And the &lt;i&gt;nafhat&lt;/i&gt;--a blast out of Arabia. The &lt;i&gt;mezzar-ifoullousen&lt;/i&gt;--a violent and cold southwesterly known to Berbers as 'that which plucks the fowls.' The &lt;i&gt;beshabar&lt;/i&gt;, a black and dry northeasterly out of the Caucasus, 'black wind.' The &lt;i&gt;Samiel&lt;/i&gt; from Turkey, 'poison and wind,' used often in battle. As well as the other 'poison winds,' the &lt;i&gt;simoom&lt;/i&gt;, of North Africa, and the &lt;i&gt;solano&lt;/i&gt;, whose dust plucks off rare petals, causing giddiness.
Other, private winds.
Travelling along the ground like a flood. Blasting off paint, throwing down telephone poles, transporting stones and statue heads. The &lt;i&gt;harmattan&lt;/i&gt; blows across the Sahara filled with red dust, dust as fire, as flour, entering and coagulating in the locks of rifles. Mariners called this red wind the 'sea of darkness.' Red sand fogs out of the Sahara were deposited as far north as Cornwall and Devon, producing showers of mud so great this was also mistaken for blood. 'Blood rains were widely reported in Portugal and Spain in 1901.'
There are always millions of tons of dust in the air, just as there are millions of cubes of air in the earth and more living flesh in the soil (worms, beetles, underground creatures) than there is grazing and existing on it. Herodotus records the death of various armies engulfed in the &lt;i&gt;simoom&lt;/i&gt; who were never seen again. One nation was 'so enraged by this evil wind that they declared war on it and marched out in full battle array, only to be rapidly and completely interred." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38565-the-old-hunger-for-voyages-fed-at-his-heart-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 07:08:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38565-the-old-hunger-for-voyages-fed-at-his-heart-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The old hunger for voyages fed at his heart....To go alone...into strange cities; to meet strange people and to pass again before they could know him; to wander, like his own legend, across the earth--it seemed to him there could be no better thing than that." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44933-a-destiny-that-leads-the-english-to-the-dutch-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 07:10:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44933-a-destiny-that-leads-the-english-to-the-dutch-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A destiny that leads the English to the Dutch is strange enough; but one that leads from Epsom into Pennsylvania, and thence into the hills that shut in Altamont over the proud coral cry of the cock, and the soft stone smile of an angel, is touched by that dark miracle of chance which makes new magic in a dusty world.

Each of us is all the sums he has not counted: subtract us into nakedness and night again, and you shall see begin in Crete four thousand years ago the love that ended yesterday in Texas.

The seed of our destruction will blossom in the desert, the alexin of our cure grows by a mountain rock, and our lives are haunted by a Georgia slattern, because a London cutpurse went unhung. Each moment is the fruit of forty thousand years. The minute-winning days, like flies, buzz home to death, and every moment is a window on all time.

This is a moment:" -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30600-child-child-have-patience-and-belief-for-life-is-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 07:10:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30600-child-child-have-patience-and-belief-for-life-is-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Child, child, have patience and belief, for life is many days, and each present hour will pass away. Son, son, you have been mad and drunken, furious and wild, filled with hatred and despair, and all the dark confusions of the soul - but so have we. You found the earth too great for your one life, you found your brain and sinew smaller than the hunger and desire that fed on them - but it has been this way with all men. You have stumbled on in darkness, you have been pulled in opposite directions, you have faltered, you have missed the way, but, child, this is the chronicle of the earth.  And now, because you have known madness and despair, and because you will grow desperate again before you come to evening, we who have stormed the ramparts of the furious earth and been hurled back, we who have been maddened by the unknowable and bitter mystery of love, we who have hungered after fame and savored all of life, the tumult, pain, and frenzy, and now sit quietly by our windows watching all that henceforth never more shall touch us - we call upon you to take heart, for we can swear to you that these things pass." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223736-for-he-had-learned-some-of-the-things-that-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 07:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223736-for-he-had-learned-some-of-the-things-that-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For he had learned some of the things that every man must find out for himself, and he had found out about them as one has to find out --through error and through trial, through fantasy and illusion, through falsehood and his own damn foolishness, through being mistaken and wrong and an idiot and egotistical and aspiring and hopeful and believing and confused." -- Thomas Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156835-we-cannot-live-only-for-ourselves-a-thousand-fibers-connect</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:11:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156835-we-cannot-live-only-for-ourselves-a-thousand-fibers-connect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot live only for ourselves. A thousand fibers connect us with our fellow men; and among those fibers, as sympathetic threads, our actions run as causes, and they come back to us as effects." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13759-at-length-i-fell-asleep-with-the-volume-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:12:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13759-at-length-i-fell-asleep-with-the-volume-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At length I fell asleep, with the volume in my hand; and never slept so sound before" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70552-real-strength-never-impairs-beauty-or-harmony-but-it-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:12:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Melville Herman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70552-real-strength-never-impairs-beauty-or-harmony-but-it-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real strength never impairs beauty or harmony, but it often bestows it, and in everything imposingly beautiful, strength has much to do with the magic." -- Melville Herman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111225-where-lies-the-final-harbor-whence-we-unmoor-no-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:13:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111225-where-lies-the-final-harbor-whence-we-unmoor-no-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where lies the final harbor, whence we unmoor no more? In what rapt ether sails the world, of which the weariest will never weary? Where is the foundling’s father hidden? Our souls are like those orphans whose unwedded mothers die in bearing them: the secret of our paternity lies in their grave, and we must there to learn it." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179967-it-is-not-down-on-any-map-true-places-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:15:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179967-it-is-not-down-on-any-map-true-places-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not down on any map; true places never are." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56879-i-have-the-satisfaction-of-knowing-that-it-is-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:17:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56879-i-have-the-satisfaction-of-knowing-that-it-is-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have the satisfaction of knowing that it is all right; that everybody else is one way or other served in much the same way--either in a physical or metaphysical point of view, that is; and so the universal thump is passed round, and all hands should rub each other's shoulder-blades, and be content." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190799-there-are-some-enterprises-in-which-a-careful-disorderliness-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:17:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190799-there-are-some-enterprises-in-which-a-careful-disorderliness-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some enterprises in which a careful disorderliness is the true method." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7335-our-souls-are-like-those-orphans-whose-unwedded-mothers-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:17:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7335-our-souls-are-like-those-orphans-whose-unwedded-mothers-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our souls are like those orphans whose unwedded mothers die in bearing them: the secret of our paternity lies in their grave, and we must there to learn it." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200036-to-the-last-i-grapple-with-thee-from-hell-s-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:18:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200036-to-the-last-i-grapple-with-thee-from-hell-s-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...to the last I grapple with thee; from hell's heart I stab at thee; for hate's sake I spit my last breath at thee." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45011-but-even-so-amid-the-tornadoed-atlantic-of-my-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:18:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45011-but-even-so-amid-the-tornadoed-atlantic-of-my-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But even so, amid the tornadoed Atlantic of my being, do I myself still for ever centrally disport in mute calm; and while ponderous planets of unwaning woe revolve round me, deep down and deep inland there I still bathe me in eternal mildness of joy." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207174-i-have-no-objection-to-any-person-s-religion-be-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:19:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207174-i-have-no-objection-to-any-person-s-religion-be-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no objection to any person's religion, be it what it may, so long as that person does not kill or insult any other person, because that other person don't believe it also. But when a man's religion becomes really frantic; when it is a positive torment to him; and, in fine, makes this earth of ours an uncomfortable inn to lodge in; then I think it high time to take that individual aside and argue the point with him." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220667-whatever-my-fate-i-ll-go-to-it-laughing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:20:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220667-whatever-my-fate-i-ll-go-to-it-laughing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever my fate, I'll go to it laughing." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:20:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to sleep with a sober cannibal than a drunk Christian." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207180-i-will-have-no-man-in-my-boat-said-starbuck</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 19:21:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207180-i-will-have-no-man-in-my-boat-said-starbuck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will have no man in my boat,&quot; said Starbuck, &quot;who is not afraid of a whale.&quot; By this, he seemed to mean, not only that the most reliable and useful courage was that which arises from the fair estimation of the encountered peril, but that an utterly fearless man is a far more dangerous comrade than a coward. 
(moby dick chap 26 p112)" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
