<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740043-joel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740043-joel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 15:55:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153368-the-world-shown-us-in-books-whether-the-books-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 15:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153368-the-world-shown-us-in-books-whether-the-books-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world shown us in books, whether the books be confessed epics or professed gospels, or in codes, or in political orations, or in philosophic systems, is not the main world at all: it is only the self-consciousness of certain abnormal people who have the specific artistic talent and temperament. A serious matter this for you and me, because the man whose consciousness does not correspond to that of the majority is a madman; and the old habit of worshipping madmen is giving way to the new habit of locking them up. And since what we call education and culture is for the most part nothing but the substitution of reading for experience, of literature for life, of the absolete fictitious for the contemporary real, education, as you no doubt observed at Oxford, destroys, by supplantation, every mind that is not strong enough to see through the imposture and to use the great Masters of Arts as what they really are and no more: that is, patentees of highly questionable methods of thinking, and manufacturers of highly questionable, and for the majority but half valid representations of life. The school boy who uses his Homer to throw at his fellow's head makes perhaps the safest and most rational use of him; and I observe with reassurance that you occasionally do the same, in your prime, with your Aristotle." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131708-mind-n-a-mysterious-form-of-matter-secreted-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 09:26:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131708-mind-n-a-mysterious-form-of-matter-secreted-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["MIND, n. A mysterious form of matter secreted by the brain. Its chief activity consists in the endeavour to ascertain its own nature, the futility of the attempt being due to the fact that it has nothing but itself to know itself with." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366380-but-if-you-have-an-enemy-do-not-requite-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 20:28:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joel add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366380-but-if-you-have-an-enemy-do-not-requite-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if you have an enemy, do not requite him evil with good, for that would put him to shame.  Rather prove that he did you some good.
  And rather be angry than put to shame.  And if you are cursed, I do not like that you want to bless.  Rather join a little in the cursing." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
