<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740221-juju]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740221-juju" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 23:03:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176200-the-pretense-in-disputed-elections-is-that-the-great-conflict</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 23:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176200-the-pretense-in-disputed-elections-is-that-the-great-conflict]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pretense in disputed elections is that the great conflict is between the two major parties.  The reality is that there is a much bigger conflict that the two parties jointly wage against large numbers of Americans who are represented by neither party and against powerless millions around the world.&quot; (p. 65)" -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176204-human-rights-pale-beside-the-rights-of-machines-in-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 23:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176204-human-rights-pale-beside-the-rights-of-machines-in-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human rights pale beside the rights of machines. In more and more cities, especially in the great metropolises of the South, people have been banned.  Automobiles usurp human space, poison the air, and frequently murder the interlopers who invade their conquered territory -and no one lifts a finger to stop them.  Is there a difference between violence that kills by car and that which kills by knife or bullet?&quot; (p.231)" -- Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176205-while-we-advance-exponentially-in-technological-capability-our-spiritual-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 23:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by James Curcio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176205-while-we-advance-exponentially-in-technological-capability-our-spiritual-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While we advance exponentially in technological capability, our spiritual or 'biological technology,' our maturity as a species, is still two or three thousand years in the past.  This is because many of us live according to ideas that were original and groundbreaking... in 500 B.C.  Most people are unwilling or unable to ask the hard questions- as in, why do we do things the way we do, and what will the end results be?&quot;  (p.120) Generation Hex" -- James Curcio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176210-a-thought-robot-activated-by-the-tremendous-energies-unleashed-during</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2009 23:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176210-a-thought-robot-activated-by-the-tremendous-energies-unleashed-during]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...A thought robot activated by the tremendous energies unleashed during collisions of fundamental opposing qualities.  A new fusion process powered by... 'dualites'?  No. There are no dualities. Only symmetries.&quot; Final Crisis: Superman Beyond" -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188105-and-it-dawned-on-me-that-i-might-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2009 22:59:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188105-and-it-dawned-on-me-that-i-might-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it dawned on me that I might have to change my inner thought patterns... that I would have to start believing in possibilities that I wouldn't have allowed before, that I had been closing my creativity down to a very narrow, controllable scale... that things had become too familiar and I might have to disorientate myself.   p.71" -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205933-if-you-saw-two-groups-of-children-arguing-over-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2009 21:13:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205933-if-you-saw-two-groups-of-children-arguing-over-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you saw two groups of children arguing over which of them could play in some waste ground, would you chose sides?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217381-one-day-as-he-slept-in-a-cave-he-dreamed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 19:46:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217381-one-day-as-he-slept-in-a-cave-he-dreamed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day, as he slept in a cave, he dreamed that he saw his own body sleeping. He came out of the cave on the night of a new moon.  The sky was clear, and he could see millions of stars. Then something happened inside of him that transformed his life forever. He looked at his hands, he felt his body, and he heard his own voice say. &quot;I am made of light, I am made of stars.&quot;
He looked at the stars again, and he realized that it's not the stars that create the light, but rather the light that creates the stars.  &quot;Everything is made of light,&quot; he said, &quot;and the space in-between isn't empty.&quot; And he knew that everything that exists is one living being, and that light is the messenger of life, because it is alive and contains all information. (xvi)" -- Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217382-under-nafta-businesses-their-property-and-their-money-can-travel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2009 20:00:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by John Gibler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217382-under-nafta-businesses-their-property-and-their-money-can-travel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Under NAFTA, businesses, their property and their money can travel back and forth across national borders with relative ease, while workers who try to do the same are dubbed illegal, and are snatched off the streets and off factory floors, and are carted back over the borders they crossed.  In the &quot;free market&quot; of NAFTA, the freedom is for the wealth and personnel of the capitalists- the thieves- there is no corresponding freedom for the refugees of land theft and conquest whose only capital is their daily toil.

Capitalism is the immense and widely celebrated ideological package used to rewrap theft as freedom, to recast imperialism as democracy.  (273) Mexico Unconquered" -- John Gibler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218921-i-used-to-be-in-school-like-a-good-boy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 19:31:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Paul Pope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218921-i-used-to-be-in-school-like-a-good-boy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to be in school, like a good boy. Medieval Literature. Von Eschenbach, Chaucer, Milton... Yes, sir, no, sir. Then I had that... Crisis.  You know it? Wake up one morning and everything's all wrong? Wake up one morning and it occurs to you the milk's spoiled and the bread is getting moldy.  Wake up and it just hits you. Someday you're gonna die. Maybe like that girl last night died. Face down in an alley with a caved in head. Such a terrible thing and what for? Why life? Why This life? Why This soap? Why these hands? What's it all mean? Deep down you fear nothing. But you still hope something. Either way, you're not really sure. That's my crisis. I don't wanna die. But if I'm gonna die, first I'm gonna live. I'm gonna peel life like fruit, and use it up. I'm gonna light up an' burn. I'll burn and burn until I'm snuffed out. Then I'll just fade away. But until then I'm gonna live! I'm ready. I'm gonna do it. Come what may, one hundred percent." -- Paul Pope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221644-for-the-powerful-crimes-are-those-that-others-commit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 21:22:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221644-for-the-powerful-crimes-are-those-that-others-commit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the powerful, crimes are those that others commit." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224065-you-must-remember-that-the-common-criminal-will-always-join</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 22:38:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224065-you-must-remember-that-the-common-criminal-will-always-join]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must remember that the common criminal will always join the armed forces for, if nothing else, regular meals and expert training in the use of guns." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228210-all-that-interconnectedness-that-facilitated-much-of-the-explosion-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 22:45:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by David Byrne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228210-all-that-interconnectedness-that-facilitated-much-of-the-explosion-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that interconnectedness that facilitated much of the explosion of megawealth over the last decade also facilitated the interpenetration of everything, so no one or no building is truly isolated and 'safe' anymore. Safety is in getting along.  (p.261)" -- David Byrne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228212-much-of-what-i-have-done-is-left-unfinished--not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2010 18:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228212-much-of-what-i-have-done-is-left-unfinished--not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Much of what I have done is left unfinished- not because I left it too soon, not because I was lazy, but because it had a life of it's own that continues without me.  Children, I suppose, are always unfinished business: they begin as part of your own body, and continue as seperate as another continent.  The work you do, if it has any meaning, passes to other hands.  The day slides into a night's dreaming.
True stories are the ones that lie open at the border, allowing a crossing, a further frontier.  The final frontier is just science fiction -don't believe it.  Like the universe, there is no end.  (p.87)" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239589-we-no-longer-live-on-what-we-have-but-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2010 11:28:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239589-we-no-longer-live-on-what-we-have-but-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We no longer live on what we have, but on promises, no longer in the present day, but in the darkness of the future, which, we expect, will at last bring the proper sunrise. We refuse to recognize that everything better is purchased at the price of something worse; that, for example, the hope of grater freedom is canceled out by increased enslavement to the state, not to speak of the terrible perils to which the most brilliant discoveries of science expose us. The less we understand of what our [forebears] sought, the less we understand ourselves, and thus we help with all our might to rob the individual of his roots and his guiding instincts, so that he becomes a particle in the mass, ruled only by what Neitzche called the spirit of gravity.  (p.236)" -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286044-it-is-our-destiny-to-live-with-the-wrong-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 21:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286044-it-is-our-destiny-to-live-with-the-wrong-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our destiny to live with the wrong as well as the right kind of citizens, and to learn from them, the wrong-minded ones, as much or more as from others. If we have not yet succeeded -after how many centuries?- in eliminating from life the elements which plague us perhaps we need to question life more closely.  Perhaps our refusal to face reality is the only ill we suffer from, and all the rest but illusion and delusion.  (p.26)" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923530-i-say-making-movies-is-like-eating-a-sandwich-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 22:27:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juju add a quote by Guillermo del Toro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923530-i-say-making-movies-is-like-eating-a-sandwich-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I say making movies is like eating a sandwich of shit. Sometimes you get more bread, sometimes less bread, but you always get shit.&quot; (Guardian interview 2006)" -- Guillermo del Toro]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
