<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740256-dan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740256-dan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 17:40:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 17:40:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who controls the past controls the future. He who controls the present controls the past." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 17:46:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18860-when-someone-seeks-said-siddhartha-then-it-easily-happens-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 14:55:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18860-when-someone-seeks-said-siddhartha-then-it-easily-happens-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone seeks,&quot; said Siddhartha, &quot;then it easily happens that his eyes see only the thing that he seeks, and he is able to find nothing, to take in nothing because he always thinks only about the thing he is seeking, because he has one goal, because he is obsessed with his goal. Seeking means: having a goal. But finding means: being free, being open, having no goal." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 10:18:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned this, at least, by my experiment: that if one advances confidently in the direction of his dreams, and endeavors to live the life which he has imagined, he will meet with a success unexpected in common hours." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 10:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5892-our-life-is-frittered-away-by-detail-simplify-simplify]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our life is frittered away by detail. Simplify, simplify." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101449-when-one-person-suffers-from-a-delusion-it-is-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 08:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101449-when-one-person-suffers-from-a-delusion-it-is-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one person suffers from a delusion, it is called insanity. When many people suffer from a delusion it is called a Religion." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109266-we-admit-that-we-are-like-apes-but-we-seldom</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 09:42:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109266-we-admit-that-we-are-like-apes-but-we-seldom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We admit that we are like apes, but we seldom realize that we are apes." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 09:43:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, please, oh please, we beg, we pray, go throw your TV set away, and in its place you can install, a lovely bookcase on the wall." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79884-i-have-a-passion-for-teaching-kids-to-become-readers</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 09:44:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79884-i-have-a-passion-for-teaching-kids-to-become-readers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a passion for teaching kids to become readers, to become comfortable with a book, not daunted. Books shouldn't be daunting, they should be funny, exciting and wonderful; and learning to be a reader gives a terrific advantage." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 10:17:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 10:19:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2008 10:20:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which does not kill us makes us stronger." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118589-the-fact-is-what-i-hated-in-the-church-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 09:32:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118589-the-fact-is-what-i-hated-in-the-church-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact is, what I hated in the Church was what I hated in society. Namely, authoritarians. Power freaks. Rigid dogmatists. Those greedy, underloved, undersexed twits who want to run everything. While the rest of us are busy living  - busy tasting and testing and hugging and kissing and goofing and growing - they are busy taking over." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47261-generally-speaking-i-think-it-is-fair-to-say-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2008 08:58:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by John Hodgman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47261-generally-speaking-i-think-it-is-fair-to-say-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Generally speaking, I think it is fair to say that I am a friend to the creatures of the Earth when I am not busy eating them or wearing them." -- John Hodgman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98062-in-all-your-amours-you-should-prefer-old-women-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 11:41:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98062-in-all-your-amours-you-should-prefer-old-women-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In all your Amours you should prefer old Women to young ones. You call this a Paradox, and demand my Reasons. They are these:

1. Because as they have more Knowledge of the World and their Minds are better stor’d with Observations, their Conversation is more improving and more lastingly agreable.

2. Because when Women cease to be handsome, they study to be good. To maintain their Influence over Men, they supply the Diminution of Beauty by an Augmentation of Utility. They learn to do a 1000 Services small and great, and are the most tender and useful of all Friends when you are sick. Thus they continue amiable. And hence there is hardly such a thing to be found as an old Woman who is not a good Woman.

3. Because there is no hazard of Children, which irregularly produc’d may be attended with much Inconvenience.

4. Because thro’ more Experience, they are more prudent and discreet in conducting an Intrigue to prevent Suspicion. The Commerce with them is therefore safer with regard to your Reputation. And with regard to theirs, if the Affair should happen to be known, considerate People might be rather inclin’d to excuse an old Woman who would kindly take care of a young Man, form his Manners by her good Counsels, and prevent his ruining his Health and Fortune among mercenary Prostitutes.

5. Because in every Animal that walks upright, the Deficiency of the Fluids that fill the Muscles appears first in the highest Part: The Face first grows lank and wrinkled; then the Neck; then the Breast and Arms; the lower Parts continuing to the last as plump as ever: So that covering all above with a Basket, and regarding only what is below the Girdle, it is impossible of two Women to know an old from a young one. And as in the dark all Cats are grey, the Pleasure of corporal Enjoyment with an old Woman is at least equal, and frequently superior, every Knack being by Practice capable of Improvement.

6. Because the Sin is less. The debauching a Virgin may be her Ruin, and make her for Life unhappy.

7. Because the Compunction is less. The having made a young Girl miserable may give you frequent bitter Reflections; none of which can attend the making an old Woman happy.

8thly and Lastly They are so grateful!!" -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
