<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740916-elmaneca-cabrera]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/740916-elmaneca-cabrera" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:20:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:20:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:20:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:21:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2009 16:21:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 11:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024-i-love-mankind-it-s-people-i-can-t-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 14:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Charles Schultz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024-i-love-mankind-it-s-people-i-can-t-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;I&lt;/b&gt; love mankind ... it's &lt;b&gt;people&lt;/b&gt; I can't stand!!" -- Charles Schultz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 12:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/991-until-i-feared-i-would-lose-it-i-never-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until I feared I would lose it, I never loved to read. One does not love breathing." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5863-a-great-book-should-leave-you-with-many-experiences-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 12:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by William Styron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5863-a-great-book-should-leave-you-with-many-experiences-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A great book should leave you with many experiences, and slightly exhausted at the end. You live several lives while reading." -- William Styron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24088-books-are-not-made-for-furniture-but-there-is-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 12:08:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24088-books-are-not-made-for-furniture-but-there-is-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are not made for furniture, but there is nothing else that so beautifully furnishes a house." -- Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 14:21:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the quietest and most constant of friends; they are the most accessible and wisest of counselors, and the most patient of teachers." -- Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 09:28:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:38:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17533-i-carry-your-heart-with-me-i-carry-it-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I carry your heart with me (I carry it in my heart)I am never without it (anywhere
I go you go,my dear; and whatever is done by only me is your doing,my darling)
I fear no fate (for you are my fate,my sweet)I want no world (for beautiful you are my world,my true)
and it's you are whatever a moon has always meant and whatever a sun will always sing is you

here is the deepest secret nobody knows
(here is the root of the root and the bud of the bud and the sky of the sky of a tree called life; which grows
higher than the soul can hope or mind can hide)
and this is the wonder that's keeping the stars apart

I carry your heart (I carry it in my heart)" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:39:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20604-learn-from-yesterday-live-for-today-hope-for-tomorrow-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20604-learn-from-yesterday-live-for-today-hope-for-tomorrow-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow.  The important thing is to not stop questioning." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming. This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are the cultivated. For these there is hope. They are the elect to whom beautiful things mean only Beauty. There is no such thing as a moral or an immoral book. Books are well written, or badly written. That is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:41:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26411-there-are-two-basic-motivating-forces-fear-and-love-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two basic motivating forces: fear and love. When we are afraid, we pull back from life. When we are in love, we open to all that life has to offer with passion, excitement, and acceptance. We need to learn to love ourselves first, in all our glory and our imperfections. If we cannot love ourselves, we cannot fully open to our ability to love others or our potential to create. Evolution and all hopes for a better world rest in the fearlessness and open-hearted vision of people who embrace life." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170332-you-don-t-forget-the-face-of-the-person-who-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:41:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170332-you-don-t-forget-the-face-of-the-person-who-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t forget the face of the person who was your last hope." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:41:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137748-the-best-love-is-the-kind-that-awakens-the-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best love is the kind that awakens the soul and makes us reach for more, that plants a fire in our hearts and brings peace to our minds. And that's what you've given me. That's what I'd hoped to give you forever" -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19449-out-of-the-huts-of-history-s-shame-i-rise-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Maya Angelou ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19449-out-of-the-huts-of-history-s-shame-i-rise-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of the huts of history's shame
I rise
Up from a past that's rooted in pain
I rise
I'm a black ocean, leaping and wide,
Welling and swelling I bear in the tide.
Leaving behind nights of terror and fear
I rise
Into a daybreak that's wondrously clear
I rise
Bringing the gifts that my ancestors gave,
I am the dream and the hope of the slave.
I rise
I rise
I rise." -- Maya Angelou ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:43:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34449-strange-as-it-may-seem-i-still-hope-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange as it may seem, I still hope for the best, even though the best, like an interesting piece of mail, so rarely arrives, and even when it does it can be lost so easily." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73186-i-knew-that-there-were-no-guarantees-no-way-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:45:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73186-i-knew-that-there-were-no-guarantees-no-way-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew that there were no guarantees. No way of knowing what came next for me, or him, or anybody. Some things don't last forever, but some things do. Like a good song, or a good book, or a good memory you can take out and unfold in your darkest times, pressing down the corners and peering in close, hoping you still recognize the person you see there." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17180-what-to-do-if-you-find-yourself-stuck-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:46:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17180-what-to-do-if-you-find-yourself-stuck-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What to do if you find yourself stuck in a crack in the ground underneath a giant boulder you can't move, with no hope of rescue.  Consider how lucky you are that life has been good to you so far. Alternatively, if life hasn't been good to you so far, which given your current circumstances seems more likely, consider how lucky you are that it won't be troubling you much longer." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29370-it-is-often-in-the-darkest-skies-that-we-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 11:46:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Richard Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29370-it-is-often-in-the-darkest-skies-that-we-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is often in the darkest 
skies that we see the 
brightest stars." -- Richard Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12364-when-beetles-fight-these-battles-in-a-bottle-with-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:27:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12364-when-beetles-fight-these-battles-in-a-bottle-with-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When beetles fight these battles in a bottle with their paddles 
and the bottle's on a poodle and the poodle's eating noodles...
...they call this a muddle puddle tweetle poodle beetle noodle 
bottle paddle battle." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255-life-doesn-t-imitate-art-it-imitates-bad-television</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:29:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255-life-doesn-t-imitate-art-it-imitates-bad-television]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life doesn't imitate art, it imitates bad television." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64899-if-you-love-something-set-it-free-but-don-t-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 13:30:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64899-if-you-love-something-set-it-free-but-don-t-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love something set it free, but don't be surprised if it comes back with herpes." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51679-sometimes-we-love-with-nothing-more-than-hope-sometimes-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 17:19:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51679-sometimes-we-love-with-nothing-more-than-hope-sometimes-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes we love with nothing more than hope. Sometimes we cry with everything except tears." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106931-some-feelings-sink-so-deep-into-the-heart-that-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 17:19:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elmaneca add a quote by Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106931-some-feelings-sink-so-deep-into-the-heart-that-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some feelings sink so deep into the heart that only loneliness can help you find them again. Some truths are so painful that only shame can help you live with them. Some things are so sad that only your soul can do the crying for them." -- Gregory David Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
