<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/74129-paizleigh-rane]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/74129-paizleigh-rane" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 08:15:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487273-over-the-years-americans-in-particular-have-been-all-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 08:15:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Cody Lundin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/487273-over-the-years-americans-in-particular-have-been-all-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the years, Americans in particular have been all too willing to squander their hard-earned independence and freedom for the illusion of feeling safe under someone else's authority. The concept of self-sufficiency has been undermined in value over a scant few generations. The vast majority of the population seems to look down their noses upon self-reliance as some quaint dusty relic, entertained only by the hyperparanoid or those hopelessly incapable of fitting into mainstream society." -- Cody Lundin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 06:30:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lonely. I've been in a room -- I've felt suicidal. I've been depressed. I've felt awful -- awful beyond all -- but I never felt that one other person could enter that room and cure what was bothering me...or that any number of people could enter that room. In other words, loneliness is something I've never been bothered with because I've always had this terrible itch for solitude. It's being at a party, or at a stadium full of people cheering for something, that I might feel loneliness. I'll quote Ibsen, &quot;The strongest men are the most alone.&quot; I've never thought, &quot;Well, some beautiful blonde will come in here and give me a fuck-job, rub my balls, and I'll feel good.&quot; No, that won't help. You know the typical crowd, &quot;Wow, it's Friday night, what are you going to do? Just sit there?&quot; Well, yeah. Because there's nothing out there. It's stupidity. Stupid people mingling with stupid people. Let them stupidify themselves. I've never been bothered with the need to rush out into the night. I hid in bars, because I didn't want to hide in factories. That's all. Sorry for all the millions, but I've never been lonely. I like myself. I'm the best form of entertainment I have. Let's drink more wine!" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82586-if-you-want-to-be-surrounded-by-souls-become-identified</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2012 11:50:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Ram Dass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82586-if-you-want-to-be-surrounded-by-souls-become-identified]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to be surrounded by Souls, become identified with your Soul.
It takes one to know one!" -- Ram Dass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79207-the-death-of-god-left-the-angels-in-a-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 09:36:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Donald Barthelme]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79207-the-death-of-god-left-the-angels-in-a-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The death of God left the angels in a strange position." -- Donald Barthelme]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469183-many-physicists-these-days-sound-like-the-delphic-oracle--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 09:39:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by John Twelve Hawks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469183-many-physicists-these-days-sound-like-the-delphic-oracle--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many physicists these days sound like the Delphic oracle - with equations." -- John Twelve Hawks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153586-when-you-plant-lettuce-if-it-does-not-grow-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 04:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153586-when-you-plant-lettuce-if-it-does-not-grow-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you plant lettuce, if it does not grow well, you 
don't blame the lettuce.  You look for reasons it is not 
doing well.  It may need fertilizer, or more water, or 
less sun.  You never blame the lettuce. Yet if we have 
problems with our friends or family, we blame the other 
person. But if we know how to take care of them, they will 
grow well, like the lettuce.  Blaming has no positive 
effect at all, nor does trying to persuade using reason 
and argument. That is my experience.  No blame, no 
reasoning, no argument, just understanding. If you 
understand, and you show that you understand, you can 
love, and the situation will change" -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:20:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:24:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think dreams aren't real just because they aren't made of matter, of particles. Dreams are real. But they are made of viewpoints, of images, of memories and puns and lost hopes." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:25:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57789-some-hats-can-only-be-worn-if-you-re-willing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:33:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57789-some-hats-can-only-be-worn-if-you-re-willing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some hats can only be worn if you're willing to be jaunty, to set them at an angle and to walk beneath them with a spring in your stride as if you're only a step away from dancing. They demand a lot of you." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62551-the-important-thing-about-songs-is-that-they-re-just-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 05:35:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62551-the-important-thing-about-songs-is-that-they-re-just-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The important thing about songs is that they're just like stories. They don't mean a damn unless there's people listenin' to them." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105923-the-problem-was-you-had-to-keep-choosing-between-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 16:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105923-the-problem-was-you-had-to-keep-choosing-between-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem was you had to keep choosing between one evil or another, and no matter what you chose, they sliced a little bit more off you, until there was nothing left. At the age of 25 most people were finished. A whole god-damned nation of assholes driving automobiles, eating, having babies, doing everything in the worst way possible, like voting for the presidential candidates who reminded them most of themselves. I had no interests. I had no interest in anything. I had no idea how I was going to escape. At least the others had some taste for life. They seemed to understand something that I didn't understand. Maybe I was lacking. It was possible. I often felt inferior. I just wanted to get away from them. But there was no place to go." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 04:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 04:58:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thermodynamic miracles... events with odds against so astronomical they're effectively impossible, like oxygen spontaneously becoming gold. I long to observe such a thing.
And yet, in each human coupling, a thousand million sperm vie for a single egg. Multiply those odds by countless generations, against the odds of your ancestors being alive; meeting; siring this precise son; that exact daughter... Until your mother loves a man she has every reason to hate, and of that union, of the thousand million children competing for fertilization, it was you, only you, that emerged. To distill so specific a form from that chaos of improbability, like turning air to gold... that is the crowning unlikelihood. The thermodynamic miracle.

But...if me, my birth, if that's a thermodynamic miracle... I mean, you could say that about anybody in the world!.

Yes. Anybody in the world. ..But the world is so full of people, so crowded with these miracles that they become commonplace and we forget... I forget. We gaze continually at the world and it grows dull in our perceptions. Yet seen from the another's vantage point. As if new, it may still take our breath away. Come...dry your eyes. For you are life, rarer than a quark and unpredictable beyond the dreams of Heisenberg; the clay in which the forces that shape all things leave their fingerprints most clearly. Dry your eyes... and let's go home." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36714-no-not-even-in-the-face-of-armageddon-never-compromise</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 04:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36714-no-not-even-in-the-face-of-armageddon-never-compromise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No. Not even in the face of Armageddon. Never compromise." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117448-if-there-was-a-god-i-would-spit-in-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 06:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by James Frey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117448-if-there-was-a-god-i-would-spit-in-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there was a God. I would spit in his face for subjecting me to this. If there was a Devil, I would sell my sould to make it end. If there was something Higher that controlled out f***ing fates, I would tell it to take my fate and shove it up its fucking ass. Shove it hard and far, you motherf***er. Please end. Please end. Please end." -- James Frey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412517-the-dark-does-not-destroy-the-light-it-defines-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:44:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412517-the-dark-does-not-destroy-the-light-it-defines-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dark does not destroy the light; it defines it.  It's our fear of the dark that casts our joy into the shadows." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630701-don-t-try-to-win-over-the-haters-you-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:44:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630701-don-t-try-to-win-over-the-haters-you-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't try to win over the haters; you are not a jackass whisperer." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631488-because-true-belonging-only-happens-when-we-present-our-authentic</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:45:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/631488-because-true-belonging-only-happens-when-we-present-our-authentic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because true belonging only happens when we present our authentic, imperfect selves to the world, our sense of belonging can never be greater than our level of self-acceptance." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625721-if-you-want-to-make-a-difference-the-next-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 04:46:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625721-if-you-want-to-make-a-difference-the-next-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to make a difference, the next time you see someone being cruel to another human being, take it personally. Take it personally because it is personal!" -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42697-we-must-become-so-alone-so-utterly-alone-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 03:34:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42697-we-must-become-so-alone-so-utterly-alone-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must become so alone, so utterly alone, that we withdraw into our innermost self. It is a way of bitter suffering. But then our solitude is overcome, we are no longer alone, for we find that our innermost self is the spirit, that it is God, the indivisible. And suddenly we find ourselves in the midst of the world, yet undisturbed by its multiplicity, for our innermost soul we know ourselves to be one with all being." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32516-when-i-have-neither-pleasure-nor-pain-and-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 03:37:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32516-when-i-have-neither-pleasure-nor-pain-and-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I have neither pleasure nor pain and have been breathing for a while the lukewarm insipid air of these so called good and tolerable days, I feel so bad in my childish soul that I smash my moldering lyre of thanksgiving in the face of the slumbering god of contentment and would rather feel the very devil burn in me than this warmth of a well-heated room.  A wild longing for strong emotions and sensations seethes in me, a rage against this toneless, flat, normal and sterile life.  I have a mad impulse to smash something, a warehouse, perhaps, or a cathedral, or myself, to commit outrages, to pull off the wigs of a few revered idols..." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836621-let-me-wake-up-next-to-you-have-coffee-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 06:58:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Charlotte Eriksson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/836621-let-me-wake-up-next-to-you-have-coffee-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me wake up next to you, have coffee in the morning and wander through the city with your hand in mine, and I'll be happy for the rest of my fucked up little life." -- Charlotte Eriksson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2447-yes-i-am-a-dreamer-for-a-dreamer-is-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 07:05:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2447-yes-i-am-a-dreamer-for-a-dreamer-is-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes: I am a dreamer. For a dreamer is one who can only find his way by moonlight, and his punishment is that he sees the dawn before the rest of the world." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 07:05:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death must be so beautiful. To lie in the soft brown earth, with the grasses waving above one's head, and listen to silence. To have no yesterday, and no tomorrow. To forget time, to forgive life, to be at peace." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635481-television-concentrates-its-blue-flicker-of-death-in-the-frontal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 10:41:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635481-television-concentrates-its-blue-flicker-of-death-in-the-frontal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Television concentrates its blue flicker of death in the frontal lobe" -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148796-take-my-love-take-my-land-take-me-where-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 07:03:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Mutant Enemy/Joss Whedon  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148796-take-my-love-take-my-land-take-me-where-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take my love, take my land
Take me where I cannot stand
I don’t care, I’m still free
You can’t take the sky from me
Take me out to the black
Tell them I ain’t comin’ back
Burn the land and boil the sea
You can’t take the sky from me
There’s no place I can be
Since I found Serenity
But you can’t take the sky from me…" -- Mutant Enemy/Joss Whedon  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301280-i-would-say-that-music-is-the-easiest-means-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 04:41:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301280-i-would-say-that-music-is-the-easiest-means-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would say that music is the easiest means in which to express, but since words are my talent, I must try to express clumsily in words what the pure music would have done better." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84471-in-the-u-s-you-have-to-be-a-deviant-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2014 12:03:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by William Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84471-in-the-u-s-you-have-to-be-a-deviant-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the U.S. you have to be a deviant or die of boredom." -- William Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515010-in-his-face-there-came-to-be-a-brooding-peace</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 17:15:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Paizleigh add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/515010-in-his-face-there-came-to-be-a-brooding-peace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his face there came to be a brooding peace that is seen most often in the faces of the very sorrowful or the very wise.  But still he wandered through the streets of the town, always silent and alone." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
