<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/742074-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/742074-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:42:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2351-though-much-is-taken-much-abides-and-though-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 16:54:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2351-though-much-is-taken-much-abides-and-though-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though much is taken, much abides; and though
We are not now that strength which in old days
Moved earth and heaven, that which we are, we are;
One equal temper of heroic hearts,
Made weak by time and fate, but strong in will
To strive, to seek, to find, and not to yield." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5012-man-is-condemned-to-be-free-because-once-thrown-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 14:27:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5012-man-is-condemned-to-be-free-because-once-thrown-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is condemned to be free; because once thrown into the world, he is responsible for everything he does. 
It is up to you to give [life] a meaning." -- Jean-Paul Sartre]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:00:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then I felt sad because I realized that once people are broken in certain ways, they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one. You wonder when your turn is going to be, or if it's already happened." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140642-no-no-first-comes-boyhood-you-get-to-play-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:00:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Brian K. Vaughan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140642-no-no-first-comes-boyhood-you-get-to-play-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No. No, first comes boyhood. You get to play with soldiers and spacemen, cowboys and ninjas, pirates and robots. But before you know it, all that comes to an end. And then, Remo Williams, is when the adventure begins." -- Brian K. Vaughan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:05:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13004-whatever-one-man-does-it-is-as-if-all-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:11:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13004-whatever-one-man-does-it-is-as-if-all-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever one man does, it is as if all men did it. For that reason, it is not unfair that one disobedience in a garden should contaminate all humanity; for that reason it is not unjust that the crucifixion of a single Jew should be sufficient to save it." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116439-it-doesn-t-matter-that-you-didn-t-believe-in-us-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:19:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116439-it-doesn-t-matter-that-you-didn-t-believe-in-us-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't matter that you didn't believe in us,&quot; said Mr. Ibis. &quot;We believed in you." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204943-the-squirrel-has-not-yet-found-the-acorn-that-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:23:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204943-the-squirrel-has-not-yet-found-the-acorn-that-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The squirrel has not yet found the acorn that will grow to the oak that will be cut to form the cradle of the babe that will grow to slay me." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50993-touched-by-her-fingers-the-two-surviving-chocolate-people-copulate</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:26:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50993-touched-by-her-fingers-the-two-surviving-chocolate-people-copulate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Touched by her fingers, the two surviving chocolate people copulate desperately, losing themselves in a melting frenzy of lust, spending the last of their brief borrowed lives in a spasm of raspberry cream and fear." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53403-rules-and-responsibilities-these-are-the-ties-that-bind-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53403-rules-and-responsibilities-these-are-the-ties-that-bind-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rules and responsibilities: these are the ties that bind us. We do what we do, because of who we are. If we did otherwise, we would not be ourselves. I will do what I have to do. And I will do what I must." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:29:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37817-you-get-what-anybody-gets---you-get-a-lifetime</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 09:29:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37817-you-get-what-anybody-gets---you-get-a-lifetime]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get what anybody gets - you get a lifetime." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 15:34:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all the world hated you and believed you wicked, while your own conscience approved of you and absolved you from guilt, you would not be without friends." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43600-to-women-who-please-me-only-by-their-faces-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 15:34:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43600-to-women-who-please-me-only-by-their-faces-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To women who please me only by their faces, I am the very devil when I find out they have neither souls nor hearts — when they open to me a perspective of flatness, triviality, and perhaps imbecility, coarseness, and ill-temper: but to the clear eye and eloquent tongue, to the soul made of fire, and the character that bends but does not break — at once supple and stable, tractable and consistent — I am ever tender and true. (Mr Rochester to Jane)" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378975-time-s-a-goon-right-you-gonna-let-that-goon-push</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 06:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378975-time-s-a-goon-right-you-gonna-let-that-goon-push]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time’s a goon, right? You gonna let that goon push you around?” Scotty shook his head. “The goon won." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66096-the-brain-appears-to-possess-a-special-area-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 22:23:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66096-the-brain-appears-to-possess-a-special-area-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The brain appears to possess a special area which we might call poetic memory and which records everything that charms or touches us, that makes our lives beautiful ... Love begins with a metaphor. Which is to say, love begins at the point when a woman enters her first word into our poetic memory." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 16:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61926-thermodynamic-miracles-events-with-odds-against-so-astronomical-they-re-effectively]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thermodynamic miracles... events with odds against so astronomical they're effectively impossible, like oxygen spontaneously becoming gold. I long to observe such a thing.
And yet, in each human coupling, a thousand million sperm vie for a single egg. Multiply those odds by countless generations, against the odds of your ancestors being alive; meeting; siring this precise son; that exact daughter... Until your mother loves a man she has every reason to hate, and of that union, of the thousand million children competing for fertilization, it was you, only you, that emerged. To distill so specific a form from that chaos of improbability, like turning air to gold... that is the crowning unlikelihood. The thermodynamic miracle.

But...if me, my birth, if that's a thermodynamic miracle... I mean, you could say that about anybody in the world!.

Yes. Anybody in the world. ..But the world is so full of people, so crowded with these miracles that they become commonplace and we forget... I forget. We gaze continually at the world and it grows dull in our perceptions. Yet seen from the another's vantage point. As if new, it may still take our breath away. Come...dry your eyes. For you are life, rarer than a quark and unpredictable beyond the dreams of Heisenberg; the clay in which the forces that shape all things leave their fingerprints most clearly. Dry your eyes... and let's go home." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13708-i-suggest-that-the-only-books-that-influence-us-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:45:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13708-i-suggest-that-the-only-books-that-influence-us-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suggest that the only books that influence us are those for which we are ready, and which have gone a little further down our particular path than we have yet gone ourselves." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:46:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84061-it-isn-t-possible-to-love-and-part-you-will-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't possible to love and part.  You will wish that it was.  You can transmute love, ignore it, muddle it, but you can never pull it out of you. I know by experience that the poets are right:  love is eternal." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12682-it-is-fate-that-i-am-here-george-persisted-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 14:53:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by E. M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12682-it-is-fate-that-i-am-here-george-persisted-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is fate that I am here,' George persisted, 'but you can call it Italy if it makes you less unhappy." -- E. M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63960-should-i-kill-myself-or-have-a-cup-of-coffee</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 07:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63960-should-i-kill-myself-or-have-a-cup-of-coffee]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Should I kill myself, or have a cup of coffee?" -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29516-there-is-but-one-truly-serious-philosophical-problem-and-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2012 07:47:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29516-there-is-but-one-truly-serious-philosophical-problem-and-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is but one truly serious philosophical problem and that is suicide. Judging whether life is or is not worth living amounts to answering the fundamental question of philosophy. All the rest — whether or not the world has three dimensions, whether the mind has nine or twelve categories — comes afterwards. These are games; one must first answer." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 16:27:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By then I knew that everything good and bad left an emptiness when it stopped.  But if it was bad, the emptiness filled up by itself.  If it was good you could only fill it by finding something better." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2012 16:26:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34107-you-expected-to-be-sad-in-the-fall-part-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You expected to be sad in the fall. Part of you died each year when the leaves fell from the trees and their branches were bare against the wind and the cold, wintery light. But you knew there would always be the spring, as you knew the river would flow again after it was frozen. When the cold rains kept on and killed the spring, it was as though a young person died for no reason." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 11:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271046-if-he-s-not-calling-you-it-s-because-you-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 12:06:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271046-if-he-s-not-calling-you-it-s-because-you-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If he’s not calling you, it’s because you are not on his mind. If he creates expectations for you, and then doesn’t follow through on little things, he will do same for big things. Be aware of this and realize that he’s okay with disappointing you. Don’t be with someone who doesn’t do what they say they’re going to do.  If he’s choosing not to make a simple effort that would put you at ease and bring harmony to a recurring fight, then he doesn’t respect your feelings and needs. “Busy” is another word for “asshole.” “Asshole” is another word for the guy you’re dating. You deserve a fcking phone call." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163539-did-you-have-one-of-those-days-today-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 14:55:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Harlan Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163539-did-you-have-one-of-those-days-today-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you have one of those days today, like a nail in the foot? Did the pterodactyl corpse dropped by the ghost of your mother from the spectral Hindenburg forever circling the Earth come smashing through the lid of your glass coffin? Did the New York strip steak you attacked at dinner suddenly show a mouth filled with needle-sharp teeth, and did it snap off the end of your fork, the last solid-gold fork from the set Anastasia pressed into your hands as they took her away to be shot? Is the slab under your apartment building moaning that it cannot stand the weight on its back a moment longer, and is the building stretching and creaking? Did a good friend betray you today, or did that good friend merely keep silent and fail to come to your aid? Are you holding the razor at your throat this very instant? Take heart, comfort is at hand. This is the hour that stretches. Djan karet. We are the cavalry. We're here. Put away the pills. We'll get you through this bloody night. Next time, it'll be your turn to help us.
&quot;Eidolons&quot; (1988)" -- Harlan Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223721-i-never-hated-a-man-enough-to-give-him-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 15:24:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Zsa Zsa Gabor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223721-i-never-hated-a-man-enough-to-give-him-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never hated a man enough to give him his diamonds back." -- Zsa Zsa Gabor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319234-when-you-hold-a-grudge-you-want-someone-else-s-sorrow</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 15:24:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319234-when-you-hold-a-grudge-you-want-someone-else-s-sorrow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you hold a grudge, you want someone else’s sorrow to reflect your level of hurt but the two rarely meet." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
