<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/743242-saundra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/743242-saundra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 05:21:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2008 05:21:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18481-and-it-never-failed-that-during-the-dry-years-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it never failed that during the dry years the people forgot about the rich years, and during the wet years they lost all memory of the dry years. It was always that way." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:23:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:24:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:24:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:25:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 04:25:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 04:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 14:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all the dragons in our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us act, just once, with beauty and courage. Perhaps everything that frightens us is, in its deepest essence, something helpless that wants our love." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23380-if-we-have-no-peace-it-is-because-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 04:06:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23380-if-we-have-no-peace-it-is-because-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we have no peace, it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 06:16:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Saundra add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142707-we-are-all-alone-born-alone-die-alone-and---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all alone, born alone, die alone, and -- in spite of True Romance magazines -- we shall all someday look back on our lives and see that, in spite of our company, we were alone the whole way. I do not say lonely -- at least, not all the time -- but essentially, and finally, alone. This is what makes your self-respect so important, and I don't see how you can respect yourself if you must look in the hearts and minds of others for your happiness." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
