<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746307-tom]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746307-tom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 20:31:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/959420-almondine-eventually-she-understood-the-house-was-keeping-a-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 20:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by David Wroblewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/959420-almondine-eventually-she-understood-the-house-was-keeping-a-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Almondine

Eventually, she understood the house was keeping a secret from her.

All that winter and all through the spring Almondine had known something was going to happen, but no matter where she looked she couldn’t find it. Sometimes, when she entered a room, there was the feeling that the thing that was going to happen had just been there, and she would stop and pant and peer around while the feeling seeped away as mysteriously as it had arrived. Weeks might pass without a sign, and then a night would come, when, lying nose to tail beneath the window in the kitchen corner, listening to the murmur of conversation and the slosh and clink of dishes being washed, she felt it in the house again and she whisked her tail in long, pensive strokes across the baseboards and silently collected her feet beneath her and waited. When half an hour passed and nothing appeared, she groaned and sighed and rolled onto her back and waited to see if it was somewhere in her sleep." -- David Wroblewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277088-in-her-life-she-d-been-nourished-and-sustained-by-certain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 20:36:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tom add a quote by David Wroblewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277088-in-her-life-she-d-been-nourished-and-sustained-by-certain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In her life, she'd been nourished and sustained by certain things, him being one of them, Trudy another, and Edgar, the third and most important, but it was really the three of them together, intersecting in her, for each of them powered her heart in a different way." -- David Wroblewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
