<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746510-inuitdebonair]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746510-inuitdebonair" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:48:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173618-it-doesn-t-matter-what-you-do-because-it-s-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:48:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173618-it-doesn-t-matter-what-you-do-because-it-s-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't matter what you do because it's going to happen anyway." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169619-in-passing-i-met-some-very-interesting-cows-and-sheep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:47:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Randy Newman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169619-in-passing-i-met-some-very-interesting-cows-and-sheep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In passing, I met some very interesting cows and sheep just north of Breda. One of the cows had escaped from England during that bogus Mad Cow thing. He (she I guess – I don’t know much about cows) told me that he swam all the way to Holland from England but I don’t believe him (her). I’m staying in a hotel adjacent to the red light district. I sat in my window for three hours this evening. I bought a brand new purple light but attracted only some drunken German businessmen. There must be a better way to deal with loneliness." -- Randy Newman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169617-be-with-me-in-the-phases-of-my-work-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:47:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169617-be-with-me-in-the-phases-of-my-work-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be With Me In The Phases Of My Work Because My Brain Feels Like It Has Been Whipped And I Yearn To Make A Small Perfect Thing Which Will Live In Your Morning Like Curious Static Through A President's Elegy Or A Nude Hunchback Acquiring A Tan On The Crowded Oily Beach. " -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169618-secret-kabals-of-vegetarians-habitually-gather-under-the-sign-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:47:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169618-secret-kabals-of-vegetarians-habitually-gather-under-the-sign-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Secret kabals of vegetarians habitually gather under the sign to exchange contraband from beyond the Vegetable Barrier. In their pinpoint eyes dances their old dream: the Total Fast. One of them reports a new atrocity published without compassionate comment by the editors of Scientific American: &quot;It has been established that, when pulled from the ground, a radish produces an electronic scream.&quot; Not even the triple bill for 65˘ will comfort them tonight. With a mad laugh born of despair, one of them throws himself on a hot-dog stand, disintegrating on the first chew into pathetic withdrawal symptoms. The rest watch him mournfully and then separate into the Montreal entertainment section. The news is more serious than any of them thought. One is ravished by a steak house with sidewalk ventilation. In a restaurant, one argues with the waiter that he ordered &quot;tomato&quot; but then in a suicide of gallantry he agrees to accept the spaghetti, meat sauce mistake." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169620-at-all-these-european-shows-there-are-autograph-collectors-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 07:48:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Randy Newman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169620-at-all-these-european-shows-there-are-autograph-collectors-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At all these European shows there are autograph collectors who stand outside for sound check and before the show and sometimes at the hotel. I don’t even know if they know who I am. At Gateshead, I signed autographs going in to the show, when I came out this little guy came up to me. Cathy said, “You already signed for him.” He said, “No! I wasn’t here before.” He was irate. Anyway, Cathy and I got in the car and went to the hotel that was about ¼ mile away. The guy beat the car there. I told him (he was Irish) that he’d just broken the Irish 200 meter record. I signed and invited him up to the room to spend the night. I love great athletes." -- Randy Newman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292379-some-christian-lawyers-some-eminent-and-stupid-judges-have-said-and-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 15:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Robert G Ingersoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292379-some-christian-lawyers-some-eminent-and-stupid-judges-have-said-and-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some Christian lawyers—some eminent and stupid judges—have said and still say, that the Ten Commandments are the foundation of all law.

Nothing could be more absurd. Long before these commandments were given there were codes of laws in India and Egypt—laws against murder, perjury, larceny, adultery and fraud. Such laws are as old as human society; as old as the love of life; as old as industry; as the idea of prosperity; as old as human love.

All of the Ten Commandments that are good were old; all that were new are foolish. If Jehovah had been civilized he would have left out the commandment about keeping the Sabbath, and in its place would have said: 'Thou shalt not enslave thy fellow-men.' He would have omitted the one about swearing, and said: 'The man shall have but one wife, and the woman but one husband.' He would have left out the one about graven images, and in its stead would have said: 'Thou shalt not wage wars of extermination, and thou shalt not unsheathe the sword except in self-defence.'

If Jehovah had been civilized, how much grander the Ten Commandments would have been.

All that we call progress—the enfranchisement of man, of labor, the substitution of imprisonment for death, of fine for imprisonment, the destruction of polygamy, the establishing of free speech, of the rights of conscience; in short, all that has tended to the development and civilization of man; all the results of investigation, observation, experience and free thought; all that man has accomplished for the benefit of man since the close of the Dark Ages—has been done in spite of the Old Testament." -- Robert G Ingersoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355229-packed-up-the-dylan-and-the-man-ray-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Inuitdebonair add a quote by Walter Becker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355229-packed-up-the-dylan-and-the-man-ray-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Packed up the Dylan and the Man Ray and the Joyce
I left a note that said well I guess I got no choice
Scuse me girl while I'm kicking it to the curb
Leaving with all I need but less than I deserve" -- Walter Becker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
