<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746891-christina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/746891-christina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 16:55:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19493-here-is-the-world-beautiful-and-terrible-things-will-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 16:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19493-here-is-the-world-beautiful-and-terrible-things-will-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is the world.  Beautiful and terrible things will happen.  Don't be afraid." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2149-i-told-you-in-the-course-of-this-paper-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:24:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2149-i-told-you-in-the-course-of-this-paper-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told you in the course of this paper that Shakespeare had a sister; but do not look for her in Sir Sidney Lee’s life of the poet. She died young—alas, she never wrote a word. She lies buried where the omnibuses now stop, opposite the Elephant and Castle. Now my belief is that this poet who never wrote a word and was buried at the cross–roads still lives. She lives in you and in me, and in many other women who are not here to–night, for they are washing up the dishes and putting the children to bed. But she lives; for great poets do not die; they are continuing presences; they need only the opportunity to walk among us in the flesh. This opportunity, as I think, it is now coming within your power to give her. For my belief is that if we live another century or so—I am talking of the common life which is the real life and not of the little separate lives which we live as individuals—and have five hundred a year each of us and rooms of our own; if we have the habit of freedom and the courage to write exactly what we think; if we escape a little from the common sitting–room and see human beings not always in their relation to each other but in relation to reality; and the sky. too, and the trees or whatever it may be in themselves; if we look past Milton’s bogey, for no human being should shut out the view; if we face the fact, for it is a fact, that there is no arm to cling to, but that we go alone and that our relation is to the world of reality and not only to the world of men and women, then the opportunity will come and the dead poet who was Shakespeare’s sister will put on the body which she has so often laid down. Drawing her life from the lives of the unknown who were her forerunners, as her brother did before her, she will be born. As for her coming without that preparation, without that effort on our part, without that determination that when she is born again she shall find it possible to live and write her poetry, that we cannot expect, for that would he impossible. But I maintain that she would come if we worked for her, and that so to work, even in poverty and obscurity, is worth while." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:27:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6203-she-would-of-been-a-good-woman-said-the-misfit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6203-she-would-of-been-a-good-woman-said-the-misfit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She would of been a good woman,&quot; said The Misfit, &quot;if it had been somebody there to shoot her every minute of her life." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 09:37:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can, with one eye squinted, take it all as a blessing." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45936-days-pass-when-i-forget-the-mystery-problems-insoluble-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 10:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christina add a quote by Denise Levertov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45936-days-pass-when-i-forget-the-mystery-problems-insoluble-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Days pass when I forget the mystery.
Problems insoluble and problems offering
their own ignored solutions
jostle for my attention, they crowd its antechamber
along with a host of diversions, my courtiers, wearing
their colored clothes; caps and bells.
                                                    And then
once more the quiet mystery
is present to me, the throng's clamor
recedes:  the mystery
that there is anything, anything at all,
let alone cosmos, joy, memory, everything,
rather than void: and that, 0 Lord,
Creator, Hallowed one, You still,
hour by hour sustain it." -- Denise Levertov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
