<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/748739-matt-arrowood]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/748739-matt-arrowood" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 18:39:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10864-did-my-heart-love-till-now-forswear-it-sight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 18:39:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10864-did-my-heart-love-till-now-forswear-it-sight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did my heart love till now? forswear it, sight!  For I ne'er saw true beauty till this night." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15679-the-cover-was-pebbled-black-leather-the-pages-onionskin-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 18:42:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Charles Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15679-the-cover-was-pebbled-black-leather-the-pages-onionskin-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cover was pebbled black leather, the pages onionskin, and he opened it carefully. It was his first Bible, the one his mother had given him, the one that had taken its time showing him what he was supposed to do with his life, his size, that voice of his. It was the one used for his ordination, and when he had buried his mother on a autumn hillside in Tennesee five years ago. King James. He didn't care about the scholars or the accuracy or the bringing of his church into whatever century they claimed it was these days; he cared about the poetry, and about the comfort it brought to those who needed to hear it." -- Charles Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023350-the-cover-was-pebbled-black-leather-the-pages-onionskin-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 19:00:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Charles L. Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023350-the-cover-was-pebbled-black-leather-the-pages-onionskin-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cover was pebbled black leather, the pages onionskin, and he opened it carefully. It was his first Bible, the one his mother had given him, the one that had taken its time showing him what he was supposed to do with his life, his size, that voice of his. It was the one used for his ordination, and when he had buried his mother on an autumn hillside in Tennessee five years ago. King James. He didn't care about the scholars or the accuracy or the bringing of his church into whatever century they claimed it was these days; he cared about the poetry, and about the comfort it brought to those who needed to hear it." -- Charles L. Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
