<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/748860-rosana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/748860-rosana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 07:23:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 07:23:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1717-two-wrongs-don-t-make-a-right-but-they-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 07:27:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Thomas Szasz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1717-two-wrongs-don-t-make-a-right-but-they-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two wrongs don't make a right, but they make a good excuse." -- Thomas Szasz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 07:33:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not read, as children do, to amuse yourself, or like the ambitious, for the purpose of instruction. No, read in order to live." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 13:20:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 20:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Anne Enright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108063-and-what-amazes-me-as-i-hit-the-motorway-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what amazes me as I hit the motorway is not the fact that everyone loses someone, but that everyone loves someone. It seems like such a massive waste of energy -- and we all do it, all the people beetling along between the white lines, merging, converging, overtaking. We each love someone, even though they will die. And we keep loving them, even when they are not there to love any more. And there is no logic or use to any of this, that I can see." -- Anne Enright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60630-loneliness-does-not-come-from-having-no-people-about-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 08:27:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60630-loneliness-does-not-come-from-having-no-people-about-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loneliness does not come from having no people about one, but from being unable to communicate the things that seem important to oneself, or from holding certain views which others find inadmissible." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22674-the-greatest-tragedy-of-the-family-is-the-unlived-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 08:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22674-the-greatest-tragedy-of-the-family-is-the-unlived-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest tragedy of the family is the unlived lives of the parents." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113339-blindness-is-a-private-matter-between-a-person-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 20:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by José Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113339-blindness-is-a-private-matter-between-a-person-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["blindness is a private matter between a person and the eyes with which he or she was born." -- José Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 19:34:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be afraid to raise your voice for honesty and truth and compassion against injustice and lying and greed. If people all over the world...would do this, it would change the earth." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126946-you-know-what-s-truly-weird-about-any-financial-crisis-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 13:24:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Bruce Sterling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126946-you-know-what-s-truly-weird-about-any-financial-crisis-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know what's truly weird about any financial crisis? We made it up. Currency, money, finance, they're all social inventions. When the sun comes up in the morning it's shining on the same physical landscape, all the atoms are in place." -- Bruce Sterling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157380-i-have-had-such-a-sickening-of-men-in-masses</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 09:23:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157380-i-have-had-such-a-sickening-of-men-in-masses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I have had such a sickening of men in masses, and of causes, that I would not cross this room to reform parliament or prevent the union or to bring about the millennium. I speak only for myself, mind - it is my own truth alone - but man as part of a movement or a crowd is indifferent to me. He is inhuman. And I have nothing to do with nations, or nationalism. The only feelings I have - for what they are - are for men as individuals; my loyalties, such as they may be, are to private persons alone." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35134-there-are-things-that-happen-and-leave-no-discernible-trace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2011 11:13:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by A. S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35134-there-are-things-that-happen-and-leave-no-discernible-trace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are things that happen and leave no discernible trace, are not spoken or written of, though it would be very wrong to say that subsequent events go on indifferently, all the same, as though such things had never been." -- A. S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 18:36:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16593-responsibility-to-yourself-means-refusing-to-let-others-do-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Responsibility to yourself means refusing to let others do your thinking, talking, and naming for you...it means that you do not treat your body as a commodity with which to purchase superficial intimacy or economic security; for our bodies to be treated as objects, our minds are in mortal danger. It means insisting that those to whom you give your friendship and love are able to respect your mind. It means being able to say, with Charlotte Bronte's Jane Eyre: &quot;I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all the extraneous delights should be withheld or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give.

Responsibility to yourself means that you don't fall for shallow and easy solutions--predigested books and ideas...marrying early as an escape from real decisions, getting pregnant as an evasion of already existing problems. It means that you refuse to sell your talents and aspirations short...and this, in turn, means resisting the forces in society which say that women should be nice, play safe, have low professional expectations, drown in love and forget about work, live through others, and stay in the places assigned to us. It means that we insist on a life of meaningful work, insist that work be as meaningful as love and friendship in our lives. It means, therefore, the courage to be &quot;different&quot;...The difference between a life lived actively, and a life of passive drifting and dispersal of energies, is an immense difference. Once we begin to feel committed to our lives, responsible to ourselves, we can never again be satisfied with the old, passive way." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194339-traveling-outgrows-its-motives-it-soon-proves-sufficient-in-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 15:37:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Nicolas Bouvier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194339-traveling-outgrows-its-motives-it-soon-proves-sufficient-in-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Traveling outgrows its motives. It soon proves sufficient in itself. You think you are making a trip, but soon it is making you - or unmaking you." -- Nicolas Bouvier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30308-the-unfed-mind-devours-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 14:03:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30308-the-unfed-mind-devours-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unfed mind devours itself." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40455-i-am-all-the-ages-i-ve-ever-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:48:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40455-i-am-all-the-ages-i-ve-ever-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am all the ages I've ever been." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 17:34:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 11:27:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159154-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding-terms</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2013 15:49:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159154-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding-terms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I think we are well-advised to keep on nodding terms with the people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not. Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends. We forget all too soon the things we thought we could never forget. We forget the loves and the betrayals alike, forget what we whispered and what we screamed, forget who we were." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552221-i-get-a-warm-feeling-among-my-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 09:16:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rosana add a quote by Anthony Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552221-i-get-a-warm-feeling-among-my-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I get a warm feeling among my books." -- Anthony Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
