<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749159-zachary]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749159-zachary" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 10:44:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68661-the-lunatic-is-all-id-e-fixe-and-whatever-he-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 10:44:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Umberto Eco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68661-the-lunatic-is-all-id-e-fixe-and-whatever-he-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lunatic is all idée fixe, and whatever he comes across confirms his lunacy. You can tell him by the liberties he takes with common sense, by his flashes of inspiration, and by the fact that sooner or later he brings up the Templars." -- Umberto Eco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 12:49:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time in the dead of winter in the Dakota Territory, Theodore Roosevelt took off in a makeshift boat down the Little Missouri River in pursuit of a couple of thieves who had stolen his prized rowboat.  After several days on the river, he caught up and got the draw on them with his trusty Winchester, at which point they surrendered.  Then Roosevelt set off in a borrowed wagon to haul the thieves cross-country to justice.  They headed across the snow-covered wastes of the Badlands to the railhead at Dickinson, and Roosevelt walked the whole way, the entire 40 miles.  It was an astonishing feat, what might be called a defining moment in Roosevelt’s eventful life.  But what makes it especially memorable is that during that time, he managed to read all of &lt;i&gt;Anna Karenina&lt;/i&gt;.  I often think of that when I hear people say they haven’t time to read." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107967-we-re-more-of-the-love-blood-and-rhetoric-school-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 06:34:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107967-we-re-more-of-the-love-blood-and-rhetoric-school-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're more of the love, blood, and rhetoric school. Well, we can do you blood and love without the rhetoric, and we can do you blood and rhetoric without the love, and we can do you all three concurrent or consecutive. But we can't give you love and rhetoric without the blood. Blood is compulsory. They're all blood, you see." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29348-some-people-and-i-am-one-of-them-hate-happy-ends-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 20:11:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29348-some-people-and-i-am-one-of-them-hate-happy-ends-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people—and I am one of them—hate happy ends. We feel cheated. Harm is the norm. Doom should not jam. The avalanche stopping in its tracks a few feet above the cowering village behaves not only unnaturally but unethically." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128303-who-claims-truth-truth-abandons-history-is-hir-d-or-coerc-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 15:04:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128303-who-claims-truth-truth-abandons-history-is-hir-d-or-coerc-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who claims Truth, Truth abandons. History is hir'd, or coerc'd, only in Interests that must ever prove base. She is too innocent, to be left within the reach of anyone in Power,- who need but touch her, and all her Credit is in the instant vanish'd, as if it had never been. She needs rather to be tended lovingly and honorably by fabulists and counterfeiters, Ballad-Mongers and Cranks of ev'ry Radius, Masters of Disguise to provide her the Costume, Toilette, and Bearing, and Speech nimble enough to keep her beyond the Desires, or even the Curiosity, of Government." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234236-does-britannia-when-she-sleeps-dream-is-america-her-dream---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 13:24:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234236-does-britannia-when-she-sleeps-dream-is-america-her-dream---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Does Britannia, when she sleeps, dream? Is America her dream?-- in which all that cannot pass in the metropolitan Wakefulness is allow'd Expression away in the restless Slumber of these Provinces, and on West-ward, wherever 'tis not yet mapp'd, nor written down, nor ever, by the majority of Mankind, seen,-- serving as a very Rubbish-Tip for subjunctive Hopes, for all that may yet be true,-- Earthly Paradise, Fountain of Youth, Realms of Prester John, Christ's Kingdom, ever behind the sunset, safe til the next Territory to the West be seen and recorded, measur'd and tied in, back into the Net-Work of Points already known, that slowly triangulates its Way into the Continent, changing all from subjunctive to declarative, reducing Possibilities to Simplicities that serve the ends of Governments,-- winning away from the realm of the Sacred, its Borderlands one by one, and assuming them unto the bare mortal World that is our home, and our Despair." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 13:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zachary add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
