<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749155-muzzlehatch]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749155-muzzlehatch" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 17:58:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81952-there-occurred-within-a-causal-radius-of-brandon-station-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 17:58:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muzzlehatch add a quote by John Cowper Powys]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81952-there-occurred-within-a-causal-radius-of-brandon-station-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There occurred within a causal radius of Brandon Station one of those infinitesimal ripples in the creative silence of the First Cause. In the soul of the great blazing sun there were complicated superhuman vibrations [connected] ... with the feelings of a few intellectual sages who had enough imagination to recognise the conscious personality of this fiery orb as it flung far and wide its life-giving magnetic forces. Roaring, cresting, heaving, gathering, mounting, advancing, receding, the enormous fire-thoughts of this huge luminary surged relentlessly to and fro, evoking a turbulent aura of psychic activity." -- John Cowper Powys]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111056-they-wept-for-humanity-those-two-not-for-themselves-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 15:12:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muzzlehatch add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111056-they-wept-for-humanity-those-two-not-for-themselves-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They wept for humanity, those two, not for themselves. They could not bear that this should be the end. Ere silence was completed their hearts were opened, and they knew what had been important on the earth. Man, the flower of all flesh, the noblest of all creatures visible, man who had once made god in his image, and had mirrored his strength on the constellations, beautiful naked man was dying, strangled in the garments that he had woven. Century after century had he toiled, and here was his reward. Truly the garment had seemed heavenly at first, shot with colours of culture, sewn with the threads of self-denial. And heavenly it had been so long as man could shed it at will and live by the essence that is his soul, and the essence, equally divine, that is his body. The sin against the body - it was for that they wept in chief; the centuries of wrong against the muscles and the nerves, and those five portals by which we can alone apprehend - glozing it over with talk of evolution, until the body was white pap, the home of ideas as colourless, last sloshy stirrings of a spirit that had grasped the stars. " -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8365-the-most-preposterous-notion-that-homo-sapiens-has-ever-dreamed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 08:35:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muzzlehatch add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8365-the-most-preposterous-notion-that-homo-sapiens-has-ever-dreamed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most preposterous notion that Homo sapiens has ever dreamed up is that the Lord God of Creation, Shaper and Ruler of all the Universes, wants the saccharine adoration of His creatures, can be swayed by their prayers, and becomes petulant if He does not receive this flattery. Yet this absurd fantasy, without a shred of evidence to bolster it, pays all the expenses of the oldest, largest, and least productive industry in all history." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410-well-art-is-art-isn-t-it-still-on-the-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 03:02:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muzzlehatch add a quote by Groucho Marx ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410-well-art-is-art-isn-t-it-still-on-the-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, art is art, isn't it? Still, on the other hand, water is water! And east is east and west is west and if you take cranberries and stew them like applesauce they taste much more like prunes than rhubarb does. Now, uh... now you tell me what you know." -- Groucho Marx ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18856-believe-those-who-are-seeking-the-truth-doubt-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 08:43:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muzzlehatch add a quote by Andre Gide ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18856-believe-those-who-are-seeking-the-truth-doubt-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Believe those who are seeking the truth. Doubt those who find it." -- Andre Gide ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
