<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749415-eileen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749415-eileen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 08:55:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51398-the-world-is-perishing-from-an-orgy-of-self-sacrificing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 08:55:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51398-the-world-is-perishing-from-an-orgy-of-self-sacrificing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is perishing from an orgy of self-sacrificing." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18860-when-someone-seeks-said-siddhartha-then-it-easily-happens-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 13:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18860-when-someone-seeks-said-siddhartha-then-it-easily-happens-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone seeks,&quot; said Siddhartha, &quot;then it easily happens that his eyes see only the thing that he seeks, and he is able to find nothing, to take in nothing because he always thinks only about the thing he is seeking, because he has one goal, because he is obsessed with his goal. Seeking means: having a goal. But finding means: being free, being open, having no goal." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93301-women-have-curious-ways-of-hurting-someone-else-they-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 13:38:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93301-women-have-curious-ways-of-hurting-someone-else-they-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women have curious ways of hurting someone else. They hurt themselves instead; or else they do it so the guy doesn't even know he's been hurt until much later. Then he finds out. Then his dick falls off." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94432-the-answer-is-that-we-are-not-helpless-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 13:17:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94432-the-answer-is-that-we-are-not-helpless-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is that we are not helpless in the face of our first impressions.  They may bubble up from the unconscious - from behind a locked door inside of our brain - but just because something is outside of awareness doesn't mean it's outside of control." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94437-arousal-leaves-us-mind-blind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 13:19:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94437-arousal-leaves-us-mind-blind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Arousal leaves us mind-blind." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94440-when-making-a-decision-of-minor-importance-i-have-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 13:28:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94440-when-making-a-decision-of-minor-importance-i-have-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When making a decision of minor importance, I have always found it advantageous to consider all the pros and cons. In vital matters, however, such as the choice of a mate or a profession, the decision should come from the unconscious, from somewhere within ourselves.  In the important decisions of personal life, we should be governed, I think, by the deep inner needs of our nature." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109699-people-move-because-of-the-wear-and-tear-of-anxiety</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 15:54:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109699-people-move-because-of-the-wear-and-tear-of-anxiety]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People move because of the wear and tear of anxiety. Because of the gnawing feeling that no matter how hard they work their efforts will yield nothing, that what they build up in one year will be torn down in one day by others. Because of the impression that the future is blocked up, that *they* might do all right but not their children.  Because of the feeling that nothing will change, that happiness and prosperity are possible only somewhere else." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109702-an-adult-female-orang-utan-cannot-defeat-an-adult-male-spotted</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 16:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109702-an-adult-female-orang-utan-cannot-defeat-an-adult-male-spotted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An adult female orang-utan cannot defeat an adult male spotted hyena. That is the plain empirical truth. Let it become known among zoologists. Had Orange Juice been a male, had she loomed as large on the scales as she did in my heart, it might have been another matter. But portly and overfed though she was from living in the comfort of a zoo, even so she tipped the scales at barely 110 pounds.  Female orang-utans are half the size of males. But it is not simply a question of weight and brute strength. Orange Juice was far from defenseless. What it comes down to is attitude and knowledge. What does a fruit eater know about killing? Where would it learn where to bite, how hard, for how long? An orang-utan may be taller, may have very strong and agile arms and long canines, but if it does not know how to use these as weapons, they are of little use. The hyena, with only its jaws, will overcome the ape because it knows what it wants and how to get it." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109703-my-face-set-to-a-grim-and-determined-expression-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 16:07:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109703-my-face-set-to-a-grim-and-determined-expression-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My face set to a grim and determined expression. I speak in all modesty as I say this, but I discovered at that moment that I have a fierce will to live. It's not something evident, in my experience. Some of us give up on life with only a resigned sigh. Others fight a little, then lose hope. Still others - and I am one of those - never give up. We fight and fight and fight. We fight no matter the cost of battle, the losses we take, the improbability of success. We fight to the every end.  It's not a question of courage. It's something constitutional, an inability to let go. It may be nothing more than life-hungry stupidity." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 16:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must say a word about fear. It is life's only true opponent. Only fear can defeat life. It is a clever, treacherous adversary, how well I know. It has no decency, respects no law or convention, shows no mercy. It goes for your weakest spot, which it finds with unnerving ease. It begins in your mind, always ... so you must fight hard to express it. You must fight hard to shine the light of words upon it. Because if you don't, if your fear becomes a wordless darkness that you avoid, perhaps even manage to forget, you open yourself to further attacks of fear because you never truly fought the opponent who defeated you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109712-for-the-first-time-i-noticed---as-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 16:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109712-for-the-first-time-i-noticed---as-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first time I noticed - as I would notice repeatedly during my ordeal, between one throe of agony and the next - that my suffering was taking place in a grand setting. I saw my suffering for what it was, finite and insignificant, and I was still. My suffering did not fit anywhere, I realized. And I could accept this. It was all right." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30719-it-matters-not-what-someone-is-born-but-what-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 05:53:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30719-it-matters-not-what-someone-is-born-but-what-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It matters not what someone is born, but what they grow to be." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77617-it-is-a-curious-thing-harry-but-perhaps-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 14:13:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77617-it-is-a-curious-thing-harry-but-perhaps-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, Harry, but perhaps those who are best suited to power are those who have never sought it. Those who, like you, have leadership thrust upon them, and take up the mantle because they must, and find to their own surprise that they wear it well." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185598-in-my-opinion-mountains-don-t-move-they-only-look-changed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185598-in-my-opinion-mountains-don-t-move-they-only-look-changed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my opinion, mountains don't move. They only look changed when you look down on them from a greaty height." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152329-i-had-just-dropped-out-of-medicine-in-my-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:35:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152329-i-had-just-dropped-out-of-medicine-in-my-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had just dropped out of medicine in my first year of residency, a few months shy of becoming a licensed M.D.  I'd discovered there was something serious, mainly a matter of nerve and perhaps empathy, that stood in my way." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152331-at-some-point-in-my-life-i-d-honestly-hoped-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:37:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152331-at-some-point-in-my-life-i-d-honestly-hoped-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point in my life I'd honestly hoped love would rescue me from the cold, drafty castle I lived in.  But at another point, much earlier I think, I'd quietly begun to hope for nothing at all in the way of love, so as not to be disappointed.  It works.  It gets to be a habit." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152333-you-think-you-re-no-good-so-you-can-t-do-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152333-you-think-you-re-no-good-so-you-can-t-do-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think you're no good, so you can't do good things.  Jesus, Codi, how long are you going to keep limping around on that crutch?  It's the other way around, it's what you *do* that makes you who you are." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152335-morality-is-not-a-large-constructed-thing-you-have-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152335-morality-is-not-a-large-constructed-thing-you-have-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Morality is not a large, constructed *thing* you have or have not, but simply a capacity.  Something you carry with you in your brain and in your hands." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113307-why-do-you-suppose-the-poets-talk-about-hearts-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:45:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113307-why-do-you-suppose-the-poets-talk-about-hearts-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you suppose the poets talk about hearts?' he asked me suddenly. 'When they discuss emotional damage? The tissue of hearts is tough as a shoe. Did you ever sew up a heart?'
I shook my head. 'No, but I've watched. I know what you mean.' The walls of a heart are thick and strong, and the surgeons use heavy needles. It takes a good bit of strength, but it pulls together neatly. As much as anything it's like binding a book.
The seat of human emotion should be the liver,' Doc Homer said. 'That would be an appropriate metaphor: we don't hold love in our hearts, we hold it in our livers.'
I understood exactly. Once in ER I saw a woman who'd been stabbed everywhere, most severely in the liver. It's an organ with the consistency of layer upon layer of wet Kleenex. Every attempt at repair just opens new holes that tear and bleed. You try to close the wound with fresh wounds, and you try and you try and you don't give up until there's nothing left." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152342-pain-reaches-the-heart-with-electrical-speed-but-truth-moves</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152342-pain-reaches-the-heart-with-electrical-speed-but-truth-moves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain reaches the heart with electrical speed, but truth moves to the heart as slowly as a glacier." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152343-i-ve-about-decided-that-s-the-main-thing-that-separates-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 17:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152343-i-ve-about-decided-that-s-the-main-thing-that-separates-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've about decided that's the main thing that separates happy people from the other people: the feeling that you're a practical item, with a use, like a sweater or a socket wrench." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189534-the-greeks-had-invented-democracy-built-the-acropolis-and-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2009 13:03:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Eileen add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189534-the-greeks-had-invented-democracy-built-the-acropolis-and-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Greeks had invented democracy, built the Acropolis and called it a day." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
