<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749788-kasey-tritch]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749788-kasey-tritch" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:15:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34049-but-what-i-really-want-is-to-just-swim-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:15:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34049-but-what-i-really-want-is-to-just-swim-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what I really want is to just swim around in a warm baby pool of these friends, jump in their dry leaf pile-to rub them all over myself, without words and clothes." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34050-but-the-grind-has-begun-the-windows-don-t-open-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by dave eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34050-but-the-grind-has-begun-the-windows-don-t-open-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the grind has begun.  The windows don’t open, and even the availability of near-constant jokes about Jews and Mormons fails to stem the tide of frustration, decay.  We’ve reached the end  of pure inspiration, and are now somewhere else, something implying routine, or doing something because people expect us to do it, going somewhere each day because we went there the day before, saying things because we have said them before, and this seems like the work of a different sort of animal, contrary to our plan, and this is very very bad." -- dave eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34051-so-i-should-be-aware-of-the-dangers-of-self-consciousness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:16:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34051-so-i-should-be-aware-of-the-dangers-of-self-consciousness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So I should be aware of the dangers of self-consciousness, but at the same time, I’ll be plowing through the fog of all these echoes, plowing through mixed metaphors, noise, and will try to show the core, which is still there, as a core, and is valid, despite the fog.  The core is the core is the core.  There is always the core, that can’t be articulated.
Only caricatured." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by dave eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34052-we-are-unusual-and-tragic-and-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are unusual and tragic and alive." -- dave eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34053-we-say-that-the-body-is-a-temple-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 11:19:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Valerie Jeremijenko]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34053-we-say-that-the-body-is-a-temple-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We say that the body is a temple, because we know that it’s nothing but mortal architecture without the self-regard of consciousness and conscience.  The contemplative moment draws us to our sources; we see inside.  We close our eyes, in fact, in order to see with clarity.  Indeed, the imagination asks us to see with our eyes closed.  So we make connections in the dark and thus we imagine what our bodies can do and be, how the breath of the spirit can come and go with perfection, how the ladder gravity of the spine can soar.  Poets speak of rhythm and breath as the lifeline of the poetic line; they speak of form as the embodiment of the poem’s energy, the bodying forth of its meaning and being.  To expire is to breathe out, to inspire is to breath in.  To aspire is to breathe with the mind, to give purpose to the heart’s rhythm.  The spine is an aspiration too, since it lifts us from foundations.  To imagine what the body can achieve is to invest it with awareness-to begin to make it twice alive: first as a body, then as an embodiment." -- Valerie Jeremijenko]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43183-that-love-is-reverence-and-worship-and-glory-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 07:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43183-that-love-is-reverence-and-worship-and-glory-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That love is reverence, and worship, and glory, and the upward glance. Not a bandage for dirty sores. But they don’t know it. Those who speak of love most promiscuously are the ones who’ve never felt it. They make some sort of feeble stew out of sympathy, compassion, contempt, and general indifference, and they call it love. Once you’ve felt what it means to love as you and I know it – the total passion for the total height – you’re incapable of anything less." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43184-she-looked-slowly-about-her-noting-every-object-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 07:34:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by ayn rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43184-she-looked-slowly-about-her-noting-every-object-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She looked slowly about her, noting every object and the reason for its presence." -- ayn rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113037-i-often-think-that-he-s-the-only-one-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 07:35:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113037-i-often-think-that-he-s-the-only-one-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often think that he's the only one of us who's achieved immortality. I don't mean in the sense of fame and I don't mean he won't die someday. But he's living it. I think he is what the conception really means. You know how people long to be eternal. But they die with everyday that passes. . . They change, they deny, they contradict- and they call it growth. At the end there is nothing left, nothing unreveresed or unbetrayed; as if there had never been an entity, only a succession of adjectives fading in and out of an unformed mass. How do they expect a permanence which they never held for a single moment? But Howard- one can imagine him living forever." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43187-when-the-fact-that-one-is-a-total-nonentity-who-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 07:35:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by ayn rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43187-when-the-fact-that-one-is-a-total-nonentity-who-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the fact that one is a total nonentity who’s done nothing more outstanding than eating, sleeping, and chatting with neighbors becomes a fact worthy of pride, of announcement to the world and of diligent study by millions of readers – the fact that one has built a cathedral becomes unrecordable and unannounceable.  A matter of perspectives and relativity.  The distance permissible between the extremes of any particular capacity is limited.  The sound perception of an ant does not include thunder." -- ayn rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43188-what-you-feel-in-the-presence-of-a-thing-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 07:36:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by ayn rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43188-what-you-feel-in-the-presence-of-a-thing-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you feel in the presence of a thing you admire is just one word – ‘Yes.’ The affirmation, the acceptance, the sign of admittance. And that ‘Yes’ is more than an answer to one thing, it’s a kind of ‘Amen’ to life, to the earth that holds this thing, to the thought that created it, to yourself for being able to see it.  But the ability to say ‘Yes’ or ‘No’ is the essence of all ownership. It’s your ownership of your own ego. Your soul, if you wish. Your soul has a single basic function-the act of valuing. ‘Yes’ or ‘No’, ‘I wish’ or ‘I do not wish.’ You can’t say ‘Yes’ without saying ‘I.’ There’s no affirmation without the one who affirms. In this sense, everything to which you grant your love is yours." -- ayn rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
