<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749923-denyse]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/749923-denyse" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 20:29:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233472-language-is-my-whore-my-mistress-my-wife-my-pen-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 20:29:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Denyse add a quote by Stephen Fry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233472-language-is-my-whore-my-mistress-my-wife-my-pen-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Language is my whore, my mistress, my wife, my pen-friend, my check-out girl. Language is a complimentary moist lemon-scented cleansing square or handy freshen-up wipette. Language is the breath of God, the dew on a fresh apple, it's the soft rain of dust that falls into a shaft of morning sun when you pull from an old bookshelf a forgotten volume of erotic diaries; language is the faint scent of urine on a pair of boxer shorts, it's a half-remembered childhood birthday party, a creak on the stair, a spluttering match held to a frosted pane, the warm wet, trusting touch of a leaking nappy, the hulk of a charred Panzer, the underside of a granite boulder, the first downy growth on the upper lip of a Mediterranean girl, cobwebs long since overrun by an old Wellington boot." -- Stephen Fry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104916-as-societies-grow-decadent-the-language-grows-decadent-too-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 20:32:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Denyse add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104916-as-societies-grow-decadent-the-language-grows-decadent-too-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As societies grow decadent, the language grows decadent, too. Words are used to disguise, not to illuminate, action: you liberate a city by destroying it. Words are to confuse, so that at election time people will solemnly vote against their own interests." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
