<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/750231-silsbee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/750231-silsbee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 18:52:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76939-there-are-those-wonderful-moments-of-clarity-in-life-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 18:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Paula Poundstone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76939-there-are-those-wonderful-moments-of-clarity-in-life-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those wonderful moments of clarity in life when one is reminded how irreparably flawed we humans are. Once, when I was nineteen, on the subway in Boston I lost my balance slightly and bumped into an elderly woman. I quickly apologized and she replied, &quot;Well, hold on to something, stupid.&quot; There it is. That's it. That's it in a nutshell. I don't want to sound negative, but I think every fetus should be shown a film of that incident, maybe projected up on the uterine wall, and then asked if it wants to come out. I am a strong believer in a woman's right to choose, but I also think that in the last trimester, the kid should be given every opportunity to back out." -- Paula Poundstone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171679-america-was-a-great-force-in-the-world-with-immense</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 20:19:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Robert Francis Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171679-america-was-a-great-force-in-the-world-with-immense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America was a great force in the world, with immense prestige, long before we became a great military power. That power has come to us and we cannot renounce it, but neither can we afford to forget that the real constructive force in the world comes not from bombs, but from imaginative ideas, warm sympathies, and a generous spirit." -- Robert Francis Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201629-brother-fox-looked-in-he-saw-two-people-he-saw</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 20:04:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201629-brother-fox-looked-in-he-saw-two-people-he-saw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Brother Fox looked in. He saw two people. He saw them raise their glasses of wine to him, liquid that for him was suspended in the air, as if by a miracle." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312127-i-am-glad-you-are-pleased-said-mma-ramotswe-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 17:07:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312127-i-am-glad-you-are-pleased-said-mma-ramotswe-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am glad you are pleased,&quot; said Mma Ramotswe. &quot;You have broken the glass ceiling that stops secretaries from reaching their full potential.&quot;

Mma Makutsi looked up, as if to search for the ceiling that she had broken. There were only the familiar ceiling boards, fly-tracked and buckling from the heat. But the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel itself could not at that moment have been more glorious in her eyes, more filled with hope and joy." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312129-if-the-lord-came-back-today-mr-j-l-b-matekoni-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 17:12:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312129-if-the-lord-came-back-today-mr-j-l-b-matekoni-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the lord came back today, [Mr. J.L.B. Matekoni] thought, he would probably be a mechanic, he reflected. That would be a great honour for mechanics everywhere. And there is no doubt but that e would choose Africa: Israel was far too dangerous these days. In fact, the more one thought about it, the more likely it was that he would choose Botswana, and Gabarone in particular. Now that would be a wonderful honour for the people of Botswana; but it would not happen, and there was no point in thinking about it any further. The Lord was not going to come back; we had had our chance and we had not made very much of it, unfortunately." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312130-mma-ramotswe-found-it-difficult-to-imagine-what-it-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 17:19:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312130-mma-ramotswe-found-it-difficult-to-imagine-what-it-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mma Ramotswe found it difficult to imagine what it would be like to have no people. There were, she knew, those who had no others in this life, who had no uncles, or aunts, or distant cousins of any degree; people who were just themselves. Many white people were like that, for some unfathomable reason; they did not seem to want to have people and were happy to be just themselves. How lonely they must be -- like spacemen deep in space, floating in darkness, but without even that silver, unfurling cord that linked the astronauts to their little metal womb of oxygen and warmth. For a moment, she indulged the metaphor, and imagined the tiny white van in space, slowly spinning against a background of stars and she, Mma Ramotswe, of the No. 1 Ladies' Space Agency, floating weightless, head over heels, tied to the tiny white van with a thin washing line." -- Alexander McCall Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260471-eleanor-looked-up-surprised-the-little-girl-was-sliding-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 14:23:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260471-eleanor-looked-up-surprised-the-little-girl-was-sliding-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eleanor looked up, surprised; the little girl was sliding back in her chair, sullenly refusing her milk, while her father frowned and her brother giggled and her mother said calmly, 'She wants her cup of stars.'

Indeed yes, Eleanor thought; indeed, so do I; a cup of stars, of course.

'Her little cup,' the mother was explaining, smiling apologetically at the waitress, who was thunderstruck at the thought that the mill's good country milk was not rich enough for the little girl. 'It has stars in the bottom, and she always drinks her milk from it at home. She calls it her cup of stars because she can see the stars while she drinks her milk.' The waitress nodded, unconvinced, and the mother told the little girl, 'You'll have your milk from your cup of stars tonight when we get home. But just for now, just to be a very good little girl, will you take a little milk from this glass?'

Don't do it, Eleanor told the little girl; insist on your cup of stars; once they have trapped you into being like everyone else you will never see your cup of stars again; don't do it; and the little girl glanced at her, and smiled a little subtle, dimpling, wholly comprehending smile, and shook her head stubbornly at the glass. Brave girl, Eleanor thought; wise, brave girl." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4963-where-is-human-nature-so-weak-as-in-the-bookstore</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 04:21:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Henry Ward Beecherr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4963-where-is-human-nature-so-weak-as-in-the-bookstore]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where is human nature so weak as in the bookstore?" -- Henry Ward Beecherr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68267-the-only-important-thing-in-a-book-is-the-meaning</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 07:51:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68267-the-only-important-thing-in-a-book-is-the-meaning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only important thing in a book is the meaning that it has for you." -- Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1572-if-she-can-t-spell-why-is-she-a-librarian-librarians</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 10:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Ramona Quimby as written by Beverly Cleary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1572-if-she-can-t-spell-why-is-she-a-librarian-librarians]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If she can't spell, why is she a librarian? Librarians should know how to spell." -- Ramona Quimby as written by Beverly Cleary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69114-didn-t-the-people-who-made-those-license-plates-care-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 10:10:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Beverly Cleary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69114-didn-t-the-people-who-made-those-license-plates-care-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Didn't the people who made those license plates care about little girls named Ramona?" -- Beverly Cleary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124075-winter-is-the-time-for-comfort-for-good-food-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 10:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Edith Sitwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124075-winter-is-the-time-for-comfort-for-good-food-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Winter is the time for comfort, for good food and warmth, for the touch of a friendly hand and for a talk beside the fire:  it is the time for home." -- Edith Sitwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32553-if-you-are-allergic-to-a-thing-it-is-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 05:02:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32553-if-you-are-allergic-to-a-thing-it-is-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are allergic to a thing, it is best not to put that thing in your mouth, particularly if the thing is cats." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125589-fuck-concepts-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 07:31:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125589-fuck-concepts-don-t-be-afraid-to-be-confused-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fuck concepts.  Don't be afraid to be confused.  Try to remain permanently confused.  Anything is possible.  Stay open, forever, so open it hurts, and then open up some more, until the day you die, world without end, amen." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850844-you-can-hate-a-place-with-all-your-heart-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Joseph Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850844-you-can-hate-a-place-with-all-your-heart-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...you can hate a place with all your heart and soul and still be homesick for it." -- Joseph Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324464-i-m-happy-which-often-looks-like-crazy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 19:56:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by David Henry Hwang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324464-i-m-happy-which-often-looks-like-crazy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm happy. Which often looks like crazy." -- David Henry Hwang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140141-sorrow-is-better-than-fear-fear-is-a-journey-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 09:46:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by Alan Paton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140141-sorrow-is-better-than-fear-fear-is-a-journey-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sorrow is better than fear. Fear is a journey, a terrible journey. But, sorrow is at least an arriving. " -- Alan Paton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130631-it-ain-t-what-they-call-you-it-s-what-you-answer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 06:50:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Silsbee add a quote by W.C. Fields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130631-it-ain-t-what-they-call-you-it-s-what-you-answer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It ain't what they call you, it's what you answer to." -- W.C. Fields]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
