<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/750388-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/750388-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189859-to-try-to-be-brave-is-to-be-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189859-to-try-to-be-brave-is-to-be-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To try to be brave is to be brave." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2836-come-then-affliction-if-my-father-wills-and-be-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2836-come-then-affliction-if-my-father-wills-and-be-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come, then, affliction, if my Father wills, and be my frowning friend. A friend that frowns is better than a smiling enemy. " -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499420-i-would-rather-be-what-god-chose-to-make-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499420-i-would-rather-be-what-god-chose-to-make-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would rather be what God chose to make me than the most glorious creature that I could think of; for to have been thought about, born in God's thought, and then made by God, is the dearest, grandest and most precious thing in all thinking." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48148-it-is-by-loving-and-not-by-being-loved-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48148-it-is-by-loving-and-not-by-being-loved-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is by loving and not by being loved that one can come nearest to the soul of another." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143883-a-beast-does-not-know-that-he-is-a-beast</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2013 18:05:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143883-a-beast-does-not-know-that-he-is-a-beast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A beast does not know that he is a beast, and the nearer a man gets to being a beast, the less he knows it." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38167-nothing-you-have-not-given-away-will-ever-really-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 18:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38167-nothing-you-have-not-given-away-will-ever-really-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing you have not given away will ever really be yours." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363092-if-i-find-in-myself-desires-which-nothing-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 18:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363092-if-i-find-in-myself-desires-which-nothing-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I find in myself desires which nothing in this world can satisfy, the only logical explanation is that I was made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422152-you-may-have-noticed-that-the-books-you-really-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 18:45:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422152-you-may-have-noticed-that-the-books-you-really-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may have noticed that the books you really love are bound together by a secret thread. You know very well what is the common quality that makes you love them, though you cannot put it into words: but most of your friends do not see it at all, and often wonder why, liking this, you should also like that. Again, you have stood before some landscape, which seems to embody what you have been looking for all your life; and then turned to the friend at your side who appears to be seeing what you saw -- but at the first words a gulf yawns between you, and you realise that this landscape means something totally different to him, that he is pursuing an alien vision and cares nothing for the ineffable suggestion by which you are transported. Even in your hobbies, has there not always been some secret attraction which the others are curiously ignorant of -- something, not to be identified with, but always on the verge of breaking through, the smell of cut wood in the workshop or the clap-clap of water against the boat's side? Are not all lifelong friendships born at the moment when at last you meet another human being who has some inkling (but faint and uncertain even in the best) of that something which you were born desiring, and which, beneath the flux of other desires and in all the momentary silences between the louder passions, night and day, year by year, from childhood to old age, you are looking for, watching for, listening for? You have never had it. All the things that have ever deeply possessed your soul have been but hints of it -- tantalising glimpses, promises never quite fulfilled, echoes that died away just as they caught your ear. But if it should really become manifest -- if there ever came an echo that did not die away but swelled into the sound itself -- you would know it. Beyond all possibility of doubt you would say &quot;Here at last is the thing I was made for&quot;. We cannot tell each other about it. It is the secret signature of each soul, the incommunicable and unappeasable want, the thing we desired before we met our wives or made our friends or chose our work, and which we shall still desire on our deathbeds, when the mind no longer knows wife or friend or work. While we are, this is. If we lose this, we lose all." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
