<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75071-aarthi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75071-aarthi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:01:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010078-as-she-only-cries-about-once-a-year-i-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:01:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Dodie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010078-as-she-only-cries-about-once-a-year-i-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As she only cries about once a year I really ought to have gone over and comforted her, but I wanted to set it all down here. I begin to see that writers are liable to become callous." -- Dodie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010079-the-vicar-and-miss-marcy-had-managed-to-by-pass-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:01:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Dodie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010079-the-vicar-and-miss-marcy-had-managed-to-by-pass-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Vicar and Miss Marcy had managed to by-pass the suffering that comes to most people - he by his religion, she by her kindness to others. And it came to me that if one does that, one is liable to miss too much along with the suffering - perhaps, in a way, life itself. Is that why Miss Marcy seems so young for her age - why the Vicar, in spite of all his cleverness, has that look of an elderly baby? I said aloud: 'I don't want to miss *anything.*' And then misery came rushing back like a river that has been dammed up. I tried to open my heart to it, to welcome it as a part of my life's experience, and at first that made it easier to bear. Then it got worse than ever before - it was physical as well as mental, my heart and ribs and shoulders and chest, even my arms, ached." -- Dodie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196464-i-am-a-restlessness-inside-a-stillness-inside-a-restlessness</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:01:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Dodie Smith (Cassandra Mortmain, I Capture the Castle)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196464-i-am-a-restlessness-inside-a-stillness-inside-a-restlessness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a restlessness inside a stillness inside a restlessness." -- Dodie Smith (Cassandra Mortmain, I Capture the Castle)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010086-fiction-is-the-unreal-estate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:03:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010086-fiction-is-the-unreal-estate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is the unreal estate." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010089-on-writers-workshops-it-is-the-dab-of-grit-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:03:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010089-on-writers-workshops-it-is-the-dab-of-grit-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On writers' workshops: &quot;It is the dab of grit that seeps into an oyster's shell that makes the pearl, not pearl-making seminars with other oysters." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010091-if-the-characters-grow-a-lot-they-begin-to-influence</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:04:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010091-if-the-characters-grow-a-lot-they-begin-to-influence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If [the characters] grow a lot, they begin to influence the course of the story instead of the other way around." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010092-your-job-is-to-make-sure-the-muse-knows-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:04:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010092-your-job-is-to-make-sure-the-muse-knows-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your job is to make sure the muse knows where you're going to be every day from nine 'til noon or seven 'til three. If he does know, I assure you that sooner or later he'll start showing up, chomping his cigar and making his magic." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010094-i-think-we-re-actually-talking-about-creative-sleep-like-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:04:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010094-i-think-we-re-actually-talking-about-creative-sleep-like-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we're actually talking about creative sleep. Like your bedroom, your writing room should be private, a place where you go to dream." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010095-life-isn-t-a-support-system-for-art-it-s-the-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:05:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010095-life-isn-t-a-support-system-for-art-it-s-the-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life isn't a support system for art. It's the other way around." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010100-our-inner-lives-must-be-lent-a-structure-and-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:07:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010100-our-inner-lives-must-be-lent-a-structure-and-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our inner lives must be lent a structure and our best thoughts reinforced to counter the continuous pull of distraction and disintegration. Religions have been wise enough to establish elaborate calendars and schedules. How free secular society leaves us by contrast. Secular life is not, of course, unacquainted with calendars and schedules. We know them well in relation to work, and accept the virtues of reminders of lunch meetings, cash-flow projections and tax deadlines. But it expects that we will spontaneously find our way to the ideas that matter to us and gives us weekends off for consumption and recreation. It privileges discovery, presenting us with an incessant stream of new information – and therefore it prompts us to forget everything. We are enticed to go to the cinema to see a newly released film, which ends up moving us to an exquisite pitch of sensitivity, sorrow and excitement. We leave the theatre vowing to reconsider our entire existence in light of the values shown on screen, and to purge ourselves of our decadence and haste. And yet by the following evening, after a day of meetings and aggravations, our cinematic experience is well on its way towards obliteration. We honour the power of culture but rarely admit with what scandalous ease we forget its individual monuments. We somehow feel, however, that it would be a violation of our spontaneity to be presented with rotas for rereading Walt Whitman." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010101-but-we-would-do-well-to-meditate-daily-rather-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010101-but-we-would-do-well-to-meditate-daily-rather-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we would do well to meditate daily, rather as the religious do on their God, on the 9.5 trillion kilometres which comprise a single light year, or perhaps on the luminosity of the largest known star in our galaxy, Eta Carinae, 7,500 light years distant, 400 times the size of the sun and 4 million times as bright. We should punctuate our calendars with celebrations in honour of VY Canis Majoris, a red hypergiant in the constellation Canis Major, 5,000 light years from earth and 2,100 times bigger than our sun. Nightly – perhaps after the main news bulletin – we might observe a moment of silence in order to contemplate the 200 to 400 billion stars in our galaxy, the 100 billion galaxies and the 3 septillion stars in the universe. Whatever their value may be to science, the stars are in the end no less valuable to mankind as solutions to our megalomania, self-pity and anxiety. To answer our need to be repeatedly connected through our senses to ideas of transcendence, we should insist that a percentage of all prominently positioned television screens on public view be hooked up to live feeds from the transponders of our extraplanetary telescopes. We would then be able to ensure that our frustrations, our broken hearts, our hatred of those who haven’t called us and our regrets over opportunities that have passed us by would continuously be rubbed up against, and salved by, images of galaxies such as Messier 101, a spiral structure which sits towards the bottom left corner of the constellation Ursa Major, 23 million light years away, majestically unaware of everything we are and consolingly unaffected by all that tears us apart." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010103-the-signal-danger-of-life-in-a-godless-society-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:07:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010103-the-signal-danger-of-life-in-a-godless-society-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The signal danger of life in a godless society is that it lacks reminders of the transcendent and therefore leaves us unprepared for disappointment and eventual annihilation. When God is dead, human beings – much to their detriment – are at risk of taking psychological centre stage. They imagine themselves to be commanders of their own destinies, they trample upon nature, forget the rhythms of the earth, deny death and shy away from valuing and honouring all that slips through their grasp, until at last they must collide catastrophically with the sharp edges of reality. Our secular world is lacking in the sorts of rituals that might put us gently in our place." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010106-we-have-almost-all-had-the-experience-of-gazing-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:08:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010106-we-have-almost-all-had-the-experience-of-gazing-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have almost all had the experience of gazing at the full moon. But those of us who are neither astronomers nor astronauts are unlikely to have scheduled moongazing appointments. For Zen Buddhists in Japan, however, every year, on the fifteenth day of the eighth month of the traditional Japanese lunisolar calendar, followers gather at nightfall around specially constructed cone-shaped viewing platforms, where for several hours prayers are read aloud which use the moon as a springboard for reflections on Zen ideas of impermanence, a ritual known as tsukimi. Candles are lit and white rice dumplings (tsukimi dango) are prepared and shared out among strangers in an atmosphere at once companionable and serene, a feeling thereby supported by a ceremony, by architecture, by good company and by food." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010108-secular-society-has-been-unfairly-impoverished-by-the-loss-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:08:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010108-secular-society-has-been-unfairly-impoverished-by-the-loss-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Secular society has been unfairly impoverished by the loss of an array of practices and themes which atheists typically find it impossible to live with because they seem too closely associated with, to quote Nietzsche’s useful phrase, ‘the bad odours of religion’. We have grown frightened of the word morality. We bridle at the thought of hearing a sermon. We flee from the idea that art should be uplifting or have an ethical mission. We don’t go on pilgrimages. We can’t build temples. We have no mechanisms for expressing gratitude. Strangers rarely sing together. We are presented with an unpleasant choice between either committing to peculiar concepts about immaterial deities or letting go entirely of a host of consoling, subtle or just charming rituals for which we struggle to find equivalents in secular society." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010110-religions-merit-our-attention-for-their-sheer-conceptual-ambition-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:08:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010110-religions-merit-our-attention-for-their-sheer-conceptual-ambition-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["religions merit our attention for their sheer conceptual ambition; for changing the world in a way that few secular institutions ever have. They have managed to combine theories about ethics and metaphysics with a practical involvement in education, fashion, politics, travel, hostelry, initiation ceremonies, publishing, art and architecture – a range of interests which puts to shame the scope of the achievements of even the greatest and most influential secular movements and individuals in history. For those interested in the spread and impact of ideas, it is hard not to be mesmerized by examples of the most successful educational and intellectual movements the planet has ever witnessed." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010113-religions-understand-that-to-belong-to-a-community-is-both</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:09:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010113-religions-understand-that-to-belong-to-a-community-is-both]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["religions understand that to belong to a community is both very desirable and not very easy." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010115-we-should-give-chaos-pride-of-place-once-a-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:09:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010115-we-should-give-chaos-pride-of-place-once-a-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should give chaos pride of place once a year or so, designating occasions on which we can be briefly exempted from the two greatest pressures of secular adult life: having to be rational and having to be faithful." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010116-an-atheist-may-of-course-also-feel-clean-after-taking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:09:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010116-an-atheist-may-of-course-also-feel-clean-after-taking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An atheist may, of course, also feel clean after taking a bath and dirty without one, but the mikveh ritual, associating outer hygiene with the recovery of a particular kind of inner purity, like so many other symbolic practices promoted by religions, manages to use a physical activity to support a spiritual lesson." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010119-mary-in-christianity-isis-in-ancient-egypt-demeter-in-greece</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:09:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010119-mary-in-christianity-isis-in-ancient-egypt-demeter-in-greece]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mary in Christianity, Isis in ancient Egypt, Demeter in Greece, Venus in Rome and Guan Yin in China have all functioned as conduits to recollections of early tenderness. Their statues often stand in darkened, womb-like spaces, their faces are compassionate and supportive, they enable us to sit, talk and cry with them. The similarities between them are too great to be coincidental. We are dealing here with figures that have evolved not out of shared cultural origins but in response to the universal needs of the human psyche." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010120-the-secular-are-at-this-moment-in-history-a-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010120-the-secular-are-at-this-moment-in-history-a-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secular are at this moment in history a great deal more optimistic than the religious – something of an irony, given the frequency with which the latter have been derided by the former for their apparent naivety and credulousness. It is the secular whose longing for perfection has grown so intense as to lead them to imagine that paradise might be realized on this earth after just a few more years of financial growth and medical research. With no evident awareness of the contradiction they may, in the same breath, gruffly dismiss a belief in angels while sincerely trusting that the combined powers of the IMF, the medical research establishment, Silicon Valley and democratic politics could together cure the ills of mankind.... It is telling that the secular world is not well versed in the art of gratitude: we no longer offer up thanks for harvests, meals, bees or clement weather. On a superficial level, we might suppose that this is because there is no one to say ‘Thank you’ to. But at base it seems more a matter of ambition and expectation. Many of those blessings for which our pious and pessimistic ancestors offered thanks, we now pride ourselves on having worked hard enough to take for granted." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010123-the-benefits-of-a-philosophy-of-neo-religious-pessimism-are-nowhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:10:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Alain de Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010123-the-benefits-of-a-philosophy-of-neo-religious-pessimism-are-nowhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The benefits of a philosophy of neo-religious pessimism are nowhere more apparent than in relation to marriage, one of modern society’s most grief-stricken arrangements, which has been rendered unnecessarily hellish by the astonishing secular supposition that it should be entered into principally for the sake of happiness. Christianity and Judaism present marriage not as a union inspired and governed by subjective enthusiasm but rather, and more modestly, as a mechanism by which individuals can assume an adult position in society and thence, with the help of a close friend, undertake to nurture and educate the next generation under divine guidance. These limited expectations tend to forestall the suspicion, so familiar to secular partners, that there might have been more intense, angelic or less fraught alternatives available elsewhere. Within the religious ideal, friction, disputes and boredom are signs not of error, but of life proceeding according to plan." -- Alain de Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010127-how-much-more-interior-can-you-get-after-all-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:11:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Julie Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010127-how-much-more-interior-can-you-get-after-all-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How much more interior can you get, after all, than the interior of bones? It's the center of the center of things. If marrow were a geological formation, it would be magma roiling under the earth's mantle. If it were a plant, it would be a delicate moss that grows only in the highest crags of Mount Everest, blooming with tiny white flowers for three days in the Nepalese spring. If it were a memory, it would be your first one, your most painful and repressed one, the one that has made you who you are." -- Julie Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010129-if-daisy-buchanan-s-laugh-is-the-sound-of-money-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:11:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Julie Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010129-if-daisy-buchanan-s-laugh-is-the-sound-of-money-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Daisy Buchanan's laugh is the sound of money, then a gimlet, well executed, is the color of it. It is just the thing when you are feeling impoverished, financially or spiritually." -- Julie Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010130-everyone-knows-there-are-foods-that-are-sexy-to-eat</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Julie Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010130-everyone-knows-there-are-foods-that-are-sexy-to-eat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone knows there are foods that are sexy to eat. What they don't talk about so much is foods that are sexy to make." -- Julie Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010134-our-oldest-grandchild-has-precisely-alice-s-coloring-which-may-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:12:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Calvin Trillin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010134-our-oldest-grandchild-has-precisely-alice-s-coloring-which-may-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our oldest grandchild has precisely Alice's coloring, which may be one reason I sometimes have trouble taking my eyes off her." -- Calvin Trillin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010135-for-alice-of-course-the-measure-of-how-you-held</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:12:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Calvin Trillin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010135-for-alice-of-course-the-measure-of-how-you-held]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Alice, of course, the measure of how you held up in the face of a life-threatening illness was not how much you changed but how much you stayed the same, in control of your own identity." -- Calvin Trillin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010142-look-at-other-people-and-ask-yourself-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:13:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010142-look-at-other-people-and-ask-yourself-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["look at other people and ask yourself if you are really seeing them or just your thoughts about them.... Without knowing it, we are coloring everything, putting our spin on it all." -- Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010144-our-ability-to-touch-love-and-kindness-and-be-touched</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:14:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010144-our-ability-to-touch-love-and-kindness-and-be-touched]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our ability to touch love and kindness and be touched by them lies buried below our own fears and hurts, below our greed and our hatreds, below our desperate clinging to the illusion that we are separate and alone." -- Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010146-make-a-list-of-what-is-really-important-to-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:14:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010146-make-a-list-of-what-is-really-important-to-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make a list of what is really important to you. Embody it." -- Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010147-at-the-deepest-level-there-is-no-giver-no-gift</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 10:14:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[aarthi add a quote by Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010147-at-the-deepest-level-there-is-no-giver-no-gift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the deepest level, there is no giver, no gift, and no recipient... only the universe rearranging itself." -- Jon Kabat-Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
