<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/751230-lori]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/751230-lori" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:22:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:22:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:25:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:27:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Luxury is not a necessity to me, but beautiful and good things are." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:28:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65611-i-am-an-excitable-person-who-only-understands-life-lyrically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an excitable person who only understands life lyrically, musically, in whom feelings are much stronger as reason. I am so thirsty for the marvelous that only the marvelous has power over me. Anything I can not transform into something marvelous, I let go. Reality doesn't impress me. I only believe in intoxication, in ecstasy, and when ordinary life shackles me, I escape, one way or another. No more walls." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98518-i-am-lonely-yet-not-everybody-will-do-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98518-i-am-lonely-yet-not-everybody-will-do-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am lonely, yet not everybody will do. I don't know why, some people fill the gaps and others emphasize my loneliness. In reality those who satisfy me are those who simply allow me to live with my ''idea of them." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were always in me, two women at least, one woman desperate and bewildered, who felt she was drowning and another who would leap into a scene, as upon a stage, conceal her true emotions because they were weaknesses, helplessness, despair, and present to the world only a smile, an eagerness, curiosity, enthusiasm, interest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the most tired woman in the world. I am tired when I get up. Life requires an effort I cannot make. Please give me that heavy book. I need to put something heavy like that on top of my head. I have to place my feet under the pillows always, so as to be able to stay on earth. Otherwise I feel myself going away, going away at a tremendous speed, on account of my lightness. I know that I am dead. As soon as I utter a phrase my sincerity dies, becomes a lie whose coldness chills me. Don't say anything, because I see that you understand me, and I am afraid of your understanding. I have such a fear of finding another like myself, and such a desire to find one! I am so utterly lonely, but I also have such a fear that my isolation be broken through, and I no longer be the head and ruler of my universe. I am in great terror of your understanding by which you penetrate into my world; and then I stand revealed and I have to share my kingdom with you." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:30:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84169-anxiety-is-love-s-greatest-killer-it-makes-others-feel-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anxiety is love's greatest killer. It makes others feel as you might when a drowning man holds on to you. You want to save him, but you know he will strangle you with his panic." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53992-i-must-be-a-mermaid-rango-i-have-no-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53992-i-must-be-a-mermaid-rango-i-have-no-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must be a mermaid, Rango. I have no fear of depths and a great fear of shallow living." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39899-man-can-never-know-the-loneliness-a-woman-knows-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:32:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39899-man-can-never-know-the-loneliness-a-woman-knows-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man can never know the loneliness a woman knows. Man lies in the woman's womb only to gather strength, he nourishes himself from this fusion, and then he rises and goes into the world, into his work, into battle, into art. He is not lonely. He is busy. The memory of the swim in amniotic fluid gives him energy, completion. Woman may be busy too, but she feels empty. Sensuality for her is not only a wave of pleasure in which she is bathed, and a charge of electric joy at contact with another. When man lies in her womb, she is fulfilled, each act of love a taking of man within her, an act of birth and rebirth, of child rearing and man bearing. Man lies in her womb and is reborn each time anew with a desire to act, to &lt;i&gt;be&lt;/i&gt;. But for woman, the climax is not in the birth, but in the moment man rests inside of her." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:33:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: I am interested in so many things, and I have a terrible fear because my mother keeps telling me that I'm just going to be exploring the rest of my life and never get anything done. But I find it really hard to set my ways and say, &quot;Well, do I want to do this, or should I try to exploit that, or should I escape and completely do one thing?&quot;

Anaïs Nin: One word I would banish from the dictionary is 'escape.' Just banish that and you'll be fine. Because that word has been misused regarding anybody who wanted to move away from a certain spot and wanted to grow. He was an escapist. You know if you forget that word you will have a much easier time. Also you're in the prime, the beginning of your life; you should experiment with everything, try everything.... We are taught all these dichotomies, and I only learned later that they could work in harmony. We have created false dichotomies; we create false ambivalences, and very painful one's sometimes -the feeling that we have to choose. But I think at one point we finally realize, sometimes subconsciously, whether or not we are really fitted for what we try and if it's what we want to do.

You have a right to experiment with your life. You will make mistakes. And they are right too. No, I think there was too rigid a pattern. You came out of an education and are supposed to know your vocation. Your vocation is fixed, and maybe ten years later you find you are not a teacher anymore or you're not a painter anymore. It may happen. It has happened. I mean Gauguin decided at a certain point he wasn't a banker anymore; he was a painter. And so he walked away from banking. I think we have a right to change course. But society is the one that keeps demanding that we fit in and not disturb things. They would like you to fit in right away so that things work now." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189111-i-hate-men-who-are-afraid-of-women-s-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:34:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189111-i-hate-men-who-are-afraid-of-women-s-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate men who are afraid of women's strength." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99661-the-truly-faithless-one-is-the-one-who-makes-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly faithless one is the one who makes love to only a fraction of you. And denies the rest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98519-i-sat-there-for-three-hours-and-did-not-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:35:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98519-i-sat-there-for-three-hours-and-did-not-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sat there for three hours and did not feel the time or the boredom of our talk and its foolish disconnection. As long as I could hear his voice, I was quite lost, quite blind, quite outside my own self." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42832-i-want-to-make-my-own-discoveries-penetrate-the-evil-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:35:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42832-i-want-to-make-my-own-discoveries-penetrate-the-evil-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to make my own discoveries…….penetrate the evil which attracts me" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37900-this-diary-is-my-kief-hashish-and-opium-pipe-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37900-this-diary-is-my-kief-hashish-and-opium-pipe-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This diary is my kief, hashish and opium pipe. This is my drug and my vice." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213366-i-will-always-be-the-virgin-prostitute-the-perverse-angel-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:46:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213366-i-will-always-be-the-virgin-prostitute-the-perverse-angel-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will always be the virgin-prostitute, the perverse angel, the two-faced sinister and saintly woman." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87441-there-were-silences-in-my-head-i-could-abandon-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87441-there-were-silences-in-my-head-i-could-abandon-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were silences in my head.  I could abandon myself completely to the pleasure of multiple relationships, to the beauty of the day, to the joys of the day.  It was as if a cancer in me had ceased gnawing me.  The cancer of introspection." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139391-he-who-had-done-more-than-any-human-being-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He, who had done more than any human being to draw her out of the caves of her secret, folded life, now threw her down into deeper recesses of fear and doubt.  The fall was greater than she had ever known, because she had ventured so far into emotion and had abandoned herself to it." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220913-what-i-cannot-love-i-overlook</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:47:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220913-what-i-cannot-love-i-overlook]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I cannot love, I overlook." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81450-many-couples-many-people-are-not-living-with-real-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:47:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81450-many-couples-many-people-are-not-living-with-real-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many couples, many people, are not living with real human beings, but with their ghosts. Who has not followed for years the spell of a particular tone of voice, from voice to voice, as the fetishist follows a beautiful  foot, scarcely seeing the woman herself? A voice, a mouth, an eye, all stemming from the original fountain of our first desire, directing it, enslaving us, until we choose to unravel the fatal web and free ourselves." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61315-i-really-believe-that-if-i-were-not-a-writer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61315-i-really-believe-that-if-i-were-not-a-writer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really believe that if I were not a writer, not a creator, not an experimenter, I might have been a very faithful wife. I think highly of faithfulness. But my temperament belongs to the writer, not to the woman" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174428-if-a-person-continues-to-see-giants-it-means-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174428-if-a-person-continues-to-see-giants-it-means-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a person continues to see giants, it means he is still looking at the world through the eyes of a child." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259182-for-you-and-for-me-the-highest-moment-the-keenest</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:49:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259182-for-you-and-for-me-the-highest-moment-the-keenest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For you and for me the highest moment, the keenest joy, is not when our minds dominate but when we lose our minds, and you and I both lose it in the same way, through love." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189113-i-often-see-how-you-sob-over-what-you-destroy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:49:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189113-i-often-see-how-you-sob-over-what-you-destroy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often see how you sob over what you destroy, how you want to stop and just worship; and you do stop, and then a moment later you are at it again with a knife, like a surgeon. " -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214314-woman-s-role-in-creation-should-be-parallel-to-her-role</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:50:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214314-woman-s-role-in-creation-should-be-parallel-to-her-role]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Woman’s role in creation should be parallel to her role in life. I don’t mean the good earth. I mean the bad earth too, the demon, the instincts, the storms of nature. Tragedies, conflicts, mysteries are personal. Man fabricated a detachment which became fatal. Woman must not fabricate. She must descend into the real womb and expose its secrets and its labyrinths. She must describe it as the city of Fez, with its Arabian Nights gentleness, tranquility and mystery. She must describe the voracious moods, the desires, the worlds contained in each cell of it. For the womb has dreams. It is not as simple as the good earth. I believe at times that man created art out of fear of exploring woman. I believe woman stuttered about herself out of fear of what she had to say. She covered herself with taboos and veils. Man invented a woman to suit his needs. He disposed of her by identifying her with nature and then paraded his contemptuous domination of nature. But woman is not nature only.
She is the mermaid with her fish-tail dipped in the unconscious." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162937-coming-near-him-like-a-ballet-dancer-she-took-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:52:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by anais nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162937-coming-near-him-like-a-ballet-dancer-she-took-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Coming near him like a ballet dancer she took a leap towards him, and he, frightened by her vehemence, and fearing that she would crash against him, instinctively became absolutely rigid, and she felt herself embracing a statue." -- anais nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259183-i-cheat-him-i-deceive-him-yet-the-world-does</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259183-i-cheat-him-i-deceive-him-yet-the-world-does]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cheat him, I deceive him, yet the world does not sink in sulphur-colored mists. Madness conquers. I can no longer put my mosaics together. I just cry and laugh." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194688-i-m-awaiting-a-lover-i-have-to-be-rent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194688-i-m-awaiting-a-lover-i-have-to-be-rent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm awaiting a lover. I have to be rent and pulled apart and live according to the demons and the imagination in me. I'm restless. Things are calling me away. My hair is being pulled by the stars again." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300906-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2011 01:56:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300906-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
