<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/751788-mirella]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/751788-mirella" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 04:42:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217320-they-say-that-people-who-live-next-to-waterfalls-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 04:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217320-they-say-that-people-who-live-next-to-waterfalls-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say that people who live next to waterfalls don't hear the water. It was terrible at first. We couldn't stand to be in the house for more than a few hours at a time. The first two weeks were filled with nights of intermittent sleep and quarreling for the sake of being heard over the water. We fought so much just to remind ourselves that we were in love, and not in hate. But the next weeks were a little better. It was possible to sleep a few good hours each night and eat in only mild discomfort. [We] still cursed the water, but less frequently, and with less fury. Her attacks on me also quieted. It's your fault, she would say. You wanted to live here. Life continued, as life continues, and time passed, as time passes, and after a little more than two months: Do you hear that? I asked her one of the rare mornings we sat at the table together. Hear it? I put down my coffee and rose from my chair. You hear that thing? What thing? she asked. Exactly! I said, running outside to pump my fist at the waterfall. Exactly! We danced, throwing handfuls of water in the air, hearing nothing at all. We alternated hugs of forgiveness and shouts of human triumph at the water. Who wins the day? Who wins the day, waterfall? We do! We do! And this is what living next to a waterfall is like.  Every widow wakes one morning, perhaps after years of pure and unwavering grieving, to realize she slept a good night's sleep and will be able to eat breakfast, and doesn't hear her husband's ghost all the time, but only some of the time. Her grief is replaced with a useful sadness. Every parent who loses a child finds a way to laugh again. The timbre begins to fade. The edge dulls. The hurt lessens. Every love is carved from loss. Mine was. Yours is. Your great-great-great-grandchildren's will be. But we learn to live in that love." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43016-you-cannot-protect-yourself-from-sadness-without-protecting-yourself-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2012 05:15:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43016-you-cannot-protect-yourself-from-sadness-without-protecting-yourself-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot protect yourself from sadness without protecting yourself from happiness." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137109-they-slipped-briskly-into-an-intimacy-from-which-they-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 15:15:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137109-they-slipped-briskly-into-an-intimacy-from-which-they-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They slipped briskly into an intimacy from which they never recovered." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233610-now-you-ve-said-it-the-hopeless-emptiness-hell-plenty-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 03:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Richard Yates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233610-now-you-ve-said-it-the-hopeless-emptiness-hell-plenty-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now you’ve said it. The hopeless emptiness. Hell, plenty of people are on to the emptiness part; out where I used to work, on the Coast, that’s all we ever talked about. We’d sit around talking about emptiness all night. Nobody ever said ‘hopeless,’ though; that’s where we’d chicken out. Because maybe it does take a certain amount of guts to see the emptiness, but it takes a whole hell of a lot more to see the hopelessness. And I guess when you do see the hopelessness, that’s when there’s nothing to do but take off. If you can" -- Richard Yates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662822-ana-iris-once-asked-me-if-i-loved-him-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 05:40:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Junot Diaz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/662822-ana-iris-once-asked-me-if-i-loved-him-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ana Iris once asked me if I loved him and I told her about the lights in my old home in the capital, how they flickered and you never knew if they would go out or not. You put down your things and you waited and couldn't do anything really until the lights decided. This, I told her, is how I feel." -- Junot Diaz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 05:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53773-the-inferno-of-the-living-is-not-something-that-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inferno of the living is not something that will be; if there is one, it is what is already here, the inferno where we live every day, that we form by being together. There are two ways to escape suffering it. The first is easy for many: accept the inferno and become such a part of it that you can no longer see it. The second is risky and demands constant vigilance and apprehension: seek and learn to recognize who and what, in the midst of inferno, are not inferno, then make them endure, give them space." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799251-misfortune-of-this-kind-comes-to-many-life-is-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 07:36:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Viktor Shklovsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799251-misfortune-of-this-kind-comes-to-many-life-is-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Misfortune of this kind comes to many. Life is well ordered, like a nécessaire, but not all of us can find our places in it. Life tailors us for a certain person and laughs when we are drawn to someone unable to love us. 
All this is simple--like postage stamps." -- Viktor Shklovsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677545-my-dear-find-what-you-love-and-let-it-kill</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 18:56:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677545-my-dear-find-what-you-love-and-let-it-kill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My dear,
Find what you love and let it kill you.
Let it drain you of your all. Let it cling onto your back and weigh you down into eventual nothingness.
Let it kill you and let it devour your remains.
For all things will kill you, both slowly and fastly, but it’s much better to be killed by a lover.
~ Falsely yours" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83039-the-only-obsession-everyone-wants-love-people-think-that-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 17:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83039-the-only-obsession-everyone-wants-love-people-think-that-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only obsession everyone wants: 'love.' People think that in falling in love they make themselves whole? The Platonic union of souls? I think otherwise. I think you're whole before you begin. And the love fractures you. You're whole, and then you're cracked open. " -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91562-why-do-people-have-to-be-this-lonely-what-s-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 08:01:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91562-why-do-people-have-to-be-this-lonely-what-s-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do people have to be this lonely? What's the point of it all? Millions of people in this world, all of them yearning, looking to others to satisfy them, yet isolating themselves. Why? Was the earth put here just to nourish human loneliness?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322452-if-you-remember-me-then-i-don-t-care-if-everyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 08:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/322452-if-you-remember-me-then-i-don-t-care-if-everyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you remember me, then I don't care if everyone else forgets." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 08:24:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50675-sometimes-fate-is-like-a-small-sandstorm-that-keeps-changing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes fate is like a small sandstorm that keeps changing directions. You change direction but the sandstorm chases you. You turn again, but the storm adjusts. Over and over you play this out, like some ominous dance with death just before dawn. Why? Because this storm isn't something that blew in from far away, something that has nothing to do with you. This storm is you. Something &lt;i&gt;inside&lt;/i&gt; of you. So all you can do is give in to it, step right inside the storm, closing your eyes and plugging up your ears so the sand doesn't get in, and walk through it, step by step. There's no sun there, no moon, no direction, no sense of time. Just fine white sand swirling up into the sky like pulverized bones. That's the kind of sandstorm you need to imagine.

An you really will have to make it through that violent, metaphysical, symbolic storm. No matter how metaphysical or symbolic it might be, make no mistake about it: it will cut through flesh like a thousand razor blades. People will bleed there, and &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; will bleed too. Hot, red blood. You'll catch that blood in your hands, your own blood and the blood of others.

And once the storm is over you won't remember how you made it through, how you managed to survive. You won't even be sure, in fact, whether the storm is really over. But one thing is certain. When you come out of the storm you won't be the same person who walked in. That's what this storm's all about." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 08:25:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen up - there's no war that will end all wars." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271037-closing-your-eyes-isn-t-going-to-change-anything-nothing-s-going</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 08:25:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271037-closing-your-eyes-isn-t-going-to-change-anything-nothing-s-going]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Closing your eyes isn't going to change anything. Nothing's going to disappear just because you can't see what's going on. In fact, things will even be worse the next time you open your eyes. That's the kind of world we live in. Keep your eyes wide open. Only a coward closes his eyes. Closing your eyes and plugging up your ears won't make time stand still." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24774-that-s-why-i-like-listening-to-schubert-while-i-m-driving</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 08:26:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24774-that-s-why-i-like-listening-to-schubert-while-i-m-driving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's why I like listening to Schubert while I'm driving. Like I said, it's because all his performances are imperfect. A dense, artistic kind of imperfection stimulates your consciousness, keeps you alert. If I listen to some utterly perfect performance of an utterly perfect piece while I'm driving, I might want to close my eyes and die right then and there. But listening to the D major, I can feel the limits of what humans are capable of - that a certain type of perfection can only be realized through a limitless accumulation of the imperfect. And personally I find that encouraging." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1016106-we-re-on-the-border-of-this-world-speaking-a-common</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 10:40:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mirella add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1016106-we-re-on-the-border-of-this-world-speaking-a-common]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're on the border of this world, speaking a common language. That's all." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
