<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/752985-alyson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/752985-alyson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 18:13:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11329-how-many-a-poor-immortal-soul-have-i-met-well-nigh</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 18:13:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11329-how-many-a-poor-immortal-soul-have-i-met-well-nigh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How many a poor immortal soul have I met well-nigh crushed and smothered under its load, creeping down the road of life, pushing before it a barn seventy-five feet by forty, its Augean stables never cleansed, and one hundred acres of land, tillage, mowing, pasture, and wood-lot. The portionless, who struggle with no such unnecessary inherited encumbrances, find it labor enough to subdue and cultivate a few cubic feet of flesh.

—chapter 1, &quot;Economy" -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41248-the-better-part-of-the-man-is-soon-ploughed-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 18:17:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41248-the-better-part-of-the-man-is-soon-ploughed-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The better part of the man is soon ploughed into the soil for compost.  By a seeming fate, commonly called necessity, they are employed, as it says in an old book, laying up treasures which moth and rust will corrupt and thieves break through and steal.  It is a fool's life, as they will find when they get to the end of it, if not before." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11343-age-is-no-better-hardly-so-well-qualified-for-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 18:21:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11343-age-is-no-better-hardly-so-well-qualified-for-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Age is no better, hardly so well, qualified for an instructor as youth, for it has not profited so much as it has lost." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11352-one-farmer-says-to-me-you-cannot-live-on-vegetable</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 18:25:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11352-one-farmer-says-to-me-you-cannot-live-on-vegetable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One farmer says to me, 'You cannot live on vegetable food solely, for it furnishes nothing to make bones with;' and so he religiously devotes a part of his day to supplying his system with the raw material of bones; walking all the while he talks behind his oxen, which, with vegetable-made bones, jerk him and his lumbering plow along in spite of every obstacle." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12175-i-doubt-if-there-are-many-normal-women-who-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 10:16:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Mary Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12175-i-doubt-if-there-are-many-normal-women-who-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I doubt if there are many normal women who can resist looking at houses. I believe, in fact, that when a house is up for sale more than half the people who look over it are not prospective buyers, but merely ladies who cannot resist exploring someone else's house." -- Mary Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21621-he-would-sit-singing-his-cheeks-turning-red-above-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 09:46:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Ruth Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21621-he-would-sit-singing-his-cheeks-turning-red-above-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He would sit singing, his cheeks turning red above his whiskers; but his voice always came out deep and steady, like the sound of long ago, if long ago could make a sound instead of being forever lost and silent." -- Ruth Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21652-grampie-s-boat-was-a-little-double-ender-a-model-not-built</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 10:52:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Ruth Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21652-grampie-s-boat-was-a-little-double-ender-a-model-not-built]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grampie's boat was a little double-ender, a model not built nowadays. She was narrow, so that she pitched and rolled something wicked in almost any sea. He could handle her, but he said she was probably the boat Christ got out of and walked away from on the water." -- Ruth Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7397-it-is-not-true-that-women-cannot-keep-secrets-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2008 15:06:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Mary Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7397-it-is-not-true-that-women-cannot-keep-secrets-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not true that women cannot keep secrets.  Where they love, they can be trusted to death and beyond, against all sense and reason.  It is their weakness, and their great strength.  " -- Mary Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 11:03:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9157-they-re-certainly-entitled-to-think-that-and-they-re-entitled-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They're certainly entitled to think that, and they're entitled to full respect for their opinions... but before I can live with other folks I've got to live with myself.  The one thing that doesn't abide by majority rule is a person's conscience." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 11:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6019-i-wanted-you-to-see-what-real-courage-is-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted you to see what real courage is, instead of getting the idea that courage is a man with a gun in his hand. It's when you know you're licked before you begin, but you begin anyway and see it through no matter what.
- Atticus Finch" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96405-i-might-like-to-have-someone-courting-me-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 12:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96405-i-might-like-to-have-someone-courting-me-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I might like to have someone courting me. But it would have to be someone who is a square shooter and who has a train load of courage. And it would have to be someone who doesn't have to talk down to folks to feel good, or to tell a person they are worthless ifthey just made a mistake. And he'd have to be not too thin. Why, I remember hugging [my brother] Ernest was like warpping your arms around a fence post,and I love Ernest, but I want a man who can hold me down in a wind. Maybe he'd have to be pretty stubborn. I don't have any use for a man that isn't stubborn. Likely a stubborn fellow will stay with you through thick and thin, and a spineless one will take off, or let his heart wander." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96504-children-are-a-burden-to-a-mother-but-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 18:17:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96504-children-are-a-burden-to-a-mother-but-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Children are a burden to a mother, but not the way a heavy box is to a mule. Our children weight hard on my heart, and thinking about them growing up honest and healthy, or just living to grow up at all, makes a load in my chest that is bigger than the safe at the bank,and more valuable to me than all the gold inside it." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111280-when-i-was-in-second-grade-my-teacher-miss-maxwell</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 13:00:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Philip Gulley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111280-when-i-was-in-second-grade-my-teacher-miss-maxwell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was in second grade, my teacher, Miss Maxwell, read from The Harmony Herald that one in every four children lived in China. I remember looking over the room, guessing which children they might be. I wasn't sure where China was, but suspected it was on bus route three. I recall being grateful I didn't live in China because I didn't care for Chinese food and couldn't speak the language." -- Philip Gulley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111283-our-first-night-in-the-house-my-wife-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 13:04:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Philip Gulley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111283-our-first-night-in-the-house-my-wife-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our first night in the house, my wife and I were lying in bed. I was thanking God for my blessings. Thanking God for not having to pull aside a dining room curain to have my children near—that they were right down the hall, asleep in their Superman underwear, their little chests rising and falling to the pulse of their dreams.

I thought how some blessings are fickle guests. Just when we think they're here to stay, they pack their bags and move. When we're in the midst of blessing, we think it's our due—that blessing lasts forever. Next thing you know we're sitting helpless beside a hospital bed. All we're left with is a name on a wall, a toy in a desk, and memories that haunt our sleep.

Sometimes we come to gratitute too late. It's only after blessing has passed on that we realize what we had.

—chapter 2" -- Philip Gulley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111345-i-can-only-make-one-person-happy-each-day-today</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 15:26:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Philip Gulley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111345-i-can-only-make-one-person-happy-each-day-today]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can only make one person happy each day.

Today is not your day.

Tomorrow doesn't look good, either.

—Frank the 70 year old secretary, chapter 9" -- Philip Gulley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112104-we-always-look-for-christ-amid-magnificence-but-christ</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2008 18:55:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Philip Gulley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112104-we-always-look-for-christ-amid-magnificence-but-christ]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...We always look for Christ amid magnificence. But ... Christ has a history of showing up amide the unlovely. Born in a dirty stall. Crowned with thorns. Died gasping on a shameful cross atop a jagged rise.

We don't need to be beautiful for Christ to take us in. He is equally at home when we're broken-down and dirty. It's like George Herbert wrote:
'And here in dust and dirt, O here,
The lilies of God's love appear.'
We think magnificence is in short supply, that dust and dirt choke out the lilies. But that's not true and never was. Lilies may root in dirt, but they reach for heaven—and in the reaching, reveal their magnificence.

—chapter 24" -- Philip Gulley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140228-the-cocktail-filled-him-with-a-whirling-exhilaration-behind-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 17:40:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140228-the-cocktail-filled-him-with-a-whirling-exhilaration-behind-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cocktail filled him with a whirling exhilaration behind which he was aware of devastating desires—to rush places in fast motors, to kiss girls, to sing, to be witty. ... He perceived that he had gifts of profligacy which had been neglected.

—chapter 8" -- Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264154-what-a-storyteller-does-is-see-more-than-most-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 18:19:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Dean Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264154-what-a-storyteller-does-is-see-more-than-most-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a storyteller does is *see* more than most of us. We say he's making up his stories, but he—or better yet, *she*—watches more carefully, and then tells us what we would have seen ourselves if we'd just stopped to look.&quot;

-Leah said—to Nadine, although she was looking at Marjorie (pg 138)" -- Dean Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264158-i-d-rather-do-something-than-read-about-it-that-s-fine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 18:24:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyson add a quote by Dean Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/264158-i-d-rather-do-something-than-read-about-it-that-s-fine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd rather do something than read about it.&quot;
&quot;That's fine, but if you do it, and then can't think what it means, it's never much of a memory. Life has more to so with memories of the past and longings for the future than it ever does with *right now*.&quot;

-pg 138-9" -- Dean Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
