<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/753118-stacey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/753118-stacey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 20:49:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476227-people-aren-t-always-what-you-want-them-to-be-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 20:49:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Chloe Rattray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/476227-people-aren-t-always-what-you-want-them-to-be-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People aren’t always what you want them to be. Sometimes they disappoint you or let you down, but you have to give them a chance first. You can’t just meet someone and expect them to be everything you’re looking for and then be angry when they’re not every hope and aspiration you projected onto them. It’s foolish to believe that someone will be what you imagine them to be. And sometimes, when you give them a chance, they turn out to be better than you imagined. Different, but better." -- Chloe Rattray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237159-getting-over-it-doesn-t-mean-forgetting-it-it-just-means</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 21:06:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stacey add a quote by Kevin Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237159-getting-over-it-doesn-t-mean-forgetting-it-it-just-means]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Getting over it doesn't mean forgetting it, it just means reducing the pain to a tolerable level, a level that doesn't destroy you. I know that right now the idea of getting over it is unimaginable. It's impossible, inconceivable, unthinkable. You don't want to get over it. Why should you? It's all you've got. You don't want kind words, you don't care what other people think or say, you don't want to know how they felt when they lost someone, They're no you, are there! They can't feel what you feel. The only thing you want is the things you can't have. It's gone. Never coming back. No one know how that feels. No one know what it's like to reach out and touch someone who isn't there and will never be there again. No one knows the unifiable emptiness. No one but you. You and me, love. We don't want anything. We want to die, but life won't let us. We're all it's got." -- Kevin Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
