<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75319-renata]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75319-renata" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 08:51:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2396-people-aren-t-either-wicked-or-noble-they-re-like-chef-s-salads</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 08:51:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2396-people-aren-t-either-wicked-or-noble-they-re-like-chef-s-salads]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People aren't either wicked or noble. They're like chef's salads, with good things and bad things chopped and mixed together in a vinaigrette of confusion and conflict." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 11:45:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 11:29:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know your problem, Quentin? You keep expecting people not to be themselves. I mean, I could hate you for being massively unpunctual and for never being interested in anything other than Margo Roth Spiegelman, and for, like, never asking me about how it's going with my girlfriend - but I don't give a shit, man, because you're you. My parents have a shit ton of black Santas, but that's okay. They're them. I'm too obsessed with a reference website to answer my phone sometimes when my friends call, or my girlfriend. That's okay, too. That's me. You like me anyway. And I like you. You're funny, and you're smart, and you may show up late, but you always show up eventually." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 15:52:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460537-if-there-is-such-a-thing-as-a-universal--and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 21:17:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Clare Vanderpool]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460537-if-there-is-such-a-thing-as-a-universal--and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is such a thing as a universal--and I wasn't ready to throw all of mine out the window--it's that there is power in a story. And if someone pays you such a kindness as to make up a tale so you'll enjoy a gingersnap, you go along with that story and enjoy every last bite." -- Clare Vanderpool]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 11:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57214-saying-i-notice-you-re-a-nerd-is-like-saying-hey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Saying 'I notice you're a nerd' is like saying, 'Hey, I notice that you'd rather be intelligent than be stupid, that you'd rather be thoughtful than be vapid, that you believe that there are things that matter more than the arrest record of Lindsay Lohan. Why is that?' In fact, it seems to me that most contemporary insults are pretty lame. Even 'lame' is kind of lame. Saying 'You're lame' is like saying 'You walk with a limp.' Yeah, whatever, so does 50 Cent, and he's done all right for himself." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 15:53:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13155-it-is-a-curious-thing-the-death-of-a-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a curious thing, the death of a loved one. We all know that our time in this world is limited, and that eventually all of us will end up underneath some sheet, never to wake up. And yet it is always a surprise when it happens to someone we know. It is like walking up the stairs to your bedroom in the dark, and thinking there is one more stair than there is. Your foot falls down, through the air, and there is a sickly moment of dark surprise as you try and readjust the way you thought of things." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371203-the-next-suitable-person-you-re-in-light-conversation-with-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 18:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/371203-the-next-suitable-person-you-re-in-light-conversation-with-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next suitable person you’re in light conversation with, you stop suddenly in the middle of the conversation and look at the person closely and say, “What’s wrong?” You say it in a concerned way.  He’ll say, “What do you mean?” You say, “Something’s wrong. I can tell. What is it?” And he’ll look stunned and say, “How did you know?” He doesn’t realize something’s always wrong, with everybody. Often more than one thing. He doesn’t know everybody’s always going around all the time with something wrong and believing they’re exerting great willpower and control to keep other people, for whom they think nothing’s ever wrong, from seeing it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 18:36:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213688-what-passes-for-hip-cynical-transcendence-of-sentiment-is-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What passes for hip cynical transcendence of sentiment is really some kind of fear of being really human, since to be really human [...] is probably to be unavoidably sentimental and naïve and goo-prone and generally pathetic." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668332-so-you-re-reluctant-i-said-to-myself-many-many-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 17:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668332-so-you-re-reluctant-i-said-to-myself-many-many-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you’re reluctant, I said to myself. Many, many people are reluctant. It’s like having feet. It’s nothing to brag about." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668553-you-may-be-right-she-said-a-phrase-which-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 17:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/668553-you-may-be-right-she-said-a-phrase-which-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may be right,' she said, a phrase which here meant 'I’m wrong, but I don’t have the courage to say so." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220402-there-ain-t-no-sin-and-there-ain-t-no-virtue-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 12:24:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220402-there-ain-t-no-sin-and-there-ain-t-no-virtue-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There ain't no sin and there ain't no virtue. There's just stuff people do." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63137-libraries-will-get-you-through-times-of-no-money-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 12:21:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Anne Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63137-libraries-will-get-you-through-times-of-no-money-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Libraries will get you through times of no money better than money will get you through times of no libraries." -- Anne Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255452-our-willingness-to-believe-the-news-is-in-many-cases</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 09:50:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Eula Biss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255452-our-willingness-to-believe-the-news-is-in-many-cases]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our willingness to believe the news is, in many cases, not entirely innocent." -- Eula Biss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013932-andrea-worked-to-harden-herself-to-the-onslaught-of-feelings</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 08:11:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Michelle Tea]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013932-andrea-worked-to-harden-herself-to-the-onslaught-of-feelings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Andrea worked to harden herself to the onslaught of feelings. The problem with feelings was, first you had one, which was generally bad enough. But then you had a feeling about your feeling, and then a feeling about how you were feeling about your feeling, and then another feeling would pop up at the sight of it all, this teetering pyramid of emotion, and all of it would look wrong to Andrea, all her feeling somehow incorrect, too much or too little, too soft or too hard, and another feeling would emerge at the thought of &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;. It was endless, having feelings. And god forbid someone &lt;i&gt;noticed&lt;/i&gt; you having them, as Sophie just had. Then you had feelings about &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;, about having been seen, and more feelings still about the other person's feelings. Oh, it was awful." -- Michelle Tea]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204-how-we-spend-our-days-is-of-course-how-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 08:20:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Renata add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1204-how-we-spend-our-days-is-of-course-how-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How we spend our days is, of course, how we spend our lives." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
