<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75315-cin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75315-cin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 11:46:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243842-books-never-cease-to-astonish-me-when-i-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 11:46:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[cin add a quote by Martha Cooley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243842-books-never-cease-to-astonish-me-when-i-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books never cease to astonish me. When I was a child, I knew--in the incontestable way that children know things--that God was an author who'd imagined me, which is why I (and everyone else) existed: to populate His narrative. My task was to imagine God in return: this was all He and I owed each other." -- Martha Cooley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212668-death-doesn-t-exist-it-never-did-it-never-will-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 23:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[cin add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212668-death-doesn-t-exist-it-never-did-it-never-will-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death doesn't exist. It never did, it never will. But we've drawn so many pictures of it, so many years, trying to pin it down, comprehend it, we've got to thinking of it as an entity, strangely alive and greedy. All it is, however, is a stopped watch, a loss, an end, a darkness. Nothing." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613008-now-and-then-there-are-readings-that-make-the-hairs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 00:07:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[cin add a quote by A.S. Byatt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/613008-now-and-then-there-are-readings-that-make-the-hairs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now and then there are readings that make the hairs on the neck, the non-existent pelt, stand on end and tremble, when every word burns and shines hard and clear and infinite and exact, like stones of fire, like points of stars in the dark—readings when the knowledge that we shall know the writing differently or better or satisfactorily, runs ahead of any capacity to say what we know, or how. In these readings, a sense that the text has appeared to be wholly new, never before seen, is followed, almost immediately, by the sense that it was always there, that we the readers, knew it was always there, and have always known it was as it was, though we have now for the first time recognised, become fully cognisant of, our knowledge." -- A.S. Byatt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837268-thus-as-i-review-the-list-of-my-friends-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 12:35:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[cin add a quote by Sōseki Natsume]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837268-thus-as-i-review-the-list-of-my-friends-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, as I review the list of my friends and acquaintances, most of them emerge as stained with maniac stigmata of one sort or another.  I begin to feel considerably reassured.  The truth may simply be that human society is no more than a massing of lunatics." -- Sōseki Natsume]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
