<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/753572-genevi-ve]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/753572-genevi-ve" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 08:50:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885902-the-night-before-i-d-discovered-am-lost-in-almost-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 08:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Jillian Weise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885902-the-night-before-i-d-discovered-am-lost-in-almost-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The night before I’d discovered am lost in almost. Did everyone already know?" -- Jillian Weise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 09:43:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18410-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think we are well advised to keep on nodding terms with the  people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not.  Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 09:43:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to reclaim the word 'feminism'. We need the word 'feminism' back real bad. When statistics come in saying that only 29% of American women would describe themselves as feminist - and only 42% of British women - I used to think, What do you think feminism IS, ladies? What part of 'liberation for women' is not for you? Is it freedom to vote? The right not to be owned by the man you marry? The campaign for equal pay? 'Vogue' by Madonna? Jeans? Did all that good shit GET ON YOUR NERVES? Or were you just DRUNK AT THE TIME OF THE SURVEY?" -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183435-every-one-of-us-is-called-upon-perhaps-many-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 13:27:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183435-every-one-of-us-is-called-upon-perhaps-many-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every one of us is called upon, perhaps many times, to start a new life.  A frightening diagnosis, a marriage, a move, loss of a job...And onward full-tilt we go, pitched and wrecked and absurdly resolute, driven in spite of everything to make good on a new shore.  To be hopeful, to embrace one possibility after another--that is surely the basic instinct...Crying out: High tide!  Time to move out into the glorious debris.  Time to take this life for what it is." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321638-addictions-started-out-like-magical-pets-pocket-monsters-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 14:16:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321638-addictions-started-out-like-magical-pets-pocket-monsters-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Addictions [...] started out like magical pets, pocket monsters. They did extraordinary tricks, showed you things you hadn't seen, were fun. But came, through some gradual dire alchemy, to make decisions for you. Eventually, they were making your most crucial life-decisions. And they were [...] less intelligent than goldfish." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231022-he-doesn-t-know-which-is-worse-a-past-he-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 07:48:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231022-he-doesn-t-know-which-is-worse-a-past-he-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He doesn't know which is worse, a past he can't regain or a present that will destroy him if he looks at it too clearly. Then there's the future. Sheer vertigo." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257699-he-d-developed-a-strangely-tender-feeling-towards-such-words-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 17:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257699-he-d-developed-a-strangely-tender-feeling-towards-such-words-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’d developed a strangely tender feeling towards such words, as if they were children abandoned in the woods and it was his duty to rescue them." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257389-don-t-be-overwise-fling-yourself-straight-into-life-without-deliberation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 18:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257389-don-t-be-overwise-fling-yourself-straight-into-life-without-deliberation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t be overwise; fling yourself straight into life, without deliberation; don’t be afraid - the flood will bear you to the bank and set you safe on your feet again." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258213-the-belly-is-an-ungrateful-wretch-it-never-remembers-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2010 11:11:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258213-the-belly-is-an-ungrateful-wretch-it-never-remembers-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The belly is an ungrateful wretch, it never remembers past favors, it always wants more tomorrow." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256477-the-body-is-so-easily-damaged-so-easily-disposed-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 13:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256477-the-body-is-so-easily-damaged-so-easily-disposed-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The body is so easily damaged, so easily disposed of, water and chemicals is all it is, hardly more to it than a jellyfish drying on sand." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256397-love-s-merciless-the-way-it-travels-in-and-keeps-emitting</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 17:13:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Kim Addonizio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256397-love-s-merciless-the-way-it-travels-in-and-keeps-emitting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love's merciless, the way it travels in and keeps emitting light." -- Kim Addonizio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259997-if-there-is-no-art-no-culture-then-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2010 18:57:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259997-if-there-is-no-art-no-culture-then-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no art, no culture, then what the fuck are we going to talk about? These are our stories and our stories are all we got!" -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56089-no-more-photos-surely-there-are-enough-no-more-shadows</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 11:59:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56089-no-more-photos-surely-there-are-enough-no-more-shadows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No more photos. Surely there are enough. No more shadows of myself thrown by light onto pieces of paper, onto squares of plastic. No more of my eyes, mouths, noses, moods, bad angles. No more yawns, teeth, wrinkles. I suffer from my own multiplicity. Two or three images would have been enough, or four, or five. That would have allowed for a firm idea: This is she. As it is, I'm watery, I ripple, from moment to moment I dissolve into my other selves. Turn the page: you, looking, are newly confused. You know me too well to know me. Or not too well: too much." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256382-i-ve-been-rereading-your-story-i-think-it-s-about-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 10:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Richard Siken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256382-i-ve-been-rereading-your-story-i-think-it-s-about-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve been rereading your story. I think it’s about me in a way that might not be flattering, but that’s okay. We dream and dream of being seen as we really are and then finally someone looks at us and sees us truly and we fail to measure up. Anyway: story received, story included. You looked at me long enough to see something mysterioso under all the gruff and bluster. Thanks. Sometimes you get so close to someone you end up on the other side of them." -- Richard Siken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235765-you-were-going-to-travel-for-love-without-shoes-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:25:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Kelly Link]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235765-you-were-going-to-travel-for-love-without-shoes-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were going to travel for love, without shoes, or cloak, or common sense. This is one of the things a woman can do when her lover leaves her. It's hard on the feet perhaps, but staying at home is hard on the heart, and you weren't quite ready to give up on him yet." -- Kelly Link]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237383-louise-i-would-gladly-fire-the-past-for-you-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:32:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237383-louise-i-would-gladly-fire-the-past-for-you-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Louise, I would gladly fire the past for you, go and not look back. I have been reckless before, never counting the cost, oblivious to the cost. Now, I've done the sums ahead. I know what it will mean to redeem myself from the accumulations of a lifetime. I know and I don't care. You set before me a space uncluttered by association. It might be a void or it might be a release. Certainly I want to take the risk. I want to take the risk because the life I have stored up is going mouldy." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78981-just-remember-that-the-things-you-put-into-your-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:25:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78981-just-remember-that-the-things-you-put-into-your-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just remember that the things you put into your head are there forever, he said. You might want to think about that.
You forget some things, dont you?
Yes. You forget what you want to remember and you remember what you want to forget." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231016-i-m-a-fool-to-confuse-this-with-goodness-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:26:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231016-i-m-a-fool-to-confuse-this-with-goodness-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a fool, to confuse this with goodness. I am not good.
I know too much to be good. I know myself.
I know myself to be vengeful, greedy, secretive and sly." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231024-but-as-surely-as-the-moon-rises-and-the-sun</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:25:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Chris Adrian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231024-but-as-surely-as-the-moon-rises-and-the-sun]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But as surely as the moon rises and the sun sets, depravity passes down through the ages, because there is always a gap between who we are and who we should be, and our parents, molested by regret, conceive us under the false hope that we will be better than them, and everything they do, every hug and blow, only makes certain that we never will be." -- Chris Adrian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237385-in-the-heat-of-her-hands-i-thought-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:35:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237385-in-the-heat-of-her-hands-i-thought-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the heat of her hands I thought, This is the campfire that mocks the sun. This place will warm me, feed me and care for me. I will hold on to this pulse against other rhythms. The world will come and go in the tide of a day but here is her hand with my future in its palm." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229679-the-universe-is-no-narrow-thing-and-the-order-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:25:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229679-the-universe-is-no-narrow-thing-and-the-order-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man’s mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160541-what-we-share-may-be-a-lot-like-a-traffic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 11:33:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160541-what-we-share-may-be-a-lot-like-a-traffic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we share may be a lot like a traffic accident but we get one another. We are survivors of each other. We have been shark to one another, but also lifeboat. That counts for something." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237389-travel-changes-you-as-you-move-through-this-life-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:38:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237389-travel-changes-you-as-you-move-through-this-life-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel changes you. As you move through this life and this world you change things slightly, you leave marks behind, however small. And in return, life - and travel - leaves marks on you. Most of the time, those marks - on your body or on your heart - are beautiful. Often, though, they hurt." -- Anthony Bourdain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185022-i-was-unfair-to-him-of-course-but-where-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:38:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185022-i-was-unfair-to-him-of-course-but-where-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was unfair to him, of course, but where would I have been without unfairness? In thrall, in harness. Young women need unfairness, it's one of their few defenses. They need their callousness, they need their ignorance. They walk in the dark, along the edges of high cliffs, humming to themselves, thinking themselves invulnerable." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140393-being-in-a-minority-even-in-a-minority-of-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 10:02:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140393-being-in-a-minority-even-in-a-minority-of-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being in a minority, even in a minority of one, did not make you mad.  There was truth and there was untruth, and if you clung to the truth even against the whole world, you were not mad." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231015-a-man-s-at-odds-to-know-his-mind-cause-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:38:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231015-a-man-s-at-odds-to-know-his-mind-cause-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man's at odds to know his mind cause his mind is aught he has to know it with. He can know his heart, but he dont want to. Rightly so. Best not to look in there. It aint the heart of a creature that is bound in the way that God has set for it. You can find meanness in the least of creatures, but when God made man the devil was at his elbow. A creature that can do anything. Make a machine. And a machine to make the machine. And evil that can run itself a thousand years, no need to tend it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 09:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 08:45:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 16:33:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geneviève add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
