<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/754333-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/754333-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:46:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245066-one-day-many-years-ago-a-man-walked-along-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 13:46:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245066-one-day-many-years-ago-a-man-walked-along-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day many years ago a man walked along and stood in the sound of the ocean on a cold sunless shore and said, &quot;We need a voice to call across the water, to warn ships; I'll make one. I'll make a voice like all of time and all of the fog that ever was; I'll make a voice that is like an empty bed beside you all night long, and like an empty house when you open the door, and like trees in autumn with no leaves. A sound like the birds flying south, crying, and a sound like November wind and the sea on the hard, cold shore. I'll make a sound that's so alone that no one can miss it, that whoever hears it will weep in their souls, and hearths will seem warmer, and being inside will seem better to all who hear it in the distant towns. I'll make me a sound and an apparatus and they'll call it a Fog Horn and whoever hears it will know the sadness of eternity and the briefness of life.&quot;

The Fog Horn blew." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122634-i-think-if-human-beings-had-genuine-courage-they-d-wear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 00:34:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122634-i-think-if-human-beings-had-genuine-courage-they-d-wear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think if human beings had genuine courage, they'd wear their costumes every day of the year, not just on Halloween. Wouldn't life be more interesting that way? And now that I think about it, why the heck don't they? Who made the rule that everybody has to dress like sheep 364 days of the year? Think of all the people you'd meet if they were in costume every day. People would be so much easier to talk to - like talking to dogs. " -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
