<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/754491-hanaa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/754491-hanaa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 10:48:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 10:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 19:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2495-do-you-hate-people-i-don-t-hate-them-i-just-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you hate people?

I don't hate them...I just feel better when they're not around." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 16:21:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody realizes that some people expend tremendous energy merely to be normal." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 17:38:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39106-there-is-an-idea-of-a-patrick-bateman-some-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…there is an idea of a Patrick Bateman, some kind of abstraction, but there is no real me, only an entity, something illusory, and though I can hide my cold gaze and you can shake my hand and feel flesh gripping yours and maybe you can even sense our lifestyles are probably comparable: I simply am not there.  It is hard for me to make sense on any given level.  Myself is fabricated, an aberration.  I am a noncontingent human being.  My personality is sketchy and unformed, my heartlessness goes deep and is persistent.  My conscience, my pity, my hopes disappeared a long time ago (probably at Harvard) if they ever did exist.  There are no more barriers to cross.  All I have in common with the uncontrollable and the insane, the vicious and the evil, all the mayhem I have caused and my utter indifference toward it, I have now surpassed.  I still, though, hold on to one single bleak truth: no one is safe, nothing is redeemed.  Yet I am blameless.  Each model of human behavior must be assumed to have some validity.  Is evil something you are?  Or is it something you do?  My pain is constant and sharp and I do not hope for a better world for anyone.  In fact, I want my pain to be inflicted on others.  I want no one to escape.  But even after admitting this—and I have countless times, in just about every act I’ve committed—and coming face-to-face with these truths, there is no catharsis.  I gain no deeper knowledge about myself, no new understanding can be extracted from my telling.  There has been no reason for me to tell you any of this.  This confession has meant nothing…." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 17:53:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107311-if-you-hide-your-ignorance-no-one-will-hit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hide your ignorance, no one will hit you and you'll never learn." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2011 23:26:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you with no regard to the actions of our enemies or the jealousies of actors. I will love you with no regard to the outrage of certain parents or the boredom of certain friends. I will love you no matter what is served in the world’s cafeterias or what game is played at each and every recess. I will love you no matter how many fire drills we are all forced to endure, and no matter what is drawn upon the blackboard in blurry, boring chalk. I will love you no matter how many mistakes I make when trying to reduce fractions, and no matter how difficult it is to memorize the periodic table.
I will love you no matter what your locker combination was, or how you decided to spend your time during study hall. I will love you no matter how your soccer team performed in the tournament or how many stains I received on my cheerleading uniform. I will love you if I never see you again, and I will love you if I see you every Tuesday. I will love you if you cut your hair and I will love you if you cut the hair of others. I will love you if you abandon your baticeering, and I will love you if you if you retire from the theater to take up some other, less dangerous occupation. I will love you if you drop your raincoat on the floor instead of hanging it up and I will love you if you betray your father. I will love you even if you announce that the poetry of Edgar Guest is the best in the world and even if you announce that the work of Zilpha Keatley Snyder is unbearably tedious. I will love you if you abandon the theremin and take up the harmonica and I will love you if you donate your marmosets to the zoo and your tree frogs to M. I will love you as a starfish loves a coral reef and as a kudzu loves trees, even if the oceans turn to sawdust and the trees fall in the forest without anyone around to hear them. I will love you as the pesto loves the fettuccini and as the horseradish loves the miyagi, as the tempura loves the ikura and the pepperoni loves the pizza.
I will love you as the manatee loves the head of lettuce and as the dark spot loves the leopard, as the leech loves the ankle of a wader and as a corpse loves the beak of the vulture. I will love you as the doctor loves his sickest patient and a lake loves its thirstiest swimmer. I will love you as the beard loves the chin, and the crumbs love the beard, and the damp napkin loves the crumbs, and the precious document loves the dampness in the napkin, and the squinting eye of the reader loves the smudged print of the document, and the tears of sadness love the squinting eye as it misreads what is written. I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat, and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms. i will love you as a child loves to overhear the conversations of its parents, and the parents love the sound of their own arguing voices, and as the pen loves to write down the words these voices utter in a notebook for safekeeping. I will love you as a shingle loves falling off a house on a windy day and striking a grumpy person across the chin, and as an oven loves malfunctioning in the middle of roasting a turkey.
I will love you as an airplane loves to fall from a clear blue sky and as an escalator loves to entangle expensive scarves in its mechanisms. I will love you as a wet paper towel loves to be crumpled into a ball and thrown at a bathroom ceiling and as an eraser loves to leave dust in the hairdos of people who talk too much. I will love you as a cufflink loves to drop from its shirt and explore the party for itself and as a pair of white gloves loves to slip delicately into the punchbowl. I will love you as the taxi loves the muddy splash of a puddle and as a library loves the patient tick of a clock." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213767-my-new-year-s-eve-toast-to-all-the-devils-lusts</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 15:50:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Patricia Highsmith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213767-my-new-year-s-eve-toast-to-all-the-devils-lusts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My New Year’s Eve Toast: to all the devils, lusts, passions, greeds, envies, loves, hates, strange desires, enemies ghostly and real, the army of memories, with which I do battle — may they never give me peace. (New Year's Eve, 1947)" -- Patricia Highsmith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185907-when-you-re-surrounded-by-all-these-people-it-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 23:27:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Fiona Apple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185907-when-you-re-surrounded-by-all-these-people-it-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're surrounded by all these people, it can be lonelier than when you're by yourself.  You can be in a huge crowd, but if you don't feel like you can trust anyone or talk to anybody, you feel like you're really alone." -- Fiona Apple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 18:34:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ambition is handicapped by laziness" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 08:41:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 17:08:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67507-very-occasionally-if-you-pay-really-close-attention-life-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 17:20:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67507-very-occasionally-if-you-pay-really-close-attention-life-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Very occasionally, if you pay really close attention, life doesn't suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139472-some-lose-all-mind-and-become-soul-insane-some-lose-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2013 00:20:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139472-some-lose-all-mind-and-become-soul-insane-some-lose-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some lose all mind and become soul,insane.
some lose all soul and become mind, intellectual.
some lose both and become accepted" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165279-because-i-rant-not-neither-rave-of-what-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 20:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by R.D. Blackmore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165279-because-i-rant-not-neither-rave-of-what-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...because I rant not, neither rave of what I feel, can you be so shallow as to dream that I feel nothing? " -- R.D. Blackmore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179519-every-weirdo-in-the-world-is-on-my-wavelength</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 16:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hanaa add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179519-every-weirdo-in-the-world-is-on-my-wavelength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every weirdo in the world is on my wavelength." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
