<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/756375-sean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/756375-sean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:12:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12770-life-is-too-short-when-you-think-of-the-length</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:12:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Sean Mangan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12770-life-is-too-short-when-you-think-of-the-length]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is too short when you think of the length of death" -- Sean Mangan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12771-can-t-you-understand-that-if-you-take-a-law-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:18:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Jerome Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12771-can-t-you-understand-that-if-you-take-a-law-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can't you understand? That if you take a law like evolution and you make it a crime to teach it in the public schools, tomorrow you can make it a crime to teach it in the private schools? And tomorrow you may make it a crime to read about it. And soon you may ban books and newspapers. And then you may turn Catholic against Protestant, and Protestant against Protestant, and try to foist your own religion upon the mind of man. If you can do one, you can do the other. Because fanaticism and ignorance is forever busy, and needs feeding. And soon, your Honor, with banners flying and with drums beating we'll be marching backward, BACKWARD, through the glorious ages of that Sixteenth Century when bigots burned the man who dared bring enlightenment and intelligence to the human mind

-Henry Drummond, a character in Inherit The Wind" -- Jerome Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12773-an-idea-is-a-greater-monument-than-a-cathedral-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:25:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Jerome Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12773-an-idea-is-a-greater-monument-than-a-cathedral-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An idea is a greater monument than a cathedral. And the advance of man's knowledge is a greater miracle than all the sticks turned to snakes or the parting of the waters." -- Jerome Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12779-we-all-know-that-something-is-eternal-and-it-ain-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:32:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12779-we-all-know-that-something-is-eternal-and-it-ain-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all know that something is eternal. And it ain’t houses and it ain’t names, and it ain’t earth, and it ain’t even the stars . . . everybody knows in their bones that something is eternal, and that something has to do with human beings. All the greatest people ever lived have been telling us that for five thousand years and yet you’d be surprised how people are always losing hold of it. There’s something way down deep that’s eternal about every human being.

-stage manager, in the play OUR TOWN" -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12784-that-s-what-it-was-like-to-be-alive-to-move</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 16:38:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12784-that-s-what-it-was-like-to-be-alive-to-move]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s what it was like to be alive. To move about in a cloud of ignorance; to go up and down trampling on the feelings of those...of those about you. To spend and waste time as though you had a million years. To be always at the mercy of one self-centered passion, or another. Now you know- that’s the happy existence you wanted to go back to. Ignorance and blindness.

-Simon Stimson, OUR TOWN" -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14414-we-re-so-busy-watching-out-for-what-s-just-ahead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 05:39:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14414-we-re-so-busy-watching-out-for-what-s-just-ahead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're so busy watching out for what's just ahead of us that we don't take time to enjoy where we are." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15768-i-walked-over-to-the-hill-where-we-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 05:51:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15768-i-walked-over-to-the-hill-where-we-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I walked over to the hill where we used to go and sled. There were a lot of little kids there. I watched them flying. Doing jumps and having races. And I thought that all those little kids are going to grow up someday. And all of those little kids are going to do the things that we do. And they will all kiss someone someday. But for now, sledding is enough. I think it would be great if sledding were always enough, but it isn't." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15770-my-mother-always-told-me-even-if-a-song-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 05:57:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Etta James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15770-my-mother-always-told-me-even-if-a-song-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother always told me, even if a song has been done a thousand times, you can still bring something of your own to it." -- Etta James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15771-all-these-years-later-people-still-wonder-about-how-bruce</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 06:02:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Linda Lee Cadwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15771-all-these-years-later-people-still-wonder-about-how-bruce]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All these years later, people still wonder about how Bruce died. I prefer to remember how he lived. " -- Linda Lee Cadwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15772-the-quality-of-strength-lined-with-tenderness-is-an-unbeatable</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 06:08:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15772-the-quality-of-strength-lined-with-tenderness-is-an-unbeatable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The quality of strength lined with tenderness is an unbeatable combination, as are intelligence and necessity when unblunted by formal education. " -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15773-it-would-perhaps-not-be-amiss-to-point-out-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 06:12:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15773-it-would-perhaps-not-be-amiss-to-point-out-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would perhaps not be amiss to point out that he had always tried to be a good dog. He had tried to do all the things his MAN and his WOMAN, and most of all his BOY, had asked or expected of him. He would have died for them, if that had been required. He had never wanted to kill anybody. He had been struck by something, possibly destiny, or fate, or only a degenerative nerve disease called rabies. Free will was not a factor." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15775-everyone-that-watches-deep-throat-is-watching-me-being-raped</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 06:17:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sean add a quote by Linda Lovelace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15775-everyone-that-watches-deep-throat-is-watching-me-being-raped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone that watches &quot;Deep Throat&quot; is watching me being raped. " -- Linda Lovelace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
