<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/758049-lisa-copen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/758049-lisa-copen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:37:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40498-i-ve-learned-that-even-when-i-have-pains-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40498-i-ve-learned-that-even-when-i-have-pains-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No pain that we suffer, no trial that we experience is wasted. It ministers to our education, to the development of such qualities as patience, faith, fortitude and humility. All that we suffer and all that we endure, especially when we endure it patiently, builds up our characters, purifies our hearts, expands our souls, and makes us more tender and charitable, more worthy to be called the children of God . . . and it is through sorrow and suffering, toil and tribulation, that we gain the education that we come here to acquire and which will make us more like our Father and Mother in heaven." -- Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:42:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16841-with-time-and-perspective-we-recognize-that-such-problems-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With time and perspective we recognize that such problems in life do come for a purpose, if only to allow the one who faces such despair to be convinced that he really does need divine strength beyond himself, that she really does need the offer of heaven’s hand. Those who feel no need for mercy usually never seek it and almost never bestow it. Those who have never had a heartache or a weakness or felt lonely or forsaken never have had to cry unto heaven for relief of such personal pain. Surely it is better to find the goodness of God and the grace of Christ, even at the price of despair, than to risk living our lives in a moral or material complacency that has never felt any need for faith or forgiveness, any need for redemption or relief." -- Jeffery R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23275-god-wants-us-to-choose-to-love-him-freely-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 08:44:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Philip Yancey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23275-god-wants-us-to-choose-to-love-him-freely-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God wants us to choose to love him freely, even when that choice involves pain, because we are committed to him, not to our own good feelings and rewards.  He wants us to cleave to him, as Job did, even when we have every reason to deny him hotly.  That, I believe, is the central message of Job.  Satan had taunted God with the accusation that humans are not truly free.  Was Job being faithful simply because God had allowed him a prosperous life?  Job's fiery trials proved the answer beyond doubt.  Job clung to God's justice when he was the best example in history of God's apparent injustice.  He did not seek the Giver because of his gifts; when all gifts were removed he still sought the Giver." -- Philip Yancey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24878-i-write-for-the-unlearned-about-things-in-which-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 15:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24878-i-write-for-the-unlearned-about-things-in-which-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write for the unlearned about things in which I am unlearned myself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972548-you-don-t-have-to-be-strong-enough-to-do-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 21:42:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Jenny  Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972548-you-don-t-have-to-be-strong-enough-to-do-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t have to be strong enough to do it all at once—no one is. You just have to be strong enough to do one thing. That’s it. Then you rest, and when you’ve regained that strength back, you tackle the next thing." -- Jenny  Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995534-a-man-needs-his-father-more-as-life-progresses-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 21:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Adriana Trigiani]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995534-a-man-needs-his-father-more-as-life-progresses-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man needs his father more as life progresses, not less. It is not enough to learn how to use a lathe, milk a cow, repair a roof; there are greater holes to mend, deeper wells to fill, that only a father’s wisdom can sustain. A father teaches his son how to think a problem through, how to lead a household, how to love his wife. A father sets an example for his son, building his character from the soul outward." -- Adriana Trigiani]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009533-he-raged-and-questioned-and-mourned-eventually-he-found-peace-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 22:36:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Sarah Sundin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009533-he-raged-and-questioned-and-mourned-eventually-he-found-peace-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He raged and questioned and mourned. Eventually he found peace—not peace like some still pond, but peace like a river, jostling over rocks, hurtling over falls, whirling in eddies. Authentic, rugged peace." -- Sarah Sundin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033574-are-you-willing-to-say-to-god-that-he-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 21:50:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Francis Chan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033574-are-you-willing-to-say-to-god-that-he-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you willing to say to God that He can have whatever He wants? Do you believe that wholehearted commitment to Him is more important than any other thing or person in your life? Do you know that nothing you do in this life will ever matter, unless it is about loving God and loving the people He has made?" -- Francis Chan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034451-it-is-a-remarkable-cycle-our-prayers-for-more-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 15:33:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Francis Chan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034451-it-is-a-remarkable-cycle-our-prayers-for-more-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a remarkable cycle: Our prayers for more love result in love, which naturally causes us to pray more, which results in more love…." -- Francis Chan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713890-having-faith-often-means-doing-what-others-see-as-crazy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 14:27:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Francis Chan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/713890-having-faith-often-means-doing-what-others-see-as-crazy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having faith often means doing what others see as crazy. Something is wrong when our lives make sense to unbelievers." -- Francis Chan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101286-you-don-t-go-on-as-much-as-you-change-direction</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 22:33:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101286-you-don-t-go-on-as-much-as-you-change-direction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t go on as much as you change direction. And which direction you take, that part’s up to you. One way leads to forgiveness and peace. The other leads down a road of bitterness. Can’t turn back from bitterness. Not very often, anyway." -- Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101287-sometimes-i-wake-up-in-the-morning-and-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 22:34:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101287-sometimes-i-wake-up-in-the-morning-and-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sometimes I wake up in the morning, and I have to make the right choice again. The shadow of bitterness comes that fast on a heart. And each time I choose, I learn again—nan tout bagay, Bondye ap travay pou byen pou moun ki renmen l. God works for good. Romans 8:28." -- Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101316-not-dealing-with-the-past-she-said-is-like-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 23:32:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1101316-not-dealing-with-the-past-she-said-is-like-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["not dealing with the past,” she said, “is like having a skunk in the middle of your living room. You don’t notice it after a while, but everyone around you smells it, and it rubs off on folks who visit, and no amount of tomato juice baths will ever wash the stink away. You can only bury the past when you acknowledge it and don’t allow it to sidle up against your leg no more. Even then, digging the hole to bury the thing is hard work. It’s the hard work of healing most folks never want to do." -- Amy K. Sorrells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1112277-he-had-no-agenda-to-convert-the-lost-his-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 21:42:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Harry Kraus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1112277-he-had-no-agenda-to-convert-the-lost-his-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had no agenda to convert the lost. His only mission was to love. And because of that, conversions followed as naturally as smoke follows fire." -- Harry Kraus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1115833-a-wise-man-once-told-me-that-grace-is-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 21:06:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Harry Kraus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1115833-a-wise-man-once-told-me-that-grace-is-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wise man once told me that grace is God at work. Legalism is me at work. The difference isn’t in the work; it’s in the motivation." -- Harry Kraus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1115867-in-africa-he-often-had-to-make-sure-his-post-op</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 21:55:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Harry Kraus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1115867-in-africa-he-often-had-to-make-sure-his-post-op]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["in Africa, he often had to make sure his post-op patients were well enough to walk five or ten kilometers to get to their homes in the bush." -- Harry Kraus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1131881-keep-on-god-gives-us-dreams-of-what-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 22:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Anne Mateer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1131881-keep-on-god-gives-us-dreams-of-what-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep on. God gives us dreams of what our lives will be, but He doesn’t guarantee them. Just asks us to trust Him with the changes." -- Anne Mateer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242670-each-moment-of-loss-she-has-come-to-believe-contains</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 22:29:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Christina Baker Kline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242670-each-moment-of-loss-she-has-come-to-believe-contains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each moment of loss, she has come to believe, contains within it the possibility of a new life. When the unimaginable happens, and your life changes irrevocably, you may find along with the pain a kind of grace. And in the place of certainty and fear—the fear of losing what you had—you are left with something startling: a depth of empathy, a quivering sensitivity to the world around you, and the unexpected blessing of gratitude for what remains." -- Christina Baker Kline]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
