<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75816-akaellen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/75816-akaellen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 07:29:05 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23056-the-voice-of-love-seemed-to-call-to-me-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 07:29:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23056-the-voice-of-love-seemed-to-call-to-me-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The voice of Love seemed to call to me, but it was a wrong number." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109804-there-is-no-surer-foundation-for-a-beautiful-friendship-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 07:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109804-there-is-no-surer-foundation-for-a-beautiful-friendship-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no surer foundation for a beautiful friendship than a mutual taste in literature." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61472-say-what-you-will-about-the-south-but-in-north</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 07:37:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61472-say-what-you-will-about-the-south-but-in-north]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Say what you will about the south, but in North Carolina a hot dog is free to swing anyway it wishes." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167717-but-hard-bitten-cynicism-leaves-one-feeling-peevish-and-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 11:49:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Julie Powell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167717-but-hard-bitten-cynicism-leaves-one-feeling-peevish-and-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But hard bitten cynicism leaves one feeling peevish, and too much of it can do lasting damage to your heart." -- Julie Powell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12837-the-answer-is-that-we-don-t-choose-our-freaks-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 12:57:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12837-the-answer-is-that-we-don-t-choose-our-freaks-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer is that we don't choose our freaks, they choose us." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172778-when-shall-we-live-if-not-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 12:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172778-when-shall-we-live-if-not-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When shall we live if not now?" -- M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 13:00:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14050-red-hair-sir-in-my-opinion-is-dangerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 13:03:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14050-red-hair-sir-in-my-opinion-is-dangerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Red hair, sir, in my opinion, is dangerous." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:38:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:40:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:41:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Piglet sidled up to Pooh from behind. &quot;Pooh?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;Yes, Piglet?&quot;
&quot;Nothing,&quot; said Piglet, taking Pooh's hand. &quot;I just wanted to be sure of you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:44:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5402-so-it-s-not-gonna-be-easy-it-s-going-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So it's not gonna be easy. It's going to be really hard; we're gonna have to work at this everyday, but I want to do that because I want you. I want all of you, forever, everyday. You and me... everyday." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:48:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49991-so-i-love-you-because-the-entire-universe-conspired-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, I love you because the entire universe conspired to help me find you." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62495-they-didn-t-agree-on-much-in-fact-they-didn-t-agree</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:51:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62495-they-didn-t-agree-on-much-in-fact-they-didn-t-agree]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They didn’t agree on much. In fact, they didn’t agree on anything. They fought all the time and challenged each other ever day. But despite their differences, they had one important thing in common. They were crazy about each other." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218377-promise-me-you-ll-always-remember-you-re-braver-than-you-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 19:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218377-promise-me-you-ll-always-remember-you-re-braver-than-you-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Promise me you'll always remember: You're braver than you believe, and stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150233-i-told-you-you-don-t-love-someone-because-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 20:10:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by L.J. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150233-i-told-you-you-don-t-love-someone-because-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told you. You don't love someone because of their looks or their clothes or their car. You love them because they sing a song only your heart can understand." -- L.J. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2011 12:01:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as a thief loves a gallery and as a crow loves a murder, as a cloud loves bats and as a range loves braes. I will love you as misfortune loves orphans, as fire loves innocence and as justice loves to sit and watch while everything goes wrong. I will love you as a battlefield loves young men and as peppermints love your allergies, and I will love you as the banana peel loves the shoe of a man who was just struck by a shingle falling off a house. I will love you as a volunteer fire department loves rushing into burning buildings and as burning buildings love to chase them back out, and as a parachute loves to leave a blimp and as a blimp operator loves to chase after it.
I will love you as a dagger loves a certain person’s back, and as a certain person loves to wear dagger proof tunics, and as a dagger proof tunic loves to go to a certain dry cleaning facility, and how a certain employee of a dry cleaning facility loves to stay up late with a pair of binoculars, watching a dagger factory for hours in the hopes of catching a burglar, and as a burglar loves sneaking up behind people with binoculars, suddenly realizing that she has left her dagger at home. I will love you as a drawer loves a secret compartment, and as a secret compartment loves a secret, and as a secret loves to make a person gasp, and as a gasping person loves a glass of brandy to calm their nerves, and as a glass of brandy loves to shatter on the floor, and as the noise of glass shattering loves to make someone else gasp, and as someone else gasping loves a nearby desk to lean against, even if leaning against it presses a lever that loves to open a drawer and reveal a secret compartment. I will love you until all such compartments are discovered and opened, and until all the secrets have gone gasping into the world. I will love you until all the codes and hearts have been broken and until every anagram and egg has been unscrambled.
I will love you until every fire is extinguised and until every home is rebuilt from the handsomest and most susceptible of woods, and until every criminal is handcuffed by the laziest of policemen. I will love until M. hates snakes and J. hates grammar, and I will love you until C. realizes S. is not worthy of his love and N. realizes he is not worthy of the V. I will love you until the bird hates a nest and the worm hates an apple, and until the apple hates a tree and the tree hates a nest, and until a bird hates a tree and an apple hates a nest, although honestly I cannot imagine that last occurrence no matter how hard I try. I will love you as we grow older, which has just happened, and has happened again, and happened several days ago, continuously, and then several years before that, and will continue to happen as the spinning hands of every clock and the flipping pages of every calendar mark the passage of time, except for the clocks that people have forgotten to wind and the calendars that people have forgotten to place in a highly visible area. I will love you as we find ourselves farther and farther from one another, where we once we were so close that we could slip the curved straw, and the long, slender spoon, between our lips and fingers respectively.
I will love you until the chances of us running into one another slip from slim to zero, and until your face is fogged by distant memory, and your memory faced by distant fog, and your fog memorized by a distant face, and your distance distanced by the memorized memory of a foggy fog. I will love you no matter where you go and who you see, no matter where you avoid and who you don’t see, and no matter who sees you avoiding where you go. I will love you no matter what happens to you, and no matter how I discover what happens to you, and no matter what happens to me as I discover this, and now matter how I am discovered after what happens to me as I am discovering this." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12675-after-all-reading-is-arguably-a-far-more-creative-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 12:21:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12675-after-all-reading-is-arguably-a-far-more-creative-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all, reading is arguably a far more creative and imaginative process than writing; when the reader creates emotion in their head, or the colors of the sky during the setting sun, or the smell of a warm summer's breeze on their face, they should reserve as much praise for themselves as they do for the writer - perhaps more." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180671-i-do-not-believe-a-person-can-take-two-issues</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 12:39:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180671-i-do-not-believe-a-person-can-take-two-issues]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not believe a person can take two issues from Scripture, those being abortion and gay marriage, and adhere to them as sins, then neglect much of the rest and call himself a fundamentalist or even a conservative. The person who believes the sum of his morality involves gay marriage and abortion alone, and neglects health care and world trade and the environment and loving his neighbor and feeding the poor is, by definition, a theological liberal, because he takes what he wants from Scripture and ignores the rest." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378646-hearing-him-talk-about-his-mother-about-his-intact-family</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 09:35:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[akaellen add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378646-hearing-him-talk-about-his-mother-about-his-intact-family]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hearing him talk about his mother, about his intact family, makes my chest hurt for a second, like someone pierced it with a needle." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
