<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/758553-bobby]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/758553-bobby" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 14:56:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 14:56:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 17:35:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440-who-knows-how-to-make-love-stay-1-tell-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who knows how to make love stay?

1. Tell love you are going to Junior's Deli on Flatbush Avenue in Brooklyn to pick up a cheesecake, and if loves stays, it can have half. It will stay.

2. Tell love you want a momento of it and obtain a lock of its hair. Burn the hair in a dime-store incense burner with yin/yang symbols on three sides. Face southwest. Talk fast over the burning hair in a convincingly exotic language. Remove the ashes of the burnt hair and use them to paint a moustache on your face. Find love. Tell it you are someone new. It will stay.

3. Wake love up in the middle of the night. Tell it the world is on fire. Dash to the bedroom window and pee out of it. Casually return to bed and assure love that everything is going to be all right. Fall asleep. Love will be there in the morning." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 17:37:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now tequila may be the favored beverage of outlaws but that doesn't mean it gives them preferential treatment. In fact, tequila probably has betrayed as many outlaws as has the central nervous system and dissatisfied wives. Tequila, scorpion honey, harsh dew of the doglands, essence of Aztec, crema de cacti; tequila, oily and thermal like the sun in solution; tequila, liquid geometry of passion; Tequila, the buzzard god who copulates in midair with the ascending souls of dying virgins; tequila, firebug in the house of good taste; O tequila, savage water of sorcery, what confusion and mischief your sly, rebellious drops do generate!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164102-history-the-more-of-it-you-have-the-more-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 19:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bobby add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164102-history-the-more-of-it-you-have-the-more-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History. The more of it you have the more you have to live it. After a little while there gets to be too much of it to memorize and maybe that's when empires start to decline." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
