<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/759164-seth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/759164-seth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 08:58:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 08:58:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to sleep with a sober cannibal than a drunk Christian." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 08:58:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25712-some-years-ago---never-mind-how-long-precisely--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some years ago - never mind how long precisely - having little or no money in my purse, and nothing particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off the spleen, and regulating the circulation. Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp, drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet; and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping into the street, and methodically knocking people's hats off - then, I account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute for pistol and ball. With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon his sword; I quietly take to the ship. There is nothing surprising in this. If they but knew it, almost all men in their degree, some time or other, cherish very nearly the same feelings towards the ocean with me." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36675-talk-not-to-me-of-blasphemy-man-i-d-strike-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 08:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36675-talk-not-to-me-of-blasphemy-man-i-d-strike-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talk not to me of blasphemy, man; I'd strike the sun if it insulted me." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58579-consider-the-subtleness-of-the-sea-how-its-most-dreaded</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 09:03:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58579-consider-the-subtleness-of-the-sea-how-its-most-dreaded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider the subtleness of the sea; how its most dreaded creatures glide under water, unapparent for the most part, and treacherously hidden beneath the loveliest tints of azure. Consider also the devilish brilliance and beauty of many of its most remorseless tribes, as the dainty embellished shape of many species of sharks. Consider, once more, the universal cannibalism of the sea; all whose creatures prey upon each other, carrying on eternal war since the world began. 

Consider all this; and then turn to the green, gentle, and most docile earth; consider them both, the sea and the land; and do you not find a strange analogy to something in yourself? For as this appalling ocean surrounds the verdant land, so in the soul of man there lies one insular Tahiti, full of peace and joy, but encompassed by all the horrors of the half-known life. God keep thee! Push not off from that isle, thou canst never return!" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56880-take-almost-any-path-you-please-and-ten-to-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 09:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56880-take-almost-any-path-you-please-and-ten-to-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take almost any path you please, and ten to one it carries you down in a dale, and leaves you there by a pool in the stream.  There is magic in it.  Let the most absent-minded of men be plunged in his deepest reveries--stand that man on his legs, set his feet a-going, and he will infallibly lead you to water, if water there be in all that region.  Should you ever be athirst in the great American desert, try this experiment, if your caravan happen to be supplied with a metaphysical professor.  Yes, as every one knows, meditation and water are wedded for ever." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136892-truly-to-enjoy-bodily-warmth-some-small-part-of-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 09:11:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Seth add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136892-truly-to-enjoy-bodily-warmth-some-small-part-of-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["truly to enjoy bodily warmth, some small part of you must be cold, for there is no quality in this world that is not what it is merely by contrast. Nothing exists in itself. If you flatter yourself that you are all over comfortable, and have been so a long time, then you cannot be said to be comfortable any more." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
