<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/760282-hayley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/760282-hayley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 15:58:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35671-between-skin-and-skin-there-is-only-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 15:58:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35671-between-skin-and-skin-there-is-only-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between skin and skin, there is only light." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 18:38:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8051-until-a-man-is-twenty-five-he-still-thinks-every-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until a man is twenty-five, he still thinks, every so often, that under the right circumstances he could be the baddest motherfucker in the world. If I moved to a martial-arts monastery in China and studied real hard for ten years. If my family was wiped out by Colombian drug dealers and I swore myself to revenge. If I got a fatal disease, had one year to live, and devoted it to wiping out street crime. If I just dropped out and devoted my life to being bad." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158909-he-knew-the-world-and-its-absurdities-as-only-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158909-he-knew-the-world-and-its-absurdities-as-only-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew the world and its absurdities as only an intelligent Irishman can; which is to say that where his knowledge or memory failed him, his imagination was always ready to fill the gap." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16077-i-acquired-expensive-habits-and-affected-manners-i-got-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2011 07:58:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by John Fowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16077-i-acquired-expensive-habits-and-affected-manners-i-got-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I acquired expensive habits and affected manners. I got a third-class degree and a first-class illusion: that I was a poet. But nothing could have been less poetic that my seeing-through-all boredom with life in general and with making a living in particular. I was too green to know that all cynicism masks a failure to cope-- an impotence, in short; and that to despise all effort is the greatest effort of all. But I did absorb a small dose of one permanently useful thing, Oxford's greatest gift to civilized life: Socratic honesty. It showed me, very intermittently, that it is not enough to revolt against one's past. One day I was outrageously bitter among some friends about the Army; back in my own rooms later it suddenly struck me that just because I said with impunity things that would have apoplexed my dead father, I was still no less under his influence. The truth was I was not a cynic by nature, only by revolt. I had got away from what I hated, but I hadn't found where I loved, and so I pretended that there was nowhere to love. Handsomely equipped to fail, I went out into the world." -- John Fowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522148-because-jack-you-volunteered-to-be-taken-down-into-eternal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 10:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522148-because-jack-you-volunteered-to-be-taken-down-into-eternal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because, Jack, you volunteered to be taken down into eternal torment in place of her. This is the absolute &lt;i&gt;minimum&lt;/i&gt; (unless I'm mistaken) that any female requires from her man." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165078-may-you-walk-a-lighted-path-may-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 10:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165078-may-you-walk-a-lighted-path-may-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May you walk a lighted path. May you fight for truth - your truth, not someone else's - and may you understand, above all things, that you are the most important concept, theory, and philosophy I have ever known." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146188-those-around-you-can-have-their-novellas-sweet-their-short</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 10:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146188-those-around-you-can-have-their-novellas-sweet-their-short]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those around you can have their novellas, sweet, their short stories of cliché and coincidence, occasionally spiced up with tricks of the quirky, the achingly mundane, the grotesque. A few will even cook up Greek tragedy, those born into misery, destined to die in misery. But you, my bride of quietness, you will craft nothing less than epic with your life. Out of all of them, your story will be the one to last." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12321-but-most-critically-sweet-never-try-to-change-the-narrative</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 10:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Marisha Pessl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12321-but-most-critically-sweet-never-try-to-change-the-narrative]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But most critically, sweet, never try to change the narrative structure of someone else's story, though you will certainly be tempted to, as you watch those poor souls in school, in life, heading unwittingly down dangerous tangents, fatal digressions from which they will unlikely be able to emerge.  Resist the temptation. Spend your energies on your story. Reworking it.  Making it better." -- Marisha Pessl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31582-whenever-serious-and-competent-people-need-to-get-things-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 10:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31582-whenever-serious-and-competent-people-need-to-get-things-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever serious and competent people need to get things done in the real world, all considerations of tradition and protocol fly out the window." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342336-even-chance-meetings-are-the-result-of-karma-things-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 08:36:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hayley add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342336-even-chance-meetings-are-the-result-of-karma-things-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even chance meetings are the result of karma… Things in life are fated by our previous lives. That even in the smallest events there’s no such thing as coincidence." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
