<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/760355-mary]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/760355-mary" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 14:21:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353011-you-can-never-visit-the-same-place-twice-each-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 14:21:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Maureen Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353011-you-can-never-visit-the-same-place-twice-each-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never visit the same place twice. Each time, it's a different story. By the very act of coming back, you wipe out what came before." -- Maureen Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338633-she-firmly-held-the-theory-that-everyone-gets-at-least</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 14:23:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Maureen Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338633-she-firmly-held-the-theory-that-everyone-gets-at-least]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She firmly held the theory that everyone gets at least one very stupid superpower." -- Maureen Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375346-idea-meets-execution-feeling-becomes-action-i-don-t-know-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 14:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Maureen Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375346-idea-meets-execution-feeling-becomes-action-i-don-t-know-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Idea meets execution. Feeling becomes action. 
I don't know why people find this idea so hard to get. I mean, you can throw any two people together, it doesn't mean they'll fall in love. Everyone knows this. No one quite understands how it works. It's just those people, where they are in their lives, how circumstance throws them together. Sure, it's happened before, but never quite in that way. Maybe they seem to come together all wrong. Maybe they've loved others. Maybe they don't always do right by each other...but it's still there, the love. The event. And no one would dare criticize it just because it's common, it's a little asymmetrical, and anyone can do it. It is unique. It is theirs. It is beautiful. They have made something that has been made a million times before and has also never existed before that moment." -- Maureen Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 08:29:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Jay Asher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t know what goes on in anyone’s life but your own. And when you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re not messing with just that part. Unfortunately, you can’t be that precise and selective. When you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re messing with their entire life. Everything. . . affects everything." -- Jay Asher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 07:10:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 07:11:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594941-a-translator-caught-in-the-space-between-two-tongues-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:44:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Elena Mauli Shapiro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594941-a-translator-caught-in-the-space-between-two-tongues-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A translator, caught in the space between two tongues. Such people tend to come a little bit unglued from the task of trying to convey meaning from one code to the other. The transfer is never safe, the meaning changes in the channel — becomes tinted, adulterated, absurd, stronger." -- Elena Mauli Shapiro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599432-i-went-on-happily-reading-well-into-the-night-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 08:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599432-i-went-on-happily-reading-well-into-the-night-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went on happily reading well into the night, when no one ventured on to the decks of the Donizetti, except for sinful shadows who were careful not to interrupt me, careful not to disturb my reading, happiness, happiness, passion regained, genuine devotion, my prayers rising up and up through the clouds to the realm of pure music, to what for want of a better name we call the choir of the angels, a non-human space but undoubtedly the only imaginable space we humans can truly inhabit, an uninhabitable space but the only one worth inhabiting, a space in which we shall cease to be but the only space in which we can be what we truly are..." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599588-i-went-on-writing-reviews-for-the-newspaper-and-critical</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 10:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599588-i-went-on-writing-reviews-for-the-newspaper-and-critical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went on writing reviews for the newspaper, and critical articles crying out for a different approach to culture, as even the most inattentive reader could hardly fail to notice if he scratched the surface a little, critical articles crying out, indeed begging, for a return to the Greek and Latin greats, to the Troubadours, to the dolce stil nuovo and the classics of Spain, France and England, more culture! more culture! read Whitman and Pound and Eliot, read Neruda and Borges and Vallejo, read Victor Hugo, for God’s sake, and Tolstoy, and proudly I cried myself hoarse in the desert, but my vociferations and on occasions my howling could only be heard by those who were able to scratch the surface of my writings with the nails of their index fingers, and they were not many, but enough for me, and life went on and on and on, like a necklace of rice grains, on each grain of which a landscape had been painted, tiny grains and microscopic landscapes, and I knew that everyone was putting that necklace on and wearing it, but no one had the patience or the strength or the courage to take it off and look at it closely and decipher each landscape grain by grain, partly because to do so required the vision of a lynx or an eagle, and partly because the landscapes usually turned out to contain unpleasant surprises like coffins, makeshift cemeteries, ghost towns, the void and the horror, the smallness of being and its ridiculous will, people watching television, people going to football matches, boredom navigating the Chilean imagination like an enormous aircraft carrier. And that’s the truth. We were bored. We intellectuals. Because you can't read all day and all night. You can't write all day and all night. Splendid isolation has never been our style..." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599596-a-nd-the-wizened-youth-trembles-more-and-more-violently-wrinkles</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2012 10:09:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599596-a-nd-the-wizened-youth-trembles-more-and-more-violently-wrinkles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[A]nd the wizened youth trembles more and more violently, wrinkles his nose and then pounces on the story. But only I know the story, the real story. And it is simple and cruel and true and it should make us laugh, it should make us die laughing. But we only know how to cry, the only thing we do wholeheartedly is cry." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626822-she-was-a-triumph-over-ugliness-so-often-more-beguiling</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 06:11:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626822-she-was-a-triumph-over-ugliness-so-often-more-beguiling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a triumph over ugliness, so often more beguiling than real beauty, if only because it contains paradox." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
