<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/761642-vibhati-kulkarny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/761642-vibhati-kulkarny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 09:07:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 09:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 09:16:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8238-he-dug-so-deeply-into-her-sentiments-that-in-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He dug so deeply into her sentiments that in search of interest he found love, because by trying to make her love him he ended up falling in love with her. Petra Cotes, for her part, loved him more and more as she felt his love increasing, and that was how in the ripeness of autumn she began to believe once more in the youthful superstition that poverty was the servitude of love. Both looked back then on the wild revelry, the gaudy wealth, and the unbridled fornication as an annoyance and they lamented that it had cost them so much of their lives to find the paradise of shared solitude. Madly in love after so many years of sterile complicity, they enjoyed the miracle of living each other as much at the table as in bed, and they grew to be so happy that even when they were two worn-out people they kept on blooming like little children and playing together like dogs." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7204-there-is-no-innocence-more-dangerous-than-the-innocence-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 09:16:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7204-there-is-no-innocence-more-dangerous-than-the-innocence-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There [is] no innocence more dangerous than the innocence of age." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2008 09:42:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion makes a person stop eating, sleeping, working, feeling at peace. A lot of people are frightened because, when it appears, it demolishes all the old things it finds in its path. 

No one wants their life thrown into chaos. That is why a lot of people keep that threat under control, and are somehow capable of sustaining a house or a structure that is already rotten. They are the engineers of the superseded. 

Other people think exactly the opposite: they surrender themselves without a second thought, hoping to find in passion the solutions to all their problems. They make the other person responsible for their happiness and blame them for their possible unhappiness. They are either euphoric because something marvelous has happened or depressed because something unexpected has just ruined everything. 

Keeping passion at bay or surrendering blindly to it - which of these two attitudes is the least destructive? 

I don't know." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2009 16:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2008 07:17:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane, be still; don't struggle so like a wild, frantic bird, that is rending its own plumage in its desperation.&quot;
&quot;I am no bird; and no net ensnares me; I am a free human being, with an independent will; which I now exert to leave you." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11478-but-he-does-insist-on-a-conversation-goddamn-it-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 22:11:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vibhati add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11478-but-he-does-insist-on-a-conversation-goddamn-it-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But he does insist on a conversation.  Goddamn it!  Why can't people just do what I want them to do and be gone?  It's a worldwide conspiracy to make me be polite when I don't want to be." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
