<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/76191-unperspicacious]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/76191-unperspicacious" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 21:26:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397325-the-easiest-way-to-solve-a-problem-is-to-deny</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 21:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397325-the-easiest-way-to-solve-a-problem-is-to-deny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The easiest way to solve a problem is to deny it exists." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564951-only-on-rare-occasions-was-the-calendar-the-basis-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 01:37:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Patricia Lim Pui Huen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/564951-only-on-rare-occasions-was-the-calendar-the-basis-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only on rare occasions was the calendar the basis of the chronology. More often than not, the narrator's sense of time is based on an internal time clock in which age and important milestones in their lives were the most common measures." -- Patricia Lim Pui Huen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/784374-in-effect-historians-abolished-poverty-by-the-simple-device-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 09:34:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Antony G. Hopkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/784374-in-effect-historians-abolished-poverty-by-the-simple-device-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In effect, historians abolished poverty by the simple device of taking it off the agenda." -- Antony G. Hopkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439206-there-are-worse-things-than-having-behaved-foolishly-in-public</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 21:00:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Fleur Adcock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439206-there-are-worse-things-than-having-behaved-foolishly-in-public]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are worse things than having behaved foolishly in public.
There are worse things than these miniature betrayals,
committed or endured or suspected; there are worse things
than not being able to sleep for thinking about them.
It is 5 a.m. All the worse things come stalking in
and stand icily about the bed looking worse and worse and worse." -- Fleur Adcock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 03:12:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22263-there-is-only-one-way-to-read-which-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one way to read, which is to browse in libraries and bookshops, picking up books that attract you, reading only those, dropping them when they bore you, skipping the parts that drag-and never, never reading anything because you feel you ought, or because it is part of a trend or a movement.  Remember that the book which bores you when you are twenty or thirty will open doors for you when you are forty or fifty-and vise versa.  Don’t read a book out of its right time for you.  " -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009742-the-all-pervading-disease-of-the-modern-world-is-the-total</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 04:34:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by E.F. Schumacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009742-the-all-pervading-disease-of-the-modern-world-is-the-total]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The all-pervading disease of the modern world is the total imbalance between city and countryside, an imbalance in terms of wealth, power, culture, attraction and hope. The former has become over-extended and the latter has atrophied. The city has become the universal magnet, while rural life has lost its savour. Yet it remains an unalterable truth that, just as a sound mind depends on a sound body, so the health of the cities depends on the health of the rural areas. The cities, with all their wealth, are merely secondary producers, while primary production, the precondition of all economic life, takes place in the countryside. The prevailing lack of balance, based on the age-old exploitation of countryman and raw material producer, today threatens all countries throughout the world, the rich even more than the poor. To restore a proper balance between city and rural life is perhaps the greatest task in front of modern man." -- E.F. Schumacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1130779-now-these-delightful-infants-are-born-haphazardly-of-any-mating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 03:18:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[unperspicacious add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1130779-now-these-delightful-infants-are-born-haphazardly-of-any-mating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now these delightful infants are born haphazardly of any mating, any parents, treated well or ill as chance dictates, dying as easily as they are born, and dying anyway so soon after they are born - and yet in each child, every one, has all the potentiality, has it still, and completely, to leap from his low half-animal state to true humanity. Each one of them with this potential, and yet so few can be reached, to make the leap." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
