<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762235-marcus]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762235-marcus" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 19:22:48 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 19:22:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love mankind, he said, &quot;but I find to my amazement that the more I love mankind as a whole, the less I love man in particular." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15194-nothing-has-ever-been-more-insupportable-for-a-man-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 19:23:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15194-nothing-has-ever-been-more-insupportable-for-a-man-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing has ever been more insupportable for a man and a human society than freedom.
–The Grand Inquisitor" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169580-strange-that-men-from-age-to-age-should-consent-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 10:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William Godwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169580-strange-that-men-from-age-to-age-should-consent-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strange that men, from age to age, should consent to hold their lives at the breath of another, merely that each in his turn may have a power of acting the tyrant according to the law! Oh, God! give me poverty! Shower upon me all the imaginary hardships of human life! I will receive them with all thankfulness. Turn me a prey to the wild beasts of the desert, so I be never again the victim of man, dressed in the gore-dripping robes of authority! Suffer me at least to call life, the pursuits of life, my own! Let me hold it at the mercy of the elements, of the hunger of the beasts, or the revenge of barbarians, but not of the cold-blooded prudence of monopolists and kings!" -- William Godwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256452-it-s-a-mystery-a-man-s-at-odds-to-know-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 11:18:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256452-it-s-a-mystery-a-man-s-at-odds-to-know-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a mystery. A man's at odds to know his mind cause his mind is aught he has to know it with. He can know his heart, but he dont want to. Rightly so. Best not to look in there. It aint the heart of a creature that is bound in the way that God has set for it. You can find meanness in the least of creatures, but when God made man the devil was at his elbow. A creature that can do anything. Make a machine. And a machine to make the machine. And evil that can run itself a thousand years, no need to tend it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 22:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who believes that the secrets of the world are forever hidden lives in mystery and fear. Superstitiion will drag him down. The rain will erode the deeds of his life. But that man who sets himself the task of singling out the thread of order from the tapestry will by the decision alone have taken charge of the world and it is only by such taking charge that he will effect a way to dictate the terms of his own fate. 

I dont see what that has to do with catchin birds. 

The freedom of birds is an insult to me. I'd have them all in zoos. 

That would be a hell of a zoo. 

The judge smiled. Yes, he said. Even so." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11551-if-he-failed-the-first-time-he-took-his-driver-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 22:01:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11551-if-he-failed-the-first-time-he-took-his-driver-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...If he failed the first time he took his driver's licence test, it was mainly because he started an argument with the examiner in an ill-timed effort to prove that nothing could be more humiliating to a rational creature than being required to encourage the development of a base conditional reflex by stopping at a red light when there was not an earthly soul around, heeled or wheeled. He was more circumspect the next time, and passed..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 13:36:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155686-a-raznochinets-needs-no-memory-it-is-enough-for-him-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A  raznochinets needs no memory—it is enough for him to tell of the books he has read, and his biography is done." -- Osip Mandelstam]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385330-as-many-truths-as-men-occasionally-i-glimpse-a-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 08:01:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385330-as-many-truths-as-men-occasionally-i-glimpse-a-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As many truths as men.  Occasionally, I glimpse a truer Truth, hiding in imperfect simulacrums of itself, but as I approach, it bestirs itself &amp; moves deeper into the thorny swamp of dissent." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449483-everybody-who-flashed-the-signs-of-loyalty-he-took-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 15:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449483-everybody-who-flashed-the-signs-of-loyalty-he-took-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody who flashed the signs of loyalty he took to be loyal. Everybody who flashed the signs of intelligence he took to be intelligent. And so he had failed to see into his daughter, failed to see into his wife, failed to see into his one and only mistress—probably had never even begun to see into himself" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470699-anna-woke-with-the-wonderful-feeling-bad-sleepers-have-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 20:18:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by James Meek]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470699-anna-woke-with-the-wonderful-feeling-bad-sleepers-have-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anna woke with the wonderful feeling bad sleepers have when they know they have slept well. As if they have stolen something and got away with it. At these times the memories of what led up to such deep sleep keep their distance for a few seconds and those few seconds are perhaps the only time the world can ever be said to show mercy." -- James Meek]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70851-the-greatest-danger-that-besets-us-does-not-come-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 14:40:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Chris Hedges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70851-the-greatest-danger-that-besets-us-does-not-come-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest danger that besets us does not come from believers or atheists; it comes from those who, under the guise of religion, science or reason, imagine that we can free ourselves from the limitations of human nature and perfect the human species." -- Chris Hedges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48975-may-blessings-be-upon-the-head-of-cadmus-the-phoenicians</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 15:17:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48975-may-blessings-be-upon-the-head-of-cadmus-the-phoenicians]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May blessings be upon the head of Cadmus, the Phoenicians, or whoever it was that invented books." -- Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813091-through-art-alone-are-we-able-to-emerge-from-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 14:53:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813091-through-art-alone-are-we-able-to-emerge-from-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through art alone are we able to emerge from ourselves, to know what another person sees of a universe which is not the same as our own and of which, without art, the landscapes would remain as unknown to us as those that may exist on the moon. Thanks to art, instead of seeing one world only, our own, we see that world multiply itself and we have at our disposal as many worlds as there are original artists, worlds more different one from the other than those which revolve in infinite space, worlds which, centuries after the extinction of the fire from which their light first emanated, whether it is called Rembrandt or Vermeer, send us still each one its special radiance." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
