<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762842-catherine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762842-catherine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 13:10:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2014 13:10:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Brenda Ueland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact that is why the lives of most women are so vaguely unsatisfactory. They are always doing secondary and menial things (that do not require all their gifts and ability) for others and never anything for themselves. Society and husbands praise them for it (when they get too miserable or have nervous breakdowns) though always a little perplexedly and half-heartedly and just to be consoling. The poor wives are reminded that that is just why wives are so splendid -- because they are so unselfish and self-sacrificing and that is the wonderful thing about them! But inwardly women know that something is wrong. They sense that if you are always doing something for others, like a servant or nurse, and never anything for yourself, you cannot do others any good. You make them physically more comfortable. But you cannot affect them spiritually in any way at all. For to teach, encourage, cheer up, console, amuse, stimulate or advise a husband or children or friends, you have to be something yourself. [...]&quot;If you would shut your door against the children for an hour a day and say; 'Mother is working on her five-act tragedy in blank verse!' you would be surprised how they would respect you. They would probably all become playwrights." -- Brenda Ueland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8031-it-is-jesus-that-you-seek-when-you-dream-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 17:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Pope John Paul II]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8031-it-is-jesus-that-you-seek-when-you-dream-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is Jesus that you seek when you dream of happiness; He is waiting for you when nothing else you find satisfies you; He is the beauty to which you are so attracted; it is He who provoked you with that thirst for fullness that will not let you settle for compromise; it is He who urges you to shed the masks of a false life; it is He who reads in your heart your most genuine choices, the choices that others try to stifle.

It is Jesus who stirs in you the desire to do something great with your lives, the will to follow an ideal, the refusal to allow yourselves to be ground down by mediocrity, the courage to commit yourselves humbly and patiently to improving yourselves and society, making the world more human and more fraternal." -- Pope John Paul II]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
