<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762863-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/762863-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:17:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355363-one-of-the-painful-things-about-our-time-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 15:17:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/355363-one-of-the-painful-things-about-our-time-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the painful things about our time is that those who feel certainty are stupid, and those with any imagination and understanding are filled with doubt and indecision." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40797-but-i-don-t-want-comfort-i-want-god-i-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 10:17:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40797-but-i-don-t-want-comfort-i-want-god-i-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don't want comfort. I want God, I want poetry, I want real danger, I want freedom, I want goodness. I want sin." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107768-i-have-a-lot-of-faith-but-i-am-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 00:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107768-i-have-a-lot-of-faith-but-i-am-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a lot of faith. But I am also afraid a lot, and have no real certainty about anything.  I remembered something Father Tom had told me--that the opposite of faith is not doubt, but certainty.  Certainty is missing the point entirely.  Faith includes noticing the mess, the emptiness and discomfort, and letting it be there until some light returns." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 15:36:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142203-have-you-ever-found-god-in-church-i-never-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 17:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142203-have-you-ever-found-god-in-church-i-never-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...have you ever found God in church? I never did. I just found a bunch of folks hoping for him to show. Any God I ever felt in church I brought in with me. And I think all the other folks did too. They come to church to share God, not find God." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63047-forgiving-and-being-reconciled-to-our-enemies-or-our-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 11:12:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Desmond Tutu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63047-forgiving-and-being-reconciled-to-our-enemies-or-our-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgiving and being reconciled to our enemies or our loved ones are not about pretending that things are other than they are. It is not about patting one another on the back and turning a blind eye to the wrong. True reconciliation exposes the awfulness, the abuse, the hurt, the truth. It could even sometimes make things worse. It is a risky undertaking but in the end it is worthwhile, because in the end only an honest confrontation with reality can bring real healing. Superficial reconciliation can bring only superficial healing." -- Desmond Tutu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119954-wounding-and-healing-are-not-opposites-they-re-part-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 11:55:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Rachel Naomi Remen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119954-wounding-and-healing-are-not-opposites-they-re-part-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wounding and healing are not opposites.  They're part of the same thing. It is our wounds that enable us to be compassionate with the wounds of others.  It is our limitations that make us kind to the limitations of other people.  It is our loneliness that helps us to to find other people or to even know they're alone with an illness. I think I have served people perfectly with parts of myself I used to be ashamed of. " -- Rachel Naomi Remen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126649-compassion-is-the-sometimes-fatal-capacity-for-feeling-what-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2012 07:44:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126649-compassion-is-the-sometimes-fatal-capacity-for-feeling-what-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is the sometimes fatal capacity for feeling what it is like to live inside somebody else's skin. It's the knowledge that there can never really be any peace and joy for me until there is peace and joy finally for you too. " -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399469-the-world-is-a-hellish-place-and-bad-writing-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 14:01:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399469-the-world-is-a-hellish-place-and-bad-writing-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is a hellish place, and bad writing is destroying the quality of our suffering." -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706272-perhaps-your-hunger-to-belong-is-always-active-and-intense</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 22:00:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by John O'Donohue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706272-perhaps-your-hunger-to-belong-is-always-active-and-intense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps your hunger to belong is always active and intense because you belonged so totally before you came here. This hunger to belong is the echo and reverberation of your invisible heritage. You are from somewhere else, where you were known, embraced and sheltered. This is also the secret root from which all longing grows. Something in you knows, perhaps remembers, that eternal belonging liberates longing into its surest and most potent creativity. This is why your longing is often wiser than your conventional sense of appropriateness, safety and truth... Your longing desires to take you towards the absolute realization of all the possibilities that sleep in the clay of your heart; it knows your eternal potential, and it will not rest until it is awakened." -- John O'Donohue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94025-one-of-the-tasks-of-true-friendship-is-to-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2013 16:34:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by John O'Donohue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94025-one-of-the-tasks-of-true-friendship-is-to-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the tasks of true friendship is to listen compassionately and creatively to the hidden silences. Often secrets are not revealed in words, they lie concealed in the silence between the words or in the depth of what is unsayable between two people." -- John O'Donohue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16300-our-scientific-power-has-outrun-our-spiritual-power-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 13:51:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16300-our-scientific-power-has-outrun-our-spiritual-power-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our scientific power has outrun our spiritual power. We have guided missiles and misguided men." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6188-the-day-we-see-the-truth-and-cease-to-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 13:58:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6188-the-day-we-see-the-truth-and-cease-to-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The day we see the truth and cease to speak is the day we begin to die" -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612901-everywhere-i-ve-turned-somebody-has-wanted-to-sacrifice-me-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 12:51:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612901-everywhere-i-ve-turned-somebody-has-wanted-to-sacrifice-me-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everywhere I've turned somebody has wanted to sacrifice me for my own good—only /they/ were the ones who benefited. And now we start on the old sacrificial merry-go-round. At what point do we stop?" -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31777-it-goes-a-long-way-back-some-twenty-years-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 12:55:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Ralph Ellison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31777-it-goes-a-long-way-back-some-twenty-years-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It goes a long way back, some twenty years.  All my life I had been looking for something, and everywhere I turned someone tried to tell me what it was.  I accepted their answers too, though they were often in contradiction and even self-contradictory.  I was naive.  I was looking for myself and asking everyone except myself questions which  I, and only I, could answer.  It took me a long time and much painful boomeranging of my expectations to achieve a realization everyone else appears to have been born with: That I am nobody but myself.  But first I had to discover that I am an invisible man!" -- Ralph Ellison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63341-the-witch-would-have-known-that-when-a-willing-victim</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 12:59:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63341-the-witch-would-have-known-that-when-a-willing-victim]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[The witch] would have known that when a willing victim who had committed no treachery was killed in a traitor’s stead, the Table would crack and Death itself would start working backwards." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71556-i-do-what-i-do-without-hope-of-reward-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2013 15:50:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71556-i-do-what-i-do-without-hope-of-reward-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do what I do without hope of reward or fear of punishment. I do not require Heaven or Hell to bribe or scare me into acting decently." -- Mary Doria Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622958-first-of-all-you-have-to-keep-unmasking-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 10:19:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622958-first-of-all-you-have-to-keep-unmasking-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, you have to keep unmasking the world about you for what it is: manipulative, controlling, power-hungry, and, in the long run, destructive. The world tells you many lies about who you are, and you simply have to be realistic enough to remind yourself of this. Every time you feel hurt, offended, or rejected, you have to dare to say to yourself: 'These feelings, strong as they may be, are not telling me the truth about myself. The truth, even though I cannot feel it right now, is that I am the chosen child of God, precious in God's eyes, called the Beloved from all eternity, and held safe in an everlasting belief." -- Henri J.M. Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
