<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/763931-marcus-lira]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/763931-marcus-lira" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118614-damn-the-absolute</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118614-damn-the-absolute]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Damn the Absolute!" -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332864-science-is-essentially-an-anarchic-enterprise-theoretical-anarchism-is-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Paul Karl Feyerabend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332864-science-is-essentially-an-anarchic-enterprise-theoretical-anarchism-is-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is essentially an anarchic enterprise: theoretical anarchism is more humanitarian and more likely to encourage progress than its law-and-order alternatives." -- Paul Karl Feyerabend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12068-you-see-gentlemen-reason-is-an-excellent-thing-there-s-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12068-you-see-gentlemen-reason-is-an-excellent-thing-there-s-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, gentlemen, reason is an excellent thing, there’s no disputing that, but reason is nothing but reason and satisfies only the rational side of man’s nature, while will is a manifestation of the whole life, that is, of the whole human life including reason and all the impulses. And although our life, in this manifestation of it, is often worthless, yet it is life and not simply extracting square roots." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11999-i-am-my-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11999-i-am-my-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am my world." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12066-reason-is-and-ought-only-to-be-the-slave-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by David Hume]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12066-reason-is-and-ought-only-to-be-the-slave-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reason is, and ought only to be the slave of the passions." -- David Hume]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7124-what-is-to-be-done-with-the-millions-of-facts</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 10:49:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7124-what-is-to-be-done-with-the-millions-of-facts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is to be done with the millions of facts that bear witness that men, consciously, that is fully understanding their real interests, have left them in the background and have rushed headlong on another path, to meet peril and danger, compelled to this course by nobody and by nothing, but, as it were, simply disliking the beaten track, and have obstinately, wilfully, struck out another difficult, absurd way, seeking it almost in the darkness. So, I suppose, this obstinacy and perversity were pleasanter to them than any advantage...

The fact is, gentlemen, it seems there must really exist something that is dearer to almost every man than his greatest advantages, or (not to be illogical) there is a most advantageous advantage (the very one omitted of which we spoke just now) which is more important and more advantageous than all other advantages, for the sake of which a man if necessary is ready to act in opposition to all laws; that is, in opposition to reason, honour, peace, prosperity -- in fact, in opposition to all those excellent and useful things if only he can attain that fundamental, most advantageous advantage which is dearer to him than all. &quot;Yes, but it's advantage all the same,&quot; you will retort. But excuse me, I'll make the point clear, and it is not a case of playing upon words. What matters is, that this advantage is remarkable from the very fact that it breaks down all our classifications, and continually shatters every system constructed by lovers of mankind for the benefit of mankind. In fact, it upsets everything...

One's own free unfettered choice, one's own caprice, however wild it may be, one's own fancy worked up at times to frenzy -- is that very &quot;most advantageous advantage&quot; which we have overlooked, which comes under no classification and against which all systems and theories are continually being shattered to atoms. And how do these wiseacres know that man wants a normal, a virtuous choice? What has made them conceive that man must want a rationally advantageous choice? What man wants is simply independent choice, whatever that independence may cost and wherever it may lead. And choice, of course, the devil only knows what choice.

Of course, this very stupid thing, this caprice of ours, may be in reality, gentlemen, more advantageous for us than anything else on earth, especially in certain cases… for in any circumstances it preserves for us what is most precious and most important -- that is, our personality, our individuality. Some, you see, maintain that this really is the most precious thing for mankind; choice can, of course, if it chooses, be in agreement with reason… It is profitable and sometimes even praiseworthy. But very often, and even most often, choice is utterly and stubbornly opposed to reason ... and ... and ... do you know that that, too, is profitable, sometimes even praiseworthy?

I believe in it, I answer for it, for the whole work of man really seems to consist in nothing but proving to himself every minute that he is a man and not a piano-key! …And this being so, can one help being tempted to rejoice that it has not yet come off, and that desire still depends on something we don't know?

You will scream at me (that is, if you condescend to do so) that no one is touching my free will, that all they are concerned with is that my will should of itself, of its own free will, coincide with my own normal interests, with the laws of nature and arithmetic. Good heavens, gentlemen, what sort of free will is left when we come to tabulation and arithmetic, when it will all be a case of twice two make four? Twice two makes four without my will. As if free will meant that!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421792-progress-has-always-been-achieved-by-probing-well-entrenched-and-well-founded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Paul Karl Feyerabend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/421792-progress-has-always-been-achieved-by-probing-well-entrenched-and-well-founded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Progress has always been achieved by probing well-entrenched and well-founded forms of life with unpopular and unfounded values. This is how man gradually freed himself from fear and from the tyranny of unexamined systems." -- Paul Karl Feyerabend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12577-the-limits-of-my-language-means-the-limits-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12577-the-limits-of-my-language-means-the-limits-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The limits of my language means the limits of my world." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28304-if-there-s-any-interaction-between-genes-and-languages-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Luigi Luca Cavalli-Sforza]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28304-if-there-s-any-interaction-between-genes-and-languages-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's any interaction between genes and languages, it is often languages that influence genes, since linguistic differences between populations lessen the chance of genetic exchange between them." -- Luigi Luca Cavalli-Sforza]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28308-it-may-be-worth-while-to-illustrate-this-view-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Charles Darwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28308-it-may-be-worth-while-to-illustrate-this-view-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be worth while to illustrate this view of classification, by taking the case of languages. If we possessed a perfect pedigree of mankind, a genealogical arrangement of the races of man would afford the best classification of the various languages now spoken throughout the world; and if all extinct languages, and all intermediate and slowly changing dialects, were to be included, such an arrangement would be the only possible one. Yet it might be that some ancient languages had altered very little and had given rise to few new languages, whilst others had altered much owing to the spreading, isolation, and state of civilisation of the several co-descended races, and had thus given rise to many new dialects and languages. The various degrees of difference between the languages of the same stock, would have to be expressed by groups subordinate to groups; but the proper or even the only possible arrangement would still be genealogical; and this would be strictly natural, as it would connect together all languages, extinct and recent, by the closest affinities, and would give the filiation and origin of each tongue." -- Charles Darwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17716-human-beings-by-changing-the-inner-attitudes-of-their-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17716-human-beings-by-changing-the-inner-attitudes-of-their-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings, by changing the inner attitudes of their minds, can change the outer aspects of their lives." -- William James ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113128-wherever-you-are-it-is-your-friends-who-make-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:21:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113128-wherever-you-are-it-is-your-friends-who-make-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever you are, it is your friends who make your world." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7168-there-are-no-differences-but-differences-of-degree-between-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7168-there-are-no-differences-but-differences-of-degree-between-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no differences but differences of degree between different degrees of difference and no difference." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17434-the-invisible-and-the-non-existent-look-very-much-alike</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Delos Banning McKown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17434-the-invisible-and-the-non-existent-look-very-much-alike]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The invisible and the non-existent look very much alike." -- Delos Banning McKown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life can only be understood backwards; but it must be lived forwards." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84486-there-are-causes-worth-dying-for-but-none-worth-killing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84486-there-are-causes-worth-dying-for-but-none-worth-killing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are causes worth dying for, but none worth killing for." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217072-love-is-linked-to-the-fact-that-in-the-end</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Renata Salecl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217072-love-is-linked-to-the-fact-that-in-the-end]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is linked to the fact that in the end we know nothing about the object
that attracts us in the Other, and that at the same time the Other knows nothing
about this object that is in him more than himself, i.e. what makes someone
attracted to him." -- Renata Salecl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12863-i-can-only-note-that-the-past-is-beautiful-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can only note that the past is beautiful because one never realises an emotion at the time. It expands later, and thus we don't have complete emotions about the present, only about the past." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Irvine Welsh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40826-society-invents-a-spurious-convoluted-logic-tae-absorb-and-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Society invents a spurious convoluted logic tae absorb and change people whae's behaviour is outside its mainstream. Suppose that ah ken aw the pros and cons, know that ah'm gaunnae huv a short life, am ah sound mind, ectetera, ectetera, but still want tae use smack? They won't let ye dae it. They won't let ye dae it, because it's seen as a sign ay thir ain failure. The fact that ye jist simply choose tae reject whut they huv tae offer. Choose us. Choose life. Choose mortgage payments; choose washing machines; choose cars; choose sitting oan a couch watching mind-numbing and spirit-crushing game shows, stuffing fuckin junk food intae yir mooth. Choose rotting away, pishing and shiteing yersel in a home, a total fuckin embarrassment tae the selfish, fucked-up brats ye've produced. Choose life. Well, ah choose no tae choose life. If the cunts cannae handle that, it's thair fuckin problem. As Harry Launder sais, ah jist intend tae keep right on to the end of the road..." -- Irvine Welsh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333372-good-humor-is-a-philosophic-state-of-mind-it-seems-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333372-good-humor-is-a-philosophic-state-of-mind-it-seems-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good-humor is a philosophic state of mind; it seems to say to Nature that we take her no more seriously than she takes us. I maintain that one should always talk of philosophy with a smile." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333847-nonetheless-it-still-remains-true-that-as-a-set-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Sidney Hook]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333847-nonetheless-it-still-remains-true-that-as-a-set-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nonetheless, it still remains true that as a set of cognitive beliefs, religious doctrines constitute a speculative hypothesis of an extremely low order of probability." -- Sidney Hook]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4708-i-think-it-s-perfectly-possible-to-explain-how-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4708-i-think-it-s-perfectly-possible-to-explain-how-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it's perfectly possible to explain how the universe came about without bringing God into it, but I don't know everything, and there may well be a God somewhere, hiding away. Actually, if he is keeping out of sight, it's because he's ashamed of his followers and all the cruelty and ignorance they're responsible for promoting in his name. If I were him, I'd want nothing to do with them." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338148-the-ultimate-source-is-probably-the-tendency-in-some-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338148-the-ultimate-source-is-probably-the-tendency-in-some-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ultimate source is probably the tendency in some of us, part of our psychological inheritance from our far-distant ancestors, the tendency to look for extreme solutions, absolute truths, abstract answers. All fanatics and fundamentalists share this tendency, which is so alien and unpleasing to the rest of us. The theory says they must do such-and-such, so they do it, never mind the human consequences, never mind the social cost, never mind the terrible damage to the fabric of everything decent and humane.

I’m afraid these fundamentalists of one sort or another will always be with us. We just have to keep them as far away as possible from the levers of power." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339831-see-the-exquisite-contrast-of-the-types-of-mind-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339831-see-the-exquisite-contrast-of-the-types-of-mind-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["See the exquisite contrast of the types of mind! The pragmatist clings to facts and concreteness, observes truth at its work in particular cases, and generalises. Truth, for him, becomes a class-name for all sorts of definite working-values in experience. For the rationalist it remains a pure abstraction, to the bare name of which we must defer. When the pragmatist undertakes to show in detail just why we must defer, the rationalist is unable to recognise the concretes from which his own abstraction is taken. He accuses us of denying truth; whereas we have only sought to trace exactly why people follow it and always ought to follow it. Your typical ultra-abstractions fairly shudders at concreteness: other things equal, he positively prefers the pale and spectral. If the two universes were offered, he would always choose the skinny outline rather than the rich thicket of reality. It is so much purer, clearer, nobler." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339869-i-would-cling-to-unhappiness-because-it-was-a-known</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Hugh Laurie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339869-i-would-cling-to-unhappiness-because-it-was-a-known]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would cling to unhappiness because it was a known, familiar state. When I was happier, it was because I knew I was on my way back to misery. I've never been convinced that happiness is the object of the game. I'm wary of happiness." -- Hugh Laurie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63485-common-sense-is-the-most-widely-shared-commodity-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Rene Descartes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63485-common-sense-is-the-most-widely-shared-commodity-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Common sense is the most widely shared commodity in the world, for every man is convinced that he is well supplied with it." -- Rene Descartes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392455-we-make-versions-and-true-versions-make-worlds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Nelson Goodman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392455-we-make-versions-and-true-versions-make-worlds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We make versions, and true versions make worlds." -- Nelson Goodman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187700-a-person-with-a-new-idea-is-a-crank-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187700-a-person-with-a-new-idea-is-a-crank-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person with a new idea is a crank until the idea succeeds." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405946-now-obviously-a-sentence-s-truth-even-when-we-hold-the-sentence-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:20:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by William G. Lycan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405946-now-obviously-a-sentence-s-truth-even-when-we-hold-the-sentence-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now (obviously) a sentence’s truth—even when we hold the sentence’s meaning fixed—depends on which world we are considering. “Brown is Prime Minister” is true in the actual world but, since Brown need not have been Prime Minister, there are countless worlds in which “Brown is Prime Minister” is false: in those worlds, Brown did not succeed Tony Blair, or never went into politics, or never even existed. And in some other worlds, someone else is Prime Minister — David Cameron, P. F. Strawson, me, Madonna, or Daffy Duck. In still others, there is no such office as Prime Minister, or not even a Britain; and so on and so forth. So a given sentence or proposition varies its truth-value from world to world." -- William G. Lycan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418647-both-quine-and-feyerabend-want-to-revise-a-version-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2011 20:19:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marcus add a quote by Ian Hacking]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418647-both-quine-and-feyerabend-want-to-revise-a-version-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both [Quine and Feyerabend] want to revise a version of positivism. Quine started with the Vienna Circle, and Feyerabend with the Copenhagen school of quantum mechanics. Both the Circle and the school have been called children of Ernst Mach; if so, the philosophies of Feyerabend and Quine must be his grandchildren." -- Ian Hacking]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
