<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/763913-lily]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/763913-lily" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 15:04:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 15:04:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don’t want to go among mad people,&quot; Alice remarked.
&quot;Oh, you can’t help that,&quot; said the Cat: &quot;we’re all mad here. I’m mad. You’re mad.&quot;
&quot;How do you know I’m mad?&quot; said Alice.
&quot;You must be,&quot; said the Cat, or you wouldn’t have come here." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 15:05:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164574-failing-and-flying-everyone-forgets-that-icarus-also-flew-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 16:24:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Jack Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164574-failing-and-flying-everyone-forgets-that-icarus-also-flew-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Failing and Flying

Everyone forgets that Icarus also flew.
It's the same when love comes to an end,
or the marriage fails and people say
they knew it was a mistake, that everybody
said it would never work. That she was 
old enough to know better. But anything
worth doing is worth doing badly.
Like being there by that summer ocean
on the other side of the island while
love was fading out of her, the stars 
burning so extravagantly those nights that
anyone could tell you they would never last.
Every morning she was asleep in my bed
like a visitation, the gentleness in her
like antelope standing in the dawn mist.
Each afternoon I watched her coming back
through the hot stony field after swimming,
the sea light behind her and the huge sky
on the other side of that. Listened to her
while we ate lunch. How can they say 
the marriage failed? Like the people who
came back from Provence (when it was Provence)
and said it was pretty but the food was greasy.
I believe Icarus was not failing as he fell,
but just coming to the end of his triumph." -- Jack Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84301-i-am-not-a-smart-man-particularly-but-one-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 13:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Wally Lamb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84301-i-am-not-a-smart-man-particularly-but-one-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not a smart man, particularly, but one day, at long last, I stumbled from the dark woods of my own, and my family's, and my country's past, holding in my hands these truths: that love grows from the rich loam of forgiveness; that mongrels make good dogs; that the evidence of God exists in the roundness of things. This much, at least, I've figured out. I know this much is true." -- Wally Lamb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216137-love-isn-t-something-natural-rather-it-requires-discipline-concentration-patience</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 13:15:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Fromm, Eric]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216137-love-isn-t-something-natural-rather-it-requires-discipline-concentration-patience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love isn't something natural. Rather it requires discipline, concentration, patience, faith, and the overcoming of narcissism. It isn't a feeling, it is a practice." -- Fromm, Eric]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209142-a-sense-of-life-meaning-ensues-but-cannot-be-deliberately</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 22:00:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Irvin D. Yalom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209142-a-sense-of-life-meaning-ensues-but-cannot-be-deliberately]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sense of life meaning ensues but cannot be deliberately pursued: life meaning is always a derivative phenomenon that materializes when we have transcended ourselves, when we have forgotten ourselves and become absorbed in someone (or something) outside ourselves" -- Irvin D. Yalom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 22:15:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18881-i-m-a-kind-of-paranoiac-in-reverse-i-suspect-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a kind of paranoiac in reverse. I suspect people of plotting to make me happy." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349410-you-are-imperfect-you-are-wired-for-struggle-but-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 18:54:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349410-you-are-imperfect-you-are-wired-for-struggle-but-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are imperfect, you are wired for struggle, but you are worthy of love and belonging." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364377-authenticity-is-a-collection-of-choices-that-we-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 18:55:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364377-authenticity-is-a-collection-of-choices-that-we-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Authenticity is a collection of choices that we have to make every day. It's about the choice to show up and be real. The choice to be honest. The choice to let our true selves be seen." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357565-owning-our-story-can-be-hard-but-not-nearly-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2011 17:36:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357565-owning-our-story-can-be-hard-but-not-nearly-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Owning our story can be hard but not nearly as difficult as spending our lives running from it. Embracing our vulnerabilities is risky but not nearly as dangerous as giving up on love and belonging and joy—the experiences that make us the most vulnerable. Only when we are brave enough to explore the darkness will we discover the infinite power of our light." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364371-if-we-share-our-shame-story-with-the-wrong-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2011 18:53:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364371-if-we-share-our-shame-story-with-the-wrong-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we share our shame story with the wrong person, they can easily become one more piece of flying debris in an already dangerous storm." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134607-i-m-a-perfectly-good-carrot-that-everyone-is-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 18:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Mary Pipher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134607-i-m-a-perfectly-good-carrot-that-everyone-is-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a perfectly good carrot that everyone is trying to turn into a rose. As a carrot, I have good color and a nice leafy top. When I'm carved into a rose, I turn brown and wither." -- Mary Pipher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62879-we-decided-that-sooner-or-later-you-had-to-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 19:00:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Melody Beattie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62879-we-decided-that-sooner-or-later-you-had-to-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We decided that sooner or later you had to learn to live without almost everybody, at least for a while.  Even people you didn't think you could live without.&quot;  p 167

love always found itself again." -- Melody Beattie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2011 10:39:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23327-that-s-one-of-the-reasons-i-never-wanted-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That’s one of the reasons I never wanted to get married. The last thing I wanted was infinite security and to be the place an arrow shoots off from. I wanted change and excitement and to shoot off in all directions myself, like the colored arrows from a Fourth of July rocket." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12852-drawing-on-my-fine-command-of-the-english-language-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 15:14:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Robert Benchley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12852-drawing-on-my-fine-command-of-the-english-language-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Drawing on my fine command of the English language, I said nothing." -- Robert Benchley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75652-peace-requires-us-to-surrender-our-illusions-of-control-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 10:57:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75652-peace-requires-us-to-surrender-our-illusions-of-control-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Peace requires us to surrender our illusions of control. We can love and care for others but we cannot possess our children, lovers, family, or friends. We can assist them, pray for them, and wish them well, yet in the end their happiness and suffering depend on their thoughts and actions, not on our wishes." -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77421-as-surely-as-there-is-a-voyage-away-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 18:50:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77421-as-surely-as-there-is-a-voyage-away-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As surely as there is a voyage away, there is a journey home." -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202404-the-most-beautiful-people-we-have-known-are-those-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2011 18:52:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Elisabeth Kübler-Ross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202404-the-most-beautiful-people-we-have-known-are-those-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most beautiful people we have known are those who have known defeat, known suffering, known struggle, known loss, and have found their way out of the depths. These persons have an appreciation, a sensitivity, and an understanding of life that fills them with compassion, gentleness, and a deep loving concern. Beautiful people do not just happen." -- Elisabeth Kübler-Ross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104698-people-are-like-stained-glass-windows-they-sparkle-and-shine-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 23:01:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Elizabeth Kubler Ross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104698-people-are-like-stained-glass-windows-they-sparkle-and-shine-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are like stained-glass windows. They sparkle and shine when the sun is out, but when the darkness sets in, their true beauty is revealed only if there is a light from within. " -- Elizabeth Kubler Ross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182676-he-had-learned-long-ago-that-in-general-the-easier</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 23:02:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Irvin D. Yalom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182676-he-had-learned-long-ago-that-in-general-the-easier]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had learned long ago that, in general, the easier it was for anxious patients to reach him, the less likely they were to call. (107)" -- Irvin D. Yalom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412517-the-dark-does-not-destroy-the-light-it-defines-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2011 23:07:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Brene Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/412517-the-dark-does-not-destroy-the-light-it-defines-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dark does not destroy the light; it defines it.  It's our fear of the dark that casts our joy into the shadows." -- Brene Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279230-without-awareness-we-are-not-truly-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 10:42:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by James F. T. Bugental]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279230-without-awareness-we-are-not-truly-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without awareness, we are not truly alive." -- James F. T. Bugental]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34888-the-secret-of-life-though-is-to-fall-seven-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 10:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34888-the-secret-of-life-though-is-to-fall-seven-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret of life, though, is to fall seven times and to get up eight times." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157912-the-alchemist-picked-up-a-book-that-someone-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 10:46:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157912-the-alchemist-picked-up-a-book-that-someone-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The alchemist picked up a book that someone in the caravan had brought. Leafing through the pages, he found a story about Narcissus.

The alchemist knew the legend of Narcissus, a youth who knelt daily beside a lake to contemplate his own beauty. He was so fascinated by himself that, one morning, he fell into the lake and drowned. At the spot where he fell, a flower was born, which was called the narcissus.

But this was not how the author of the book ended the story.

He said that when Narcissus died, the goddesses of the forest appeared and found the lake, which had been fresh water, transformed into a lake of salty tears.

'Why do you weep?' the goddesses asked.

'I weep for Narcissus,&quot; the lake replied.

'Ah, it is no surprise that you weep for Narcissus,' they said, 'for though we always pursued him in the forest, you alone could contemplate his beauty close at hand.'

'But... was Narcissus beautiful?' the lake asked.

'Who better than you to know that?' the goddesses asked in wonder. 'After all, it was by your banks that he knelt each day to contemplate himself!'

The lake was silent for some time. Finally, it said:

'I weep for Narcissus, but I never noticed that Narcissus was beautiful. I weep because, each time he knelt beside my banks, I could see, in the depths of his eyes, my own beauty reflected.'

'What a lovely story,' the alchemist thought." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 13:33:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71463-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-speak-with-integrity-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2011 13:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71463-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-speak-with-integrity-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["1. Be Impeccable With Your Word
Speak with integrity. Say only what you mean. Avoid using the word to speak against yourself or to gossip about others. Use the power of your word in the direction of truth and love. 

2. Don't Take Anything Personally
Nothing others do is because of you. What others say and do is a projection of their own reality, their own dream. When you are immune to the opinions and actions of others, you won't be the victim of needless suffering. 

3. Don't Make Assumptions
Find the courage to ask questions and to express what you really want. Communicate with others as clearly as you can to avoid misunderstandings, sadness and drama. With just this one agreement, you can completely transform your life. 

4. Always Do Your Best
Your best is going to change from moment to moment; it will be different when you are healthy as opposed to sick. Under any circumstance, simply do your best, and you will avoid self-judgment, self-abuse and regret." -- Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110038-i-think-it-pisses-god-off-if-you-walk-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 09:20:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110038-i-think-it-pisses-god-off-if-you-walk-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it pisses God off if you walk by the color purple in a field somewhere and don't notice it. People think pleasing God is all God cares about.  But any fool living in the world can see it always trying to please us back." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142203-have-you-ever-found-god-in-church-i-never-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 09:21:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142203-have-you-ever-found-god-in-church-i-never-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...have you ever found God in church? I never did. I just found a bunch of folks hoping for him to show. Any God I ever felt in church I brought in with me. And I think all the other folks did too. They come to church to share God, not find God." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87427-forgiveness-means-giving-up-all-hope-for-a-better-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 16:05:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Lily Tomlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87427-forgiveness-means-giving-up-all-hope-for-a-better-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgiveness means giving up all hope for a better past." -- Lily Tomlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66975-imagine-that-the-universe-is-a-great-spinning-engine-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 21:43:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66975-imagine-that-the-universe-is-a-great-spinning-engine-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine that the universe is a great spinning engine.  You want to stay near the core of the thing - right in the hub of the wheel - not out at the edges where all the wild whirling takes place, where you can get frayed and crazy.  The hub of calmness - that's your heart.  That's where God lives within you.  So stop looking for answers in the world.  Just keep coming back to that center and you'll always find peace." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
