<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764059-megan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764059-megan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 16:13:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 16:13:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1-the-story-so-far-in-the-beginning-the-universe-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story so far:
In the beginning the Universe was created.
This has made a lot of people very angry and been widely regarded as a bad move." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7143-remember-the-time-you-feel-lonely-is-the-time-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 17:05:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7143-remember-the-time-you-feel-lonely-is-the-time-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember: the time you feel lonely is the time you most need to be by yourself. Life's cruelest irony." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372993-but-i-think-the-first-real-change-in-women-s-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 05:36:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372993-but-i-think-the-first-real-change-in-women-s-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I think the first real change in women’s body image came when JLo turned it butt-style. That was the first time that having a large-scale situation in the back was part of mainstream American beauty. Girls wanted butts now. Men were free to admit that they had always enjoyed them. And then, what felt like moments later, boom—Beyoncé brought the leg meat. A back porch and thick muscular legs were now widely admired. And from that day forward, women embraced their diversity and realized that all shapes and sizes are beautiful. Ah ha ha. No. I’m totally messing with you. All Beyonce and JLo have done is add to the laundry list of attributes women must have to qualify as beautiful. Now every girl is expected to have Caucasian blue eyes, full Spanish lips, a classic button nose, hairless Asian skin with a California tan, a Jamaican dance hall ass, long Swedish legs, small Japanese feet, the abs of a lesbian gym owner, the hips of a nine-year-old boy, the arms of Michelle Obama, and doll tits. The person closest to actually achieving this look is Kim Kardashian, who, as we know, was made by Russian scientists to sabotage our athletes." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162101-hey-said-shadow-huginn-or-muninn-or-whoever-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 12:49:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162101-hey-said-shadow-huginn-or-muninn-or-whoever-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hey,&quot; said Shadow. &quot;Huginn or Muninn, or whoever you are.&quot; 
The bird turned, head tipped, suspiciously, on one side, and it stared at him with bright eyes.
&quot;Say 'Nevermore,'&quot; said Shadow.
&quot;Fuck you,&quot; said the raven." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284329-then-as-he-had-kept-watch-sam-had-noticed-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 09:36:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284329-then-as-he-had-kept-watch-sam-had-noticed-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then as he had kept watch Sam had noticed that at times a light seemed to be shining faintly within; but now the light was even clearer and stronger. Frodo's face was peaceful, the marks of fear and care had left it; but it looked old, old and beautiful, as if the chiseling of the shaping years was now revealed in many fine lines that had before been hidden, though the identity of the face was not changed. Not that Sam Gamgee put it that way to himself. He shook his head, as if finding words useless, and murmured: &quot;I love him. He's like that, and sometimes it shines through, somehow. But I love him, whether or no." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 05:41:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope that in this year to come, you make mistakes. Because if you are making mistakes...you're Doing Something." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
