<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764215-dave]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764215-dave" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:04:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12803-a-long-habit-of-not-thinking-a-thing-wrong-gives</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 12:04:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Thomas Paine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12803-a-long-habit-of-not-thinking-a-thing-wrong-gives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A long habit of not thinking a thing wrong, gives it a superficial appearance of being right, and raises at first a formidable outcry in defense of custom. But the tumult soon subsides. Time makes more converts than reason." -- Thomas Paine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14537-civilization-in-fact-grows-more-maudlin-and-hysterical-especially-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by H.L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14537-civilization-in-fact-grows-more-maudlin-and-hysterical-especially-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Civilization, in fact, grows more maudlin and hysterical; especially under democracy it tends to degenerate into a mere combat of crazes; the whole aim of practical politics is to keep the populace alarmed (and hence clamorous to be led to safety) by an endless series of hobgoblins, most of them imaginary.  Wars are no longer waged by the will of superior men, capable of judging dispassionately and intelligently the causes behind them and the effects flowing out of them.  The are now begun by first throwing a mob into a panic; they are ended only when it has spent its ferine fury." -- H.L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31549-every-normal-man-must-be-tempted-at-times-to-spit</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by H.L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31549-every-normal-man-must-be-tempted-at-times-to-spit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every normal man must be tempted, at times, to spit on his hands, hoist the black flag, and begin slitting throats." -- H.L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23454-and-i-said-to-myself-that-s-true-hope-needs-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Yehuda Amichai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23454-and-i-said-to-myself-that-s-true-hope-needs-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I said to myself: That's true, hope needs to be
like barbed wire to keep out despair,
hope must be a mine field." -- Yehuda Amichai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The absence of the will to live is, alas, not sufficient to make one want to die." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36304-often-we-ask-ourselves-to-make-absolute-sense-out-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Tony Hoagland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36304-often-we-ask-ourselves-to-make-absolute-sense-out-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often we ask ourselves
to make absolute sense
out of what just happens,
and in this way, what we are practicing

is suffering,
which everybody practices,
but strangely few of us
grow graceful in." -- Tony Hoagland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 21:22:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face—for ever." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284795-the-world-i-live-in-is-loathsome-to-me-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 20:07:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284795-the-world-i-live-in-is-loathsome-to-me-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world I live in is loathsome to me, but I feel one with the men who suffer in it" -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132945-the-writer-can-grow-as-a-person-or-he-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 12:43:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Norman Mailer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132945-the-writer-can-grow-as-a-person-or-he-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer can grow as a person or he can shrink. ... His curiosity, his reaction to life must not diminish. The fatal thing is to shrink, to be interested in less, sympathetic to less, desiccating to the point where life itself loses its flavor, and one’s passion for human understanding changes to weariness and distaste." -- Norman Mailer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82610-i-would-say-that-the-thrust-of-my-life-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 11:53:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by ram dass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82610-i-would-say-that-the-thrust-of-my-life-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would say that the thrust of my life has been initially about getting free, and then realizing that my freedom is not independent of everybody else. Then I am arriving at that circle where one works on oneself as a gift to other people so that one doesn't create more suffering. I help people as a work on myself and I work on myself to help people." -- ram dass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82624-the-dance-goes-from-realizing-that-you-re-separate-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 11:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by ram dass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82624-the-dance-goes-from-realizing-that-you-re-separate-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dance goes from realizing that you're separate (which is the awakening) to then trying to find your way back into the totality of which you are not only a part, but which you are." -- ram dass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71539-you-can-kill-time-in-a-number-of-ways-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 13:03:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71539-you-can-kill-time-in-a-number-of-ways-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can kill time in a number of ways but it always depends on the kind of time you're fighting: some time is unkillable, immortal" -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 12:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A non-writing writer is a monster courting insanity.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Max Brod&lt;/i&gt;, July 5, 1922]" -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301572-instead-of-committing-suicide-people-go-to-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2012 17:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301572-instead-of-committing-suicide-people-go-to-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of committing suicide, people go to work." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95648-fame-requires-every-kind-of-excess-i-mean-true-fame</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 17:20:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95648-fame-requires-every-kind-of-excess-i-mean-true-fame]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fame requires every kind of excess. I mean true fame, a devouring neon, not the somber renown of waning statesmen or chinless kings. I mean long journeys across gray space. I mean danger, the edge of every void, the circumstance of one man imparting an erotic terror to the dreams of the republic. Understand the man who must inhabit these extreme regions, monstrous and vulval, damp with memories of violation. Even if half-mad he is absorbed into the public's total madness; even if fully rational, a bureaucrat in hell, a secret genius of survival, he is sure to be destroyed by the public's contempt for survivors. Fame, this special kind, feeds itself on outrage, on what the counselors of lesser men would consider bad publicity-hysteria in limousines, knife fights in the audience, bizarre litigation, treachery, pandemonium and drugs. Perhaps the only natural law attaching to true fame is that the famous man is compelled, eventually, to commit suicide.
(Is it clear I was a hero of rock'n'roll?)
Toward the end of the final tour it became apparent that our audience wanted more than music, more even than its own reduplicated noise. It's possible the culture had reached its limit, a point of severe tension. There was less sense of simple visceral abandon at our concerts during these last weeks. Few cases of arson and vandalism. Fewer still of rape. No smoke bombs or threats of worse explosives. Our followers, in their isolation, were not concerned with precedent now. They were free of old saints and martyrs, but fearfully so, left with their own unlabeled flesh. Those without tickets didn't storm the barricades, and during a performance the boys and girls directly below us, scratching at the stage, were less murderous in their love of me, as if realizing finally that my death, to be authentic, must be self-willed- a succesful piece of instruction only if it occured by my own hand, preferrably ina  foreign city. I began to think their education would not be complete until they outdid me as a teacher, until one day they merely pantomimed the kind of massive response the group was used to getting. As we performed they would dance, collapse, clutch each other, wave their arms, all the while making absolutely no sound. We would stand in the incandescent pit of a huge stadium filled with wildly rippling bodies, all totally silent. Our recent music, deprived of people's screams, was next to meaningless, and there would have been no choice but to stop playing. A profound joke it would have been. A lesson in something or other.
In Houston I left the group, saying nothing, and boarded a plane for New York City, that contaminated shrine, place of my birth. I knew Azarian would assume leadership of the band, his body being prettiest. As to the rest, I left them to their respective uproars- news media, promotion people, agents, accountants, various members of the managerial peerage. The public would come closer to understanding my disappearance than anyone else. It was not quite as total as the act they needed and nobody could be sure whether I was gone for good. For my closest followers, it foreshadowed a period of waiting. Either I'd return with a new language for them to speak or they'd seek a divine silence attendant to my own.
I took a taxi past the cemetaries toward Manhattan, tides of ash-light breaking across the spires. new York seemed older than the cities of Europe, a sadistic gift of the sixteenth century, ever on the verge of plague. The cab driver was young, however, a freckled kid with a moderate orange Afro. I told him to take the tunnel.
Is there a tunnel?&quot; he said." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
