<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764459-gina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764459-gina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:08:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16601-the-only-thing-worse-than-a-boy-who-hates-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16601-the-only-thing-worse-than-a-boy-who-hates-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing worse than a boy who hates you: a boy that loves you." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:26:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:30:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4424-the-legitimate-powers-of-government-extend-to-such-acts-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4424-the-legitimate-powers-of-government-extend-to-such-acts-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The legitimate powers of government extend to such acts only as are injurious to others. It does me no injury for my neighbor to say there are twenty gods or no god. It neither picks my pocket nor breaks my leg." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:30:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6373-we-took-the-liberty-to-make-some-enquiries-concerning-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We took the liberty to make some enquiries concerning the ground of their pretensions to make war upon nations who had done them no injury, and observed that we considered all mankind as our friends who had done us no wrong, nor had given us any provocation.

The Ambassador [of Tripoli] answered us that it was founded on the Laws of their Prophet, that it was written in their Koran, that all nations who should not have acknowledged their authority were sinners, that it was their right and duty to make war upon them wherever they could be found, and to make slaves of all they could take as Prisoners, and that every Musselman who should be slain in battle was sure to go to Paradise.

{&lt;i&gt;Letter from the commissioners, [author:John Adams|1480] &amp; Thomas Jefferson, to [author:John Jay|63860], 28 March 1786&lt;/i&gt;}" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:33:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12018-love-is-the-ultimate-outlaw-it-just-won-t-adhere-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the ultimate outlaw. It just won't adhere to any rules. The most any of us can do is to sign on as its accomplice. Instead of vowing to honor and obey, maybe we should swear to aid and abet. That would mean that security is out of the question. The words &quot;make&quot; and &quot;stay&quot; become inappropriate. My love for you has no strings attached. I love you for free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:34:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7514-now-tequila-may-be-the-favored-beverage-of-outlaws-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now tequila may be the favored beverage of outlaws but that doesn't mean it gives them preferential treatment. In fact, tequila probably has betrayed as many outlaws as has the central nervous system and dissatisfied wives. Tequila, scorpion honey, harsh dew of the doglands, essence of Aztec, crema de cacti; tequila, oily and thermal like the sun in solution; tequila, liquid geometry of passion; Tequila, the buzzard god who copulates in midair with the ascending souls of dying virgins; tequila, firebug in the house of good taste; O tequila, savage water of sorcery, what confusion and mischief your sly, rebellious drops do generate!" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 11:34:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we're incomplete, we're always searching for somebody to complete us. When, after a few years or a few months of a relationship, we find that we're still unfulfilled, we blame our partners and take up with somebody more promising. This can go on and on--series polygamy--until we admit that while a partner can add sweet dimensions to our lives, we, each of us, are responsible for our own fulfillment. Nobody else can provide it for us, and to believe otherwise is to delude ourselves dangerously and to program for eventual failure every relationship we enter." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11631-well-behaved-women-seldom-make-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2008 08:19:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Laurel Thatcher Ulrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11631-well-behaved-women-seldom-make-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well-behaved women seldom make history." -- Laurel Thatcher Ulrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2008 12:52:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19189-in-ancient-times-cats-were-worshipped-as-gods-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In ancient times cats were worshipped as gods; they have not forgotten this." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 14:28:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13519-reality-continues-to-ruin-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality continues to ruin my life." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6533-it-was-lonely-on-the-hill-and-cold-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 16:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6533-it-was-lonely-on-the-hill-and-cold-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was lonely on the hill, and cold. And all you could do was keep going. You could scream, cry, and stamp your feet, but apart from making you feel warmer, it wouldn’t do any good. You could say it was unfair, and that was true, but the universe didn’t care because it didn’t know what “fair” meant. That was the big problem about being a witch. It was up to you. It was always up to you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37969-you-can-t-map-a-sense-of-humor-anyway-what-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 17:08:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37969-you-can-t-map-a-sense-of-humor-anyway-what-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't map a sense of humor.  Anyway, what is a fantasy map but a space beyond which There Be Dragons?  On the Discworld we know that There Be Dragons Everywhere.  They might not all have scales and forked tongues, but they Be Here all right, grinning and jostling and trying to sell you souvenirs. " -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 18:12:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7322-a-good-bookshop-is-just-a-genteel-black-hole-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 13:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7322-a-good-bookshop-is-just-a-genteel-black-hole-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good bookshop is just a genteel Black Hole that knows how to read." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 08:20:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10087-if-cats-looked-like-frogs-we-d-realize-what-nasty-cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 10:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10087-if-cats-looked-like-frogs-we-d-realize-what-nasty-cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If cats looked like frogs we'd realize what nasty, cruel little bastards they are.  Style.  That's what people remember." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78092-six-mistakes-mankind-keeps-making-century-after-century-believing-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2008 19:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78092-six-mistakes-mankind-keeps-making-century-after-century-believing-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Six mistakes mankind keeps making century after century:
Believing that personal gain is made by crushing others;
Worrying about things that cannot be changed or corrected;
Insisting that a thing is impossible because we cannot accomplish it;
Refusing to set aside trivial preferences;
Neglecting development and refinement of the mind;
Attempting to compel others to believe and live as we do." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51664-the-intelligence-of-that-creature-known-as-a-crowd-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2008 13:23:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51664-the-intelligence-of-that-creature-known-as-a-crowd-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The intelligence of that creature known as a crowd is the square root of the number of people in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9846-you-can-safely-assume-you-ve-created-god-in-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 17:20:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9846-you-can-safely-assume-you-ve-created-god-in-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can safely assume you've created God in your own image when it turns out that God hates all the same people you do." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37815-the-mind-once-stretched-by-a-new-idea-never-returns</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2008 12:49:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37815-the-mind-once-stretched-by-a-new-idea-never-returns]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind, once stretched by a new idea, never returns to its original dimensions." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25863-people-think-it-must-be-fun-to-be-a-super</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 10:10:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25863-people-think-it-must-be-fun-to-be-a-super]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think it must be fun to be a super genius, but they don't realize how hard it is to put up with all the idiots in the world." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14793-every-generation-imagines-itself-to-be-more-intelligent-than-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 11:19:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14793-every-generation-imagines-itself-to-be-more-intelligent-than-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every generation imagines itself to be more intelligent than the one that went before it, and wiser than the one that comes after it." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79822-come-come-whoever-you-are-wanderer-worshiper-lover-of-leaving</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 19:49:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Jelaluddin Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79822-come-come-whoever-you-are-wanderer-worshiper-lover-of-leaving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come, come, whoever you are. Wanderer, worshiper, lover of leaving. It doesn't matter. Ours is not a caravan of despair. come, even if you have broken your vows a thousand times. Come, yet again , come , come." -- Jelaluddin Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 08:43:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64892-don-t-underestimate-the-value-of-irony-it-is-extremely-valuable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 17:33:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64892-don-t-underestimate-the-value-of-irony-it-is-extremely-valuable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t underestimate the value of irony—it is extremely valuable." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68224-both-tolerance-and-respect-are-empty-virtues-until-we-actually</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2008 18:45:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gina add a quote by Stephen Prothero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68224-both-tolerance-and-respect-are-empty-virtues-until-we-actually]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both tolerance and respect are empty virtues until we actually understand whatever it is we are supposed to be tolerating or respecting." -- Stephen Prothero]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
