<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764775-anf]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764775-anf" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 15:05:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 15:05:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14011-when-you-assume-you-make-a-you-know-what-out-of-u</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 15:07:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by David Leonhardt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14011-when-you-assume-you-make-a-you-know-what-out-of-u]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you assume you make a you-know-what out of U and me.  Yep, so let's stop assuming so much.  We are often quick to explain details to strangers, who we understand might not be reading our minds, but we often assume that those people closest to us, those who share our household such as spouses, children parents and siblings, can read our minds.  And we get upset with them when they don't go figure.

I wonder how many angry words are directed not at an action or inaction as would at first appear, but simply at the fact that somebody did not read our minds.

So let's give those people we care most about the benefit of the doubt and do a little less assuming and a little more explaining." -- David Leonhardt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14012-feel-the-fear-and-do-it-anyway</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 15:09:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Susan  Jeffers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14012-feel-the-fear-and-do-it-anyway]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Feel the fear and do it anyway!" -- Susan  Jeffers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41699-it-is-easier-to-live-through-someone-else-than-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 05:43:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Betty Friedan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41699-it-is-easier-to-live-through-someone-else-than-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is easier to live through someone else than to complete yourself.  The freedom to lead and plan your own life is frightening if you have never faced it before.  It is frightening when a woman finally realizes that there is no answer to the question 'who am I' except the voice inside herself." -- Betty Friedan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47570-don-t-mistake-activity-with-achievement</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 05:43:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by John Wooden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47570-don-t-mistake-activity-with-achievement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't mistake activity with achievement." -- John Wooden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180011-i-don-t-have-much-in-the-way-of-money-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:33:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180011-i-don-t-have-much-in-the-way-of-money-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't have much in the way of money or worldly possessions, I'm not beautiful, intelligent or clever, but I'm happy, and I intend to stay that way!  I was born happy, I love people, I have a trusting nature, and I'd like everyone else to be happy too. " -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189004-how-lovely-to-think-that-no-one-need-wait-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 20:34:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189004-how-lovely-to-think-that-no-one-need-wait-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How lovely to think that no one need wait a moment, we can start now, start slowly changing the world! How lovely that everyone, great and small, can make their contribution toward introducing justice straightaway... And you can always, always give something, even if it is only kindness!" -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676-how-wonderful-it-is-that-nobody-need-wait-a-single</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/676-how-wonderful-it-is-that-nobody-need-wait-a-single]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18493-parents-can-only-give-good-advice-or-put-them-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18493-parents-can-only-give-good-advice-or-put-them-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Parents can only give good advice or put them on the right paths, but the final forming of a person's character lies in their own hands." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81804-no-one-has-ever-become-poor-by-giving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81804-no-one-has-ever-become-poor-by-giving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one has ever become poor by giving." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7108-human-greatness-does-not-lie-in-wealth-or-power-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7108-human-greatness-does-not-lie-in-wealth-or-power-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human greatness does not lie in wealth or power, but in character and goodness. People are just people, and all people have faults and shortcomings, but all of us are born with a basic goodness." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44463-where-there-s-hope-there-s-life-it-fills-us-with-fresh</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44463-where-there-s-hope-there-s-life-it-fills-us-with-fresh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where there's hope, there's life.  It fills us with fresh courage and makes us strong again." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21220-women-should-be-respected-as-well-generally-speaking-men-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21220-women-should-be-respected-as-well-generally-speaking-men-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women should be respected as well! Generally speaking, men are held in great esteem in all parts of the world, so why shouldn't women have their share? Soldiers and war heroes are honored and commemorated, explorers are granted immortal fame, martyrs are revered, but how many people look upon women too as soldiers?...Women, who struggle and suffer pain to ensure the continuation of the human race, make much tougher and more courageous soldiers than all those big-mouthed freedom-fighting heroes put together!" -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198974-look-at-how-a-single-candle-can-both-defy-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198974-look-at-how-a-single-candle-can-both-defy-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look at how a single candle can both defy and define the darkness." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45377-ever-since-i-was-a-little-girl-and-could-barely</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:31:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45377-ever-since-i-was-a-little-girl-and-could-barely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever since I was a little girl and could barely talk, the word 'why' has lived and grown along with me. It's a well-known fact that children ask questions about anything and everything, since almost everything is new to them. That is especially true of me, and not just as a child. Even when I was older, I couldn't stop asking questions.
  I have to admit that it can be annoying sometimes, but I comfort myself with the thought that &quot;You won't know until you ask,&quot; though by now I've asked so much that they ought to have made me a professor.
  When I got older, I noticed that not all questions can be asked and that many whys can never be answered. As a result, I tried to work things out for myself by mulling over my own questions. And I came to the important discovery that questions which you either can't or shouldn't ask in public, or questions which you can't put into words, can easily be solved in your own head. So the word 'why' not only taught me to ask, but also to think. And thinking has never hurt anyone. On the contrary, it does us all a world of good." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131370-how-noble-and-good-everyone-could-be-if-every-evening</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:32:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131370-how-noble-and-good-everyone-could-be-if-every-evening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How noble and good everyone could be if, every evening before falling asleep, they were to recall to their minds the events of the whole day and consider exactly what has been good and bad.  Then without realizing it, you try to improve yourself at the start of each new day." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193986-i-wish-to-go-on-living-even-after-my-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2011 21:32:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193986-i-wish-to-go-on-living-even-after-my-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish to go on living even after my death." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37970-the-main-reason-i-became-a-teacher-is-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2011 04:54:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Phillip Done]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37970-the-main-reason-i-became-a-teacher-is-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The main reason I became a teacher is that I like being the first one to introduce kids to words and music and people and numbers and concepts and idea that they have never heard about or thought about before.  I like being the first one to tell them about Long John Silver and negative numbers and Beethoven and alliteration and &quot;Oh, What a Beautiful Morning&quot; and similes and right angles and Ebenezer Scrooge. . . Just think about what you know today.  You read.  You write.  You work with numbers.  You solve problems.  We take all these things for granted.  But of course you haven't always read.  You haven't always known how to write.  You weren't born knowing how to subtract 199 from 600.  Someone showed you.  There was a moment when you moved from not knowing to knowing, from not understanding to understanding.  That's why I became a teacher." -- Phillip Done]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 13:56:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174145-this-is-a-good-sign-having-a-broken-heart-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:10:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174145-this-is-a-good-sign-having-a-broken-heart-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is a good sign, having a broken heart. It means we have tried for something." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31763-your-emotions-are-the-slaves-to-your-thoughts-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31763-your-emotions-are-the-slaves-to-your-thoughts-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your emotions are the slaves to your thoughts, and you are the slave to your emotions." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I get lonely these days, I think: So BE lonely, Liz. Learn your way around loneliness. Make a map of it. Sit with it, for once in your life. Welcome to the human experience. But never again use another person's body or emotions as a scratching post for your own unfulfilled yearnings." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37598-to-lose-balance-sometimes-for-love-is-part-of-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37598-to-lose-balance-sometimes-for-love-is-part-of-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To lose balance sometimes for love is part of living a balanced
life." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25512-never-forget-that-once-upon-a-time-in-an-unguarded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 14:13:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25512-never-forget-that-once-upon-a-time-in-an-unguarded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget that once upon a time, in an unguarded moment, you recognized yourself as a friend." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332897-i-d-learned-enough-from-life-s-experiences-to-understand-that-destiny-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 03:58:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/332897-i-d-learned-enough-from-life-s-experiences-to-understand-that-destiny-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd learned enough from life's experiences to understand that destiny's interventions can sometimes be read as invitation for us to address and even surmount our biggest fears. It doesn't take a great genius to recognize that when you are pushed by circumstance to do the one thing you have always most specifically loathed and feared, this can be, at the very least, an interesting growth opportunity." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398342-child-psychologists-have-demonstrated-that-our-minds-are-actually-constructed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 10:07:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Sidney Poitier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398342-child-psychologists-have-demonstrated-that-our-minds-are-actually-constructed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Child psychologists have demonstrated that our minds are actually constructed by these thousands of tiny interactions during the first few years of life. We aren't just what we're taught. It's what we experience during those early years - a smile here, a jarring sound there - that creates the pathways and connections of the brain. We put our kids to fifteen years of quick-cut advertising, passive television watching, and sadistic video games, and we expect to see emerge a new generation of calm, compassionate, and engaged human beings?" -- Sidney Poitier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66670-i-don-t-mean-to-be-like-some-old-guy-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 05:17:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Sidney Poitier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66670-i-don-t-mean-to-be-like-some-old-guy-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't mean to be like some old guy from the olden days who says, &quot;I walked thirty miles to school every morning, so you kids should too.&quot;  That's a statement born of envy and resentment. What I'm saying is something quite different. What I'm saying is that by having very little, I had it good.  Children need a sense of pulling their own weight, of contributing to the family in some way, and some sense of the family's interdependence.  They take pride in knowing that they're contributing.  They learn responsibility and discipline through meaningful work.  The values developed within a family that operates on those principles then extend to the society at large.  By not being quite so indulged and &quot;protected&quot; from reality by overflowing abundance, children see the bonds that connect them to others." -- Sidney Poitier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131741-things-just-happen-in-the-right-way-at-the-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 19:42:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131741-things-just-happen-in-the-right-way-at-the-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things just happen in the right way, at the right time.  At least when you let them, when you work with circumstances instead of saying, 'This isn't supposed to be happening this way,' and trying harder to make it happen some other way." -- Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135997-i-m-not-saying-i-m-gonna-change-the-world-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2011 10:40:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anf add a quote by Tupac Shakur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135997-i-m-not-saying-i-m-gonna-change-the-world-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not saying I'm gonna change the world, but I guarantee that I will spark the brain that will change the world." -- Tupac Shakur]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
