<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764907-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/764907-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 20:31:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158453-it-can-be-crazy-hard-to-keep-your-faith-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 20:31:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Andrew Klavan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158453-it-can-be-crazy-hard-to-keep-your-faith-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It can be crazy hard. To keep your faith, to keep going. It can be harder than I ever would have imagined. Sometimes things happen to you, really bad things that aren't fair, things that make you feel so terrible you're not even sure who you are anymore or whether you're right or wrong, good or bad. Sometimes you feel like there's no one to turn to, and you're all alone and so scared you can hardly move and so tired you just want to curl up in a ball and go to sleep forever. I guess that's kind of the way Alex felt that last night I saw him. And that's the way I felt now. But I guess I had one advantage over Alex. I guess in some way I'd been training for this time my whole life. I'd been training every day, even in simple things, little things. I trained to keep my mind sharp when I went to school. I trained in karate to keep my body and spirit strong. Even when I just went to church, or when I prayed by myself, it was a kind of training: I was training to remember that I was not alone. I was never alone." -- Andrew Klavan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199729-i-m-not-going-to-wear-a-red-dress-she-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 17:59:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199729-i-m-not-going-to-wear-a-red-dress-she-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not going to wear a red dress,&quot; she said.
&quot;It would look stunning, My Lady,&quot; she called.
She spoke to the bubbles gathered on the surface of the water. &quot;If there's anyone I wish to stun at dinner, I'll hit him in the face." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215590-maybe-if-you-re-lucky-enough-to-have-someone-who-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 18:57:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Heather Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215590-maybe-if-you-re-lucky-enough-to-have-someone-who-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...maybe, if you're lucky enough to have someone who really cares about you, someone you can trust, someone who reminds you to believe in yourself, you can survive absolutely anything..." -- Heather Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222808-what-if-the-person-you-were-meant-to-be-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2010 00:47:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Lauren Kate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222808-what-if-the-person-you-were-meant-to-be-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if the person you were meant to be with could never be yours?" -- Lauren Kate]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
