<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/765025-hannah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/765025-hannah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 19:07:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182336-come-on-hathaway-he-said-taking-my-arm-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2009 19:07:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hannah add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182336-come-on-hathaway-he-said-taking-my-arm-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Come on, Hathaway,&quot; he said, taking my arm. &quot;You can be my partner. Let’s see what you’ve been doing all this time.&quot;
An hour later, he had his answer.
&quot;Not practicing, huh?&quot;
&quot;Ow,” I groaned, momentarily incapable of normal speech.
He extended a hand and helped me up from the mat he’d knocked me down on—about fifty times.
&quot;I hate you,” I told him, rubbing a spot on my thigh that was going to have a wicked bruise tomorrow.
&quot;You’d hate me more if I held back.&quot;
&quot;Yeah, that’s true,&quot; I agreed, staggering along as the class put the equipment back.
&quot;You actually did okay.&quot;
&quot;What? I just had my ass handed to me.&quot;
&quot;Well, of course you did. It’s been two years. But hey, you’re still walking. That’s something.&quot; He grinned mockingly.
&quot;Did I mention I hate you?”
He flashed me another smile, which quickly faded to something more serious. &quot;Don’t take this the wrong way…I mean, you really are a scrapper, but there’s no way you’ll be able to take your trials in the spring—&quot;
&quot;They’re making me take extra practice sessions,&quot; I explained. Not that it mattered. I planned on getting Lissa and me out of here before those practices really became an issue.
&quot;Extra sessions with who?&quot;
&quot;That tall guy. Dimitri.&quot;
Mason stopped walking and stared at me. &quot;You’re putting in extra time with Belikov?&quot;
&quot;Yeah, so what?&quot;
&quot;So the man is a god.&quot;
&quot;Exaggerate much?&quot; I asked.
&quot;No, I’m serious. I mean, he’s all quiet and antisocial usually but when he fights...wow. If you think you’re hurting now, you’re going to be dead when he’s done with you.&quot;
Great. Something else to improve my day." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
