<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/765526-esther]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/765526-esther" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 19:24:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 19:24:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796-classic---a-book-which-people-praise-and-don-t-read]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Classic' - a book which people praise and don't read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2008 09:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98678-to-live-by-grace-means-to-acknowledge-my-whole-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 10:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98678-to-live-by-grace-means-to-acknowledge-my-whole-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live by grace means to acknowledge my whole life story, the light side and the dark. In admitting my shadow side I learn who I am and what God's grace means." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238664-the-engaged-mind-illuminated-by-truth-awakens-awareness-the-engaged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 09:00:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238664-the-engaged-mind-illuminated-by-truth-awakens-awareness-the-engaged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The engaged mind, illuminated by truth, awakens awareness; the engaged heart, affected by love, awakens passion. May I say once more - this essential energy of the soul is not an ecstatic trance, high emotion or a sanguine stance toward life: It is a fierce longing for God, an unyielding resolve to live in and out of our belovedness. - pg. 152
 " -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204206-what-makes-a-genius-the-ability-to-see-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 10:19:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204206-what-makes-a-genius-the-ability-to-see-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What makes a genius?  The ability to see.  To see what?  The butterfly in a caterpillar, the eagle in an egg, the saint in a selfish person, life in death, unity in separation, 
God in the human and human in God and suffering as the form in which the incomprehensibility of God himself appears." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 09:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:35:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in my father's bookshop, I heard a regular customer say that few things leave a deeper mark on a reader than the first book that finds its way into his heart.  Those first images, the echo of words we think we have left behind, accompany us throughout our lives and sculpt a palace in our memory to which, sooner or later—no matter how many books we read, how many worlds we discover, or how much we learn or forget—we will return." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55320-every-book-every-volume-you-see-here-has-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:36:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55320-every-book-every-volume-you-see-here-has-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every book, every volume you see here, has a soul. The soul of the person who wrote it and of those who read it and lived and dreamed with it. Every time a book changes hands, every time someone runs his eyes down its pages, its spirit grows and strengthens." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafón]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326555-if-we-were-left-to-ourselves-with-the-task-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:07:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by David Platt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326555-if-we-were-left-to-ourselves-with-the-task-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we were left to ourselves with the task of taking the gospel to the world, we would immediately begin planning innovative strategies and plotting elaborate schemes. We would organize conventions, develop programs, and create foundations… But Jesus is so different from us. With the task of taking the gospel to the world, he wandered through the streets and byways…All He wanted was a few men who would think as He did, love as He did, see as He did, teach as He did and serve as He did. All He needed was to revolutionize the hearts of a few, and they would impact the world." -- David Platt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326556-we-are-settling-for-a-christianity-that-revolves-around-catering</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:08:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by David Platt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326556-we-are-settling-for-a-christianity-that-revolves-around-catering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are settling for a Christianity that revolves around catering to ourselves when the central message of Christianity is actually about abandoning ourselves." -- David Platt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326557-the-price-is-certainly-high-for-people-who-don-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 01:08:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by David Platt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326557-the-price-is-certainly-high-for-people-who-don-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The price is certainly high for people who don’t know Christ and who live in a world where Christians shrink back from self-denying faith and settle into self-indulging faith. While Christians choose to spend their lives fulfilling the American dream instead of giving their lives to proclaiming the kingdom of God, literally billions in need of the Gospel remain in the dark" -- David Platt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327515-we-need-to-make-some-dramatic-concrete-moves-to-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 11:51:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Ronald J. Sider]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327515-we-need-to-make-some-dramatic-concrete-moves-to-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to make some dramatic, concrete moves to escape the materialism that seeps into our minds via diabolically clever and incessant advertising. We have been brainwashed to believe that bigger houses, more prosperous businesses, and more sophisticated gadgets are the way to joy and fulfillment. As a result, we are caught in an absurd, materialistic spiral. The more we make, the more we think we need in order to live decently and respectably. Somehow we have to break this cycle because it makes us sin against our needy brothers and sisters and, therefore, against our Lord. And it also destroys us. Sharing with others is the way to real joy." -- Ronald J. Sider]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350845-this-beloved-of-ours-is-merciful-and-good-besides-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 11:48:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Santa Teresa de Jesús]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350845-this-beloved-of-ours-is-merciful-and-good-besides-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This Beloved of ours is merciful and good. Besides, he so deeply longs for our love that he keeps calling us to come closer. This voice of his is so sweet that the poor soul falls apart in the face of her own inability to instantly do whatever he asks of her. And so you can see, hearing him hurts much more than not being able to hear him… For now, his voice reaches us through words spoken by good people, through listening to spiritual talks, and reading sacred literature. God calls to us in countless little ways all the time. Through illnesses and suffering and through sorrow he calls to us. Through a truth glimpsed fleetingly in a state of prayer he calls to us. No matter how halfhearted such insights may be, God rejoices whenever we learn what he is trying to teach us." -- Santa Teresa de Jesús]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350846-there-is-a-secret-place-a-radiant-sanctuary-as-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 11:49:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Mirabai Starr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350846-there-is-a-secret-place-a-radiant-sanctuary-as-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a secret place. A radiant sanctuary. As real as your own kitchen. More real than that. Constructed of the purest elements. Overflowing with the ten thousand beautiful things. Worlds within worlds. Forests, rivers. Velvet coverlets thrown over featherbeds, fountains bubbling beneath a canopy of stars. Bountiful forests, universal libraries. A wine cellar offering an intoxi cation so sweet you will never be sober again. A clarity so complete you will never again forget. This magnificent refuge is inside you. Enter. Shatter the darkness that shrouds the doorway… Believe the incredible truth that the Beloved has chosen for his dwelling place the core of your own being because that is the single most beautiful place in all of creation." -- Mirabai Starr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 15:40:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, I do believe in magic. I was born and raised in a magic time, in a magic town, among magicians. Oh, most everybody else didn’t realize we lived in that web of magic, connected by silver filaments of chance and circumstance. But I knew it all along. When I was twelve years old, the world was my magic lantern, and by its green spirit glow I saw the past, the present and into the future. You probably did too; you just don’t recall it. See, this is my opinion: we all start out knowing magic. We are born with whirlwinds, forest fires, and comets inside us. We are born able to sing to birds and read the clouds and see our destiny in grains of sand. But then we get the magic educated right out of our souls. We get it churched out, spanked out, washed out, and combed out. We get put on the straight and narrow and told to be responsible. Told to act our age. Told to grow up, for God’s sake. And you know why we were told that? Because the people doing the telling were afraid of our wildness and youth, and because the magic we knew made them ashamed and sad of what they’d allowed to wither in themselves.

After you go so far away from it, though, you can’t really get it back. You can have seconds of it. Just seconds of knowing and remembering. When people get weepy at movies, it’s because in that dark theater the golden pool of magic is touched, just briefly. Then they come out into the hard sun of logic and reason again and it dries up, and they’re left feeling a little heartsad and not knowing why. When a song stirs a memory, when motes of dust turning in a shaft of light takes your attention from the world, when you listen to a train passing on a track at night in the distance and wonder where it might be going, you step beyond who you are and where you are. For the briefest of instants, you have stepped into the magic realm.

That’s what I believe.

The truth of life is that every year we get farther away from the essence that is born within us. We get shouldered with burdens, some of them good, some of them not so good. Things happen to us. Loved ones die. People get in wrecks and get crippled. People lose their way, for one reason or another. It’s not hard to do, in this world of crazy mazes. Life itself does its best to take that memory of magic away from us. You don’t know it’s happening until one day you feel you’ve lost something but you’re not sure what it is. It’s like smiling at a pretty girl and she calls you “sir.” It just happens.

These memories of who I was and where I lived are important to me. They make up a large part of who I’m going to be when my journey winds down. I need the memory of magic if I am ever going to conjure magic again. I need to know and remember, and I want to tell you." -- Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48148-it-is-by-loving-and-not-by-being-loved-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 14:31:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by George MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48148-it-is-by-loving-and-not-by-being-loved-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is by loving and not by being loved that one can come nearest to the soul of another." -- George MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10002-it-is-hard-to-fail-but-it-is-worse-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 14:32:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10002-it-is-hard-to-fail-but-it-is-worse-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219647-hope-knows-that-if-great-trials-are-avoided-great-deeds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 23:09:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219647-hope-knows-that-if-great-trials-are-avoided-great-deeds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope knows that if great trials are avoided great deeds remain undone and the possibility of growth into greatness of soul is aborted." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460793-the-artist-s-job-is-not-to-succumb-to-despair-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 13:54:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460793-the-artist-s-job-is-not-to-succumb-to-despair-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The artist's job is not to succumb to despair but to find an antidote for the emptiness of existence." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1072047-we-say-that-slavery-has-vanished-from-european-civilization-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 14:17:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Esther add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1072047-we-say-that-slavery-has-vanished-from-european-civilization-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We say that slavery has vanished from European civilization, but this is not true. Slavery still exists, but now it applies only to women and its name is prostitution." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
