<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/766779-peggy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/766779-peggy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 13:41:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48385-but-the-biggest-mistake-i-made-is-the-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 13:41:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peggy add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48385-but-the-biggest-mistake-i-made-is-the-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["but the biggest mistake I made is the one that most of us make while doing this. I did not live in the moment enough. This is particularly clear now that the moment is gone, captured only in photographs. There is one picture of the three on them sitting in the grass on a quilt in the shadow of the swing set on a summer day, ages 6, 4, and 1. And I wish I could remember what we ate, and what we talked about, and how they sounded, and how they looked when they slept that night. I wish I had not been in a hurry to get on to the next things: dinner, bath, book, bed. I wish I had treasured the doing a little more and the getting it done a little less." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13271-learn-to-enjoy-every-minute-of-your-life-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 13:42:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peggy add a quote by Earl Nightingale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13271-learn-to-enjoy-every-minute-of-your-life-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learn to enjoy every minute of your life. Be happy now. Don't wait for something outside of yourself to make you happy in the future. 
Think how really precious is the time you have to spend, whether it's at work or with your family. Every minute should be enjoyed and savored" -- Earl Nightingale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55833-there-on-the-sofa-as-i-nursed-maxie-and-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 19:54:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peggy add a quote by Katherine Center]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55833-there-on-the-sofa-as-i-nursed-maxie-and-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There on the sofa, as I nursed Maxie and her eyes slid closed, I said to the girls, ‘I think nursing is where kisses come from.’ I had been thinking about it. Nursing had to be the place where nurturing and sweet milk and soft skin and mouths and warmth all came together and started to mean something about love.
	I had always assumed kissing was a learned thing, like waving bye-bye or speaking a language. But since Maxie, I’d decided that it was innate, the adult version of something we know to do from the moment we’re born. All of it tied together in the cycle of life." -- Katherine Center]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55834-and-the-way-i-loved-her-was-like-nothing-else</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 19:55:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Peggy add a quote by Katherine Center]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55834-and-the-way-i-loved-her-was-like-nothing-else]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the way I loved her was like nothing else. This, I decided, was the love all other loves were measured against. They say girls look to marry their fathers, but I decided after having Maxie that we all, every one of us, were looking to marry our mothers. Sitting on the sofa with her wrapped in a soft blanket in my arms, I’d think, ‘This baby has it so good.’ 
It just seemed that the love I’d been searching and hoping for all my life was what Maxie already had right now: two big arms and a lap, a warm blanket, the background music of a heartbeat and a pair of lungs, food at a moment’s notice, sleep at every urge, and a person totally obsessed with her, whose every moment—waking or otherwise—was totally devoted to her comfort and care. Was that so much to ask for?" -- Katherine Center]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
