<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/767410-kyle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/767410-kyle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:30:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2532-great-heroes-need-great-sorrows-and-burdens-or-half-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2532-great-heroes-need-great-sorrows-and-burdens-or-half-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great heroes need great sorrows and burdens, or half their greatness goes unnoticed. It is all part of the fairy tale." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10393-the-true-secret-in-being-a-hero-lies-in-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:31:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10393-the-true-secret-in-being-a-hero-lies-in-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true secret in being a hero lies in knowing the order of things. The swineherd cannot already be wed to the princess when he embarks on his adventures, nor can the boy knock on the witch's door when she is already away on vacation. The wicked uncle cannot be found out and foiled before he does something wicked. Things must happen when it is time for them to happen. Quests may not simply be abandoned; prophecies may not be left to rot like unpicked fruit; unicorns may go unrescued for a very long time, but not forever. The happy ending cannot come in the middle of the story." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9133-it-s-a-rare-man-who-is-taken-for-what-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:31:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9133-it-s-a-rare-man-who-is-taken-for-what-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a rare man who is taken for what he truly is." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119766-i-have-been-mortal-and-some-part-of-me-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:31:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119766-i-have-been-mortal-and-some-part-of-me-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been mortal, and some part of me is mortal yet. I am full of tears and hunger and the fear of death, although I cannot weep, and I want nothing, and I cannot die. I am not like the others now, for no unicorn was ever born who could regret, but I do. I regret." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225074-marveling-at-his-own-boldness-he-said-softly-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:31:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225074-marveling-at-his-own-boldness-he-said-softly-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marveling at his own boldness, he said softly, &quot;I would enter your sleep if I could, and guard you there, and slay the thing that hounds you, as I would if it had the courage to face me in fair daylight. But I cannot come in unless you dream of me." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239435-as-for-you-and-your-heart-and-the-things-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239435-as-for-you-and-your-heart-and-the-things-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for you and your heart and the things you said and didn't say, she will remember them all when men are fairy tales in books written by rabbits." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102701-then-what-is-magic-for-prince-l-r-demanded-wildly-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:32:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102701-then-what-is-magic-for-prince-l-r-demanded-wildly-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then what is magic for?&quot; Prince Lír demanded wildly. &quot;What use is wizardry if it cannot save a unicorn?&quot; He gripped the magician's shoulder hard, to keep from falling.

Schmedrick did not turn his head. With a touch of sad mockery in his voice, he said, &quot;That's what heroes are for." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219889-where-have-you-been-she-cried-damn-you-where-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:32:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219889-where-have-you-been-she-cried-damn-you-where-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where have you been?&quot; she cried. &quot;Damn you, where have you been?&quot; She took a few steps toward Schmendrick, but she was looking beyond him, at the unicorn.

When she tried to get by, the magician stood in her way. &quot;You don't talk like that,&quot; he told her, still uncertain that Molly had recognized the unicorn. &quot;Don't you know how to behave, woman? You don't curtsy, either.&quot;

But Molly pushed him aside and went up to the unicorn, scolding her as though she were a strayed milk cow. &quot;&lt;i&gt;Where have you been?&lt;/i&gt;&quot; Before the whiteness and the shining horn, Molly shrank to a shrilling beetle, but this time it was the unicorn's old dark eyes that looked down.

&quot;I am here now,&quot; she said at last.

Molly laughed with her lips flat. &quot;And what good is it to me that you're here now? Where where you twenty years ago, ten years ago? How dare you, how dare you come to me now, when I am &lt;i&gt;this?&lt;/i&gt;&quot; With a flap of her hand she summed herself up: barren face, desert eyes, and yellowing heart. &quot;I wish you had never come. Why did you come now?&quot; The tears began to slide down the sides of her nose.

The unicorn made no reply, and Schmendrick said, &quot;She is the last. She is the last unicorn in the world.&quot;

&quot;She would be.&quot; Molly sniffed. &quot;It would be the last unicorn in the world to come to Molly Grue.&quot; She reached up then to lay her hand on the unicorn's cheek; but both of them flinched a little, and the touch came to rest on on the swift, shivering place under the jaw. Molly said, &quot;It's all right. I forgive you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368733-take-me-with-you-for-laughs-for-luck-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:32:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368733-take-me-with-you-for-laughs-for-luck-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take me with you.  For laughs, for luck, for the unknown.  Take me with you." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482951-the-last-unicorn-lived-in-a-lilac-wood-and-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:38:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482951-the-last-unicorn-lived-in-a-lilac-wood-and-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The last unicorn lived in a lilac wood, and she lived all alone." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540120-the-unicorn-lived-in-a-lilac-wood-and-she-lived</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 21:41:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540120-the-unicorn-lived-in-a-lilac-wood-and-she-lived]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unicorn lived in a lilac wood, and she lived all alone. She was very old, though she did not know it, and she was no longer the careless color of sea foam but rather the color of snow falling on a moonlit night. But her eyes were still clear and unwearied, and she still moved like a shadow on the sea." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
