<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/768748-torianna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/768748-torianna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 06:09:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 06:09:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Torianna add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I discovered that my obsession for having each thing in the right place, each subject at the right time, each word in the right style, was not the well-deserved reward of an ordered mind but just the opposite: a complete system of pretense invented by me to hide the disorder of my nature. I discovered that I am not disciplined out of virtue but as a reaction to my negligence, that I appear generous in order to conceal my meanness, that I pass myself off as prudent because I am evil-minded, that I am conciliatory in order not to succumb to my repressed rage, that I am punctual only to hide how little I care about other people’s time. I learned, in short, that love is not a condition of the spirit but a sign of the zodiac." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 11:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Torianna add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 11:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Torianna add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
