<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/769895-steven]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/769895-steven" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 03:53:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15142-all-government-in-its-essence-is-a-conspiracy-against-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 03:53:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steven add a quote by H. L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15142-all-government-in-its-essence-is-a-conspiracy-against-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All government, in its essence, is a conspiracy against the superior man: its one permanent object is to oppress him and cripple him. If it be aristocratic in organization, then it seeks to protect the man who is superior only in law against the man who is superior in fact; if it be democratic, then it seeks to protect the man who is inferior in every way against both. One of its primary functions is to regiment men by force, to make them as much alike as possible and as dependent upon one another as possible, to search out and combat originality among them. All it can see in an original idea is potential change, and hence an invasion of its prerogatives. The most dangerous man to any government is the man who is able to think things out for himself, without regard to the prevailing superstitions and taboos. Almost inevitably he comes to the conclusion that the government he lives under is dishonest, insane and intolerable, and so, if he is romantic, he tries to change it. And even if he is not romantic personally he is very apt to spread discontent among those who are." -- H. L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 00:04:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steven add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 16:28:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steven add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
