<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772008-james]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772008-james" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 12:00:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11114-horror-fiction-shows-us-that-the-control-we-believe-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 12:00:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11114-horror-fiction-shows-us-that-the-control-we-believe-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Horror fiction] shows us that the control we believe we have is purely illusory, and that every moment we teeter on chaos and oblivion." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 12:01:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6606-running-a-close-second-as-a-writing-lesson-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Running a close second [as a writing lesson] was the realization that stopping a piece of work just because it's hard, either emotionally or imaginatively, is a bad idea. Sometimes you have to go on when you don't feel like it, and sometimes you're doing good work when it feels like all you're managing is to shovel shit from a sitting position." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7255-so-i-had-this-problem----work-or-starve-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 12:02:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Robert Bloch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7255-so-i-had-this-problem----work-or-starve-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So I had this problem -- work or starve. So I thought I'd combine the two and decided to become a writer." -- Robert Bloch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465543-horror-itself-is-a-bit-of-a-bullied-genre-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 18:36:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Kealan Patrick Burke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465543-horror-itself-is-a-bit-of-a-bullied-genre-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Horror itself is a bit of a bullied genre, the antagonist being literary snobbery and public misconception. And I think good horror tackles our darkest fears, whatever they may be. It takes us into the minds of the victims, explores the threats, disseminates fear, studies how it changes us. It pulls back the curtain on the ugly underbelly of society, tears away the masks the monsters wear out in the world, shows us the potential truth of the human condition. Horror is truth, unflinching and honest. Not everybody wants to see that, but good horror ensures that it's there to be seen." -- Kealan Patrick Burke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543097-no-reader-has-any-obligation-to-an-author-whether-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 17:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Stacia Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543097-no-reader-has-any-obligation-to-an-author-whether-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["NO reader has ANY obligation to an author, whether it be to leave a review or to write a &quot;constructive&quot; one. I put out a product. You are consumers of that product. Since when does that mean you have to kiss my ass? Hey, I like Pop-Tarts and eat them a few times a year; since when does that mean I'm obligated to support Kellogg's in any way except legally purchasing the Pop-Tarts before I eat them? I wasn't aware that purchasing and consuming a product meant I was under some sort of fucking thrall in which I'm only allowed to either praise the Pop-Tart (which to be honest isn't hard, especially the S'mores flavor) or, if I am going to criticize a flavor, offer a specific and detailed analysis as to why, phrased in as inoffensive and gentle a manner as possible so as not to upset the gentle people at Kellogg's.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Something in the Water?&lt;/i&gt; (blog post; January 9, 2012)]" -- Stacia Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837975-everyone-has-something-to-hide-and-if-they-couldn-t-hide</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 17:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Richard Matheson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/837975-everyone-has-something-to-hide-and-if-they-couldn-t-hide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone has something to hide. And if they couldn't hide it the world would be in a lot worse mess than it is." -- Richard Matheson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553635-cruelty-is-not-taught-it-is-as-certain-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 11:08:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Lee Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553635-cruelty-is-not-taught-it-is-as-certain-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cruelty is not taught. It is as certain as a compass point. One can be instructed in the specifics of cruelty, like one can be taught to use a spoon, a knife, a fork, but even without these skills a man will still eat. The need is with us." -- Lee Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
