<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772448-anton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772448-anton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 18:37:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271781-serenity-now-you-could-wish-for-that-naming-no-conditions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 18:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271781-serenity-now-you-could-wish-for-that-naming-no-conditions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Serenity. Now you could wish for that, naming no conditions: a permanent inner vacation, escape made good. To somehow have this motionlessness that he drew in with the sweet air he inhaled for his inward weather always.

But there were problems too with wishing for moral qualities, serenity, large-mindedness. The interdiction (which Pierce thought obvious) against wishing for such things as artistic abilities -- sit down at the piano, the Appassionata flows suddenly from your fingertips -- applied in a way to wisdom too, to enlightenment, to heart-knowledge, useless unless earned, the earning of it being no doubt all that it consisted of." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314183-i-reminded-myself-when-a-book-lies-unopened-it-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 12:54:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314183-i-reminded-myself-when-a-book-lies-unopened-it-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I reminded myself: when a book lies unopened it might contain anything in the world, anything imaginable. It therefore, in that pregnant moment before opening, contains everything. Every possibility, both perfect and putrid. Surely such mysteries are the most enticing things You grant us in this mortal mere -- the fruit in the garden, too, was like this. Unknown, and therefore infinite. Eve and her mate swallowed eternity, every possible thing, and made the world between them." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431059-keeping-hatred-inside-makes-you-git-mean-and-evil-inside</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 17:09:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Margaret Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431059-keeping-hatred-inside-makes-you-git-mean-and-evil-inside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keeping hatred inside makes you git mean and evil inside. We supposen to love everybody like God loves us. And when you forgives you feels sorry for the one what hurt you, you returns love for hate, and good for evil. And that stretches your heart and makes you bigger inside with a bigger heart so's you can love everybody when your heart is big enough. Your chest gets broad like this, and you can lick the world with a loving heart! Now when you hates you shrinks up inside and gets littler and you squeezes your heart tight and you stays so mad with peoples you feels sick all the time like you needs the doctor. Folks with a loving heart don't never need no doctor." -- Margaret Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477570-thinking-and-prayer-are-much-the-same-thing-anyway-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 14:04:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/477570-thinking-and-prayer-are-much-the-same-thing-anyway-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thinking and prayer are much the same thing anyway, when you stop to think about it -- if that makes any sense. Prayer goes up and thought comes down -- or so it seems. As far as I can tell, that's the only difference." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338740-if-you-love-books-enough-books-will-love-you-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 06:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Jo Walton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338740-if-you-love-books-enough-books-will-love-you-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love books enough, books will love you back." -- Jo Walton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101267-if-you-want-to-write-if-you-want-to-create</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 20:21:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101267-if-you-want-to-write-if-you-want-to-create]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to write, if you want to create, you must be the most sublime fool that God ever turned out and sent rambling. You must write every single day of your life. You must read dreadful dumb books and glorious books, and let them wrestle in beautiful fights inside your head, vulgar one moment, brilliant the next. You must lurk in libraries and climb the stacks like ladders to sniff books like perfumes and wear books like hats upon your crazy heads. I wish you a wrestling match with your Creative Muse that will last a lifetime. I wish craziness and foolishness and madness upon you. May you live with hysteria, and out of it make fine stories — science fiction or otherwise. Which finally means, may you be in love every day for the next 20,000 days. And out of that love, remake a world." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606270-what-would-your-good-be-doing-if-there-were-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2012 18:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Mikhail Bulgakov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606270-what-would-your-good-be-doing-if-there-were-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would your good be doing if there were no evil, and what would the earth look like if shadows disappeared from it? After all, shadows are cast by objects and people. There is the shadow of my sword. But there are also shadows of trees and living creatures. Would you like to denude the earth of all the trees and all the living beings in order to satisfy your fantasy of rejoicing in the naked light?" -- Mikhail Bulgakov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644220-although-my-understanding-of-exactly-how-much-trouble-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 18:44:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Jennifer Finney Boylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644220-although-my-understanding-of-exactly-how-much-trouble-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although my understanding of exactly how much trouble I was in grew more specific over time, as a child I surely understood enough about my condition to know it was something I'd better keep private. By intuition I was certain that the thing I knew to be true was something others would find both impossible and hilarious. My conviction, by the way, had nothing to do with a desire to be &lt;i&gt;feminine&lt;/i&gt;, but it had everything to do with being &lt;i&gt;female&lt;/i&gt;. Which is an odd believe for a person born male. It certainly had nothing to do with whether I was attracted to girls or boys. This last point was the one that, years later, would most frequently elude people, including the overeducated smarty-pants who constituted much of my inner circle. But being gay or lesbian is about sexual orientation. Being transgedered is about identity." -- Jennifer Finney Boylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644270-i-really-did-choose-to-be-jim-every-single-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 20:22:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Jennifer Finney Boylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/644270-i-really-did-choose-to-be-jim-every-single-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I really did &quot;choose&quot; to be Jim every single day, but that once I put my sword down I haven't chosen Jenny at all; I simply wake up and here I am." -- Jennifer Finney Boylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141059-if-you-trust-in-yourself-and-believe-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 13:04:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141059-if-you-trust-in-yourself-and-believe-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you trust in yourself. . .and believe in your dreams. . .and follow your star. . . you'll still get beaten by people who spent their time working hard and learning things and weren't so lazy." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326658-we-are-never-allowed-to-forget-that-some-books-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 08:17:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326658-we-are-never-allowed-to-forget-that-some-books-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are never allowed to forget that some books are badly written; we should remember that sometimes they're badly read, too." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675909-the-annoying-thing-about-reading-is-that-you-can-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 18:03:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675909-the-annoying-thing-about-reading-is-that-you-can-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The annoying thing about reading is that you can never get the job done." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22331-we-are-not-always-what-we-seem-and-hardly-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 08:51:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22331-we-are-not-always-what-we-seem-and-hardly-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not always what we seem, and hardly ever what we dream." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752737-no-she-said-answering-his-eyes-i-can-never-regret-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 08:52:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anton add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752737-no-she-said-answering-his-eyes-i-can-never-regret-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No,&quot; she said, answering his eyes. &quot;I can never regret.&quot;[...]&quot;I can sorrow,&quot; she offered gently, &quot;but it's not the same thing." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
