<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772437-kathleen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772437-kathleen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:18:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20855-the-greatest-gift-is-the-passion-for-reading-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:18:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Elizabeth Hardwick ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20855-the-greatest-gift-is-the-passion-for-reading-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The greatest gift is the passion for reading.
It is cheap, it consoles, it distracts, it excites,
it gives you knowledge of the world and experience of a wide kind.
It is a moral illumination." -- Elizabeth Hardwick ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8165-it-is-only-a-novel-or-in-short-only-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:19:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8165-it-is-only-a-novel-or-in-short-only-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is only a novel... or, in short, only some work in which the greatest powers of the mind are displayed, in which the most thorough knowledge of human nature, the happiest delineation of its varieties, the liveliest effusions of wit and humour, are conveyed to the world in the best-chosen language" -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255694-is-he-well-educated-yes-i-think-so-as-far</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:19:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255694-is-he-well-educated-yes-i-think-so-as-far]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is he well educated?&quot;
&quot;Yes, I think so, as far as he's gone,&quot; I answered. &quot;Of course he will go on being educated every day of his life, same as father. He says it is all rot about 'finishing' your education. You never do. You learn more important things each day..." -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2052-the-pleasure-of-all-reading-is-doubled-when-one-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 12:19:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2052-the-pleasure-of-all-reading-is-doubled-when-one-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pleasure of all reading is doubled when one lives with another who shares the same books." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18525-one-half-of-the-world-cannot-understand-the-pleasures-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18525-one-half-of-the-world-cannot-understand-the-pleasures-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One half of the world cannot understand the pleasures of the other." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220087-tu-ne-cede-malis-sed-contra-audentior-ito</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Virgil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220087-tu-ne-cede-malis-sed-contra-audentior-ito]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tu ne cede malis, sed contra audentior ito" -- Virgil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67014-people-were-always-saying-to-margaret-well-julia-sings-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Maud Hart Lovelace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67014-people-were-always-saying-to-margaret-well-julia-sings-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People were always saying to Margaret, 'Well, Julia sings and Betsy writes. Now what is little Margaret going to do?' Margaret would smile politely, for she was very polite, but privately she stormed to Betsy with flashing eyes, 'I'm not going to do anything. I want to just live. Can't people just live?" -- Maud Hart Lovelace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6677-give-me-a-moment-because-i-like-to-cry-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:10:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6677-give-me-a-moment-because-i-like-to-cry-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give me a moment, because I like to cry for joy. It's so delicious, John dear, to cry for joy." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149601-the-woman-whose-behavior-indicates-that-she-will-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 16:10:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Elizabeth Jenkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149601-the-woman-whose-behavior-indicates-that-she-will-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The woman whose behavior indicates that she will make a scene if she is told the truth asks to be deceived." -- Elizabeth Jenkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300553-it-was-a-mere-matter-of-seeing-common-things-together</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 19:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300553-it-was-a-mere-matter-of-seeing-common-things-together]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a mere matter of seeing common things together and exchanging common speech concerning them, but each was so strongly conscious of the other that no sentence could seem wholly impersonal. There are times when the whole world is personal to a mood whose intensity seems a reason for all things. Words are of small moment when the mere sound of a voice makes an unreasonable joy." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306518-those-darling-byegone-times-mr-carker-said-cleopatra-with-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 18:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306518-those-darling-byegone-times-mr-carker-said-cleopatra-with-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those darling byegone times, Mr Carker,' said Cleopatra, 'with their delicious fortresses, and their dear old dungeons, and their delightful places of torture, and their romantic vengeances, and their picturesque assaults and sieges, and everything that makes life truly charming! How dreadfully we have degenerated!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378938-and-yet-even-among-the-friends-of-liberty-many-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 16:29:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Ron Paul]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378938-and-yet-even-among-the-friends-of-liberty-many-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet even among the friends of liberty, many people are deceived into believing that government can make them safe from all harm, provide fairly distributed economic security, and improve individual moral behavior. If the government is granted a monopoly on the use of force to achieve these goals, history shows that power is always abused. Every single time." -- Ron Paul]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393469-it-s-an-odd-thing-but-when-you-tell-someone-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 15:33:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Josephine Tey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393469-it-s-an-odd-thing-but-when-you-tell-someone-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's an odd thing but when you tell someone the true facts of a mythical tale they are indignant not with the teller but with you. They don't &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to have their ideas upset. It rouses some vague uneasiness in them, I think, and they resent it. So they reject it and refuse to think about it. If they were merely indifferent it would be natural and understandable. But it is much stronger than that, much more positive. They are annoyed.

Very odd, isn't it." -- Josephine Tey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402004-i-don-t-agree-with-you-in-the-least-said-temple</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 14:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by E. Nesbit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402004-i-don-t-agree-with-you-in-the-least-said-temple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't agree with you in the least,&quot; said Temple— &quot;about marriage, I mean. A man ought to want to get married—&quot;
 
&quot;To anybody? Without its being anybody in particular?&quot;
 
&quot;Yes,&quot; said Temple stoutly. &quot;If he gets to thirty without wanting to marry any one in particular, he ought to look about till he finds some one he does want. It's the right and proper thing to marry and have kiddies." -- E. Nesbit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402008-they-call-it-love-said-vernon-i-don-t-know-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 14:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by E. Nesbit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402008-they-call-it-love-said-vernon-i-don-t-know-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They call it love,&quot; said Vernon. &quot;I don't know what they mean by it. What do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; mean [by love]?&quot;

&quot;I don't exactly know,&quot; said Temple slowly. &quot;I suppose it's wanting to be with a person, and thinking about nothing else. And thinking they're the most beautiful and all that. And going over everything that they've ever said to you, and wanting— Well, I suppose if it's really love you want to marry them." -- E. Nesbit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432744-the-most-common-and-the-monstrous-defect-in-the-education</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2011 21:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Charlotte Mason]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432744-the-most-common-and-the-monstrous-defect-in-the-education]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most common and the monstrous defect in the education of the day is that children fail to acquire the habit of reading." -- Charlotte Mason]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436458-i-ve-tried-to-keep-pleasant-mabel-went-on-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 00:34:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436458-i-ve-tried-to-keep-pleasant-mabel-went-on-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've tried to keep pleasant,&quot; Mabel went on. &quot;You don't know &lt;i&gt;how&lt;/i&gt; I've tried. I have that verse pinned up on my dresser, about

&lt;i&gt;The man worth while is the man who can smile,
When everything goes dead wrong.&quot;&lt;/i&gt;

&quot;Take it down,&quot; Mother said cheerfully. &quot;If there's a verse in the world that has been worked overtime, it's that one. I can't think of anything more inane than to smile when everything goes dead wrong, unless it is to cry when everything is passably right. That verse always seemed to me to be a surface sort of affair. Take it down and substitute 'I will lift up mine eyes unto the hills from whence cometh my help.' &lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; goes to the heart of things--when you feel &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; strength, then the dead-wrong things begin to miraculously right themselves." -- Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436459-katherine-it-was-who-took-upon-herself-the-complete-charge</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 00:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436459-katherine-it-was-who-took-upon-herself-the-complete-charge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Katherine it was who took upon herself the complete charge of [Junior's] speech. Not an insignificant &quot;have went&quot; nor an infinitesimal &quot;I seen&quot; ever escaped the keen ears of his eldest sister, who immediately corrected him. Mother sometimes thought Katherine a little severe when, in the interest of proper speaking, she would stop him in the midst of an exciting account of a home-run. There were times, thought Mother, when the spirit of the thing was so much more important than the flesh in which it was clothed." -- Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436461-as-i-stood-in-my-lonely-bedroom-at-the-hotel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 00:50:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/436461-as-i-stood-in-my-lonely-bedroom-at-the-hotel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I stood in my lonely bedroom at the hotel, trying to tie my white tie myself, it struck me for the first time that there must be whole squads of chappies in the world who had to get along without a man to look after them. I'd always thought of Jeeves as a kind of natural phenomenon; but, by Jove! of course, when you come to think of it, there must be quite a lot of fellows who have to press their own clothes themselves and haven't got anybody to bring them tea in the morning, and so on. It was rather a solemn thought, don't you know. I mean to say, ever since then I've been able to appreciate the frightful privations the poor have to stick." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445496-pain-has-been-and-grief-enough-and-bitterness-and-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 15:57:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Margaret Widdemer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/445496-pain-has-been-and-grief-enough-and-bitterness-and-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain has been and grief enough and bitterness and crying,
Sharp ways and stony ways I think it was she trod;
But all there is to see now is a white bird flying,
Whose blood-stained wings go circling high—circling up to God!" -- Margaret Widdemer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446329-let-me-tell-you-something-allen-i-ve-been-around-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 21:37:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446329-let-me-tell-you-something-allen-i-ve-been-around-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Let me tell you something, Allen.  I've been around now, enough to know there are some bigger things in the world than marriage and a prosaic settling down under one roof.&quot;

&quot;Now, I'll tell &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; something.&quot;  He sat up straighter under the wheel.  &quot;There &lt;i&gt;isn't&lt;/i&gt;,—not a thing—when it's two people who really care, and, and settling down under one roof, as you say, is the beginning of a real home. There's &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; finer..." -- Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449016-as-a-matter-of-fact-it-required-only-a-tolerable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 13:49:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449016-as-a-matter-of-fact-it-required-only-a-tolerable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a matter of fact it required only a tolerable show of virtue for Peter to win encomiums at any time. He would brush his curly mop of hair away from his forehead, lift his eyes, part his lips, showing a row of tiny white teeth; then a dimple would appear in each cheek and a seraphic expression (wholly at variance with the facts) would overspread the baby face, whereupon the beholder...would cry &quot;Angel boy!&quot; and kiss him. He was even kissed now, though he had done nothing at all but exist and be an enchanting personage, which is one of the injustices of a world where a large number of virtuous and well-behaved people go unkissed to their graves!" -- Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449017-oh-kathleen-sighed-nancy-as-the-two-went-into-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 13:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449017-oh-kathleen-sighed-nancy-as-the-two-went-into-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, Kathleen!&quot; sighed Nancy as the two went into the kitchen together. &quot;Isn't mother the most interesting 'scolder' you ever listened to? I love to hear her do it, especially when somebody else is getting it. When it's I, I grow smaller and smaller, curling myself up like a little worm. Then when she has finished I squirm to the door and wriggle out. Other mothers say: 'If you don't, I shall tell your father!' 'Do as I tell you, and ask no questions.' 'I never heard of such behavior in my life!' 'Haven't you any sense of propriety?' 'If this happens again I shall have to do something desperate.' 'Leave the room at once,' and so on; but mother sets you to thinking.&quot;

&quot;Mother doesn't really scold,&quot; Kathleen objected.

&quot;No, but she shows you how wrong you are, just the same..." -- Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449019-julia-carey-had-never-even-when-very-young-experienced-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 13:59:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449019-julia-carey-had-never-even-when-very-young-experienced-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Julia Carey] had never, even when very young, experienced a desire to sit at the feet of superior wisdom, always greatly preferring a chair of her own. She seldom did wrong, in her own opinion, because the moment she entertained an idea it at once became right, her vanity serving as a pair of blinders to keep her from seeing the truth." -- Kate Douglas Wiggin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122874-rich-gifts-wax-poor-when-givers-prove-unkind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:58:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122874-rich-gifts-wax-poor-when-givers-prove-unkind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rich gifts wax poor when givers prove unkind." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178175-do-not-as-some-ungracious-pastors-do-show-me-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 01:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178175-do-not-as-some-ungracious-pastors-do-show-me-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not, as some ungracious pastors do,
Show me the steep and thorny way to heaven;
Whilst, like a puff'd and reckless libertine,
Himself the primrose path of dalliance treads
And recks not his own read." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443587-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:25:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443587-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care for myself.  The more solitary, the more friendless, the more I will respect myself.  I will keep the law given by God;  sanctioned by man.  I will hold the principles received by me when I was sane, not mad -- as I am now.  Laws and principles are not for times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be.  If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth? They have a worth -- so I have always believed; and if I cannot believe it now, it is because I am insane -- quite insane, with my veins running fire, and my heart beating faster than I can count its throbs.  Preconceived opinions, foregone determinations are all I have at this hour to stand; there I plant my foot." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94823-i-do-not-think-sir-you-have-any-right-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 00:26:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94823-i-do-not-think-sir-you-have-any-right-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not think, sir, you have any right to command me, merely because you are older than I, or because you have seen more of the world than I have; your claim to superiority depends on the use you have made of your time and experience." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467900-it-must-be-admitted-frankly-that-aunt-becky-was-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 17:50:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467900-it-must-be-admitted-frankly-that-aunt-becky-was-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It must be admitted frankly that Aunt Becky was not particularly beloved by her clan. She was too fond of telling them what she called the plain truth. And, as Uncle Pippin said, while the truth was all right, &lt;i&gt;in its place&lt;/i&gt;, there was no sense in pouring out great gobs of it around where it wasn't wanted. To Aunt Becky, however, tact and diplomacy and discretion, never to mention any consideration for any one's feelings, were things unknown." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
