<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772528-ben]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772528-ben" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:03:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53213-so-much-held-in-a-heart-in-a-lifetime-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:03:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Brian  Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53213-so-much-held-in-a-heart-in-a-lifetime-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So much held in a heart in a lifetime. So much held in a heart in a day, an hour, a moment. We are utterly open with no one, in the end -- not mother and father, not wife or husband, not lover, not child, not friend. We open windows to each but we live alone in the house of the heart. Perhaps we must. Perhaps we could not bear to be so naked, for fear of a constantly harrowed heart. When young we think there will come one person who will savor and sustain us always; when we are older we know this is the dream of a child, that all hearts finally are bruised and scarred, scored and torn, repaired by time and will, patched by force of character, yet fragile and rickety forevermore, no matter how ferocious the defense and how many bricks you bring to the wall. You can brick up your heart as stout and tight and hard and cold and impregnable as you possibly can and down it comes in an instant, felled by a woman's second glance, a child's apple breath, the shatter of glass in the road, the words 'I have something to tell you,' a cat with a broken spine dragging itself into the forest to die, the brush of your mother's papery ancient hand in a thicket of your hair, the memory of your father's voice early in the morning echoing from the kitchen where he is making pancakes for his children." -- Brian  Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53214-every-single-one-of-us-is-a-little-civilization-built</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:11:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53214-every-single-one-of-us-is-a-little-civilization-built]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every single one of us is a little civilization built on the ruins of any number of preceding civilizations, but with our own variant notions of what is beautiful and what is acceptable - which, I haste to add, we generally do not satisfy and by which we struggle to live." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53216-and-if-he-were-really-to-do-good-he-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:13:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Boris Pasternak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53216-and-if-he-were-really-to-do-good-he-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And if he were really to do good  he would have needed  in addition to his principles, a heart capable of violating them - a heart which knows only of particular  not of general  cases  and which achieves greatness in little actions." -- Boris Pasternak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7797-the-mind-i-love-must-have-wild-places-a-tangled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:19:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7797-the-mind-i-love-must-have-wild-places-a-tangled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind I love must have wild places, a tangled orchard where dark damsons drop in the heavy grass, an overgrown little wood, the chance of a snake or two, a pool that nobody's fathomed the depth of, and paths threaded with flowers planted by the mind." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 10:06:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53219-what-most-moved-me-in-his-letter-was-the-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:22:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53219-what-most-moved-me-in-his-letter-was-the-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What most moved me in his letter was the sense of frustration that permeated the lieutenent's words: the frustration of never quite being able to depict or explain anything to his full satisfaction." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53221-but-didn-t-you-say-you-were-satisfied-with-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53221-but-didn-t-you-say-you-were-satisfied-with-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But didn't you say you were satisfied with your life?&quot;

&quot;Word games,&quot; I dismissed. &quot;Every army needs a flag." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53222-it-is-a-good-thing-to-know-what-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2008 21:27:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53222-it-is-a-good-thing-to-know-what-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a good thing to know what it is to be poor, and a better thing if you can do it in company." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119950-whenever-in-my-dreams-i-see-the-dead-they-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 12:50:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119950-whenever-in-my-dreams-i-see-the-dead-they-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever in my dreams I see the dead, they always appear silent, bothered, strangely depressed, quite unlike their dear, bright selves. I am aware of them, without any astonishment, in surroundings they never visited during their earthly existence, in the house of some friend of mine they never knew. They sit apart, frowning at the floor, as if death were a dark taint, a shameful family secret. It is certainly not then - not in dreams - but when one is wide awake, at moments of robust joy and achievement, on the highest terrace of consciousness, that mortality has a chance to peer beyond its own limits, from the mast, from the past and its castle tower. And although nothing much can be seen through the mist, there is somehow the blissful feeling that one is looking in the right direction." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40093-you-are-lucky-to-be-one-of-those-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 08:11:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40093-you-are-lucky-to-be-one-of-those-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are lucky to be one of those people who wishes to build sand castles with words, who is willing to create a place where your imagination can wander.  We build this place with the sand of memories; these castles are our memories and inventiveness made tangible.  So part of us believes that when the tide starts coming in, we won't really have lost anything, because actually only a symbol of it was there in the sand.  Another part of us thinks we'll figure out a way to divert the ocean.  This is what separates artists from ordinary people: the belief, deep in our hearts, that if we build our castles well enough, somehow the ocean won't wash them away.  I think this is a wonderful kind of person to be." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151272-imagine-that-human-existence-is-defined-by-an-ache-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 12:37:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151272-imagine-that-human-existence-is-defined-by-an-ache-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine that human existence is defined by an Ache: the Ache of our not being, each of us, the center of the universe;  of our desires forever outnumbering our means of satisfying them." -- Jonathan Franzen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190377-i-glance-around-at-the-nest-we-have-made-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 16:58:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by John Updike]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190377-i-glance-around-at-the-nest-we-have-made-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I glance around at the nest we have made, at the floorboards polished by our bare feet, at the continents of stain on the ceiling like an old and all-wrong discoverer's map, at the earnestly bloated canvases I conscientiously cover with great streaks straining to say what even I am begining to suspect is the unsayable thing, and I grow frightened." -- John Updike]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190378-that-swimming-sloping-elusive-something-about-the-dark-bluish-tint-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 16:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190378-that-swimming-sloping-elusive-something-about-the-dark-bluish-tint-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...that swimming, sloping, elusive something about the dark-bluish tint of the iris which seemed still to retain the shadows it had absorbed of ancient, fabulous forests where there were more birds than tigers and more fruit than thorns, and where, in some dappled depth, man's mind had been born..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190379-when-i-loved-you-and-you-loved-me-you-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Charles Wagner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190379-when-i-loved-you-and-you-loved-me-you-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I loved you and you loved me,
You were the sky, the sea, the tree;
Now the skies are skies, and seas are seas,
And trees are brown and they are trees. " -- Charles Wagner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7335-our-souls-are-like-those-orphans-whose-unwedded-mothers-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:03:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7335-our-souls-are-like-those-orphans-whose-unwedded-mothers-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our souls are like those orphans whose unwedded mothers die in bearing them: the secret of our paternity lies in their grave, and we must there to learn it." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190382-there-are-these-rare-moments-when-musicians-together-touch-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:03:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190382-there-are-these-rare-moments-when-musicians-together-touch-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are these rare moments when musicians together touch something sweeter than they’ve ever found before in rehearsals or performance, beyond the merely collaborative or technically proficient, when their expression becomes as easy and graceful as friendship or love. This is when they give us a glimpse of what we might be, of our best selves, and of an impossible world in which you give everything you have to others, but lose nothing of yourself. Out in the real world there exist detailed plans, visionary projects for peaceable realms, all conflicts resolved, happiness for everyone, for ever - mirages for which people are prepared to die and kill. Christ's kingdom on earth, the workers' paradise, the ideal Islamic state. But only in music, and only on rare occasions, does the curtain actually lift on this dream of community, and it's tantalizingly conjured, before fading away with the last notes." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190384-books-lie-he-said-god-dont-lie-no-said-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190384-books-lie-he-said-god-dont-lie-no-said-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books lie, he said.
God dont lie.
No, said the judge. He does not. And these are his words.
He held up a chunk of rock.
He speaks in stones and trees, the bones of things.
The squatters in their rags nodded among themselves and were soon reckoning him correct, this man of learning, in all his speculations, and this the judge encouraged until they were right proselytes of the new order whereupon he laughed at them for fools." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190385-i-would-think-how-words-go-straight-up-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190385-i-would-think-how-words-go-straight-up-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I would think how words go straight up in a thin line, quick and harmless, and how terribly doing goes along the earth, clinging to it, so that after a while the two lines are too far apart for the same person to straddle from one to the other; and that sin and love and fear are just sounds that people who never sinned nor loved nor feared have for what they never had and cannot have until they forget the words." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190386-but-were-the-coming-narrative-to-reveal-in-any-instance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 17:12:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190386-but-were-the-coming-narrative-to-reveal-in-any-instance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But were the coming narrative to reveal in any instance, the complete abasement of poor Starbuck's fortitude, scarce might I have the heart to write it; for it is a thing most sorrowful, nay shocking, to expose the fall of valour in the soul. Men may seem detestable as joint stock-companies and nations; knaves, fools, and murderers there may be; men may have mean and meagre faces; but man, in the ideal, is so noble and so sparkling, such a grand and glowing creature, that over any ignominious blemish in him all his fellows should run to throw their costliest robes. That immaculate manliness we feel within ourselves, so far within us, that it remains intact though all the outer character seem gone; bleeds with keenest anguish at the undraped spectacle of a valor-ruined man. Nor can piety itself, at such a shameful sight, completely stifle her upbraidings against the permitting stars. But this august dignity I treat of, is not the dignity of kings and robes, but that abounding dignity which has no robed investiture. Thou shalt see it shining in the arm that wields a pick or drives a spike; that democratic dignity which, on all hands, radiates without end from God; Himself! The great God absolute! The centre and circumference of all democracy! His omnipresence, our divine equality! " -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191326-he-had-said-i-am-a-man-and-that-meant</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 21:59:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191326-he-had-said-i-am-a-man-and-that-meant]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had said, &quot;I am a man,&quot; and that meant certain things to Juana.  It meant that he was half insane and half god.  It meant that Kino would drive his strength against a mountain and plunge his strength against the sea.  Juana, in her woman's soul, knew that the mountain would stand while the man broke himself; that the sea would surge while the man drowned in it.  And yet it was this thing that made him a man, half insane and half god, and Juana had need of a man; she could not live without a man." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17370-originality-is-the-fine-art-of-remembering-what-you-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 19:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Lawrence J. Peter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17370-originality-is-the-fine-art-of-remembering-what-you-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Originality is the fine art of remembering what you hear but forgetting where you heard it." -- Lawrence J. Peter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204424-in-this-personal-existence-of-ours-bounded-as-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 10:46:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by George F. Keenan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204424-in-this-personal-existence-of-ours-bounded-as-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this personal existence of ours, bounded as it is at both ends by suffering and uncertainty, and constantly attended by the possibility of illness and accident and tragedy, total security is likewise a myth.  Here, too, an anxious perfectionism can operate to destroy those real underpinnings of existence, founded in faith, modesty, humor, and a sense of relativity, on which alone a tolerable human existence can be built.  The first criterion of a healthy spirit is the ability to walk cheerfully and sensibly amid the congenital uncertainties of existence, to recognize as natural the inevitable precariousness of the human condition, to accept this without being disoriented by it, and to live effectively and usefully in its shadow." -- George F. Keenan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244057-the-answer-must-be-i-think-that-beauty-and-grace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2010 22:12:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244057-the-answer-must-be-i-think-that-beauty-and-grace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer must be, I think, that beauty and grace are performed whether or not we will or sense them.  The least we can do is try to be there." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260558-they-are-able-to-forgive-themselves-as-a-wise-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 18:09:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Charles Van Doren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260558-they-are-able-to-forgive-themselves-as-a-wise-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...they are able to forgive themselves, as a wise man once said, for being human.  That is knowing that life is hard and virtue rare, they keep the ancient faith that it is better to love than to hate, to live fully even if imperfectly." -- Charles Van Doren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117747-for-it-is-said-that-humans-are-never-satisfied-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 18:10:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117747-for-it-is-said-that-humans-are-never-satisfied-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it is said that humans are never satisfied, that you give them one thing and they want something more. And this is said in disparagement, whereas it is one of the greatest talents the species has and one that has made it superior to animals that are satisfied with what they have." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260560-as-you-get-older-it-is-harder-to-have-heroes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 18:15:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260560-as-you-get-older-it-is-harder-to-have-heroes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As you get older it is harder to have heroes, but it is sort of necessary." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18287-i-don-t-like-work--no-man-does--but-i-like-what-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 18:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18287-i-don-t-like-work--no-man-does--but-i-like-what-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't like work--no man does--but I like what is in the work--the chance to find yourself. Your own reality--for yourself not for others--what no other man can ever know. They can only see the mere show, and never can tell what it really means." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260563-it-was-odd-she-thought-how-if-one-was-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 18:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260563-it-was-odd-she-thought-how-if-one-was-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was odd, she thought, how if one was alone, one leant to inanimate things; trees, streams, flowers; felt they expressed one; felt they became one; felt they knew one, in a sense were one; felt an irrational tenderness thus (she looked at that long steady light) as for oneself." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35845-spend-the-afternoon-you-can-t-take-it-with-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 10:46:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35845-spend-the-afternoon-you-can-t-take-it-with-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spend the afternoon, you can't take it with you." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312944-a-wonderful-fact-to-reflect-upon-that-every-human-creature</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 16:05:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312944-a-wonderful-fact-to-reflect-upon-that-every-human-creature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wonderful fact to reflect upon, that every human creature is constituted to be that profound secret and mystery to every other. A solemn consideration, when I enter a great city by night, that every one of those darkly clustered houses encloses its own secret; that every room in every one of them encloses its own secret; that every beating heart in the hundreds of thousands of breasts there, is, in some of its imaginings, a secret to the heart nearest it! Something of the awfulness, even of Death itself, is referable to this. No more can I turn the leaves of this dear book that I loved, and vainly hope in time to read it all. No more can I look into the depths of this unfathomable water, wherein, as momentary lights glanced into it, I have had glimpses of buried treasure and other things submerged. It was appointed that the book should shut with a a spring, for ever and for ever, when I had read but a page. It was appointed that the water should be locked in an eternal frost, when the light was playing on its surface, and I stood in ignorance on the shore. My friend is dead, my neighbour is dead, my love, the darling of my soul, is dead; it is the inexorable consolidation and perpetuation of the secret that was always in that individuality, and which I shall carry in mine to my life's end. In any of the burial-places of this city through which I pass, is there a sleeper more inscrutable than its busy inhabitants are, in their innermost personality, to me, or than I am to them?" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
