<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772667-shane-avery]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772667-shane-avery" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 18:27:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32538-there-is-no-such-thing-in-a-civilized-society-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 18:27:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Edward Bellamy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32538-there-is-no-such-thing-in-a-civilized-society-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no such thing in a civilized society as self-support.  In a state of society so barbarous as not even to know family cooperation, each individual may possibly support himself, though even then for a part of his life only; but from the moment that men begin to live together, and constitute even the rudest of society, self-support becomes impossible.  As men grow more civilized, and the subdivision of occupations and services is carried out, a complex mutual dependence becomes the universal rule.  Every man, however solitary may seem his occupation, is a member of a vast industrial partnership, as large as the nation, as large as humanity.  The necessity of mutual dependence should imply the duty and guarantee of mutual support..." -- Edward Bellamy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105509-men-have-unlearned-the-ability-to-recognize-the-godly-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 21:09:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Hans Cornelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105509-men-have-unlearned-the-ability-to-recognize-the-godly-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men have unlearned the ability to recognize the godly in themselves and in things: nature and art, family and state have only interest for them as sensations.  Therefore their lives flow meaninglessly by, and their shared culture is inwardly empty and will collapse because it is worthy of collapse." -- Hans Cornelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134871-thus-we-arrive-at-the-singular-conclusion-that-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 17:55:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134871-thus-we-arrive-at-the-singular-conclusion-that-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus we arrive at the singular conclusion that of all the information passed by our cultural assets it is precisely the elements which might be of the greatest importance to us and which have the task of solving the riddles of the universe and of reconciling us to the sufferings of life -- it is precisely those elements that are the least well authenticated of any." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135138-we-need-not-deplore-the-renunciation-of-historical-truth-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 14:45:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135138-we-need-not-deplore-the-renunciation-of-historical-truth-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need not deplore the renunciation of historical truth when we put forward rational grounds for the precepts of civilization.  The truths contained in religious doctrines are after all so distorted and systematically disguised that the mass of humanity cannot recognize them as truth.  The case is similar to what happens when we tell a child that new-born babies are brought by the stork.  Here, too, we are telling the truth in symbolic clothing, for we &lt;i&gt; know what the large bird signifies &lt;/i&gt;.  But the child does not know it.  He hears only the distorted part of what we say, and feels that he has been deceived; and we know how often his distrust of the grown-ups and his refractoriness actually take their start from this impression.  We have become convinced that it is better to avoid such symbolic  disguisings of the truth in what we tell children and not to withhold from them a knowledge of the true state of affairs commensurate with their intellectual level." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135150-thus-i-must-contradict-you-when-you-go-on-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 15:26:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135150-thus-i-must-contradict-you-when-you-go-on-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus I must contradict you when you go on to argue that men are completely unable to do without the consolation of the religious illusion, that without it they could not bear the troubles of life and the cruelties of reality.  That is true, certainly, of the men into whom you have instilled the sweet -- or bitter-sweet -- poison from childhood onwards.  But what of the other men, who have been sensibly brought up?  Perhaps those who do not suffer from the neurosis will need no intoxicant to deaden it.  They will, it is true, find themselves in a difficult situation.  They will have to admit to themselves the full extent of their helplessness and their insignificance in the machinery of the universe; they can no longer be the centre of creation, no longer the object of tender care on the part of a beneficent Providence.  They will be in the same position as a child who has left the parental house where he was so warm and comfortable.  But surely infantilism is destined to be surmounted.  Men cannot remain children for ever; they must in the end go out into 'hostile life'.  We may call this '&lt;i&gt;education to reality&lt;/i&gt;.  Need I confess to you that the whole purpose of my book is to point out the necessity for this forward step?" -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135154-scientific-knowledge-has-taught-humans-much-since-the-days-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 15:36:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135154-scientific-knowledge-has-taught-humans-much-since-the-days-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["scientific knowledge has taught [humans] much since the days of the Deluge, and it will increase their power still further.  And, as for the great necessities of Fate, against which there is no help, they will learn to endure them with resignation.  Of what use to them is the mirage of wide acres in the moon, whose harvest no one has ever yet seen?  As honest smallholders on this earth they will know how to cultivate their plot in such a way that it supports them.  By withdrawing their expectations from the other world and concentrating all their liberated energies into their life on earth, they will probably succeed in achieving a state of things in which life will become tolerable for everyone and civilization no longer oppressive to anyone.  Then, with one of our fellow-unbelievers, they will be able to say without regret: 'We leave Heaven to the angels and the sparrows." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136897-the-time-comes-when-each-of-us-has-to-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 14:46:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136897-the-time-comes-when-each-of-us-has-to-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time comes when each of us has to give up as illusions the expectations which, in his youth, he pinned upon his fellow-men, and when he may learn how much difficulty and pain has been added to his life by their ill-will." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137168-the-commandment-love-thy-neighbour-as-thyself-is-the-strongest</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2009 14:05:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137168-the-commandment-love-thy-neighbour-as-thyself-is-the-strongest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The commandment, 'Love thy neighbour as thyself', is the strongest defence against human aggressiveness and an excellent example of the unpsychological [expectations] of the cultural super-ego.  The commandment is impossible to fulfil; such an enormous inflation of love can only lower its value, not get rid of the difficulty.  Civilization pays no attention to all this; it merely admonishes us that the harder it is to obey the precept the more meritorious it is to do so.  But anyone who follows such a precept in present-day civilization only puts himself at a disadvantage &lt;i&gt; vis-a-vis &lt;/i&gt; the person who disregards it.  What a potent obstacle to civilization aggressiveness must be, if the defence against it can cause as much unhappiness as aggressiveness itself!  'Natural' ethics, as it is called, has nothing to offer here except the narcissistic satisfaction of being able to think oneself better than others.  At this point the ethics based on religion introduces its promises of a better after-life.  But so long as virtue is not rewarded here on earth, ethics will, I fancy, preach in vain.  I too think it quite certain that a real change in the relations of human beings to possessions would be of more help in this direction than any ethical commands; but the recognition of this fact among socialists has been obscured and made useless for practical purposes by a fresh idealistic misconception of human nature." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139421-the-bourgeoisie-wherever-it-has-got-the-upper-hand-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 18:10:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Karl Marx; Friedrich Engels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139421-the-bourgeoisie-wherever-it-has-got-the-upper-hand-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bourgeoisie, wherever it has got the upper hand, has put an end to all feudal, patriarchal, idyllic relations.  It has pitilessly torn asunder the motley feudal ties that bound man to his &quot;natural superiors,&quot; and has left remaining no other nexus between man and man than naked self-interest, than callous &quot;cash payment.&quot;  It has drowned the most heavenly ecstasies of religious fervour, of chivalrous enthusiasm, of philistine sentimentalism, in the icy water of egotistical calculation.  It has resolved personal worth into exchange value, and in place of the numberless indefeasible chartered freedoms, has set up that single, unconscionable freedom -- Free Trade.  It one word, for exploitation, veiled by religious and political illusions, it has substituted naked, shameless, direct, brutal exploitation." -- Karl Marx; Friedrich Engels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150175-woe-to-you-my-princess-when-i-come-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 19:34:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150175-woe-to-you-my-princess-when-i-come-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Woe to you, my Princess, when I come.  I will kiss you quite red and feed you till you are plump.  And if you are froward, you shall see who is the stronger, a gentle little girl who doesn't eat enough, or a big wild man who has cocaine in his body. -- A love letter from Freud to his fiancée." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153166-what-time-has-been-wasted-during-man-s-destiny-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 14:30:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Sean O'Casey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153166-what-time-has-been-wasted-during-man-s-destiny-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What time has been wasted during man's destiny in the struggle to decide what man's next world will be like! The keener the effort to find out, the less he knew about the present one he lived in. The one lovely world he knew, lived in, that gave him all he had, was, according to preacher and prelate, the one to be least in his thoughts. He was recommended, ordered, from the day of his birth to bid goodbye to it. Oh, we have had enough of the abuse of this fair earth! It is no sad truth that this should be our home. Were it but to give us simple shelter, simple clothing, simple food, adding the lily and the rose, the apple and the pear, it would be a fit home for mortal or immortal man." -- Sean O'Casey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153386-every-sound-reason-is-on-the-side-of-law-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 17:41:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153386-every-sound-reason-is-on-the-side-of-law-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every sound reason is on the side of law and order in their insistence that the eternity of joy be reserved for the hereafter, and in their endeavor to subordinate the struggle against death and disease to the never-ceasing requirements of national and international security." -- Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153387-under-conditions-of-a-truly-human-existence-the-difference-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2009 17:55:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153387-under-conditions-of-a-truly-human-existence-the-difference-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Under conditions of a truly human existence, the difference between succumbing to disease at the age of ten, thirty, fifty, or seventy, and dying a &quot;natural&quot; death after a fulfilled life, may well be a difference worth fighting for with all instinctual energy.  Not those who die, but those who die before they must and want to die, those who die in agony and pain, are the great indictment against civilization.  They also testify to the unredeemable guilt of mankind.  Their death arouses the painful awareness that it was unnecessary, that it could be otherwise.  It takes all the institutions and values of a repressive order to pacify the bad conscience of this guilt.  Once again, the deep connection between the death instinct and the sense of guilt becomes apparent.  The silent &quot;professional agreement&quot; with the fact of death and disease is perhaps one of the most widespread expressions of the death instinct -- or, rather, of its social usefulness.  In a repressive civilization, death itself becomes an instrument of repression.  Whether death is feared as constant threat, or glorified as supreme sacrifice, or accepted as fate, the education for consent to death introduces an element of surrender into life from the beginning -- surrender and submission.  It stifles &quot;utopian&quot; efforts.  The powers that be have a deep affinity to death; death is a token of unfreedom, of defeat.  Theology and philosophy today compete with each other in celebrating death as an existential category: perverting a biological fact into an ontological essence, they bestow transcendental blessing on the guilt of mankind which they help to perpetuate -- they betray the promise of utopia." -- Herbert Marcuse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154858-freedom-is-not-a-constant-attribute-which-we-either-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2009 18:05:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shane add a quote by Erich Fromm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154858-freedom-is-not-a-constant-attribute-which-we-either-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom is not a constant attribute which we either &quot;have&quot; or &quot;have not.&quot;  In fact, there is no such thing as &quot;freedom&quot; except as a word and an abstract concept.  There is only one reality: the &lt;i&gt; act &lt;/i&gt; of freeing ourselves in the process of making choices.  In this process the degree of our capacity to make choices varies with each act, with our practice of life." -- Erich Fromm]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
