<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772625-michael-newnham]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/772625-michael-newnham" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:23:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327442-your-faith-will-not-fail-while-god-sustains-it-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:23:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by J.I. Packer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327442-your-faith-will-not-fail-while-god-sustains-it-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your faith will not fail while God sustains it; you are not strong enough to fall away while God is resolved to hold you." -- J.I. Packer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215182-god-uses-chronic-pain-and-weakness-along-with-other-afflictions</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:23:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by J.I. Packer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215182-god-uses-chronic-pain-and-weakness-along-with-other-afflictions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God uses chronic pain and weakness, along with other afflictions, as his chisel for sculpting our lives. Felt weakness deepens dependence on Christ for strength each day. The weaker we feel, the harder we lean. And the harder we lean, the stronger we grow spiritually, even while our bodies waste away. To live with your ‘thorn’ uncomplainingly — that is, sweet, patient, and free in heart to love and help others, even though every day you feel weak — is true sanctification. It is true healing for the spirit. It is a supreme victory of grace." -- J.I. Packer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275720-optimism-hopes-for-the-best-without-any-guarantee-of-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:23:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michael add a quote by J. I. Packer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275720-optimism-hopes-for-the-best-without-any-guarantee-of-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Optimism hopes for the best without any guarantee of its arriving and is often no more than whistling in the dark. Christian hope, by contrast, is faith looking ahead to the fulfillment of the promises of God, as when the Anglican burial service inters the corpse 'in sure and certain hope of the Resurrection to eternal life, through our Lord Jesus Christ.' Optimism is a wish without warrant; Christian hope is a certainty, guaranteed by God himself. Optimism reflects ignorance as to whether good things will ever actually come. Christian hope expresses knowledge that every day of his life, and every moment beyond it, the believer can say with truth, on the basis of God's own commitment, that the best is yet to come." -- J. I. Packer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
