<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/773462-kyle-harris]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/773462-kyle-harris" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:04:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26479-no-sense-of-the-irony-of-human-experience-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26479-no-sense-of-the-irony-of-human-experience-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No sense of the irony of human experience, that we are the highest form of life on earth, and yet ineffably sad because we know what no other animal knows, that we must die." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26485-i-ve-got-death-inside-me-it-s-just-a-question-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:05:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26485-i-ve-got-death-inside-me-it-s-just-a-question-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've got death inside me. It's just a question of whether or not I can outlive it." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:06:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TO BE HOPEFUL in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness.
What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places—and there are so many—where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction.
And if we do act, in however small a way, we don’t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:07:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was love at first sight, at last sight, at ever and ever sight." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936-study-hard-what-interests-you-the-most-in-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 16:09:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Richard Feynmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/936-study-hard-what-interests-you-the-most-in-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Study hard what interests you the most in the most undisciplined, irreverent and original manner possible." -- Richard Feynmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52089-to-me-history-ought-to-be-a-source-of-pleasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2010 17:46:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52089-to-me-history-ought-to-be-a-source-of-pleasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me, history ought to be a source of pleasure. It isn't just part of our civic responsibility. To me, it's an enlargement of the experience of being alive, just the way literature or art or music is.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;The Title Always Comes Last&lt;/i&gt;; NEH 2003 Jefferson Lecturer interview profile]" -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637-i-hate-to-advocate-drugs-alcohol-violence-or-insanity-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 17:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637-i-hate-to-advocate-drugs-alcohol-violence-or-insanity-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate to advocate drugs, alcohol, violence, or insanity to anyone, but they've always worked for me." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 12:08:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 12:10:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165398-there-s-good-self-consciousness-and-then-there-s-toxic-paralyzing-raped-by-psychic-bedouins-self-</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 12:11:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165398-there-s-good-self-consciousness-and-then-there-s-toxic-paralyzing-raped-by-psychic-bedouins-self-]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's good self-consciousness, and then there's toxic, paralyzing, raped-by-psychic-Bedouins self-consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144180-i-had-kind-of-a-midlife-crisis-at-twenty-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 12:12:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144180-i-had-kind-of-a-midlife-crisis-at-twenty-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had kind of a midlife crisis at twenty  which probably doesn’t augur well for my longevity" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 22:23:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kyle add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The so-called ‘psychotically depressed’ person who tries to kill herself doesn’t do so out of quote ‘hopelessness’ or any abstract conviction that life’s assets and debits do not square. And surely not because death seems suddenly appealing. The person in whom Its invisible agony reaches a certain unendurable level will kill herself the same way a trapped person will eventually jump from the window of a burning high-rise. Make no mistake about people who leap from burning windows. Their terror of falling from a great height is still just as great as it would be for you or me standing speculatively at the same window just checking out the view; i.e. the fear of falling remains a constant. The variable here is the other terror, the fire’s flames: when the flames get close enough, falling to death becomes the slightly less terrible of two terrors. It’s not desiring the fall; it’s terror of the flames. And yet nobody down on the sidewalk, looking up and yelling ‘Don’t!’ and ‘Hang on!’, can understand the jump. Not really. You’d have to have personally been trapped and felt flames to really understand a terror way beyond falling." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
