<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/774983-patsy-mcquade]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/774983-patsy-mcquade" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 22:45:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162142-i-suspect-the-most-we-can-hope-for-and-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 22:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162142-i-suspect-the-most-we-can-hope-for-and-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suspect the most we can hope for, and it's no small hope, is that we never give up, that we never stop giving ourselves permission to try to love and receive love." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277680-the-only-difference-between-obama-and-bush-is-that-obama</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2013 10:25:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Penn Jillette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277680-the-only-difference-between-obama-and-bush-is-that-obama]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only difference between Obama and Bush is that Obama is killing more people. He’s about double the numbers now. Can you imagine if McCain had won and did precisely what Obama has done, with every speech and every political maneuver overseas? There’d be riots in the streets about the people we’re killing. And yet because it’s Obama, and he’s better looking and better at reading the teleprompter, we let him get away with it." -- Penn Jillette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010606-alexander-assured-her-eva-none-of-us-know-our-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:19:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Sue Townsend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1010606-alexander-assured-her-eva-none-of-us-know-our-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alexander assured her, 'Eva, none of us know our children.  Because they are not us." -- Sue Townsend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728750-will-you-lie-to-me-and-promise-to-read-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 16:30:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Sue Townsend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728750-will-you-lie-to-me-and-promise-to-read-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Will you lie to me and promise to read them? Books need to be read. The pages need to be turned." -- Sue Townsend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353288-even-under-the-best-of-circumstances-there-s-just-something-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:51:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353288-even-under-the-best-of-circumstances-there-s-just-something-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even under the best of circumstances, there's just something so damn tragic about growing up." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280426-you-re-terrified-of-being-alone-anything-you-do-now-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:51:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280426-you-re-terrified-of-being-alone-anything-you-do-now-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're terrified of being alone. Anything you do now will be motivated by that fear. You have to stop worrying about finding love again. It will come when it comes. Get comfortable with being alone. It will empower you." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353559-it-would-be-a-terrible-mistake-to-go-through-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:51:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353559-it-would-be-a-terrible-mistake-to-go-through-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be a terrible mistake to go through life thinking that people are the sum total of what you see." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211892-we-all-start-out-so-damn-sure-thinking-we-ve-got</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:52:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211892-we-all-start-out-so-damn-sure-thinking-we-ve-got]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all start out so damn sure, thinking we've got the world on a string. If we ever stopped to think about the infinite number of ways we could be undone, we'd never leave our bedrooms." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280425-you-have-to-look-at-what-you-have-right-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:52:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280425-you-have-to-look-at-what-you-have-right-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to look at what you have right in front of you, at what it could be, and stop measuring it against what you've lost. I know this to be wise and true, just as I know that pretty much no one can do it." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211891-we-are-all-smiling-in-the-picture-three-brothers-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:52:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211891-we-are-all-smiling-in-the-picture-three-brothers-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all smiling in the picture, three brothers having a grand old time just playing around in the living room, no agendas, no buried resentments or permanent scars. Even under the best of circumstances, there's just something so damn tragic about growing up." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324996-we-are-injured-and-angry-scared-and-sad-some-families</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 12:52:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324996-we-are-injured-and-angry-scared-and-sad-some-families]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are injured and angry, scared and sad. Some families, like some couples, become toxic to each other after prolonged exposure." -- Jonathan Tropper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403228-how-can-you-come-to-understand-your-life-when-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:45:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403228-how-can-you-come-to-understand-your-life-when-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can you come to understand your life when even the beginning is so complicated: a single cell imprinted with the color of your eyes and the shape of your face the pattern on your palm and the moods that will shadow you through your life. How can you be alive when every choice you make breaks the world into a thousand filaments each careless step branching into long tributaries of alternate lives shuddering outward and outward like sheet lightning." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63940-there-is-hardly-anything-at-all-his-life-is-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:49:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63940-there-is-hardly-anything-at-all-his-life-is-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is hardly anything at all. His life is suddenly a large, empty house, with each vacant room waiting to be furnished. His made-up wife. His invented father. His pretend childhood. He wonders if it is possible to unlie yourself. " -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410389-what-if-she-never-knows-the-end-of-the-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:49:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410389-what-if-she-never-knows-the-end-of-the-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if she never knows the end of the story? She shudders, and her mind continues to lurch forward into the future, that simple expectation of time passing - another moment, and another moment. It seems impossible that it will abruptly cease. It seems impossible that you will never know what happens next, that the thread you've been following your whole life will just... cut off, like a book with the last pages torn out. That doesn't seem fair, she thinks." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63938-sometimes-he-thinks-that-if-he-could-only-trace-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:50:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63938-sometimes-he-thinks-that-if-he-could-only-trace-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes he thinks that if he could only trace the path of his life carefully enough, everything would become clear. The ways that he screwed up would make sense. He closes his eyes tightly. His life wasn't always a mistake, he thinks, and he breathes uncertainly for awhile, trying to find a pathway into unconsciousness, into sleep. " -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403230-the-true-terror-jonah-thought-the-true-mystery-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:51:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403230-the-true-terror-jonah-thought-the-true-mystery-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true terror Jonah thought the true mystery of life was not that we are all going to die but that we were all born that we were all once little babies like this unknowing and slowly reeling in the world gathering it loop by loop like a ball of string. The true terror was that we once didn't exist and then through no fault of our own we had to." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459131-the-baby-s-large-eyes-settled-on-him-and-though-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:52:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/459131-the-baby-s-large-eyes-settled-on-him-and-though-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The baby's large eyes settled on him, and though this has been one of his happiest nights in his whole life, it made him melancholy.  He had read somewhere that babies are instinctively drawn to faces, that they will fixate even on drawings or abstract, facelike shapes, and round objects with markings that might resemble eye-mouth-nose.  It was information that struck him as terribly sad, terribly lonely - to imagine the infants of the world scoping the blurry atmosphere above them for faces the way primitive people scrutinized the stars for patterns, the way castaways stare at the moon, the blinking of a satellite.  It made him sad to think of the baby gathering information - a mind, a soul, slowly solidifying around these impressions, coming to understand cause and effect, coming out of a blank or fog into reality.  Into a reality.  The true terror, Jonah thought, the true mystery of life was not that we are all going to die, but that we were all born, that we were all once little babies like this, unknowing and slowly reeling in the world, gathering it loop by loop like a ball of string.  The true terror was that we once didn't exist and then, through no fault of our own, we had to." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518722-her-name-was-mrs-marina-orlova-and-she-had-grown-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:52:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518722-her-name-was-mrs-marina-orlova-and-she-had-grown-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her name...was Mrs. marina Orlova, and she had grown up in Siberia.  Later, she would tell him that she loathed the American custom of constantly smiling:  &quot;They are like chimpanzees,&quot; she said, in her bitter exclamatory voice.  She grimaced, baring her teeth grotesquely.  &quot;Eee!&quot; she said.  &quot;I smile at you!  Eee!  It is repulsive." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017677-the-first-time-she-had-tried-to-kill-herself-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:53:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017677-the-first-time-she-had-tried-to-kill-herself-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first time she had tried to kill herself, she had intuited that there was no escape.  She had seen, with sudden clarity,  that her life was a series of boxes, a maze that she would run and run through and never find an exit, and she thought, almost peacefully, I don't want it.  I don't want my life." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920039-it-s-hard-to-believe-that-this-is-how-it-s-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 11:53:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Dan Chaon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920039-it-s-hard-to-believe-that-this-is-how-it-s-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's hard to believe that this is how it's done. That this is how we get here into the world, by accident or design, the microscopic pieces of ourselves borne by fluids and blood and growing into a tiny kingdom of cells inside someone else's body. It seems so difficult to become alive. So improbable. . . 
	How can it be possible? she wonders. How can you come to understand your life when even the beginning is so complicated: a single cell imprinted with the color of your eyes and the shape of your face, the pattern on your palm and the moods that will shadow you through your life. How can you be alive when every choice you make breaks the world into a thousand filaments, each careless step branching into long tributaries of alternate lives, shuddering outward and outward like sheet lightning." -- Dan Chaon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715844-she-liked-people-me-i-can-take-them-or-leave</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 12:02:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patsy add a quote by Sue Townsend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715844-she-liked-people-me-i-can-take-them-or-leave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She liked people. Me, I can take them or leave them, but mostly leave them." -- Sue Townsend]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
