<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77608-alison]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77608-alison" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 17:42:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525698-the-story-is-told-that-when-joe-was-a-child</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 17:42:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[alison add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525698-the-story-is-told-that-when-joe-was-a-child]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story is told that when Joe was a child his cousins emptied his Christmas stocking and replaced the gifts with horse manure. Joe took one look and bolted for the door, eyes glittering with excitement. 'Wait, Joe, where are you going? What did ol' Santa bring you?' According to the story Joe paused at the door for a piece of rope. 'Brought me a bran'-new pony but he got away. I'll catch 'em if I hurry.' And ever since then it seemed that Joe had been accepting more than his share of hardship as good fortune, and more than his share of shit as a sign of Shetland ponies just around the corner, Thoroughbred stallions just up the road." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356910-touch-it-is-touch-that-is-the-deadliest-enemy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 16:21:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[alison add a quote by Wallace Stegner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356910-touch-it-is-touch-that-is-the-deadliest-enemy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Touch.  It is touch that is the deadliest enemy of chastity, loyalty, monogamy, gentility with its codes and conventions and restraints.  By touch we are betrayed and betray others ... an accidental brushing of shoulders or touching of hands ... hands laid on shoulders in a gesture of comfort that lies like a thief, that takes, not gives, that wants, not offers, that awakes, not pacifies.  When one flesh is waiting, there is electricity in the merest contact." -- Wallace Stegner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
