<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/776233-kristin-marie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/776233-kristin-marie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 21:19:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167628-time-baby---so-much-so-much-time-left-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 21:19:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167628-time-baby---so-much-so-much-time-left-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time, Baby - so much, so much time left until the end of my life - sometimes I go crazy at how slowly time passes yet how quickly my body ages.
But I shouldn't allow myself to think like this. I have to remind myself that time only frightens me when I think of having to spend it alone. Sometimes I scare myself with how many of my thoughts revolve around making me feel better about sleeping alone in a room." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:46:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59937-everyone-at-some-point-in-their-lives-wakes-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone, at some point in their lives, wakes up in the middle of the night with the feeling that they are all alone in the world, and that nobody loves them now and that nobody will ever love them, and that they will never have a decent night's sleep again and will spend their lives wandering blearily around a loveless landscape, hoping desperately that their circumstances will improve, but suspecting, in their heart of hearts, that they will remain unloved forever. The best thing to do in these circumstances is to wake somebody else up, so that they can feel this way, too." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31008-a-good-library-will-never-be-too-neat-or-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:46:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31008-a-good-library-will-never-be-too-neat-or-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good library will never be too neat, or too dusty, because somebody will always be in it, taking books off the shelves and staying up late reading them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102256-wishing-like-sipping-a-glass-of-punch-or-pulling-aside</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:47:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102256-wishing-like-sipping-a-glass-of-punch-or-pulling-aside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wishing, like sipping a glass of punch, or pulling aside a bearskin rug in order to access a hidden trapdoor in the floor, is merely a quiet way to spend one's time before the candles are extinguished on one's birthday cake." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268417-unless-you-have-been-very-very-lucky-you-have-undoubtedly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 17:47:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268417-unless-you-have-been-very-very-lucky-you-have-undoubtedly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless you have been very, very lucky, you have undoubtedly experienced events in your life that have made you cry. So unless you have been very, very lucky, you know that a good, long session of weeping can often make you feel better, even if your circumstances have not changed one bit." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100637-and-then-i-felt-sad-because-i-realized-that-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then I felt sad because I realized that once people are broken in certain ways, they can't ever be fixed, and this is something nobody ever tells you when you are young and it never fails to surprise you as you grow older as you see the people in your life break one by one. You wonder when your turn is going to be, or if it's already happened." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79587-in-the-end-i-think-the-relationships-that-survive-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:39:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79587-in-the-end-i-think-the-relationships-that-survive-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, I think the relationships that survive in this world are the ones where  two people can finish each other's sentences. Forget drama and torrid sex and the clash of opposites. Give me banter any day of the week. " -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80653-i-am-going-to-give-you-a-piece-of-advice</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:40:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80653-i-am-going-to-give-you-a-piece-of-advice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am going to give you a piece of advice... advice I wish I'd been told in guidance class back in high school, in between the don't-do-acid and don't-drink-and-drive films. I wish our counselors had told us, 'When you grow older a dreadful, horrible sensation will come over you. It's called loneliness, and you think you know what it is now, but you don't. Here is the list of the symptoms, and don't worry—loneliness is the most universal sensation on the planet. Just remember one fact—loneliness will pass. You will survive and you will be a better human for it." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:40:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148090-when-you-re-young-you-always-feel-that-life-hasn-t-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you're young, you always feel that life hasn't yet begun—that &quot;life&quot; is always scheduled to begin next week, next month, next year, after the holidays—whenever.  But then suddenly you're old and the scheduled life didn't arrive.  You find yourself asking, 'Well then, exactly what was it I was having—that interlude—the scrambly madness—all that time I had before?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10941-my-secret-is-that-i-need-god-that-i-am-sick</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10941-my-secret-is-that-i-need-god-that-i-am-sick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My secret is that I need God—that I am sick and can no longer make it alone. I need God to help me give, because I no longer seem to be capable of giving; to help me be kind, as I no longer seem capable of kindness; to help me love, as I seem beyond being able to love." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69188-i-think-that-every-reader-on-earth-has-a-list</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69188-i-think-that-every-reader-on-earth-has-a-list]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that every reader on earth has a list of cherished books as unique as their fingerprints....I think that, as you age, you tend to gravitate towards the classics, but those aren't the books that give you the same sort of hope for the world that a cherished book does." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134374-question-if-there-were-two-of-you-which-one-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134374-question-if-there-were-two-of-you-which-one-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: If there were two of you which one would win?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182265-so-where-do-you-start-when-you-want-to-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:43:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182265-so-where-do-you-start-when-you-want-to-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So where do you start when you want to start your life again?" -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130606-believe-that-you-ve-had-most-of-your-important-memories-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:43:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130606-believe-that-you-ve-had-most-of-your-important-memories-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["believe that you've had most of your important memories by the time you're thirty. After that, memory becomes water overflowing into an already full cup. New experiences just don't register in the same way or with the same impact. I could be shooting heroin with the Princess of Wales, naked in a crashing jet, and the experience still couldn't compare to the time the cops chased us after we threw the Taylors' patio furniture into their pool in eleventh grade." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150954-everybody-has-a-gripping-stranger-in-their-lives-andy-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:43:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150954-everybody-has-a-gripping-stranger-in-their-lives-andy-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a ‘gripping stranger’ in their lives, Andy, a stranger who unwittingly possesses a bizarre hold over you. Maybe it’s the kid in cut-offs who mows your lawn or the woman wearing White Shoulders who stamps your book at the library—a stranger who, if you were to come home and find a message from them on your answering machine saying ‘Drop everything. I love you. Come away with me now to Florida,’ you’d follow them." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152287-my-mind-then-wandered-i-thought-of-this-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:44:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152287-my-mind-then-wandered-i-thought-of-this-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mind then wandered.  I thought of this: I thought of how every day each of us experiences a few little moments that have just a bit more resonance than other moments—we hear a word that sticks in our mind—or maybe we have a small experience that pulls us out of ourselves, if only briefly—we share a hotel elevator with a bride in her veils, say, or a stranger gives us a piece of bread to feed to the mallard ducks in the lagoon; a small child starts a conversation with us in a Dairy Queen—or we have an episode like the one I had with the M&amp;M cars back at the Husky station.

        And if we were to collect these small moments in a notebook and save them over a period of months we would see certain trends emerge from our collection—certain voices would emerge that have been trying to speak through us.  We would realize that we have been having another life altogether; one we didn’t even know was going on inside us.  And maybe this other life is more important than the one we think of as being real—this clunky day-to-day world of furniture and noise and metal.  So just maybe it is these small silent moments which are the true story-making events of our lives." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182105-inasmuch-as-i-am-a-spiritual-man-i-do-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:46:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182105-inasmuch-as-i-am-a-spiritual-man-i-do-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inasmuch as I am a spiritual man, I do believe in God - I think that He created an
order for the world; I believe that, in constantly bombarding Him with requests for miracles,
we're also asking that He unravel the fabric of the world. A world of continuous miracles
would be a cartoon, not a world." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276827-there-are-three-things-we-cry-for-in-life-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276827-there-are-three-things-we-cry-for-in-life-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there are three things we cry for in life: things that are lost, things that are found, and things that are magnificent." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182257-sometimes-i-think-god-is-like-weather---you-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 19:49:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182257-sometimes-i-think-god-is-like-weather---you-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I think God is like weather - you may not like
the weather, but it has nothing to do with you. You just happen to be there. Deal with it. Sadness
and grief are part of being human and always will be." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:06:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103252-i-regret-that-it-takes-a-life-to-learn-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I regret that it takes a life to learn how to live." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:06:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83017-i-like-to-see-people-reunited-i-like-to-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like to see people reunited, I like to see people run to each other, I like the kissing and the crying, I like the impatience, the stories that the mouth can't tell fast enough, the ears that aren't big enough, the eyes that can't take in all of the change, I like the hugging, the bringing together, the end of missing someone." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:07:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235132-it-was-late-and-we-were-tired-we-assumed-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:10:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235132-it-was-late-and-we-were-tired-we-assumed-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was late, and we were tired.
We assumed there would be other nights.
Anna’s breathing started to slow, but I still wanted to talk.
She rolled onto her side.
I said, I want to tell you something.
She said, You can tell me tomorrow.
I had never told her how much I loved her.
She was my sister.
We slept in the same bed.
There was never a right time to say it.
It was always unnecessary.
The books in my father’s shed were sighing.
The sheets were rising and falling around me with Anna’s breathing.
I thought about waking her.
But it was unnecessary.
There would be other nights.
And how can you said I love you to someone you love?
I rolled on my side and fell asleep next to her.
Here is the point of everything I have been trying to tell you, Oskar.
It’s always necessary." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235136-i-remember-spending-an-afternoon-with-mr-richter-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:11:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235136-i-remember-spending-an-afternoon-with-mr-richter-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember spending an afternoon with Mr. Richter in the Central Park Zoo, I went weighted down with food for the animals, only someone who’d never been an animal would put up a sign saying not to feed them, Mr. Richter told a joke, I tossed hamburger to the lions, he rattled the cages with his laughter, the animals went to the corners, we laughed and laughed, together and separately, out loud and silently, we were determined to ignore whatever needed to be ignored, to build a new world from nothing if nothing in our world could be salvaged, it was one of the best days of my life, a day during which I lived my life and didn’t think about my life at all." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296585-what-about-a-device-that-knew-everyone-you-knew-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:16:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296585-what-about-a-device-that-knew-everyone-you-knew-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about a device that knew everyone you knew? So when an ambulance went down the street, a big sign on the roof could flash
DON’T WORRY! DON’T WORRY!
if the sick person’s device didn’t detect the device of someone he knew nearby. And if the device did detect the device of someone he knew, the ambulance could flash the name of the person in the ambulance, and either
IT’S NOTHING MAJOR! IT’S NOTHING MAJOR!
Or, if it was something major,
IT’S MAJOR! IT’S MAJOR!
And maybe you could rate the people you knew by how much you loved them, so if the person in the ambulance detected the device of the person he loved the most, or the person who loved him the most, and the person in the ambulance was really badly hurt, and might even die, the ambulance could flash
GOODBYE! I LOVE YOU! GOODBYE! I LOVE YOU!
One thing that’s nice to think about is someone who was the first person on lot’s of people’s lists, so that when he was dying, and his ambulance went down the streets to the hospital, the whole time it would flash
GOODBYE! I LOVE YOU! GOODBYE! I LOVE YOU!" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80742-songs-are-as-sad-as-the-listener</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 20:23:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80742-songs-are-as-sad-as-the-listener]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Songs are as sad as the listener." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 23:22:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sorry for my inability to let unimportant things go, for my inability to hold on to the important things." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241134-i-ll-understand-if-you-don-t-want-me-but-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:05:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Maeve Binchy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241134-i-ll-understand-if-you-don-t-want-me-but-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll understand if you don't want me. But I will be heartbroken. You are all I ever dreamed of and hoped for. You are much, much more. Please know that I didn't think I was mean-minded. But I realize I am. I don't want you to put your arms around me and say it's all right, that you forgive me. I want you to be sure that you do, and my love for you will last as long as I live. I can see no lightness, no humour, no joke to make. I just hope that we will be able to go back to when we had laughter, and the world was coloured, not black and white and grey. I am so sorry for hurting you. I could inflict all kinds of pain on myself, but it would not take back any I gave to you. - David Power" -- Maeve Binchy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133743-i-look-placid-you-see-that-s-why-people-think-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 00:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Maeve Binchy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133743-i-look-placid-you-see-that-s-why-people-think-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I look placid, you see, that's why people think I'm fine.  Inside I worry a lot." -- Maeve Binchy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
