<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/776431-rivers]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/776431-rivers" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:28:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:28:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13959-do-you-know-how-long-a-year-takes-when-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13959-do-you-know-how-long-a-year-takes-when-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know how long a year takes when it's going away?' Dunbar repeated to Clevinger. 'This long.' He snapped his fingers. 'A second ago you were stepping into college with your lungs full of fresh air. Today you're an old man.'

'Old?' asked Clevinger with surprise. 'What are you talking about?'

'Old.'

'I'm not old.'

'You're inches away from death every time you go on a mission. How much older can you be at your age? A half minute before that you were stepping into high school, and an unhooked brassiere was as close as you ever hoped to get to Paradise. Only a fifth of a second before that you were a small kid with a ten-week summer vacation that lasted a hundred thousand years and still ended too soon. Zip! They go rocketing by so fast. How the hell else are you ever going to slow down?' Dunbar was almost angry when he finished.

'Well, maybe it is true,' Clevinger conceded unwillingly in a subdued tone. 'Maybe a long life does have to be filled with many unpleasant conditions if it's to seem long. But in that event, who wants one?'

'I do,' Dunbar told him.

'Why?' Clevinger asked.

'What else is there?" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23143-between-the-wish-and-the-thing-the-world-lies-waiting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:38:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23143-between-the-wish-and-the-thing-the-world-lies-waiting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between the wish and the thing the world lies waiting." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132778-though-men-in-the-mass-forget-the-origins-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:40:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Loren Eiseley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132778-though-men-in-the-mass-forget-the-origins-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though men in the mass forget the origins of their need, they still bring wolfhounds into city apartments, where dog and man both sit brooding in wistful discomfort.

The magic that gleams an instant between Argos and Odysseus is both the recognition of diversity and the need for affection across the illusions of form.  It is nature's cry to homeless, far-wandering, insatiable man: &quot;Do not forget your brethren, nor the green wood from which you sprang.  To do so is to invite disaster." -- Loren Eiseley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:28:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who believes that the secrets of the world are forever hidden lives in mystery and fear. Superstitiion will drag him down. The rain will erode the deeds of his life. But that man who sets himself the task of singling out the thread of order from the tapestry will by the decision alone have taken charge of the world and it is only by such taking charge that he will effect a way to dictate the terms of his own fate. 

I dont see what that has to do with catchin birds. 

The freedom of birds is an insult to me. I'd have them all in zoos. 

That would be a hell of a zoo. 

The judge smiled. Yes, he said. Even so." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 21:52:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16731-it-s-been-a-prevalent-notion-fallen-sparks-fragments-of-vessels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's been a prevalent notion. Fallen sparks. Fragments of vessels broken at the Creation. And someday, somehow, before the end, a gathering back to home. A messenger from the Kingdom, arriving at the last moment. But I tell you there is no such message, no such home -- only the millions of last moments . . . nothing more. Our history is an aggregate of last moments." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182369-the-time-of-dangling-insects-arrived-white-houses-with-caterpillars</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 10:38:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182369-the-time-of-dangling-insects-arrived-white-houses-with-caterpillars]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time of dangling insects arrived.  White houses with caterpillars dangling from the eaves.  White stones in driveways.  You can walk at night down the middle of the street and hear women talking on the telephone.  Warmer weather produces voices in the dark.  They are talking about their adolescent sons.  How big, how fast.  The sons are almost frightening.  The quantities they eat.  The way they loom in doorways.  These are the days that are full of wormy bugs.  They are in the grass, stuck to the siding, hanging in the hair, hanging from the trees and eaves, stuck to the window screens.  The women talk long-distance to grandparents of growing boys.  They share the Trimline phone, beamish old folks in hand-knit sweaters on fixed incomes. 

What happens to them when the commercial ends?" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:28:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11132-every-moment-in-your-life-is-a-turning-and-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:29:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11132-every-moment-in-your-life-is-a-turning-and-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every moment in your life is a turning and every one a choosing. Somewhere you made a choice. All followed to this. The accounting is scrupulous. The shape is drawn. No line can be erased. I had no belief in your ability to move a coin to your bidding. How could you? A person's path through the world seldom changes and even more seldom will it change abruptly. And the shape of your path was visible from the beginning." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203670-out-of-the-choked-devonian-waters-emerged-sight-and-sound</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 10:38:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Loren Eiseley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203670-out-of-the-choked-devonian-waters-emerged-sight-and-sound]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of the choked Devonian waters emerged sight and sound and the music that rolls invisible through the composer's brain.  They are there still in the ooze along the tideline, though no one notices.  The world is fixed, we say: fish in the sea, birds in the air.  But in the mangrove swamps by the Niger, fish climb trees and ogle uneasy naturalists who try unsuccessfully to chase them back to the water.  There are things still coming ashore. " -- Loren Eiseley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277512-a-true-democratic-spirit-is-up-there-with-religious-faith</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 18:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277512-a-true-democratic-spirit-is-up-there-with-religious-faith]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true Democratic Spirit is up there with religious faith and emotional maturity and all those other top-of-the-Maslow-Pyramid-type qualities that people spend their whole lives working on.  A Democratic Spirit's constituent rigor and humility and self-honesty are, in fact, so hard to maintain on certain issues that it's almost irresistibly tempting to fall in with some established dogmatic camp and to follow that camp's line on the issue and to let your position harden within the camp and  become inflexible and to believe that he other camps are either evil or insane and to spend all your time and energy trying to shout over them." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150519-since-the-first-human-eye-saw-a-leaf-in-devonian</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2009 21:41:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Loren Eiseley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150519-since-the-first-human-eye-saw-a-leaf-in-devonian]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Since the first human eye saw a leaf in Devonian sandstone and a puzzled finger
reached to touch it, sadness has lain over the heart of man. By this tenuous
thread of living protoplasm, stretching backward into time, we are linked forever to lost beaches whose sands have long since hardened into stone. The stars that caught our blind
amphibian stare have shifted far or vanished in their courses, but still that naked, glistening thread winds onward. No one knows the secret of its beginning or its end. Its
forms are phantoms. The thread alone is real; the thread is life." -- Loren Eiseley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2008 07:52:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1716-travel-is-fatal-to-prejudice-bigotry-and-narrow-mindedness-and-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts. Broad, wholesome, charitable views of men and things cannot be acquired by vegetating in one little corner of the earth all one's lifetime." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22932-when-the-flames-came-up-her-eyes-burned-out-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 12:25:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22932-when-the-flames-came-up-her-eyes-burned-out-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the flames came up her eyes burned out there like gatelamps to another world. A world burning on the shore of an unknowable void. A world construed out of blood and blood's alcahest and blood in its core and in its integument because it was nothing save blood had power to resonate against that void which threatened hourly to devour it. He wrapped himself in the blanket and watched her. When those eyes and the nation to which they stood witness were gone at last with their dignity back into their origins there would perhaps be other fires and other witnesses and other worlds otherwise beheld. But they would not be this one." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 12:35:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the nature of his profession that his experience with death should be greater than for most and he said that while it was true that time heals bereavement it does so only at the cost of the slow extinction of those loved ones from the heart's memory which is the sole place of their abode then or now. Faces fade, voices dim. Seize them back, whispered the sepulturero. Speak with them. Call their names. Do this and do not let sorrow die for it is the sweetening of every gift." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22940-the-names-of-the-cerros-and-the-sierras-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 12:39:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22940-the-names-of-the-cerros-and-the-sierras-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The names of the cerros and the sierras and the deserts exist only on maps. We name them that we do not lose our way. Yet it was because the way was lost to us already that we have made those names. The world cannot be lost. We are the ones. And it is because these names and these coordinates are our own naming that they cannot save us. They cannot find for us the way again." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:11:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything is necessary. Every least thing. This is the hard lesson. Nothing can be dispensed with. Nothing despised. Because the seams are hid from us, you see. The joinery. The way in which the world is made. We have no way to know what could be taken away. What omitted. We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 20:00:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it came to me then. That we were wonderful traveling companions but in the end no more than lonely lumps of metal in their own separate orbits.  From far off they look like beautiful shooting stars, but in reality they're nothing more than prisons, where each of us is locked up alone, going nowhere. When the orbits of these two satellites of ours happened to cross paths, we could be together. Maybe even open our hearts to each other. But that was only for the briefest moment. In the next instant we'd be in absolute solitude. Until we burned up and became nothing." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:20:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17-don-t-part-with-your-illusions-when-they-are-gone-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:20:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17-don-t-part-with-your-illusions-when-they-are-gone-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't part with your illusions. When they are gone you may still exist, but you have ceased to live." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 19:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen up - there's no war that will end all wars." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5789-but-who-prays-for-satan-who-in-eighteen-centuries-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:21:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by mark twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5789-but-who-prays-for-satan-who-in-eighteen-centuries-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But who prays for Satan? Who, in eighteen centuries, has had the common humanity to pray for the one sinner that needed it most?" -- mark twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:21:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5785-the-fear-of-death-follows-from-the-fear-of-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fear of death follows from the fear of life. A man who lives fully is prepared to die at any time." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:21:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5115-loyalty-to-country-always-loyalty-to-government-when-it-deserves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loyalty to country ALWAYS. Loyalty to government, when it deserves it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:21:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6655-don-t-go-around-saying-the-world-owes-you-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t go around saying the world owes you a living. The world owes you nothing. It was here first." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691-heaven-goes-by-favor-if-it-went-by-merit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:22:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691-heaven-goes-by-favor-if-it-went-by-merit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heaven goes by favor. If it went by merit, you would stay out and your dog would go in." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209213-lights-come-and-go-in-the-night-sky-men-troubled</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 21:10:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Loren Eiseley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209213-lights-come-and-go-in-the-night-sky-men-troubled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lights come and go in the night sky.  Men,  troubled at last by the things they build, may toss in their sleep and dream bad dreams, or lie awake while the meteors whisper greenly overhead.  But nowhere in all space or on a thousand worlds will there be men to share our loneliness." -- Loren Eiseley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16893-but-even-so-every-now-and-then-i-would-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:25:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16893-but-even-so-every-now-and-then-i-would-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But even so, every now and then I would feel a violent stab of loneliness. The very water I drink, the very air I breathe, would feel like long, sharp needles. The pages of a book in my hands would take on the threatening metallic gleam of razor blades. I could hear the roots of loneliness creeping through me when the world was hushed at four o'clock in the morning." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:25:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know one’s own state is not a simple matter. One cannot look directly at one’s own face with one’s own eyes, for example. One has no choice but to look at one’s reflection in the mirror. Through experience, we come to believe that the image is correct, but that is all." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23139-nor-does-god-whisper-through-the-trees-his-voice-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 20:28:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rivers add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23139-nor-does-god-whisper-through-the-trees-his-voice-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor does God whisper through the trees. His voice is not to be mistaken. When men hear it they fall to their knees and their souls are riven and they cry out to Him and there is no fear but only wildness of heart that springs from such longing..." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
