<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77711-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77711-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 13:57:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283340-q-where-and-when-do-you-do-your-writing-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 13:57:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283340-q-where-and-when-do-you-do-your-writing-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Q: Where and when do you do your writing? 

A: Any small room with no natural light will do. As for when, I have no particular schedules... afternoons are best, but I'm too lethargic for any real regime. When I'm in the flow of something I can do a regular 9 to 5; when I don't know where I'm going with an idea, I'm lucky if I do two hours of productive work. There is nothing more off-putting to a would-be novelist to hear about how so-and-so wakes up at four in the a.m, walks the dog, drinks three liters of black coffee and then writes 3,000 words a day, or that some other asshole only works half an hour every two weeks, does fifty press-ups and stands on his head before and after the &quot;creative moment.&quot; I remember reading that kind of stuff in profiles like this and becoming convinced everything I was doing was wrong. What's the American phrase? If it ain't broke..." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313433-fiction-is-empathy-technology</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 17:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Steven Pinker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313433-fiction-is-empathy-technology]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fiction is empathy technology." -- Steven Pinker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54406-at-no-other-time-than-autumn-does-the-earth-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 08:49:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54406-at-no-other-time-than-autumn-does-the-earth-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At no other time (than autumn) does the earth let itself be inhaled in one smell, the ripe earth; in a smell that is in no way inferior to the smell of the sea, bitter where it borders on taste, and more honeysweet where you feel it touching the first sounds.  Containing depth within itself, darkness, something of the grave almost." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14410-it-was-inevitable-the-scent-of-bitter-almonds-always-reminded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 08:49:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14410-it-was-inevitable-the-scent-of-bitter-almonds-always-reminded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was inevitable: the scent of bitter almonds always reminded him of the fate of unrequited love." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2011 16:16:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104400-from-daydreams-on-the-road-there-was-no-waking-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From daydreams on the road there was no waking. He plodded on. He could remember everything of her save her scent. Seated in a theatre with her beside him leaning forward listening to the music. Gold scrollwork and sconces and the tall columnar folds of the drapes at either side of the stage. She held his hand in her lap and he could feel the tops of her stockings through the thin stuff of her summer dress. Freeze this frame. Now call down your dark and your cold and be damned." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166448-they-heard-somewhere-in-that-tenantless-night-a-bell-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 11:30:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166448-they-heard-somewhere-in-that-tenantless-night-a-bell-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They heard somewhere in that tenantless night a bell that tolled and ceased where no bell was and they rode out on the round dais of the earth which alone was dark and no light to it and which carried their figures and bore them up into the swarming stars so that they rode not under but among them and they rode at once jaunty and circumspect, like thieves newly loosed in that dark electric, like young thieves in a glowing orchard, loosely jacketed against the cold and ten thousand worlds for the choosing." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383911-we-stand-there-quiet-my-questions-all-seem-wrong-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 18:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383911-we-stand-there-quiet-my-questions-all-seem-wrong-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We stand there, quiet. My questions all seem wrong: How did you get so old? Was it all at once, in a day, or did you peter out bit by bit? When did you stop having parties? Did everyone else get old too, or was it just you? Are other people still here, hiding in the palm trees or holding their breath underwater? When did you last swim your laps? Do your bones hurt? Did you know this was coming and hide that you knew, or did it ambush you from behind?" -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150154-reading-is-pleasure-and-happiness-to-be-alive-or-sadness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 15:05:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150154-reading-is-pleasure-and-happiness-to-be-alive-or-sadness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading is pleasure and happiness to be alive or sadness to be alive and above all it's knowledge and questions." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365581-to-me-at-least-in-retrospect-the-really-interesting-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 21:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365581-to-me-at-least-in-retrospect-the-really-interesting-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me, at least in retrospect, the really interesting question is why dullness proves to be such a powerful impediment to attention. Why we recoil from the dull. Maybe it’s because dullness is intrinsically painful; maybe that’s where phrases like ‘deadly dull’ or ‘excruciatingly dull’ come from. But there might be more to it. Maybe dullness is associated with psychic pain because something that’s dull or opaque fails to provide enough stimulation to distract people from some other, deeper type of pain that is always there, if only in an ambient, low-level way, and which most of us spend nearly all our time and energy trying to distract ourselves from feeling, or at least from feeling directly or with our full attention. Admittedly, the whole thing’s pretty confusing, and hard to talk about abstractly…but surely something must lie behind not just Muzak in dull or tedious places any more but now also actual TV in waiting rooms, supermarkets’ checkouts, airport gates, SUVs’ backseats. Walkman, iPods, BlackBerries, cell phones that attach to your head. This terror of silence with nothing diverting to do. I can’t think anyone really believes that today’s so-called ‘information society’ is just about information. Everyone knows it’s about something else, way down." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85175-years-ago-i-recognized-my-kinship-with-all-living-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 18:03:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Eugene V. Debs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85175-years-ago-i-recognized-my-kinship-with-all-living-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Years ago I recognized my kinship with all living things, and I made up my mind that I was not one bit better than the meanest on the earth. I said then and I say now, that while there is a lower class, I am in it; while there is a criminal element, I am of it; while there is a soul in prison, I am not free." -- Eugene V. Debs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645355-there-is-absolutely-no-single-aspect-of-one-s-personality-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 18:03:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Chris Ware]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645355-there-is-absolutely-no-single-aspect-of-one-s-personality-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is absolutely no single aspect of one’s personality that is more important to develop than empathy, which is not a skill at which men typically are asked to excel. I believe empathy is not only the core of art, literature and music, but should also be at the core of society, from ethics to economics.&quot; (Chris Ware in an interview, http://bit.ly/empathyware)" -- Chris Ware]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159154-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding-terms</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 20:06:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159154-i-think-we-are-well-advised-to-keep-on-nodding-terms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I think we are well-advised to keep on nodding terms with the people we used to be, whether we find them attractive company or not. Otherwise they turn up unannounced and surprise us, come hammering on the mind's door at 4 a.m. of a bad night and demand to know who deserted them, who betrayed them, who is going to make amends. We forget all too soon the things we thought we could never forget. We forget the loves and the betrayals alike, forget what we whispered and what we screamed, forget who we were." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43474-i-am-still-every-age-that-i-have-been-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 19:11:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43474-i-am-still-every-age-that-i-have-been-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am still every age that I have been. Because I was once a child, I am always a child. Because I was once a searching adolescent, given to moods and ecstasies, these are still part of me, and always will be... This does not mean that I ought to be trapped or enclosed in any of these ages...the delayed adolescent, the childish adult, but that they are in me to be drawn on; to forget is a form of suicide... Far too many people misunderstand what *putting away childish things* means, and think that forgetting what it is like to think and feel and touch and smell and taste and see and hear like a three-year-old or a thirteen-year-old or a twenty-three-year-old means being grownup. When I'm with these people I, like the kids, feel that if this is what it means to be a grown-up, then I don't ever want to be one. Instead of which, if I can retain a child's awareness and joy, and *be* fifty-one, then I will really learn what it means to be grownup." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 21:28:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492045-people-s-lives-in-jubilee-as-elsewhere-were-dull-simple-amazing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2013 09:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Alice Munro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492045-people-s-lives-in-jubilee-as-elsewhere-were-dull-simple-amazing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People’s lives, in Jubilee as elsewhere, were dull, simple, amazing, and unfathomable – deep caves paved with kitchen linoleum." -- Alice Munro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 10:57:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If more of us valued food  and cheer and song above hoarded gold, it would be a merrier world." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1015249-literature-is-literature-its-purpose-is-to-challenge-and-disorient</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 08:46:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Mark Slouka ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1015249-literature-is-literature-its-purpose-is-to-challenge-and-disorient]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature is literature. Its purpose is to challenge and disorient us, to break us down a little bit so that we are forced to rebuild ourselves. Over time, over the course of many books, we construct a deeper, truer self." -- Mark Slouka ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132967-they-say-a-person-needs-just-three-things-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 07:37:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by Tom Bodett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132967-they-say-a-person-needs-just-three-things-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say a person needs just three things to be truly happy in this world: someone to love, something to do, and something to hope for." -- Tom Bodett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505843-do-not-ask-your-children-to-strive-for-extraordinary-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 14:30:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elizabeth add a quote by William  Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505843-do-not-ask-your-children-to-strive-for-extraordinary-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not ask your children
to strive for extraordinary lives.
Such striving may seem admirable,
but it is the way of foolishness.
Help them instead to find the wonder
and the marvel of an ordinary life.
Show them the joy of tasting
tomatoes, apples and pears.
Show them how to cry
when pets and people die.
Show them the infinite pleasure
in the touch of a hand.
And make the ordinary come alive for them.
The extraordinary will take care of itself." -- William  Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
