<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/777123-terence]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/777123-terence" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 16:12:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16006-no-matter-whether-one-is-flying-over-newfoundland-or-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 16:12:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by W.G. Sebald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16006-no-matter-whether-one-is-flying-over-newfoundland-or-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter whether one is flying over Newfoundland or the sea of lights that stretches from Boston to Philadelphia after nightfall, over the Arabian deserts which gleam like mother-of-pearl, over the Ruhr or the city of Frankfurt, it is as though there were no people, only the things they have made and in which they are hiding." -- W.G. Sebald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46496-by-associating-votive-offerings-with-sacred-images-the-catholic-church</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2008 09:42:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Aby Warburg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46496-by-associating-votive-offerings-with-sacred-images-the-catholic-church]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By associating votive offerings with sacred images, the Catholic Church, it its wisdom, had left its formerly pagan flock a legitimate outlet for the inveterate impulse to associate oneself, or one's own effigy, with the Divine as expressed in the palpable form of the human image." -- Aby Warburg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161236-places-draw-us-to-them-for-reasons-beyond-the-feelings</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 08:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Peter &amp; Alison Smithson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161236-places-draw-us-to-them-for-reasons-beyond-the-feelings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Places draw us to them for reasons beyond the feelings derived from the five senses...some deeper recognition is at work, felt throough an unextinguishable animal sensibility." -- Peter &amp; Alison Smithson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491887-if-your-educe-sculpture-to-the-flat-plane-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 10:41:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Richard Serra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491887-if-your-educe-sculpture-to-the-flat-plane-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If your educe sculpture to the flat plane of the temporal experience of the work. (...) the experience of the work is inseparable from the place in which the work resides.  Apart from that condition, any experience of the work is a deception." -- Richard Serra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279749-if-you-re-lucky-at-the-right-time-you-come-across</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 09:14:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Terence add a quote by Greil Marcus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279749-if-you-re-lucky-at-the-right-time-you-come-across]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're lucky, at the right time you come across music that is not only &quot;great,&quot; or interesting, or &quot;incredible,&quot; or fun, but actually sustaining. Though some elusive but tangible process, a piece of music cuts through all defenses and makes sense of every fear and desire you bring to it. As it does so, it exposes all you've held back, and then makes sense of that, too. Though someone else is doing the talking, the experience is like a confession. Your emotions shoot out to crazy extremes; you feel both ennobled and unworthy, saved and damned. You hear that this is what life is all about, that this is what it is for. Yet it is this recognition itself that makes you understand that life can never be this good, this whole. With a clarity life denies for its own good reasons, you see places to which you can never get." -- Greil Marcus]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
