<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/777245-tyler]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/777245-tyler" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:22:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28725-not-that-parents-are-alone-in-their-extreme-behavior-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:22:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jim Trelease]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28725-not-that-parents-are-alone-in-their-extreme-behavior-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not that parents are alone in their extreme behavior. That have more than enough company among school boards and high-ranking politicians who think if you &quot;fix the schools, they'll fix the kids.&quot; So, in Gadsden, Alabama, school officials eliminated kindergarten nap time in 2003 so the children would have more test-prep time. Two hours away in Atlanta, school officials figured that if you eliminated recess, the kids will study more. And just in case those shifty teachers try to sneak it in, Atlanta started building schools without playgrounds. &quot;We are intent on improving academic performance,&quot; said the superintendent. &quot;You don't do that by having kids hanging on the monkey bars.&quot; Meanwhile, Georgia's governor wanted the state to give Mozart CDs to newborns because research showed Mozart improved babies' IQs (which later proved to be mythical research). Right behind him is Lincoln, Rhode Island, where they canceled the district spelling bee because only one child would win, leaving all others behind, thus violating the intent of No Child Left Behind--or, as they might say in Lincoln, no child gets ahead." -- Jim Trelease]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28726-this-is-not-a-book-about-teaching-a-child-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:23:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jim Trelease]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28726-this-is-not-a-book-about-teaching-a-child-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not a book about teaching a child how to read; it's about teaching a child to want to read. There's an education adage that goes, &quot;What we teach children to love and desire will always outweigh what we make them learn.&quot; The fact is that some children learn to read sooner than others, while some learn better than others. There is a difference. For the parent who thinks that sooner is better, who has an eighteen-month-old child barking at flash cards, my response is: sooner is not better. Are the dinner guests who arrive an hour early better guests than those who arrive on time? Of course not." -- Jim Trelease]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28727-founded-by-president-truman-at-12-01-a-m-on-november-4</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:25:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by dan brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28727-founded-by-president-truman-at-12-01-a-m-on-november-4]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Founded by President Truman at 12:01 A.M. on November 4, 1952, the NSA had been the most clandestine intelligence agency in the world for almost fifty years. The NSA's seven-page inception doctrine laid out a very concise agenda: to protect U.S. government communications and to intercept the communications of foreign powers.
&quot;The roof of the NSA's main operations building was littered with over five hundred antennas, including two large radomes that looked like enormous golf balls. The building itself was mammoth--over two million square feet, twice the size of CIA headquarters. Inside were eight million feet of telephone wire and eighty thousand square feet of permanently sealed windows." -- dan brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28728-jabba-resembled-a-giant-tadpole-like-the-cinematic-creature-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Dan Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28728-jabba-resembled-a-giant-tadpole-like-the-cinematic-creature-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jabba resembled a giant tadpole, like the cinematic creature for whom he was nicknamed, the man was a hairless spheroid. As resident guardian angel of all NSA computer systems, Jabba marched from department to department, tweaking, soldering, and reaffirming his credo that prevention was the best medicine. No NSA computer had ever been infected under Jabba's reign; he intended to keep it that way." -- Dan Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34423-the-good-writers-touch-life-often-the-mediocre-ones-run</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:30:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34423-the-good-writers-touch-life-often-the-mediocre-ones-run]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The good writers touch life often. The mediocre ones run a quick hand over her. The bad ones rape her and leave her for the flies." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28733-shut-the-door-they-re-coming-through-the-window-shut-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:30:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28733-shut-the-door-they-re-coming-through-the-window-shut-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shut the door, they're coming through the window, shut the window, they're coming through the door,&quot; are the words to an old song. They fit my lifestyle with newly arriving butcher/censors every month. Only six weeks ago, I discovered that, over the years, some cubby-hole editors at Ballantine Books, fearful of contaminating the young, had, bit by bit, censored some 75 separate sections from the novel. Students, reading the novel which, after all, deals with censorship and book-burning in the future, write to tell me of this exquisite irony..." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28734-for-it-is-a-mad-world-and-it-will-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:31:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28734-for-it-is-a-mad-world-and-it-will-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it is a mad world and it will get madder if we allow the minorities, be they dwarf or giant, orangutan or dolphin, nuclear-head or water conservationalist, pro-computerologist or Neo-Luddite, simpleton or sage, to interfere with aesthetics. The real world is the playing ground for each and every group, to make or unmake laws. But the tip of the nose of my book or stories or poems is where their rights end and my territorial imperatives begin, run and rule. If Mormons do not like my plays, let them write their own. If the Irish hate my Dublin stories, let them rent typewriters. If teachers and grammar school editors find my jawbreaker sentences shatter their mushmilk teeth, let them eat stale cake dunked in weak tea of their own ungodly manufacture. If the Chicano intellectuals which to re-cut my &quot;Wonderful Ice Cream Suit&quot; so it shapes &quot;Zoot,&quot; may the belt unravel and the pants fall." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28735-the-story-about-bessie-goldberg-that-i-heard-from-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:32:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28735-the-story-about-bessie-goldberg-that-i-heard-from-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The story about Bessie Goldberg that I heard from my parents was that a nice old lady had been killed down the street and an innocent black man went to prison for the crime. Meanwhile--unknown to anyone--a violent psychopath named Al was working alone at our house all day and probably committed the murder. In our family this story eventually acquired the tidy symbolism of a folk tale. Roy Smith was a stand-in for everything that was decent but utterly defenseless. Albert DeSalvo, of course, was a stand-in for pure random evil." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28736-the-state-s-case-against-smith-however-did-claim-to-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 20:33:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Sebastian Junger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28736-the-state-s-case-against-smith-however-did-claim-to-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The state's case against Smith, however, did claim to speak to his actual guilt or innocence, and it has to be considered carefully. The reason this is important has nothing to do with Roy Smith or Bessie Goldberg or even Al DeSalvo; they're all dead. In some ways there is nothing less relevant than an old murder case. The reason it is important is this: Here is a group of people who have gathered to judge--and possibly execute--a fellow citizen. It's the highest calling there is, the very thing that separates us from social anarchy, and it has to be done well. A trial, however, is just a microcosm of the entire political system. When a democratic government decides to raise taxes or wage war or write child safety laws, it is essentially saying to an enormous jury, &quot;This is our theory of how the world works, and this is our proposal for dealing with it. If our theory makes sense to you, vote for us in the next election. If it doesn't, throw us out.&quot; The ability of citizens to scrutinize the theories insisted on by their government is their only protection against abuse of power and, ultimately, against tyranny. If ordinary citizens can't coolly and rationally evaluate a prosecutor's summation in a criminal trial, they won't have a chance at calling to task a deceitful government. And all governments are deceitful--they're deceitful because it's easier than being honest. Most of the time, it's no more sinister than that." -- Sebastian Junger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41829-it-is-an-awful-thing-to-look-on-such-sad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 11:08:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41829-it-is-an-awful-thing-to-look-on-such-sad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is an awful thing to look on such sad circumstance and not be able to shed a tear. It is not because I do not feel for these folks, but maybe I feel too much. Part of me is glad, in a low down, mean way, that it is not Albert's or Mama's graves we are digging. Glad that it is some soldiers I don't know and neighbors and friends but not family. Lord, I must be the cussedest woman there is to think that. Finally, I felt so guilty for thinking those things that I cried. Then I began to feel the heartaches of our friends and neighbors and I cried for them, too, as we said prayers over each and every grave." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41830-i-must-think-about-something-else-for-a-while-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 11:08:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41830-i-must-think-about-something-else-for-a-while-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must think about something else for a while. But then I remember his warn arms and his big strong legs touching mine and how hard and wide his chest was and how hot his kiss was, and I got outside and feed the chickens. They are getting mighty fat." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41831-on-the-night-that-i-was-born-my-paternal-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 11:09:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Dean R. Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41831-on-the-night-that-i-was-born-my-paternal-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the night that I was born, my paternal grandfather, Josef Tock, made ten predictions that shaped my life. Then he died in the very minute that my mother gave birth to me." -- Dean R. Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41832-there-are-days-when-it-seems-to-me-that-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 11:10:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Dean R. Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41832-there-are-days-when-it-seems-to-me-that-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are days when it seems to me that in literature the most convincing depiction of the world in which we live is to be found in the phantasmagorical kingdom through which Lewis Carroll took Alice on a tour." -- Dean R. Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42156-i-wondered-if-the-fire-had-been-out-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 20:59:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jeannette Walls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42156-i-wondered-if-the-fire-had-been-out-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wondered if the fire had been out to get me. I wondered if all fire was related, like Dad said all humans were related, if the fire that had burned me that day while I cooked hot dogs was somehow connected o the fire I had flushed down the toilet and the fire burning at the hotel. I didn't have the answers to those questions, but what I did know was that I lived in a world that at any moment could erupt into fire. It was the sort of knowledge that kept you on your toes." -- Jeannette Walls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57385-so-janie-began-to-think-of-death-death-that-strange</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 11:09:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57385-so-janie-began-to-think-of-death-death-that-strange]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So Janie began to think of Death. Death, that strange being with the huge square toes who lived way in the West. The great one who lived in the straight house like a platform without sides to it, and without a roof. What need has Death for a cover, and what winds can blow against him? He stands in his high house that overlooks the world. Stands watchful and motionless all day with his sword drawn back, waiting for the messenger to bid him come. Been standing there before there was a where or a when or a then. She was liable to find a feather from his wings lying in her yard any day now. She was sad and afraid too. Poor Jody! He ought not to have to wrassle in there by himself. She sent Sam in to suggest a visit, but Jody said No. These medical doctors wuz all right with the Godly sick, but they didn't know a thing about a case like his. He'd be all right just as soon as the two-headed man found what had been buried against him. He wasn't going to die at all. That was what he thought. But Sam told her different, so she knew. And then if he hadn't the next morning she was bound to know, for people began to gather in the big yard under the palm and china-berry trees. People who would not have dared to foot the place before crept in and did not come to the house. Just squatted under the trees and waited. Rumor, that wingless bird, had shadowed over the town." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57386-mrs-turner-was-a-milky-sort-of-a-woman-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 11:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57386-mrs-turner-was-a-milky-sort-of-a-woman-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mrs. Turner was a milky sort of a woman that belonged to child-bed. Her shoulders rounded a little, and she must have been conscious of her pelvis because she kept it stuck out in front of her so she could always see it. Tea Cake made a lot of fun about Mrs. Turners shape behind her back. He claimed that she had been shaped up by a cow kicking her from behind. She was an ironing board with things throwed at it. Then that same cow took and stepped in her mouth when she was a baby and left it wide and flat with her chin and nose almost meeting." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3090-the-secret-of-life-is-honesty-and-fair-dealing-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2008 11:12:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3090-the-secret-of-life-is-honesty-and-fair-dealing-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The secret of life is honesty and fair dealing. If you can fake that, you've got it made." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63579-whatever-any-of-us-may-have-thought-about-hatsumomo-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2008 23:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Arthur Golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63579-whatever-any-of-us-may-have-thought-about-hatsumomo-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever any of us may have thought about Hatsumomo, she was like an empress in our okiya since she earned the income be which we all lived. And being an empress she would have been very displeased, upon returning late at night, to find her palace dark and all the servants asleep. That is to say, when she came home too drunk to unbutton her socks, someone had to unbutton them for her; and if she felt hungry, she certainly wasn't going to stroll into the kitchen and prepare something by herself--such as an umeboshi ochazuke, which was a favorite snack of hers, made with leftover rice and pickled sour plums, soaked in hot tea. Actually our okiya wasn't at all unusual in this respect. The job of waiting up to bow and welcome the geisha home almost always fell to the most junior of the &quot;cocoons&quot;--as the young geisha-in-training were often called. And from the moment I began taking lessons at the school, the most junior cocoon in our okiya was me. Long before midnight, Pumpkin and the two elderly maids were sound asleep on their futons only a meter or so away on the wood floor of the entrance hall; but I had to go on kneeling there, struggling to stay awake until sometimes as late as two o'clock in the morning. Granny's room was nearby and she slept with her light on and her door opened a crack. The bar of light that fell across my empty futon made me think of a day, not long before Satsu [Chiyo's sister] and I were taken away from our village, when I'd peered into the back room of our house to see my mother asleep there. My father had draped fishing nets across the paper screens to darken the room, but it looked so gloomy I decided to open one of the windows; and when I did, a strip of bright sunlight fell across my mother's futon and showed her hand so pale and bony. To see the yellow lights streaming from Granny's room onto my futon...I had to wonder if my mother was still alive. We ere so much alike, I felt sure I would have known if she'd died; but of course, I'd had no sign one way or the other." -- Arthur Golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73009-one-thing-that-i-used-to-believe-that-has-stuck</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 21:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Greg Knauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73009-one-thing-that-i-used-to-believe-that-has-stuck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing that I used to believe that has stuck with me is, of course, that farts are funny. Burps, too. Sneezes, even. Pretty much the whole gamut of bodily noises is a treasure trove of ready-made comedy. You gather a handful of small boys together and let them entertain themselves and there will be more sharp honks than an angry L.A. freeway. But there's a time and place for such fun, and every second of every day, no matter the location or company, turns out not to be the appropriate venue for a gastrointestinal symphony." -- Greg Knauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74738-i-have-never-read-anything-quite-like-mark-haddon-s-funny</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 14:28:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by arthur golden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74738-i-have-never-read-anything-quite-like-mark-haddon-s-funny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never read anything quite like Mark Haddon's funny and agonizingly honest book, or encountered a narrator more vivid and memorable. I advise you to buy two copies; you won't want to lend yours out." -- arthur golden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74739-he-was-asking-too-many-questions-and-he-was-asking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 14:29:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Mark Haddon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74739-he-was-asking-too-many-questions-and-he-was-asking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was asking too many questions and he was asking them too quickly. They were stacking up in my head like loaves in the factory where Uncle Terry works. The factory is a bakery and he operates the slicing machines. And sometimes a slicer is not working fast enough but the bread keeps coming and there is a blockage. I sometimes think of my mind as a machine, but not always as a bread-slicing machine. It makes it easier to explain to other people what is going on inside it." -- Mark Haddon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74742-carlos-was-known-to-the-pushcart-peddlers-as-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 14:30:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jean Merrill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74742-carlos-was-known-to-the-pushcart-peddlers-as-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Carlos was known to the pushcart peddlers as the most skillful carton-flattener in the Lower East Side section of New York City. Carlos' business was to go around to small stores that had clean cardboard cartons which they wished to be rid of. With two or three deft motions, Carlos would flatten the cartons and carefully stack them on his pushcart. Carlos was the only flattener in the business who could stack to a height of twelve feet without the cartons slipping off." -- Jean Merrill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76966-take-these-said-the-old-man-holding-out-a-white</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:19:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76966-take-these-said-the-old-man-holding-out-a-white]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take these,&quot; said the old man, holding out a white stone and a black stone that had been embedded at the center of the breastplate. &quot;They are called Urim and Thummim. The black signifies 'yes,' and the white 'no.' When you are unable to read the omens, they will help you to do so. Always ask an objective question." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32460-at-that-moment-it-seemed-to-him-that-time-stood</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 21:20:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32460-at-that-moment-it-seemed-to-him-that-time-stood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At that moment, it seemed to him that time stood still, and the Soul of the World surged within him. When he looked into her dark eyes, and saw that her lips were poised between a laugh and silence, he learned the most important part of the language that all the world spoke—the language that everyone on earth was capable of understanding in their heart. It was love. Something older than humanity, more ancient than the desert. Something that exerted the same force whenever two pairs of eyes met, as had theirs here at the well." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84632-balanced-atop-the-highest-spire-of-the-salt-lake-temple</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:03:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84632-balanced-atop-the-highest-spire-of-the-salt-lake-temple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Balanced atop the highest spire of the Salt Lake Temple, gleaming in the Utah sun, a statue of the angel Moroni stands watch over downtown Salt Lake City with his golden trumpet raised. This massive granite edifice is the spiritual and temporal nexus of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS), which presents itself as the world's only true religion. Temple Square is to Mormons what the Vatican is to Catholics, or the Kaaba in Mecca is to Muslims. At last count there were more than eleven million Saints the world over, and Mormonism is the fastest-growing faith in the Western Hemisphere. At present in the United States there are more Mormons than Presbyterians or Episcopalians. On the planet as a whole, there are now more Mormons than Jews. Mormonism is considered in some sober academic circles to be well on its way to becoming a major world religion--the first such faith to emerge since Islam." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84633-when-debbie-was-fourteen-she-felt-impressed-by-the-lord</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:04:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84633-when-debbie-was-fourteen-she-felt-impressed-by-the-lord]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Debbie was fourteen, she felt &quot;impressed by the Lord&quot; to marry Ray Blackmore, the community leader. Debbie asked her father to share her divine impression with Prophet LeRoy Johnson, who would periodically travel to Bountiful from Short Creek to perform various religious duties. Because Debbie was lithe and beautiful, Uncle Roy approved of the match. A year later the prophet returned to Canada and married her to the ailing fifty-seven-year-old Blackmore. As his sixth wife, Debbie became a stepmother to Blackmore's thirty-one kids, most of whom were older than she was. And because he happened to be the father of Debbie's own stepmother, Mem, she unwittingly became a stepmother to her stepmother, and thus a step grandmother to herself." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84635-whether-one-believes-that-the-faith-he-spawned-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:04:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84635-whether-one-believes-that-the-faith-he-spawned-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether one believes that the faith he spawned is the world's only true religion or a preposterous fable, Joseph emerges from the fog of time as one of the most remarkable figures ever to have breathed American air. &quot;Whatever his lapses,&quot; Harold Bloom argues in The American Religion, &quot;Smith was an authentic religious genius, unique in our national history.... In proportion to his importance and his complexity, he remains the least-studied personage, of an undiminished vitality, in our entire national sage." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84636-for-a-person-accustomed-to-the-multi-ethnic-commotion-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:04:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84636-for-a-person-accustomed-to-the-multi-ethnic-commotion-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For a person accustomed to the multi ethnic commotion of Los Angeles, Vancouver, New York, or even Denver, walking across the BYU campus can be a jarring experience. One sees no graffiti, not a speck of litter. More than 99 percent of the thirty thousand students are white. Each of the young Mormons one encounters is astonishingly well groomed and neatly dressed. Beards, tattoos, and pierced ears (or other body parts) are strictly forbidden for men. Immodest attire and more than a single piercing per ear are forbidden among women. Smoking, using profane language, and drinking alcohol or even coffee are likewise banned. Heeding the dictum &quot;Cougars don't cut corners,&quot; students keep to the sidewalks as they hurry to make it to class on time; nobody would think of attempting to shave a few precious seconds by treading on the manicured grass. Everyone is cheerful, friendly, and unfailingly polite.

Most non-Mormons think of Salt Lake City as the geographic heart of Mormonism, but in fact half the population of Salt Lake is Gentile, and many Mormons regard the city as a sinful, iniquitous place that's been corrupted by outsiders. To the Saints themselves, the true Mormon heartland is here in Provo and surrounding Utah County--the site of chaste little towns like Highland, American Fork, Orem, Payson and Salem--where the population is nearly 90 percent LDS. The Sabbath is taken seriously in these parts. Almost all businesses close on Sundays, as do public swimming pools, even on the hottest days of the summer months.

This part of the state is demographically notable in other aspects, as well. The LDS Church forbids abortions, frowns on contraception, and teaches that Mormon couples have a sacred duty to give birth to as many children as they can support--which goes a long way toward explaining why Utah County has the highest birth rate in the United States; it is higher, in fact, than the birth rate in Bangladesh. This also happens to be the most Republican county in the most Republican state in the nation. Not coincidentally, Utah County is a stronghold not only of Mormonism but also Mormon Fundamentalism." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84637-alleging-that-the-mormons-had-committed-a-long-list-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84637-alleging-that-the-mormons-had-committed-a-long-list-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alleging that the Mormons had committed a long list of treasonous acts, in May 1857 Buchanan dispatched a contingent of federal officials to restore the rule of law in Utah, including a new territorial governor to replace Brigham Young. More ominously, the new president ordered twenty-five hundred heavily armed soldiers to escort these officials into Salt Lake City and subdue the Saints if necessary. For all intents and purposes, the United States had declared war on the Mormons." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84638-i-was-irresistibly-drawn-to-write-about-latter-day-saints-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 14:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84638-i-was-irresistibly-drawn-to-write-about-latter-day-saints-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was irresistibly drawn to write about Latter-Day Saints not only because I already knew something about their theology, and admired much about their culture, but also because of the utterly unique circumstances in which their religion was born: the Mormon Church was founded a mere 173 years ago, in a literate society, in the age of the printing press. As a consequence, the creation of what became a worldwide faith was abundantly documented in firsthand accounts. Thanks to the Mormons, we have been given an unprecedented opportunity to appreciate--in astonishingly detail--how an important religion came to be." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
