<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77964-kate-holmden]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/77964-kate-holmden" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:10:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:10:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2400-some-humans-would-do-anything-to-see-if-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:09:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2400-some-humans-would-do-anything-to-see-if-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some humans would do anything to see if it was possible to do it. If you put a large switch in some cave somewhere, with a sign on it saying 'End-of-the-World Switch. PLEASE DO NOT TOUCH', the paint wouldn't even have time to dry." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62393-laura-felt-a-warmth-inside-her-it-was-very-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2013 14:20:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62393-laura-felt-a-warmth-inside-her-it-was-very-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laura felt a warmth inside her. It was very small, but it was strong. It was steady, like a tiny light in the dark, and it burned very low but no winds could make it flicker because it would not give up." -- Laura Ingalls Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:05:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:11:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:05:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36325-she-was-already-learning-that-if-you-ignore-the-rules</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:06:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36325-she-was-already-learning-that-if-you-ignore-the-rules]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was already learning that if you ignore the rules people will, half the time, quietly rewrite them so that they don't apply to you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30533-just-because-you-have-the-emotional-range-of-a-teaspoon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:08:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30533-just-because-you-have-the-emotional-range-of-a-teaspoon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you have the emotional range of a teaspoon doesn't mean we all have." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:08:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:09:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 07:09:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 13:40:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it odd how much fatter a book gets when you've read it several times?&quot; Mo had said...&quot;As if something were left between the pages every time you read it.  Feelings, thoughts, sounds, smells...and then, when you look at the book again many years later, you find yourself there, too, a slightly younger self, slightly different, as if the book had preserved you like a pressed flower...both strange and familiar." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440921-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 11:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440921-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where,
I love you simply, without problems or pride:
I love you in this way because I don’t know any other way of loving." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
