<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/779669-davey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/779669-davey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 15:56:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32568-if-you-have-enough-book-space-i-don-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 15:56:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Davey add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32568-if-you-have-enough-book-space-i-don-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have enough book space, I don't want to talk to you." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99299-there-are-it-has-been-said-two-types-of-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 16:00:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Davey add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99299-there-are-it-has-been-said-two-types-of-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are, it has been said, two types of people in the world.  There are those who, when presented with a glass that is exactly half full, say: this glass is half full.  And then there are those who say: this glass is half empty. 
	The world belongs, however, to those who can look at the glass and say: What's up with this glass? Excuse me? Excuse me? This is my glass? I don't think so.  My glass was full!  And it was a bigger glass! Who's been pinching my beer?
	And at the other end of the bar the world is full of the other type of person, who has a broken glass, or a glass that has been carelessly knocked over (usually by one of the people calling for a larger glass) or who had no glass at all, because he was at the back of the crowd and had failed to catch the barman's eye.  " -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 16:03:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Davey add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72745-the-reason-that-the-rich-were-so-rich-vimes-reasoned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason that the rich were so rich, Vimes reasoned, was because they managed to spend less money.

Take boots, for example. He earned thirty-eight dollars a month plus allowances. A really good pair of leather boots cost fifty dollars. But an affordable pair of boots, which were sort of OK for a season or two and then leaked like hell when the cardboard gave out, cost about ten dollars. Those were the kind of boots Vimes always bought, and wore until the soles were so thin that he could tell where he was in Ankh-Morpork on a foggy night by the feel of the cobbles.

But the thing was that good boots lasted for years and years. A man who could afford fifty dollars had a pair of boots that'd still be keeping his feet dry in ten years' time, while the poor man who could only afford cheap boots would have spent a hundred dollars on boots in the same time and would still have wet feet.

This was the Captain Samuel Vimes 'Boots' theory of socioeconomic unfairness." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270644-there-is-always-a-choice-you-mean-i-could-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 16:31:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Davey add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270644-there-is-always-a-choice-you-mean-i-could-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always a choice.&quot; 
&quot;You mean I could choose certain death?&quot; 
&quot;A choice nevertheless, or perhaps an alternative. You see I believe in freedom. Not many people do, although they will of course protest otherwise. And no practical definition of freedom would be complete without the freedom to take the consequences. Indeed, it is the freedom upon which all the others are based." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162884-frying-pan-jack-and-i-were-in-that-camp-that-s-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 20:34:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Davey add a quote by Utah Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162884-frying-pan-jack-and-i-were-in-that-camp-that-s-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Frying-Pan Jack and I were in that camp, that's where he said to me, he'd been tramping since 1927, 'I told myself in '27,  if I cannot dictate the conditions of my labor, I will henceforth cease to work.' You don't have to go to college to figure these things out, no sir. He said, 'I learned when I was young that the only true life I had was the life of my brain. But if it's true that the only real life I had was the life of my  brain, what sense does it make to hand that brain to someone for eight hours a day,  for their particular use, on the presumption that at the end of the day they will give it back in an unmutilated condition? Fat chance!" -- Utah Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
