<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780236-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780236-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 20:24:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118514-monday-june-9-people-think-they-know-you-they-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 20:24:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by William H. Woodwell Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118514-monday-june-9-people-think-they-know-you-they-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Monday, June 9: People think they know you.  They think they know how you're handling a situation.  But the truth is no one knows.  No one knows what happens after you leave them, when you're lying in bed or sitting over your breakfast alone and all you want to do is cry or scream.  They don't know what's going on inside your head--the mind-numbing cocktail of anger and sadness and guilt.  This isn't their fault.  They just don't know.  And so they pretend and they say you're doing great when you're really not.  And this makes everyone feel better.  Everybody but you." -- William H. Woodwell Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399957-anyone-can-achieve-their-fullest-potential-who-we-are-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 20:24:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Martin Heidegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399957-anyone-can-achieve-their-fullest-potential-who-we-are-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone can achieve their fullest potential, who we are might be predetermined, but the path we follow is always of our own choosing. We should never allow our fears or the expectations of others to set the frontiers of our destiny. Your destiny can't be changed but, it can be challenged. Every man is born as many men and dies as a single one." -- Martin Heidegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103878-their-intrinsic-worth-is-not-enough-for-not-all-turn</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 14:10:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Balthazar Gracian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103878-their-intrinsic-worth-is-not-enough-for-not-all-turn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Their intrinsic worth is not enough,  for not all turn the goods over and look deep.  Most run where the crowd is--because the others run" -- Balthazar Gracian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47149-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 14:01:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Tim O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47149-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true war story is never moral. It does not instruct, nor encourage virtue, nor suggest models of proper human behavior, nor restrain men from doing the things men have always done. If a story seems moral, do not believe it. If at the end of a war story you feel uplifted, or if you feel that some small bit of rectitude has been salvaged from the larger waste, then you have been made the victim of a very old and terrible lie. There is no rectitude whatsoever. There is no virtue. As a first rule of thumb, therefore, you can tell a true war story by its absolute and uncompromising allegiance to obscenity and evil. " -- Tim O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104976-if-the-britannica-has-taught-me-anything-it-s-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 13:26:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104976-if-the-britannica-has-taught-me-anything-it-s-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the Britannica has taught me anything, it's to be more careful. I don't want to turn into an unseemly noun or verb or adjective someday. I don't want to be like Charles Boycott, the landlord in Ireland who refused to lower rents during a famine, leading to the original boycott. I don't want to be like Charles Lynch, who headed an irregular court that hung loyalists during the Revolutionary War. I can't have &quot;Jacobs&quot; be a verb that means staying home all the time or washing your hands too frequently." -- A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104974-i-was-smart-enough-to-know-that-i-shouldn-t-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 14:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104974-i-was-smart-enough-to-know-that-i-shouldn-t-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was smart enough to know that I shouldn't tell anyone the reason I needed that icy air.  No need to spill the secret that I was the genius of all geniuses, the Leonardo da Vinci of the 1980s. That would just inspire envy and skepticism. So I'd just stare at the closed window and stew. If ten minutes went by without my lungs getting fresh air, I panicked. I needed to make sure the monoxide hadn't eaten my cranium.   " -- A.J. Jacobs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103-be-not-afraid-of-greatness-some-are-born-great-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 14:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103-be-not-afraid-of-greatness-some-are-born-great-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be not afraid of greatness. Some are born great, some achieve greatness, and others have greatness thrust upon them." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
