<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780723-jenn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780723-jenn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 07:29:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14198-i-am-burdened-with-what-the-buddhists-call-the-monkey</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 07:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14198-i-am-burdened-with-what-the-buddhists-call-the-monkey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am burdened with what the Buddhists call the 'monkey mind' -- the thoughts that swing from limb to limb, stopping only to scratch themselves, spit and howl." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58529-i-m-not-lazy-i-m-simply-judicious-about-excess-movement</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 07:51:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Jen Lancaster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58529-i-m-not-lazy-i-m-simply-judicious-about-excess-movement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not lazy. I'm simply judicious about excess movement." -- Jen Lancaster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119475-heaven-such-as-it-is-is-right-here-on-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 07:38:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119475-heaven-such-as-it-is-is-right-here-on-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heaven, such as it is, is right here on earth. Behold: my revelation: I stand at the door in the morning, and lo, there is a newspaper, in sight like unto an emerald. And holy, holy, holy is the coffee, which was, and is, and is to come. And hark, I hear the voice of an angel round about the radio saying, &quot;Since my baby left me I found a new place to dwell.&quot; And lo, after this I beheld a great multitude, which no man could number, of shoes. And after these things I will hasten unto a taxicab and to a theater, where a ticket will be given unto me, and lo, it will be a matinee, and a film that doeth great wonders. And when it is finished, the heavens will open, and out will cometh a rain fragrant as myrrh, and yea, I have an umbrella." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205769-i-always-thought-insanity-would-be-a-dark-bitter-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 16:38:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205769-i-always-thought-insanity-would-be-a-dark-bitter-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always thought insanity would be a dark, bitter feeling, but it is drenching and delicious if you really roll around in it." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32781-words-can-be-like-x-rays-if-you-use-them-properly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2012 06:47:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32781-words-can-be-like-x-rays-if-you-use-them-properly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words can be like X-rays if you use them properly -- they’ll go through anything. You read and you’re pierced." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429292-we-need-to-reclaim-the-word-feminism-we-need-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need to reclaim the word 'feminism'. We need the word 'feminism' back real bad. When statistics come in saying that only 29% of American women would describe themselves as feminist - and only 42% of British women - I used to think, What do you think feminism IS, ladies? What part of 'liberation for women' is not for you? Is it freedom to vote? The right not to be owned by the man you marry? The campaign for equal pay? 'Vogue' by Madonna? Jeans? Did all that good shit GET ON YOUR NERVES? Or were you just DRUNK AT THE TIME OF THE SURVEY?" -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408386-if-you-want-to-know-what-s-in-motherhood-for-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:21:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/408386-if-you-want-to-know-what-s-in-motherhood-for-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to know what's in motherhood for you, as a woman, then - in truth - it's nothing you couldn't get from, say, reading the 100 greatest books in human history; learning a foreign language well enough to argue in it; climbing hills; loving recklessly; sitting quietly, alone, in the dawn; drinking whisky with revolutionaries; learning to do close-hand magic; swimming in a river in winter; growing foxgloves, peas and roses; calling your mum; singing while you walk; being polite; and always, always helping strangers. No one has ever claimed for a moment that childless men have missed out on a vital aspect of their existence, and were the poorer, and crippled by it." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492364-batman-doesn-t-want-a-baby-in-order-to-feel-he-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492364-batman-doesn-t-want-a-baby-in-order-to-feel-he-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Batman doesn’t want a baby in order to feel he’s ‘done everything’. He’s just saved Gotham again! If this means that Batman must be a feminist role model above, say, Nicola Horlick, then so be it." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543324-no-really-what-exactly-did-you-do-today-jenny-quantify</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:22:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Jenny Lawson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543324-no-really-what-exactly-did-you-do-today-jenny-quantify]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No really. What exactly did you do today, Jenny? Quantify it for me.&quot;
&quot;It's not quantifiable. There aren't even metrics for the shit I do." -- Jenny Lawson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543328-and-whenever-i-had-menstral-cramps-i-could-just-pretend</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:28:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Jenny Lawson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543328-and-whenever-i-had-menstral-cramps-i-could-just-pretend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...and whenever I had menstral cramps, I could just pretend that Voldemort was close." -- Jenny Lawson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626235-it-s-difficult-to-see-the-glass-ceiling-because-it-s-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 09:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626235-it-s-difficult-to-see-the-glass-ceiling-because-it-s-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's difficult to see the glass ceiling because it's made of glass. Virtually invisible. What we need is for more birds to fly above it and shit all over it, so we can see it properly." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505236-i-cannot-understand-anti-abortion-arguments-that-centre-on-the-sanctity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2012 07:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505236-i-cannot-understand-anti-abortion-arguments-that-centre-on-the-sanctity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot understand anti-abortion arguments that centre on the sanctity of life.  As a species we've fairly comprehensively demonstrated that we don't believe in the sanctity of life.  The shrugging acceptance of war, famine, epidemic, pain and life-long poverty shows us that, whatever we tell ourselves, we've made only the most feeble of efforts to &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; treat human life as sacred." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205151-i-am-a-child-of-cosmopolitan-culture-have-been-traumatized</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 07:35:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Helen Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205151-i-am-a-child-of-cosmopolitan-culture-have-been-traumatized]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a child of Cosmopolitan culture, have been traumatized by supermodels and too many quizzes and know that neither my personality nor my body is up to it if left to its own devices. I can't take the pressure." -- Helen Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119844-junction-nineteen-una-she-came-off-at-junction-nineteen-you-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 07:36:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Helen Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119844-junction-nineteen-una-she-came-off-at-junction-nineteen-you-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Junction nineteen!  Una, she came off at Junction nineteen!  You've added an hour to your journey before you even started.  Come on, let's get you a drink.  How's your love life, anyway?&quot;

Oh GOD.  Why can't married people understand that this is no longer a polite question to ask?  We wouldn't rush up to THEM and roar, &quot;How's your marriage going?  Still having sex?&quot;  Everyone knows that dating in your thirties is not the happy-go-lucky free-for-it-all it was when you were twenty-two and that the honest answer is more likely to be, &quot;Actually, last night my married lover appeared wearing suspenders and a darling little Angora crop-top, told me he was gay/a sex addict/a narcotic addict/a commitment phobic and beat me up with a dildo,&quot; than, &quot;Super, thanks." -- Helen Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203862-it-s-brilliant-being-depressed-you-can-behave-as-badly-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 06:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenn add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203862-it-s-brilliant-being-depressed-you-can-behave-as-badly-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's brilliant, being depressed; you can behave as badly as you like." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
