<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780927-patrick]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/780927-patrick" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 08:59:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22089-to-get-a-better-idea-try-this-focus-on-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 08:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22089-to-get-a-better-idea-try-this-focus-on-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To get a better idea try this: focus on these words, and whatever you do don’t let your eyes wander past the perimeter of this page. Now imagine just beyond your peripheral vision, maybe behind you, maybe to the side of you, maybe even in front of you, but right where you can’t see it, something is quietly closing in on you, so quiet in fact that you can only hear it as silence. Find those pockets without sound. That’s where it is. Right at this moment. But don’t look. Keep your eyes here. Now take a deep breath. Go ahead take and even deeper one. Only this time as you start to exhale try to imagine how fast it will happen, how hard it’s gonna hit you, how many times it will stab your jugular with it’s teeth or are they nails?, don’t worry, that particular detail doesn’t matter, because before you have time to even process that you should be moving, you should be running, you should at the very least be flinging up your arms – you sure as hell should be getting rid of this book – you won’t have time to even scream.&lt;br&gt;
Don’t look.&lt;br&gt;
I didn’t." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 08:59:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This much I'm certain of: it doesn't happen immediately. You'll finish [the book] and that will be that, until a moment will come, maybe in a month, maybe a year, maybe even several years. You'll be sick or feeling troubled or deeply in love or quietly uncertain or even content for the first time in your life. It won't matter. Out of the blue, beyond any cause you can trace, you'll suddenly realize things are not how you perceived them to be at all. For some reason, you will no longer be the person you believed you once were. You'll detect slow and subtle shifts going on all around you, more importantly shifts in you. Worse, you'll realize it's always been shifting, like a shimmer of sorts, a vast shimmer, only dark like a room. But you won't understand why or how. You'll have forgotten what granted you this awareness in the first place&lt;br&gt;
...&lt;br&gt;
You might try then, as I did, to find a sky so full of stars it will blind you again. Only no sky can blind you now. Even with all that iridescent magic up there, your eye will no longer linger on the light, it will no longer trace constellations. You'll care only about the darkness and you'll watch it for hours, for days, maybe even for years, trying in vain to believe you're some kind of indispensable, universe-appointed sentinel, as if just by looking you could actually keep it all at bay. It will get so bad you'll be afraid to look away, you'll be afraid to sleep.&lt;br&gt;
Then no matter where you are, in a crowded restaurant or on some desolate street or even in the comforts of your own home, you'll watch yourself dismantle every assurance you ever lived by. You'll stand aside as a great complexity intrudes, tearing apart, piece by piece, all of your carefully conceived denials, whether deliberate or unconscious. And then for better or worse you'll turn, unable to resist, though try to resist you still will, fighting with everything you've got not to face the thing you most dread, what is now, what will be, what has always come before, the creature you truly are, the creature we all are, buried in the nameless black of a name.&lt;br&gt;
And then the nightmares will begin." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22433-to-know-one-s-own-state-is-not-a-simple-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know one’s own state is not a simple matter. One cannot look directly at one’s own face with one’s own eyes, for example. One has no choice but to look at one’s reflection in the mirror. Through experience, we come to believe that the image is correct, but that is all." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:01:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it came to me then. That we were wonderful traveling companions but in the end no more than lonely lumps of metal in their own separate orbits.  From far off they look like beautiful shooting stars, but in reality they're nothing more than prisons, where each of us is locked up alone, going nowhere. When the orbits of these two satellites of ours happened to cross paths, we could be together. Maybe even open our hearts to each other. But that was only for the briefest moment. In the next instant we'd be in absolute solitude. Until we burned up and became nothing." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
