<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/781213-natalie-aristy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/781213-natalie-aristy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:17:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6670-don-t-be-afraid-people-are-so-afraid-don-t-be-afraid</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:17:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6670-don-t-be-afraid-people-are-so-afraid-don-t-be-afraid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be afraid; people are so afraid; don't be afraid to live in the raw wind, naked, alone...Learn at least this: What you are capable of. Let nothing stand in your way." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521263-it-s-all-going-to-be-okay-she-would-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:32:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Anne Ursu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521263-it-s-all-going-to-be-okay-she-would-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;It’s all going to be okay.&lt;/i&gt; She would like to hear that now, even if it was a lie. Because some lies are beautiful. Stories do not tell you that." -- Anne Ursu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43596-the-fact-that-i-am-writing-to-you-in-english</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Gustavo Perez Firmat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43596-the-fact-that-i-am-writing-to-you-in-english]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that I
am writing to you
in English
already falsifies what I
wanted to tell you.
My subject:
how to explain to you that I
don't belong to English
though I belong nowhere else" -- Gustavo Perez Firmat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13324-respect-the-delicate-ecology-of-your-delusions</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13324-respect-the-delicate-ecology-of-your-delusions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Respect the delicate ecology of your delusions." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12358-the-white-cracker-who-wrote-the-national-anthem-knew-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 10:18:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12358-the-white-cracker-who-wrote-the-national-anthem-knew-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The white cracker who wrote the National Anthem knew what he was doing. He set the word &quot;free&quot; to a note so high nobody could reach it. That was deliberate." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521254-her-father-said-she-was-a-princess-he-did-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:33:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Anne Ursu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521254-her-father-said-she-was-a-princess-he-did-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her father said she was a princess. He did not see that she was a brave knight." -- Anne Ursu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125898-you-re-always-you-and-that-don-t-change-and-you-re-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125898-you-re-always-you-and-that-don-t-change-and-you-re-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're always you, and that don't change, and you're always changing, and there's nothing you can do about it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141850-one-summer-morning-at-sunrise-a-long-time-ago-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 17:52:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141850-one-summer-morning-at-sunrise-a-long-time-ago-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One summer morning at sunrise a long time ago
I met a little girl with a book under her arm.
I asked her why she was out so early and
she answered that there were too many books and
far too little time.  And there she was absolutely right." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 11:00:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a girl, and her uncle sold her. Put like that it seems so simple.

No man, proclaimed Donne, is an island, and he was wrong. If we were not islands, we would be lost, drowned in each other's tragedies. We are insulated (a word that means, literally, remember, made into an island) from the tragedy of others, by our island nature and by the repetitive shape and form of the stories. The shape does not change: there was a human being who was born, lived and then by some means or other, died. There. You may fill in the details from your own experience. As unoriginal as any other tale, as unique as any other life. Lives are snowflakes- forming patterns we have seen before, as like one another as peas in a pod (and have you ever looked at peas in a pod? I mean, really looked at them? There's not a chance you'll mistake one for another, after a minute's close inspection) but still unique.

Without individuals we see only numbers, a thousand dead, a hundred thousand dead, &quot;casualties may rise to a million.&quot; With individual stories, the statistics become people- but even that is a lie, for the people continue to suffer in numbers that themselves are numbing and meaningless. Look, see the child's swollen, swollen belly and the flies that crawl at the corners of his eyes, this skeletal limbs: will it make it easier for you to know his name, his age, his dreams, his fears? To see him from the inside? And if it does, are we not doing a disservice to his sister, who lies in the searing dust beside him, a distorted distended caricature of a human child? And there, if we feel for them, are they now more important to us than a thousand other children touched by the same famine, a thousand other young lives who will soon be food for the flies' own myriad squirming children?

We draw our lines around these moments of pain, remain upon our islands, and they cannot hurt us. They are covered with a smooth, safe, nacreous layer to let them slip, pearllike, from our souls without real pain.

Fiction allows us to slide into these other heads, these other places, and look out through other eyes. And then in the tale we stop before we die, or we die vicariously and unharmed, and in the world beyond the tale we turn the page or close the book, and we resume our lives.

A life that is, like any other, unlike any other.

And the simple truth is this: There was a girl, and her uncle sold her." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191699-moominvalley-in-november-chapter-5-the-hemulen-the-hemulen-woke</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 17:50:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191699-moominvalley-in-november-chapter-5-the-hemulen-the-hemulen-woke]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Moominvalley in November
Chapter 5, THE HEMULEN:

The hemulen woke up slowly and recognised himself and wished he had been someone he didn't know. He felt even tireder than when he went to bed, and here it was -- another day which would go on until evening and then there would be another one and another one which would be the same as all days are when they are lived by a hemulen.

He crept under the bedcover and buried his nose in the pillow, then he shifted his stomach to the edge of the bed where the sheets were cool. He took possession of the whole bed with outstretched arms and legs he was waiting for a nice dream that wouldn't come. He curled up and made himself small but it didn't help a bit. He tried being the hemulen that everybody like, he tried being the hemulen that no one liked. But however hard he tried he remained a hemulen doing his best without anything really coming off. In the end he got up and pulled on his trousers.

The Hemulen didn't like getting dressed and undressed, it gave him a feeling that the days passed without anything of importance happening. Even so, he spent the whole day arranging, organising and directing things from morning till night! All around him there were people living slipshod and aimless lives, wherever he looked there was something to be put to rights and he worked his fingers to the bone trying to get them to see how they ought to live.

It's as though they don't want to live well, the Hemulen thought sadly as he brushed his teeth. He looked at the photograph of himself with his boat which was been taken when the boat was launched. It was a beautiful picture but it made him feel even sadder.

I ought to learn how to sail, the Hemulen thought. But I've never got enough time..." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53452-the-only-thing-you-can-do-easily-is-be-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:06:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53452-the-only-thing-you-can-do-easily-is-be-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only thing you can do easily is be wrong, and that's hardly worth the effort." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431709-she-d-read-once-that-if-you-ran-into-a-bear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:32:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Anne Ursu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431709-she-d-read-once-that-if-you-ran-into-a-bear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She'd read once that if you ran into a bear in the woods you should avoid eye contact and you shouldn't run away, but all she knew about wolves is that you should never tell them how to find your grandmother's house." -- Anne Ursu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:34:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:39:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21831-tomorrow-may-be-hell-but-today-was-a-good-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:39:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21831-tomorrow-may-be-hell-but-today-was-a-good-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow may be hell, but today was a good writing day, and on the good writing days nothing else matters." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 10:39:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a writer is a very peculiar sort of a job: it's always you versus a blank sheet of paper (or a blank screen) and quite often the blank piece of paper wins." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546034-most-of-the-people-are-homesick-anyway-and-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 10:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/546034-most-of-the-people-are-homesick-anyway-and-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of the people are homesick anyway, and a little lonely, and they hide themselves in their hair and are turned into flowers." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43915-when-writing-a-novel-that-s-pretty-much-entirely-what-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 11:19:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43915-when-writing-a-novel-that-s-pretty-much-entirely-what-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When writing a novel, that's pretty much entirely what life turns into: 'House burned down. Car stolen. Cat exploded. Did 1500 easy words, so all in all it was a pretty good day." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 10:57:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549915-just-think-never-to-be-glad-or-disappointed-never-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 10:56:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549915-just-think-never-to-be-glad-or-disappointed-never-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["‎''Just think, never to be glad or disappointed. Never to like anyone and get cross at him and forgive him. Never to sleep or feel cold, never to make a mistake and have a stomach-ache and be cured from it, never to have a birthday party, drink beer, and have a bad conscience...
How terrible." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392579-in-this-box-are-all-the-words-i-know-most-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 14:53:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/392579-in-this-box-are-all-the-words-i-know-most-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this box are all the words I know…Most of them you will never need, some you will use constantly, but with them you may ask all the questions which have never been answered and answer all the questions which have never been asked.  All the great books of the past and all the ones yet to come are made with these words.  With them there is no obstacle you cannot overcome.  All you must learn to do is to use them well and in the right places." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281749-you-must-never-feel-badly-about-making-mistakes-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:06:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281749-you-must-never-feel-badly-about-making-mistakes-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must never feel badly about making mistakes ... as long as you take the trouble to learn from them. For you often learn more by being wrong for the right reasons than you do by being right for the wrong reasons." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206875-whether-or-not-you-find-your-own-way-you-re-bound</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:06:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206875-whether-or-not-you-find-your-own-way-you-re-bound]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether or not you find your own way, you're bound to find some way. If you happen to find my way, please return it, as it was lost years ago. I imagine by now it's quite rusty." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204338-so-many-things-are-possible-just-as-long-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:06:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Norton Juster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204338-so-many-things-are-possible-just-as-long-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many things are possible just as long as you don't know they're impossible." -- Norton Juster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521266-in-woods-where-the-woodsmen-told-lies-maybe-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 15:33:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Anne Ursu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521266-in-woods-where-the-woodsmen-told-lies-maybe-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In woods where the woodsmen told lies, maybe it was the wolves who told the truth." -- Anne Ursu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2013 06:53:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12428-i-want-to-stand-as-close-to-the-edge-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to stand as close to the edge as I can without going over. Out on the edge you see all kinds of things you can't see from the center." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34897-if-you-talk-to-a-man-in-a-language-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Nelson Mandela]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34897-if-you-talk-to-a-man-in-a-language-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you talk to a man in a language he understands, that goes to his head. If you talk to him in his language, that goes to his heart." -- Nelson Mandela]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45583-no-two-languages-are-ever-sufficiently-similar-to-be-considered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 10:17:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45583-no-two-languages-are-ever-sufficiently-similar-to-be-considered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No two languages are ever sufficiently similar to be considered as representing the same social reality. The worlds in which different societies live are distinct worlds, not merely the same world with different labels attached." -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
