<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78406-katja]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78406-katja" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:04:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:04:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katja add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know that feeling at the end of the day, when the anxiety of that-which-I-must-do falls away and, for maybe the first time that day, you see, with some clarity, the people you love and the ways you have, during that day, slightly ignored them, turned away from them to get back to what you were doing, blurted out some mildly hurtful thing, projected, instead of the deep love you really feel, a surge of defensiveness or self-protection or suspicion?  That moment when you think, Oh God, what have I done with this day?  And what am I doing with my life?  And how must I change to avoid catastrophic end-of-life regrets?

I feel like that now: tired of the Me I've always been, tired of making the same mistakes, repetitively stumbling after the same small ego strokes, being caught in the same loops of anxiety and defensiveness.  At the end of my life, I know I won't be wishing I'd held more back, been less effusive, more often stood on ceremony, forgiven less, spent more days oblivious to the secret wishes and fears of the people around me...  

--&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53198-smile-first-then-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:05:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katja add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53198-smile-first-then-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...smile first, then speak." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165929-the-mind-is-a-machine-that-is-constantly-asking-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:11:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katja add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165929-the-mind-is-a-machine-that-is-constantly-asking-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind is a machine that is constantly asking: What would I prefer?  Close your eyes, refuse to move, and watch what your mind does.  What it does is become discontent with That Which Is.  A desire arises, you satisfy that desire, and another arises in its place.  This wanting and rewanting is an endless cycle for which, turns out, there is already a name: samsara.  Samsara is at the heart of the vast human carnival: greed, neurosis, mad ambition, adultery, crimes of passion, the hacking to death of a terrified man on a hillside in the name of A More Pure And Thus Perfect Nation--and all of this takes place because we believe we will be made happy once our desires have been satisfied.  

I know this.  But still I'm full of desire...  --&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50062-there-is-no-end-to-the-making-and-selling-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:15:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katja add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50062-there-is-no-end-to-the-making-and-selling-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...There is no end to the making and selling of things there is no end to the making and selling of things there is no end...

Man, it occurs to me, is a joyful, buying-and-selling piece of work. I have been wrong, dead wrong, when I've decried consumerism. Consumerism is what we are. It is, in a sense, a holy impulse. A human being is someone who joyfully goes in pursuit of things, brings them home, then immediately starts planning how to get more." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70598-at-precisely-nine-in-the-morning-working-with-focus-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 22:16:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katja add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70598-at-precisely-nine-in-the-morning-working-with-focus-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At precisely nine in the morning, working with focus and stealth, our entire membership succeeded in simultaneously beheading no one... not a single one of us blew himself/herself up in a crowded public place... in addition, zero (0) planes were flown into buildings.
All this was accomplished so surreptitiosly, it attracted little public notice." -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
