<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/784856-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/784856-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 23:40:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313548-it-was-anyway-all-a-long-time-ago-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 23:40:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313548-it-was-anyway-all-a-long-time-ago-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was anyway all a long time ago; the world, we know now, is as it is and not different; if there was ever a time when there were passages, doors, the borders open and many crossing, that time is not now. The world is older than it was. Even the weather isn’t as we remember it clearly once being; never lately does there come a summer day such as we remember, never clouds as white as that, never grass as odorous or shade as deep and full of promise as we remember they can be, as once upon a time they were." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359541-stories-last-longer-but-only-by-becoming-only-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 23:40:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by John Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359541-stories-last-longer-but-only-by-becoming-only-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories last longer: but only by becoming only stories." -- John Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522326-ghosts-are-those-memories-that-are-too-strong-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 02:47:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Caitlín R. Kiernan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522326-ghosts-are-those-memories-that-are-too-strong-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ghosts are those memories that are too strong to be forgotten for good, echoing across the years and refusing to be obliterated by time." -- Caitlín R. Kiernan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115975-if-you-are-falling-dive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 21:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115975-if-you-are-falling-dive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are falling....dive." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156592-in-books-i-have-traveled-not-only-to-other-worlds</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 19:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156592-in-books-i-have-traveled-not-only-to-other-worlds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In books I have traveled, not only to other worlds, but into my own. I learned who I was and who I wanted to be, what I might aspire to, and what I might dare to dream about my world and myself. More powerfully and persuasively than from the &quot;shalt nots&quot; of the Ten Commandments, I learned the difference between good and evil, right and wrong. A Wrinkle in Time described that evil, that wrong, existing in a different dimension from our own. But I felt that I, too, existed much of the time in a different dimension from everyone else I knew. There was waking, and there was sleeping. And then there were books, a kind of parallel universe in which anything might happen and frequently did, a universe in which I might be a newcomer but was never really a stranger. My real, true world. My perfect island." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 16:28:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 17:30:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8202-most-men-lead-lives-of-quiet-desperation-and-go-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men lead lives of quiet desperation and go to the grave with the song still in them." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1148007-the-most-problematic-depression-episodes-plunge-me-into-a-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 22:48:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Cat Treadwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1148007-the-most-problematic-depression-episodes-plunge-me-into-a-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most problematic depression episodes plunge me into a feeling of disconnection. I am no longer a part of the world. All the colours, meaning and richness become hidden or lost to me. There is a numbing absence of feeling that strips away any inspiration and creativity. I become dead to myself, a husk, a shell. The fall into this state can be violently fast, although the triggers have all been external. Life does not treat many of us kindly. Most of the time, I draw inspiration from the world around me. That sense of connection to all other living and perhaps-not-living things nourishes and sustains me. Being pushed out of that sense of belonging is brutal. I have self-esteem issues and, subjected as I was to barrages of abuse, bitter criticism, invasive scrutiny and some terrifying processes in my life, I’ve been crushed, repeatedly. I’ve come to places where I’ve felt so awful that the only imaginable way out, I thought, was to die. I’m still alive because of the love and dedication of my husband. I hold the hope that I won’t have to crawl through hell again anytime soon, that I can build internal reserves strong enough to resist external pressures." -- Cat Treadwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869739-there-is-no-mystery-in-this-association-of-woods-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 03:44:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869739-there-is-no-mystery-in-this-association-of-woods-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no mystery in this association of woods and otherworlds, for as anyone who has walked the woods knows, they are places of correspondence, of call and answer. Visual affinities of color, relief and texture abound. A fallen branch echoes the deltoid form of a streambed into which it has come to rest. Chrome yellow autumn elm leaves find their color rhyme in the eye-ring of the blackbird. Different aspects of the forest link unexpectedly with each other, and so it is that within the stories, different times and worlds can be joined." -- Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869732-before-coming-to-the-black-wood-i-had-read-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 03:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869732-before-coming-to-the-black-wood-i-had-read-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before coming to the Black Wood, I had read as widely in tree lore as possible. As well as the many accounts I encountered of damage to trees and woodland -- of what in German is called Waldsterben, or 'forest-death' -- I also met with and noted down stories of astonishment at woods and trees. Stories of how Chinese woodsmen in the T'ang and S'ung dynasties -- in obedience to the Taoist philosophy of a continuity of nature between humans and other species -- would bow to the trees which they felled, and offer a promise that the tree would be used well, in buildings that would dignify the wood once it had become timber.  The story of Xerxes, the Persian king who so loved sycamores that, when marching to war with the Greeks, he halted his army of many thousands of men in order that they might contemplate and admire one outstanding specimen. Thoreau's story of how he felt so attached to the trees in the woods around his home-town of Concord, Massachusetts, that he would call regularly on them, gladly tramping 'eight or ten miles through the deepest snow to keep an appointment with a beech-tree, or yellow-birch, or an old acquaintance among the pines.

When Willa Cather moved to the prairies of Nebraska, she missed the wooded hills of her native Virginia. Pining for trees, she would sometimes travel south 'to our German neighbors, to admire their catalpa grove, or to see the big elm tree that grew out of a crack in the earth. Trees were so rare in that country that we used to feel anxious about them, and visit them as if they were persons'...." -- Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739500-humans-are-animals-and-like-all-animals-we-leave-tracks</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 03:44:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739500-humans-are-animals-and-like-all-animals-we-leave-tracks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humans are animals and like all animals we leave tracks as we walk: signs of passage made in snow, sand, mud, grass, dew, earth or moss.... We easily forget that we are track-markers, through, because most of our journeys now occur on asphalt and concrete--and these are substances not easily impressed." -- Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951571-wild-animals-like-wild-places-are-invaluable-to-us-precisely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 03:45:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/951571-wild-animals-like-wild-places-are-invaluable-to-us-precisely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wild animals, like wild places, are invaluable to us precisely because they are not us. They are uncompromisingly different. The paths they follow, the impulses that guide them, are of other orders. The seal's holding gaze, before it flukes to push another tunnel through the sea, the hare's run, the hawk's high gyres : such things are wild. Seeing them, you are made briefly aware of a world at work around and beside our own, a world operating in patterns and purposes that you do not share. These are creatures, you realise that live by voices inaudible to you." -- Robert Macfarlane]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
