<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78611-nitya-sivasubramanian]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78611-nitya-sivasubramanian" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:12:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235838-there-are-two-kinds-of-folks-who-sit-around-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:12:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Richard Castle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235838-there-are-two-kinds-of-folks-who-sit-around-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of folks who sit around thinking about how to kill people: psychopaths and mystery writers." -- Richard Castle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602580-rook-was-a-journalist-but-strove-to-be-a-storyteller</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:14:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Richard Castle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/602580-rook-was-a-journalist-but-strove-to-be-a-storyteller]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rook was a journalist but strove to be a storyteller, one who let his subjects speak for themselves and stayed out of their way as much as possible." -- Richard Castle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130823-nothing-in-life-is-fair-fair-is-a-dirty-word</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:16:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130823-nothing-in-life-is-fair-fair-is-a-dirty-word]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing in life is fair.  Fair is a dirty word and I'll thank you not to use that language around me." -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394253-i-often-find-myself-in-situations-where-it-seems-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:17:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394253-i-often-find-myself-in-situations-where-it-seems-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often find myself in situations where it seems to me like everyone else has read the instruction book" -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250830-i-know-family-comes-first-but-shouldn-t-that-mean-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:17:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250830-i-know-family-comes-first-but-shouldn-t-that-mean-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know family comes first, but shouldn't that mean after breakfast?" -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479842-i-sighed-as-comforting-as-it-may-be-to-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:18:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479842-i-sighed-as-comforting-as-it-may-be-to-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sighed; as comforting as it may be to some of us, sarcasm, like youth, is wasted on the young." -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342519-there-is-a-technical-term-for-someone-who-confuses-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:20:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by S. M. Stirling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/342519-there-is-a-technical-term-for-someone-who-confuses-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a technical term for someone who confuses the opinions of a character in a book with those of the author. That term is idiot." -- S. M. Stirling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665066-the-artificial-primacy-of-defense-among-our-national-priorities-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:22:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Rachel Maddow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665066-the-artificial-primacy-of-defense-among-our-national-priorities-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The artificial primacy of defense among our national priorities is a constant unearned windfall for some, but it's privation for the rest of America; it steals from what we could be and can do.  In Econ 101, they teach that the big-picture fight over national priorities is guns versus butter.  Now it's butter versus margarine—guns get a pass.

Overall, we're weaker for it, and at enormous cost." -- Rachel Maddow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692767-there-was-no-aphrodisiac-more-powerful-than-talking-no-seduction</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 12:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Manju Kapur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692767-there-was-no-aphrodisiac-more-powerful-than-talking-no-seduction]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was no aphrodisiac more powerful than talking, no seduction more effective than curiosity." -- Manju Kapur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:11:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think dreams aren't real just because they aren't made of matter, of particles. Dreams are real. But they are made of viewpoints, of images, of memories and puns and lost hopes." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7391-most-books-on-witchcraft-will-tell-you-that-witches-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:12:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7391-most-books-on-witchcraft-will-tell-you-that-witches-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most books on witchcraft will tell you that witches work naked.  This is because most books on witchcraft were written by men." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:12:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58240-being-a-writer-is-a-very-peculiar-sort-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a writer is a very peculiar sort of a job: it's always you versus a blank sheet of paper (or a blank screen) and quite often the blank piece of paper wins." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:12:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65656-this-is-how-you-do-it-you-sit-down-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:12:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65656-this-is-how-you-do-it-you-sit-down-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how you do it: you sit down at the keyboard and you put one word after another until its done. It's that easy, and that hard." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:12:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39535-each-person-who-ever-was-or-is-or-will-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39535-each-person-who-ever-was-or-is-or-will-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each person who ever was or is or will be has a song. It isn't a song that anybody else wrote. It has its own melody, it has its own words. Very few people get to sing their song. Most of us fear that we cannot do it justice with our voices, or that our words are too foolish or too honest, or too odd. So people live their song instead." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156274-stories-you-read-when-you-re-the-right-age-never-quite</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156274-stories-you-read-when-you-re-the-right-age-never-quite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories you read when you're the right age never quite leave you. You may forget who wrote them or what the story was called. Sometimes you'll forget precisely what happened, but if a story touches you it will stay with you, haunting the places in your mind that you rarely ever visit." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21491-stories-may-well-be-lies-but-they-are-good-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories may well be lies, but they are good lies that say true things, and which can sometimes pay the rent." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133494-what-s-your-name-coraline-asked-the-cat-look-i-m-coraline</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133494-what-s-your-name-coraline-asked-the-cat-look-i-m-coraline]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What's your name,' Coraline asked the cat. 'Look, I'm Coraline. Okay?'
'Cats don't have names,' it said.
'No?' said Coraline.
'No,' said the cat. 'Now you people have names. That's because you don't know who you are. We know who we are, so we don't need names." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25303-it-may-help-to-understand-human-affairs-to-be-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may help to understand human affairs to be clear that most of the great triumphs and tragedies of history are caused, not by people being fundamentally good or fundamentally bad, but by people being fundamentally people." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138277-because-she-said-when-you-re-scared-but-you-still-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138277-because-she-said-when-you-re-scared-but-you-still-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because,' she said, 'when you're scared but you still do it anyway, that's brave." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125057-books-make-great-gifts-because-they-have-whole-worlds-inside</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:13:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125057-books-make-great-gifts-because-they-have-whole-worlds-inside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books make great gifts because they have whole worlds inside of them. And it's much cheaper to buy somebody a book than it is to buy them the whole world!" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:14:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42627-most-people-don-t-realize-how-important-librarians-are-i-ran]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people don't realize how important librarians are. I ran across a book recently which suggested that the peace and prosperity of a culture was solely related to how many librarians it contained. Possibly a slight overstatement. But a culture that doesn't value its librarians doesn't value ideas and without ideas, well, where are we?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193851-picking-five-favorite-books-is-like-picking-the-five-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 03:14:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nitya add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193851-picking-five-favorite-books-is-like-picking-the-five-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Picking five favorite books is like picking the five body parts you'd most like not to lose." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
