<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/787676-mandy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/787676-mandy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 15:41:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52639-our-life-is-composed-greatly-from-dreams-from-the-unconscious</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 15:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52639-our-life-is-composed-greatly-from-dreams-from-the-unconscious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our life is composed greatly from dreams, from the unconscious, and they must be brought into connection with action. They must be woven together. " -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2014 17:27:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 08:13:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are a dreamer come in
If you are a dreamer a wisher a liar
A hoper a pray-er a magic-bean-buyer
If youre a pretender com sit by my fire
For we have some flax golden tales to spin
Come in! 
Come in!" -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311499-no-i-don-t-want-to-speak-of-that-but-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 11:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311499-no-i-don-t-want-to-speak-of-that-but-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No!  I don't want to speak of that!  But I'm going to.  I want you to hear.  I want you to know what's in store for you.  There will be days when you'll look at your hands and you'll want to take something and smash every bone in them, because they'll be taunting you with what they could do, if you found a chance for them to do it, and you can't find that chance, and you can't bear your living body because it has failed those hands somewhere.  There will be days when a bus driver will snap at you as you enter a bus, and he'll be only asking for a dime, but that won't be what you hear; you'll hear that you're nothing, that he's laughing at you, that it's written on your forehead, that thing they hate you for.  There will be days when you'll stand in the corner of a hall and listen to a creature on a platform talking about buildings, about the work you love, and the things he'll say will make you wait for somebody to rise and crack him open between two thumbnails; and then you'll hear people applauding him, and you'll want to scream, because you won't know whether they're real or you are, whether you're in a room full of gored skulls, or whether someone has just emptied your own head, and you'll say nothing, because the sounds you could make - they're not a language in that room any longer; but you'd want to speak, you won't anyway, because you'll be brushed aside, you who have nothing to tell them about buildings!  Is that what you want?" -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282327-i-try-to-believe-in-as-many-as-six-impossible</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 12:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mandy add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282327-i-try-to-believe-in-as-many-as-six-impossible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I try to believe in as many as six impossible things before breakfast. Count them, Alice. One, there are drinks that make you shrink. Two, there are foods that make you grow. Three, animals can talk. Four, cats can disappear. Five, there is a place called Underland. Six, I can slay the Jabberwocky." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
