<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78792-cat]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/78792-cat" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 11:02:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 11:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47882-to-crave-and-to-have-are-as-like-as-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To crave and to have are as like as a thing and its shadow. For when does a berry break upon the tongue as sweetly as when one longs to taste it, and when is the taste refracted into so many hues and savors of ripeness and earth, and when do our senses know any thing so utterly as when we lack it? And here again is a foreshadowing -- the world will be made whole. For to wish for a hand on one's hair is all but to feel it. So whatever we may lose, very craving gives it back to us again." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212282-i-hated-waiting-if-i-had-one-particular-complaint-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 11:14:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212282-i-hated-waiting-if-i-had-one-particular-complaint-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hated waiting. If I had one particular complaint, it was that my life seemed composed entirely of expectation. I expected - an arrival, an explanation, an apology. There never had been one, a fact I could have accepted, were it not true that, just when I got used to the limits and dimensions of one moment, I was expelled into the next and made to wonder again if any shapes hid in its shadows. That most moments were substantially the same did not detract at all from the possibility that the next moment might be utterly different. And so the ordinary demanded unblinking attention. Any tedious hour might be the last of its kind." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323613-having-a-sister-or-a-friend-is-like-sitting-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 11:15:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/323613-having-a-sister-or-a-friend-is-like-sitting-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a sister or a friend is like sitting at night in a lighted house. Those outside can watch you if they want, but you need not see them. You simply say, &quot;Here are the perimeters of our attention. If you prowl around under the windows till the crickets go silent, we will pull the shades. If you wish us to suffer your envious curiosity, you must permit us not to notice it.&quot; Anyone with one solid human bond is that smug, and it is the smugness as much as the comfort and safety that lonely people covet and admire." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344891-patriotism-red-hot-is-compatible-with-the-existence-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 14:24:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Charlotte Perkins Gilman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/344891-patriotism-red-hot-is-compatible-with-the-existence-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Patriotism, red hot, is compatible with the existence of a neglect of national interests, a dishonesty, a cold indifference to the suffering of millions. Patriotism is largely pride, and very largely combativeness. Patriotism generally has a chip on its shoulder." -- Charlotte Perkins Gilman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354265-dreams-of-innocence-are-just-that-they-usually-depend-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 11:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354265-dreams-of-innocence-are-just-that-they-usually-depend-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dreams of innocence are just that; they usually depend on a denial of reality that can be its own form of hubris." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396706-the-repetitive-phases-of-cooking-leave-plenty-of-mental-space</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 11:20:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396706-the-repetitive-phases-of-cooking-leave-plenty-of-mental-space]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The repetitive phases of cooking leave plenty of mental space for reflection, and as I chopped and minced and sliced I thought about the rhythms of cooking, one of which involves destroying the order of the things we bring from nature into our kitchens, only to then create from them a new order. We butcher, grind, chop, grate, mince, and liquefy raw ingredients, breaking down formerly living things so that we might recombine them in new, more cultivated forms. When you think about it, this is the same rhythm, once removed, that governs all eating in nature, which invariably entails the destruction of certain living things, by chewing and then digestion, in order to sustain other living things. In &lt;i&gt;The Hungry Soul&lt;/i&gt; Leon Kass calls this the great paradox of eating: 'that to preserve their life and form living things necessarily destroy life and form.' If there is any shame in that destruction, only we humans seem to feel it, and then only on occasion. But cooking doesn't only distance us from our destructiveness, turning the pile of blood and guts into a savory salami, it also symbolically redeems it, making good our karmic debts: &lt;i&gt;Look what good, what beauty, can come of this!&lt;/i&gt; Putting a great dish on the table is our way of celebrating the wonders of form we humans can create from this matter--this quantity of sacrificed life--just before the body takes its first destructive bite." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834793-there-is-great-value-in-being-able-to-say-yes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 17:01:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Tamar Adler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834793-there-is-great-value-in-being-able-to-say-yes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is great value in being able to say &quot;yes&quot; when people ask if there is anything they can do. By letting people pick herbs or slice bread instead of bringing a salad, you make your kitchen a universe in which you can give completely and ask for help. The more environments with that atmospheric makeup we can find or create, the better." -- Tamar Adler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830423-grown-ups-don-t-look-like-grown-ups-on-the-inside-either-outside</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 03:42:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830423-grown-ups-don-t-look-like-grown-ups-on-the-inside-either-outside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grown-ups don't look like grown-ups on the inside either. Outside, they're big and thoughtless and they always know what they're doing. Inside, they look just like they always have. Like they did when they were your age. Truth is, there aren't any grown-ups. Not one, in the whole wide world." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152730-i-became-aware-of-just-how-fleeting-the-sense-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 18:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cat add a quote by Teju Cole]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152730-i-became-aware-of-just-how-fleeting-the-sense-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I became aware of just how fleeting the sense of happiness was, and how flimsy its basis: a warm restaurant after having come in from the rain, the smell of food and wine, interesting conversation, daylight falling weakly on the polished cherrywood of the tables. It took so little to move the mood from one level to another, as one might push pieces on a chessboard. Even to be aware of this, in the midst of a happy moment, was to push one of those pieces, and to become slightly less happy." -- Teju Cole]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
