<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/788671-hbs]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/788671-hbs" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:58:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141087-there-was-once-a-lady-who-was-arrogant-and-proud</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 10:58:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hbs add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141087-there-was-once-a-lady-who-was-arrogant-and-proud]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was once a lady who was arrogant and proud. Determined to attain enlightenment, she asked all the authorities how to go about it. She was told, &quot;Well, if you climb to the top of this very high mountain, you'll find a cave there. Sitting inside that cave is a wise old woman. She will tell you.&quot; Having endured great hardships, the lady finally found this cave. Sure enough, sitting there was a gentle spiritual-looking old woman in white clothing, who smiled beatifically. Overcome with awe and respect, the lady prostrated at the feet of this woman and said, &quot;I want to attain enlightenment. Show me how.&quot; This wise woman looked at her and asked sweetly, &quot;Are you sure you want to attain enlightenment?&quot; And the woman said, &quot;Of course I'm sure.&quot; Whereupon the smiling woman turned into a demon, stood up brandishing a great big stick, and started chasing her, saying, &quot;Now! Now! Now!&quot; For the rest of her life, that lady could never get away from the demon who was always saying, Now! Now--that's the key. Mindfulness trains us to be awake and alive, fully curious, about now." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
