<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/789575-tee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/789575-tee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:01:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13829-you-were-in-my-arms-for-the-first-time-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13829-you-were-in-my-arms-for-the-first-time-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were in my arms for the first time, and you said my name, 'Tristan.'
I answered you: 'Isolde.'
Isolde. The world became a word." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13830-when-my-friend-melot-set-the-trap-i-think-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:01:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13830-when-my-friend-melot-set-the-trap-i-think-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When my friend Melot set the trap, I think I knew it. I turned to death full face, as I had turned to love with my whole body. I would let death enter me as you had entered me. You had crept along my blood vessels through the wound, and the blood that circulates returns to the heart. You circulated me, you made me blush like a girl in the hoop of your hands. You were in my arteries and my lymph, you were the colour just under my skin, and if I cut myself, it was you I bled. Red Isolde, alive on my fingers, and always the force of blood pushing you back to my heart." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13831-the-boat-was-vacuum-packed-with-albanians-four-generations-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:02:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13831-the-boat-was-vacuum-packed-with-albanians-four-generations-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The boat was vacuum-packed with Albanians, four generations to a family: great-grandmother, air-dried like a chilli pepper, deep red skin and a hot temper; grandmother, all sun-dried tomato, tough, chewy, skin split with the heat; getting the kids to rub olive oil into her arms; mother, moist as a purple fig, open everywhere - blouse, skirt, mouth, eyes, a wide-open woman, lips licking the salt spray flying from the open boat. Then there were the kids, aged four and six, a couple of squirs, zesty as lemons." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13832-he-wrote-on-a-piece-of-paper-with-his-pencil</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:02:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13832-he-wrote-on-a-piece-of-paper-with-his-pencil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wrote on a piece of paper with his pencil.
Psychosis: out of touch with reality.
Since then, I have been trying to find out what reality is, so that I can touch it." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13833-though-she-d-try-to-do-otherwise-she-had-never-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:03:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13833-though-she-d-try-to-do-otherwise-she-had-never-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though she'd try to do otherwise, she had never been able to stop cluttering her present with her past. Now somebody she didn't know would pack her treasures into plastic bags and carry them away. A life, at its end, is a pile of cloth and paper, and goods that can be bagged and labelled. None of the best things - the voice and the laugh, the tilt of the head, the things seen and felt and spoken - are allowed to stay behind." -- Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13834-she-had-witnessed-the-world-s-most-beautiful-things-and-allowed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2008 01:03:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13834-she-had-witnessed-the-world-s-most-beautiful-things-and-allowed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had witnessed the world's most beautiful things, and allowed herself to grow old and unlovely. She had felt the heat of a leviathan's roar, and the warmth within a cat's paw. She had conversed with the wind and had wiped soldier's tears. She had made people see, she'd seen herself in the sea. Butterflies had landed on her wrists, she had planted trees. She had loved, and let love go. So she smiled." -- Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10715-i-have-the-choice-of-being-constantly-active-and-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 22:09:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10715-i-have-the-choice-of-being-constantly-active-and-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have the choice of being constantly active and happy or introspectively passive and sad. Or I can go mad by ricocheting in between." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18383-at-the-same-time-you-have-to-find-the-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 22:26:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18383-at-the-same-time-you-have-to-find-the-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the same time, you have to find the right distance between people. Too close, and they overwhelm you, too far and they abandon you. How to hold them in the right relation?" -- Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18384-without-love-most-of-life-remains-concealed-nothing-is-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 22:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18384-without-love-most-of-life-remains-concealed-nothing-is-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without love, most of life remains concealed. Nothing is as fascinating as love, unfortunately." -- Hanif Kureishi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25838-that-s-the-way-it-is-if-you-believe-in-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:58:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Ben Okri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25838-that-s-the-way-it-is-if-you-believe-in-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the way it is. If you believe in something your very belief renders you unqualified to do it. Your earnestness will come across. Your passion will show. Your enthusiasm will make everyone nervous. And your naivety will irritate. Which means that you will become suspect. Which means you will be prone to disillusionment. Which means that you will not be able to sustain your belief in the face of all the piranha fish which nibble away at your idea and your faith, 'till only the skeleton of your dream is left. Which means that you have to become a fanatic, a fool, a joke, an embarrassment. The world - which is to say the powers that be - would listen to your ardent ideas with a stiff smile on its face, then put up impossible obstacles, watch you finally give up your cherished idea, having mangled it beyond recognition, and after you slope away in profound discouragement it will take up your idea, dust it down, give it a new spin, and hand it over to someone who doesn't believe in it at all." -- Ben Okri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:59:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25839-i-discovered-that-my-obsession-for-having-each-thing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I discovered that my obsession for having each thing in the right place, each subject at the right time, each word in the right style, was not the well-deserved reward of an ordered mind but just the opposite: a complete system of pretense invented by me to hide the disorder of my nature. I discovered that I am not disciplined out of virtue but as a reaction to my negligence, that I appear generous in order to conceal my meanness, that I pass myself off as prudent because I am evil-minded, that I am conciliatory in order not to succumb to my repressed rage, that I am punctual only to hide how little I care about other people’s time. I learned, in short, that love is not a condition of the spirit but a sign of the zodiac." -- Gabriel Garcia Marquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25844-my-fear-of-life-is-necessary-to-me-as-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 17:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Edvard Munch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25844-my-fear-of-life-is-necessary-to-me-as-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My fear of life is necessary to me, as is my illness. Without anxiety and illness, I am a ship without a rudder. My art is grounded in reflections over being different from others. My sufferings are part of my self and my art. They are indistinguishable from me, and their destruction would destroy my art. I want to keep those sufferings" -- Edvard Munch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 04:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11171-men-fear-thought-as-they-fear-nothing-else-on-earth</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 22:58:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11171-men-fear-thought-as-they-fear-nothing-else-on-earth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men fear thought as they fear nothing else on earth -- more than ruin, more even than death.  Thought is subversive and revolutionary, destructive and terrible, thought is merciless to privilege, established institutions, and comfortable habits; thought is anarchic and lawless, indifferent to authority, careless of the well-tried wisdom of the ages.  Thought looks into the pit of hell and is not afraid ... Thought is great and swift and free, the light of the world, and the chief glory of man." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117863-i-have-wanted-to-kill-myself-a-hundred-times-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 04:05:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117863-i-have-wanted-to-kill-myself-a-hundred-times-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have wanted to kill myself a hundred times, but somehow I am still in love with life. This ridiculous weakness is perhaps one of our more stupid melancholy propensities, for is there anything more stupid than to be eager to go on carrying a burden which one would gladly throw away, to loathe one’s very being and yet to hold it fast, to fondle the snake that devours us until it has eaten our hearts away?" -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41092-if-we-could-sniff-or-swallow-something-that-would-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 02:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41092-if-we-could-sniff-or-swallow-something-that-would-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we could sniff or swallow something that would, for five or six hours each day, abolish our solitude as individuals, atone us with our fellows in a glowing exaltation of affection and make life in all its aspects seem not only worth living, but divinely beautiful and significant, and if this heavenly, world-transfiguring drug were of such a kind that we could wake up next morning with a clear head and an undamaged constitution - then, it seems to me, all our problems (and not merely the one small problem of discovering a novel pleasure) would be wholly solved and earth would become paradise." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41101-i-write-to-discover-what-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 05:25:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41101-i-write-to-discover-what-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write to discover what I think" -- Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:53:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:53:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:53:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which does not kill us makes us stronger." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:53:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:54:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:55:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365-you-have-to-write-the-book-that-wants-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to write the book that wants to be written. And if the book will be too difficult for grown-ups, then you write it for children." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:56:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 01:57:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:04:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1222-you-cannot-find-peace-by-avoiding-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot find peace by avoiding life." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:05:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:07:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's a book that you want to read, but it hasn't been written yet, then you must write it." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4078-the-saddest-aspect-of-life-right-now-is-that-science]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 02:13:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[tee add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/652-i-became-insane-with-long-intervals-of-horrible-sanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I became insane, with long intervals of horrible sanity." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
