<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79031-elaine-atkins]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79031-elaine-atkins" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:28:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7989-of-course-it-is-happening-inside-your-head-harry-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:28:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7989-of-course-it-is-happening-inside-your-head-harry-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course it is happening inside your head, Harry, but why on earth should that mean that it is not real?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3487-we-are-only-as-strong-as-we-are-united-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:29:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3487-we-are-only-as-strong-as-we-are-united-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are only as strong as we are united, as weak as we are divided." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48126-experience-is-what-you-get-when-you-didn-t-get-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:34:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Randy Pausch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48126-experience-is-what-you-get-when-you-didn-t-get-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Experience is what you get when you didn't get what you wanted. And experience is often the most valuable thing you have to offer." -- Randy Pausch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33234-you-are-not-stuck-where-you-are-unless-you-decide</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Wayne W. Dyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33234-you-are-not-stuck-where-you-are-unless-you-decide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not stuck where you are unless you decide to be." -- Wayne W. Dyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29104-someone-who-thinks-death-is-the-scariest-thing-doesn-t-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:39:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29104-someone-who-thinks-death-is-the-scariest-thing-doesn-t-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone who thinks death is the scariest thing doesn't know a thing about life." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:39:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["some things don't matter much. Like the color of a house. How big is that in the overall scheme of life? But lifting a person's heart--now, that matters. The whole problem with people is...they know what matters, but they don't choose it...The hardest thing on earth is choosing what matters." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32224-the-truth-is-once-you-learn-how-to-die-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2010 10:40:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32224-the-truth-is-once-you-learn-how-to-die-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, once you learn how to die, you learn how to live." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73122-the-word-says-god-don-t-give-us-credit-for-lovin</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 07:16:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Denver Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73122-the-word-says-god-don-t-give-us-credit-for-lovin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Word says God don't give us credit for lovin the folks we want to love anyway.  No, He gives us credit for loving the unlovable." -- Denver Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146054-our-limitation-is-god-s-opportunity-when-you-get-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 07:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Denver Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146054-our-limitation-is-god-s-opportunity-when-you-get-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our limitation is God's opportunity.  When you get all the way to the end of your rope and there ain't nothin you can do, that's when God takes over." -- Denver Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100624-the-truth-about-it-is-whether-we-is-rich-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 07:17:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Denver Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100624-the-truth-about-it-is-whether-we-is-rich-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about it is, whether we is rich or poor or somethin in between, this earth ain't no final restin place. So in a way, we is all homeless--just workin our way toward home." -- Denver Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:40:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2381-when-the-power-of-love-overcomes-the-love-of-power</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Jimi Hendrix ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2381-when-the-power-of-love-overcomes-the-love-of-power]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the power of love overcomes the love of power, the world will know peace." -- Jimi Hendrix ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:43:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:44:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:45:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:47:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36317-why-did-you-do-all-this-for-me-he-asked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did you do all this for me?' he asked. 'I don't deserve it. I've never done anything for you.' 'You have been my friend,' replied Charlotte. 'That in itself is a tremendous thing." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11525-when-i-stand-before-god-at-the-end-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:56:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11525-when-i-stand-before-god-at-the-end-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I stand before God at the end of my life, I would hope that I would not have a single bit of talent left, and could say, 'I used everything you gave me." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68472-a-girl-calls-and-asks-does-it-hurt-very-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:57:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68472-a-girl-calls-and-asks-does-it-hurt-very-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A girl calls and asks, &quot;Does it hurt very much to die?&quot;
&quot;Well, sweetheart,&quot; I tell her, &quot;yes, but it hurts a lot more to keep living." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:57:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we listened to our intellect we'd never have a love affair. We'd never have a friendship. We'd never go in business because we'd be cynical: &quot;It's gonna go wrong.&quot; Or &quot;She's going to hurt me.&quot; Or,&quot;I've had a couple of bad love affairs, so therefore . . .&quot; Well, that's nonsense. You're going to miss life. You've got to jump off the cliff all the time and build your wings on the way down." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16476-yes-we-praise-women-over-40-for-a-multitude-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 12:58:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Frank Kaiser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16476-yes-we-praise-women-over-40-for-a-multitude-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, we praise women over 40 for a multitude of reasons. Unfortunately, it's not reciprocal. For every stunning, smart, well-coiffed, hot woman over 40, there is a bald, paunchy relic in yellow pants making a fool of himself with some 22-year old waitress. Ladies, I apologize. For all those men who say, &quot;Why buy the cow when you can get the milk for free?&quot;, here's an update for you. Nowadays 80% of women are against marriage. Why? Because women realize it's not worth buying an entire pig just to get a little sausage!" -- Frank Kaiser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/759-at-the-end-of-life-we-will-not-be-judged</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:02:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/759-at-the-end-of-life-we-will-not-be-judged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the end of life we will not be judged by how many diplomas we have received, how much money we have made, how many great things we have done.
We will be judged by &quot;I was hungry, and you gave me something to eat, I was naked and you clothed me. I was homeless, and you took me in." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:06:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49262-if-i-had-my-life-to-live-over-i-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IF I HAD MY LIFE TO LIVE OVER

I would have talked less and listened more.

I would have invited friends over to dinner even if the carpet was stained and the sofa faded.

I would have eaten the popcorn in the &quot;good&quot; living room and worried much less about the dirt when someone wanted to light a fire in the fireplace.

I would have taken the time to listen to my grandfather rambling about his youth.

I would never have insisted the car windows be rolled up on a summer day because my hair had just been teased and sprayed.

I would have burned the pink candle sculped like a rose before it melted 
in storage.

I would have sat on the lawn with my children and not worried about grass stains.

I would have cried and laughed less while watching television, and more 
while watching life.

I would have gone to bed when I was sick, instead of pretending the earth would go into a holding pattern if I weren't there for the day.

I would never have bought anything just because it was practical, wouldn't show soil or was guaranteed to last a lifetime.

Instead of wishing away nine months of pregnancy, I'd have cherished every moment, realising that the wonderment growing inside me was the only chance in life to assist God in a miracle.

When my kids kissed me impetuously, I would never have said, &quot;Later. Now go get washed up for dinner.&quot;

There would have been more &quot;I love you's&quot; and more &quot;I'm sorry's&quot;

. . . but mostly, given another shot at life, I would seize every minute . . . 
look at it and really see it . . . and never give it back." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16451-on-some-positions-cowardice-asks-the-question-is-it-expedient</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:13:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16451-on-some-positions-cowardice-asks-the-question-is-it-expedient]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On some positions, cowardice asks the question, is it expedient? And then expedience comes along and asks the question, is it politic? Vanity asks the question, is it popular? Conscience asks the question, is it right?

There comes a time when one must take the position that is neither safe nor politic nor popular, but he must do it because conscience tells him it is right." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70944-may-i-share-with-you-a-formula-that-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:17:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70944-may-i-share-with-you-a-formula-that-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May I share with you a formula that in my judgment will help you and help me to journey well through mortality... First, fill your mind with truth; second, fill your life with service; and third, fill your heart with love." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5721-you-have-peace-the-old-woman-said-when-you-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:18:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5721-you-have-peace-the-old-woman-said-when-you-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have peace,&quot; the old woman said, &quot;when you make it with yourself." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:25:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:26:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:26:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 13:26:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elaine add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
