<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79063-maren]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79063-maren" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 15:06:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205628-what-was-happening-to-them-was-that-every-bad-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2009 15:06:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205628-what-was-happening-to-them-was-that-every-bad-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What was happening to them was that every bad time produced a bad feeling that in turn produced several more bad times and several more bad feelings, so that their life together became crowded with bad times and bad feelings, so crowded that almost nothing else could grow in that dark field. But then she had a feeling of peace one morning that lingered from the evening before spent sewing while he sat reading in the next room. And a day or two later, she had a feeling of contentment that lingered in the morning from the evening before when he kept her company in the kitchen while she washed the dinner dishes. If the good times increased, she thought, each good time might produce a good feeling that would in turn produce several more good times that would produce several more good feelings. What she meant was that the good times might multiply perhaps as rapidly as the square of the square, or perhaps more rapidly, like mice, or like mushrooms springing up overnight from the scattered spore of a parent mushroom which in turn had sprung up overnight with a crowd of others from the scattered spore of a parent, until her life with him with be so crowded with good times that the good times might crowd out the bad as the bad times had by now almost crowded out the good. " -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230921-the-cradle-rocks-above-an-abyss-and-common-sense-tells</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 15:09:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230921-the-cradle-rocks-above-an-abyss-and-common-sense-tells]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cradle rocks above an abyss, and common sense tells us that our existence is but a brief crack of light between two eternities of darkness." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195137-genius-is-an-african-who-dreams-up-snow</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 15:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195137-genius-is-an-african-who-dreams-up-snow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genius is an African who dreams up snow." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2009 16:37:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will lose someone you can’t live without,and your heart will be badly broken, and the bad news is that you never completely get over the loss of your beloved. But this is also the good news. They live forever in your broken heart that doesn’t seal back up. And you come through. It’s like having a broken leg that never heals perfectly—that still hurts when the weather gets cold, but you learn to dance with the limp." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201755-one-cannot-make-bargains-for-blisses-or-catch-them-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 11:24:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Alice Carey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201755-one-cannot-make-bargains-for-blisses-or-catch-them-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One cannot make bargains for blisses
Or catch them like fishes in nets
And sometimes the things that life misses 
Help more than the things that it gets. " -- Alice Carey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201756-if-you-were-queen-of-pleasure-and-i-were-king</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 11:25:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Algernon Charles Swinburne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201756-if-you-were-queen-of-pleasure-and-i-were-king]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you were queen of pleasure
And I were king of pain
We'd hunt down love together
Pluck out his flying-feather,
And teach his feet a measure,
And find his mouth a rein;
If you were queen of pleasure
And I were king of pain." -- Algernon Charles Swinburne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11893-i-m-living-so-far-beyond-my-income-that-we-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2009 11:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by E. E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11893-i-m-living-so-far-beyond-my-income-that-we-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm living so far beyond my income that we  may almost be said to be living apart." -- E. E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204168-you-can-call-your-turkey-organic-and-torture-it-daily</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 12:41:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204168-you-can-call-your-turkey-organic-and-torture-it-daily]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can call your turkey organic and torture it daily. " -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57688-i-hate-writing-i-love-having-written</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 14:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57688-i-hate-writing-i-love-having-written]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate writing, I love having written." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 15:13:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67118-a-non-writing-writer-is-a-monster-courting-insanity-letter-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A non-writing writer is a monster courting insanity.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Max Brod&lt;/i&gt;, July 5, 1922]" -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41701-listen-there-s-a-hell-of-a-good-universe-next-door</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 15:39:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41701-listen-there-s-a-hell-of-a-good-universe-next-door]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["listen: there’s a hell
of a good universe next door; let’s go" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219618-it-is-often-falsely-assumed-even-by-feminists-that-sexuality</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2010 13:13:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Germaine Greer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219618-it-is-often-falsely-assumed-even-by-feminists-that-sexuality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is often falsely assumed, even by feminists, that sexuality is the enemy of the female who really wants to develop these aspects of her personality, and this is perhaps the most misleading aspect of movements like the National Organization of Women. It was not the insistence upon her sex that weakened the American woman student's desire to make something of her education, but the insistence upon a &lt;i&gt;passive&lt;/i&gt; sexual &lt;i&gt;role&lt;/i&gt;" -- Germaine Greer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 13:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 13:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Pat Conroy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11540-you-get-a-little-moody-sometimes-but-i-think-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a little moody sometimes but I think that's because you like to read. People that like to read are always a little fucked up." -- Pat Conroy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 13:41:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that almost all our sadnesses are moments of tension, which we feel as paralysis because we no longer hear our astonished emotions living. Because we are alone with the unfamiliar presence that has entered us; because everything we trust and are used to is for a moment taken away from us; because we stand in the midst of a transition where we cannot remain standing. That is why the sadness passes: the new presence inside us, the presence that has been added, has entered our heart, has gone into its innermost chamber and is no longer even there, - is already in our bloodstream. And we don't know what it was. We could easily be made to believe that nothing happened, and yet we have changed, as a house that a guest has entered changes. We can't say who has come, perhaps we will never know, but many signs indicate that the future enters us in this way in order to be transformed in us, long before it happens. And that is why it is so important to be solitary and attentive when one is sad: because the seemingly uneventful and motionless moment when our future steps into us is so much closer to life than that other loud and accidental point of time when it happens to us as if from outside. The quieter we are, the more patient and open we are in our sadnesses, the more deeply and serenely the new presence can enter us, and the more we can make it our own, the more it becomes our fate." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20650-she-was-wearing-a-pair-of-my-pajamas-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 13:42:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20650-she-was-wearing-a-pair-of-my-pajamas-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was wearing a pair of my pajamas with the sleeves rolled up. When she laughed I wanted her again. A minute later she asked me if I loved her. I told her it didn't mean anything but that I didn't think so. She looked sad. But as we were fixing lunch, and for no apparent reason, she laughed in such a way that I kissed her." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78762-when-that-slow-motion-silent-explosion-of-love-takes-place-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 13:43:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by vladimir nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78762-when-that-slow-motion-silent-explosion-of-love-takes-place-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When that slow-motion, silent explosion of love takes place in me, unfolding its melting fringes and overwhelming me with the sense of something much vaster, much more enduring and powerful than the accumulation of matter or energy in any imaginable cosmos, then my mind cannot but pinch itself to see if it is really awake.  I have to make a rapid inventory of the universe, just as a man in a dream tries to condone the absurdity of his position by making sure he is dreaming.  I have to have all space and all time participate in my emotion, in my mortal love, so that the edge of its mortality is taken off, thus helping me to fight the utter degradation, ridicule, and horror of having developed an infinity of sensation and thought within a finite existence." -- vladimir nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
