<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792547-jons]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792547-jons" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 11:18:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/814-the-leaves-streamed-down-trembling-in-the-sun-they-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 11:18:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jons add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/814-the-leaves-streamed-down-trembling-in-the-sun-they-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The leaves streamed down, trembling in the sun. They were not green, only a few, scattered through the torrent, stood out in single drops of green so bright and pure that it hurt the eyes; the rest were not a color, but a light, the substance of fire on metal, living sparks without edges. And it looked as if the forest were a spread of light boiling slowly to produce this color, the green rising in small bubbles, the condensed essence of spring. The trees met, blending over the road and the spots of sun on the ground moved with the shifting of the branches, like a conscious caress." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19856-but-ransom-as-time-wore-on-became-aware-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jons add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19856-but-ransom-as-time-wore-on-became-aware-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But Ransom, as time wore on, became aware of another and more spiritual cause for his progressive lightening and exultation of heart. A nightmare, long engendered in the modern mind by the mythology that follows in the wake of science, was falling off him. He had read of 'Space': at the back of his thinking for years had lurked the dismal fancy of the black, cold vacuity, the utter deadness, which was supposed to separate the worlds. He had not known how much it affected him till now-now that the very name 'Space' seemed a blasphemous libel for this empyrean ocean of radiance in which they swam. He could not call it 'dead'; he felt life pouring into him from it every moment. How indeed should it be otherwise, since out of this ocean all the worlds and all their life had come? He had thought it barren: he now saw that it was the womb of worlds, whose blazing and innumerable offspring looked down nightly even upon the earth with so many eyes-and here, with how many more! No: Space was the wrong name." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14638-cyberspace-a-consensual-hallucination-experienced-daily-by-billions-of-legitimate</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jons add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14638-cyberspace-a-consensual-hallucination-experienced-daily-by-billions-of-legitimate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cyberspace. A consensual hallucination experienced daily by billions of legitimate operators, in every nation, by children being taught mathematical concepts... A graphic representation of data abstracted from banks of every computer in the human system. Unthinkable complexity. Lines of light ranged in the nonspace of the mind, clusters and constellations of data. Like city lights, receding..." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146781-she-was-made-after-the-time-of-ribs-and-mud</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 00:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jons add a quote by Salvador Plascencia]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146781-she-was-made-after-the-time-of-ribs-and-mud]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was made after the time of ribs and mud.  By papal decree there were to be no more people born of the ground or from the marrow of bones.  All would be created from the propulsions and mounts performed underneath bedsheets- rare exception granted for immaculate conceptions.  The mixing pits were sledged and the cutting tables, where ribs were extracted from pigs and goats, were sawed in half.  Although the monks were devout and obedient to the thunder of Rome, the wool of their robes was soaked not only by the salt of sweat but also by that of tears.  The monks rolled down their heavy sleeves, hid their slaughter knives in the burlap of their scrips, and wiped the hoes clean.  They closed the factory down, chained the doors with Vatican-crested locks, and marched off in holy formation.  Three lines, their faces staring down in humility, closing their eyes when walking over puddles, avoiding their unshaven reflections.  " -- Salvador Plascencia]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78946-over-the-millennia-the-seed-of-stories-planted-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 11:18:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[jons add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78946-over-the-millennia-the-seed-of-stories-planted-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Over the millennia the seed of stories planted in the fertile soil of bits and scraps of facts was watered by wishes and began to take root and grow.  Eventually, a bountiful fruit of rumors burst forth, to be spread on the wind of whispers that said we hid a fabled hoard of gold.  Nothing could convince the believers that it was not true.  The truth does not glitter for these people like gold does." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
