<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792512-tamtam]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792512-tamtam" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:10:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:10:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Groucho Marx ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3730-i-find-television-very-educating-every-time-somebody-turns-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I find television very educating. Every time somebody turns on the set, I go into the other room and read a book." -- Groucho Marx ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14912-if-you-want-your-children-to-be-intelligent-read-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14912-if-you-want-your-children-to-be-intelligent-read-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want your children to be intelligent, read them fairy tales. If you want them to be more intelligent, read them more fairy tales." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 08:59:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38221-stories-of-imagination-tend-to-upset-those-without-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38221-stories-of-imagination-tend-to-upset-those-without-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories of imagination tend to upset those without one." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39434-confidence-is-ignorance-if-you-re-feeling-cocky-it-s-because-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Eoin Colfer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39434-confidence-is-ignorance-if-you-re-feeling-cocky-it-s-because-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Confidence is ignorance. If you're feeling cocky, it's because there's something you don't know." -- Eoin Colfer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2567-the-queen-s-pride-was-his-ship-and-he-loved-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 11:09:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2567-the-queen-s-pride-was-his-ship-and-he-loved-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Queen's Pride was his ship, and he loved her. (That was the way his sentences always went: It is raining today and I love you. My cold is better and I love you. Say hello to Horse and I love you. Like that.)" -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80172-charlotte-it-s-too-bad-they-don-t-give-out-diplomas-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2008 14:45:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Janette Rallison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80172-charlotte-it-s-too-bad-they-don-t-give-out-diplomas-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Charlotte: &quot;It’s too bad they don’t give out diplomas for what you learn at the mall, because I could graduate with honors in that subject. No really. Since I’ve worked there, I’ve become an expert on all things shopping-related. For example, I can tell you right off who to distrust at the mall:

1) Skinny people who work at Cinnabon. I mean, if they’re not eating the stuff they sell, how good can it be?

2) The salesladies at department store makeup counters. No matter what they tell you, buying all that lip gloss will not make you look like the pouty models in the store posters.

3) And most importantly—my best friend’s boyfriend, Bryant, who showed up at the food court with a mysterious blonde draped on his arm." -- Janette Rallison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55592-get-on-your-knees-and-pray-then-get-on-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 19:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55592-get-on-your-knees-and-pray-then-get-on-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get on your knees and pray, then get on your feet and work." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227509-the-book-of-mormon-is-the-most-correct-of-any</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2011 21:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[TamTam add a quote by Joseph Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227509-the-book-of-mormon-is-the-most-correct-of-any]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Book of Mormon is the most correct of any book on this Earth, and the keystone of our religion, and a man would get nearer to God by abiding by its precepts, than any other book." -- Joseph Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
