<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792881-sylvia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/792881-sylvia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 19:40:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 19:40:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sylvia add a quote by Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37445-every-room-i-ve-lived-in-since-i-was-given-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every room I've lived in since I was given my own room at eleven was lined with, and usually overfull of, books. My employment in bookstores was always continuous with my private hours: shelving and alphabetizing, building shelves, and browsing-- in my collection and others-- in order to understand a small amount about the widest possible number of books. Such numbers of books are constantly acquired that constant culling is necessary; if I slouch in this discipline, the books erupt. I've also bricked myself in with music--vinyl records, then compact discs. My homes have been improbably information-dense, like capsules for survival of a nuclear war, or models of the interior of my own skull. That comparison--room as brain-- is one I've often reached for in describing the rooms of others, but it began with the suspicion that I'd externalized my own brain, for anyone who cared to look." -- Jonathan Lethem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2830-everything-was-beautiful-and-nothing-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 20:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sylvia add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2830-everything-was-beautiful-and-nothing-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything was beautiful and nothing hurt." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 21:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sylvia add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
