<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/793231-carol-rodi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/793231-carol-rodi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 19:22:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243053-you-do-not-need-to-know-precisely-what-is-happening</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2013 19:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Thomas Merton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243053-you-do-not-need-to-know-precisely-what-is-happening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not need to know precisely what is happening, or exactly where it is all going. What you need is to recognize the possibilities and challenges offered by the present moment, and to embrace them with courage, faith and hope." -- Thomas Merton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135122-the-attitude-that-nature-is-chaotic-and-that-the-artist</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 23:03:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Willem De Kooning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135122-the-attitude-that-nature-is-chaotic-and-that-the-artist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The attitude that nature is chaotic and that the artist puts order into it is a very absurd point of view, I think. All that we can hope for is to put some order into ourselves" -- Willem De Kooning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2013 21:19:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Martha Graham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47070-there-is-a-vitality-a-life-force-an-energy-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a vitality, a life force, an energy, a quickening that is translated through you into action, and because there is only one of you in all of time, this expression is unique. And if you block it, it will never exist through any other medium and it will be lost. The world will not have it. It is not your business to determine how good it is nor how valuable nor how it compares with other expressions. It is your business to keep it yours clearly and directly, to keep the channel open. You do not even have to believe in yourself or your work. You have to keep yourself open and aware to the urges that motivate you. Keep the channel open. ... No artist is pleased. [There is] no satisfaction whatever at any time. There is only a queer divine dissatisfaction, a blessed unrest that keeps us marching and makes us more alive than the others" -- Martha Graham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165429-life-is-glorious-but-life-is-also-wretched-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 17:22:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165429-life-is-glorious-but-life-is-also-wretched-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is glorious, but life is also wretched. It is both. Appreciating the gloriousness inspires us, encourages us, cheers us up, gives us a bigger perspective, energizes us. We feel connected. But if that's all that's happening, we get arrogant and start to look down on others, and there is a sense of making ourselves a big deal and being really serious about it, wanting it to be like that forever. The gloriousness becomes tinged by craving and addiction. On the other hand, wretchedness--life's painful aspect--softens us up considerably. Knowing pain is a very important ingredient of being there for another person. When you are feeling a lot of grief, you can look right into somebody's eyes because you feel you haven't got anything to lose--you're just there. The wretchedness humbles us and softens us, but if we were only wretched, we would all just go down the tubes. We'd be so depressed, discouraged, and hopeless that we wouldn't have enough energy to eat an apple. Gloriousness and wretchedness need each other. One inspires us, the other softens us. They go together." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 18:05:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95915-let-everything-happen-to-you-beauty-and-terror-just-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 19:57:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95915-let-everything-happen-to-you-beauty-and-terror-just-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let everything happen to you
Beauty and terror
Just keep going
No feeling is final" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 09:28:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point of marriage is not to create a quick commonality by tearing down all boundaries; on the contrary, a good marriage is one in which each partner appoints the other to be the guardian of his solitude, and thus they show each other the greatest possible trust. A merging of two people is an impossibility, and where it seems to exist, it is a hemming-in, a mutual consent that robs one party or both parties of their fullest freedom and development. But once the realization is accepted that even between the closest people infinite distances exist, a marvelous living side-by-side can grow up for them, if they succeed in loving the expanse between them, which gives them the possibility of always seeing each other as a whole and before an immense sky." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 12:08:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will lose someone you can’t live without,and your heart will be badly broken, and the bad news is that you never completely get over the loss of your beloved. But this is also the good news. They live forever in your broken heart that doesn’t seal back up. And you come through. It’s like having a broken leg that never heals perfectly—that still hurts when the weather gets cold, but you learn to dance with the limp." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235610-i-ve-never-forgotten-him-dare-i-say-i-miss-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 14:55:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235610-i-ve-never-forgotten-him-dare-i-say-i-miss-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never forgotten him. Dare I say I miss him? I do. I miss him. I still see him in my dreams. They are nightmares mostly, but nightmares tinged with love. Such is the strangeness of the human heart. I still cannot understand how he could abandon me so unceremoniously, without any sort of goodbye, without looking back even once. The pain is like an axe that chops my heart.  " -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396940-no-one-can-tell-what-goes-on-in-between-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 13:33:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396940-no-one-can-tell-what-goes-on-in-between-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can tell what goes on in between the person you were and the person you become.  No one can chart that blue and lonely section of hell.  There are no maps of the change.  You just come out the other side.

Or you don't." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154010-in-my-childhood-diary-i-wrote-i-have-decided-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 07:40:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154010-in-my-childhood-diary-i-wrote-i-have-decided-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my childhood diary I wrote: “I have decided that it is better not to love anyone, because when you love people, then you have to be separated from them, and that hurts too much." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407290-she-couldn-t-remember-the-last-time-she-hugged-someone-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 20:29:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/407290-she-couldn-t-remember-the-last-time-she-hugged-someone-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She couldn't remember the last time she hugged someone, really hugged someone." -- Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731204-holly-smiled-weakly-gerry-would-know-exactly-how-she-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 20:31:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/731204-holly-smiled-weakly-gerry-would-know-exactly-how-she-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holly smiled weakly. Gerry would know exactly how she was feeling, he would know exactly
what to say and he would know exactly what to do. He would give her one of his famous hugs
and all her problems would melt away. She grabbed a pillow from her bed and hugged it tight.
She couldn't remember the last time she hugged someone, really hugged someone. And the
depressing thing was that she couldn't imagine ever embracing anyone the same way again." -- Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163328-we-often-think-of-peace-as-the-absence-of-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 07:53:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163328-we-often-think-of-peace-as-the-absence-of-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We often think of peace as the absence of war, that if powerful countries would reduce their weapon arsenals, we could have peace. But if we look deeply into the weapons, we see our own minds- our own prejudices, fears and ignorance. Even if we transport all the bombs to the moon, the roots of war and the roots of bombs are still there, in our hearts and minds, and sooner or later we will make new bombs. To work for peace is to uproot war from ourselves and from the hearts of men and women. To prepare for war, to give millions of men and women the opportunity to practice killing day and night in their hearts, is to plant millions of seeds of violence, anger, frustration, and fear that will be passed on for generations to come. " -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
