<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/793269-maren]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/793269-maren" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 09:30:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58395-if-i-were-satan-and-wanted-to-destroy-a-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 09:30:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Patricia Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58395-if-i-were-satan-and-wanted-to-destroy-a-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I were Satan and wanted to destroy a society, I think I would stage a full blown blitz on women. I would keep them so distraught and distracted that they would never find the calming strength and serenity for which their gender has always been known." -- Patricia Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 16:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149344-could-we-wear-spandex-and-blow-things-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2011 18:17:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Lisa Mantchev]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149344-could-we-wear-spandex-and-blow-things-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Could we wear spandex and blow things up?" -- Lisa Mantchev]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988403-you-deserve-all-that-and-more-it-made-me-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:42:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988403-you-deserve-all-that-and-more-it-made-me-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You deserve all that and more. It made me happy to see you suffer. I would do it all over again if I could.&quot; I realized I was shaking as the words tumbled out of me. &quot;I would do it again and again. Every night I would torment you and laugh. Do you understand? You are never safe with me.&quot; I drew a shuddering breath, trying to will away the sting of tears.

He opened his eyes and stared up at me as if I were the door out of Arcadia and back to the true sky. &quot;That's what makes you my favorite.&quot; He reached up and wiped a tear off my cheek with his thumb. &quot;Every wicked bit of you." -- Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1018766-i-coudn-t-be-kind-to-him-after-what-he-d-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:42:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1018766-i-coudn-t-be-kind-to-him-after-what-he-d-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I coudn't be kind to him after what he'd done, couldn't be cruel after what  I had done" -- Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023092-we-ll-both-be-foolish-i-said-and-vicious-and-cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:43:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1023092-we-ll-both-be-foolish-i-said-and-vicious-and-cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We'll both be foolish,&quot; I said, &quot;and vicious and cruel. We will never be safe with each other.&quot;

&quot;Don't try too hard to be cheerful.&quot; His fingers threaded through mine.

&quot;But we'll pretend we know how to love.&quot; I smiled at him. &quot;And someday we'll learn.&quot;

And we walked through the gateway together." -- Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025020-the-fire-roared-down-upon-us-it-curled-through-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:43:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1025020-the-fire-roared-down-upon-us-it-curled-through-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fire roared down upon us. It curled through our hair, then wrapped around our wrists and faces, trying to drag us apart. It seared across my skin, hotter than the Heart of Fire, and yet more painful was how it seared through my mind. The fire burned away my memories, taking back his name and mine, both of my pasts and all of my hopes, the sky and the sparrow and the world itself. I clung to somebody I did not know, could not imagine knowing, but I still knew beyond all doubt that he was mine.

We fell until we had been falling forever and always, and always would continue falling, because nothing existed outside this chaos of fire and shadow.

But I held on to him.

And he held on to me." -- Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033531-his-hands-tightened-around-mine-i-love-you-he-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 22:44:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033531-his-hands-tightened-around-mine-i-love-you-he-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His hands tightened around mine. “I love you,” he said. “I love you more than any other creature, because you are cruel, and kind, and alive. Nyx Triskelion, will you be my wife?”
I knew it was insane to be happy, to feel this desperate exultation at his words. But I felt like I had been waiting all my life to hear them. I had been waiting, all my life, for someone undeceived to love me. And now he did, and it felt like walking into the dazzling sunlight of the Heart of Earth.
Except that the sunlight was false, and his love was real.
It was real.
Very deliberately, I pulled my hands out of his. “You’re a demon,” I said, staring at the ground.
“Most likely.”
“I know what you’ve done.”
“The exciting parts, anyway.”
“And I still don’t know your name.” My hands trembled as I undid my belt, then started to unclasp the brooches. It seemed forever since that first day when I had ripped my bodice open so
easily. “But I know you’re my husband.”
The dress slid down to land on the ground about my feet. Ignifex touched my cheek very gently, as if I was a bird that might be startled into flight. Finally I met his eyes.
“And,” I said. “I suppose I do love you.”
Then he pulled me into his arms." -- Rosamund Hodge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22283-if-a-child-is-to-keep-alive-his-inborn-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 10:19:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maren add a quote by Rachel Carson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22283-if-a-child-is-to-keep-alive-his-inborn-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a child is to keep alive his inborn sense of wonder, he needs the companionship of at least one adult who can share it, rediscovering with him the joy, excitement, and mystery of the world we live in." -- Rachel Carson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
