<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/794273-margot]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/794273-margot" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 06:19:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772698-the-worm-drives-helically-through-the-wood-and-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 06:19:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by John M. Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772698-the-worm-drives-helically-through-the-wood-and-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worm drives helically through the wood
And does not know the dust left in the bore
Once made the table integral and good;
And suddenly the crystal hits the floor.
Electrons find their paths in subtle ways,
A massless eddy in a trail of smoke;
The names of lovers, light of other days
Perhaps you will not miss them. That's the joke.
The universe winds down. That's how it's made.
But memory is everything to lose;
Although some of the colors have to fade,
Do not believe you'll get the chance to choose.
Regret, by definition, comes too late;
Say what you mean. Bear witness. Iterate." -- John M. Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357705-impossible-i-realize-to-enter-another-s-solitude-if-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357705-impossible-i-realize-to-enter-another-s-solitude-if-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Impossible, I realize, to enter another’s solitude. If it is true that we can ever come to know another human being, even to a small degree, it is only to the extent that he is willing to make himself known. A man will say: I am cold. Or else he will say nothing, and we will see him shivering. Either way, we will know that he is cold. But what of the man who says nothing and does not shiver? Where all is intractable, here all is hermetic and evasive, one can do no more than observe. But whether one can make sense of what he observes is another matter entirely" -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 09:50:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239991-melt-all-the-guns-i-thought-break-the-knives-burn</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 04:29:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239991-melt-all-the-guns-i-thought-break-the-knives-burn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Melt all the guns, I thought, break the knives, burn the guillotines-and the malicious will still write letters that kill." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41926-every-life-is-inexplicable-i-kept-telling-myself-no-matter</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41926-every-life-is-inexplicable-i-kept-telling-myself-no-matter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every life is inexplicable, I kept telling myself. No matter how many facts are told, no matter how many details are given, the essential thing resists telling. To say that so and so was born here and went there, that he did this and did that, that he married this woman and had these children, that he lived, that he died, that he left behind these books or this battle or that bridge – none of that tells us very much." -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32379-a-stranger-is-shot-in-the-street-you-hardly-move</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 04:29:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32379-a-stranger-is-shot-in-the-street-you-hardly-move]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A stranger is shot in the street, you hardly move to help. But if, half an hour before, you spent just ten minutes with the fellow and knew a little about him and his family, you might just jump in front of his killer and try to stop it. Really knowing is good. Not knowing, or refusing to know is bad, or amoral, at least. You can’t act if you don’t know." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385538-my-music-teacher-offered-twittering-madrigals-and-something-about-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385538-my-music-teacher-offered-twittering-madrigals-and-something-about-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My music teacher offered twittering madrigals and something about how, in Italy, in Italy, the oranges hang on the tree. He treated me - the humiliation of it - as a soprano.

These, by contrast, are the six elements of a Sacred Harp alto: rage, darkness, motherhood, earth, malice, and sex. Once you feel it, you can always do it. You know where to go for it, though it will cost you." -- Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179925-sometimes-the-man-who-looks-happiest-in-town-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 04:31:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179925-sometimes-the-man-who-looks-happiest-in-town-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the man who looks happiest in town, with the biggest smile, is the one carrying the biggest load of sin.  There are smiles &amp; smiles; learn to tell the dark variety from the light.  The seal-barker, the laugh-shouter, half the time he's covering up.  He's had his fun &amp; he's guilty.  And all men do love sin, Will, oh how they love it, never doubt, in all shapes, sizes, colors &amp; smells.  Times come when troughs, not tables, suit appetites.  Hear a man too loudly praising others &amp; look to wonder if he didn't just get up from the sty.  On the other hand, that unhappy, pale, put-upon man walking by, who looks all guilt &amp; sin, why, often that's your good man with a capital G, Will.  For being good is a fearful occupation; men strain at it &amp; sometimes break in two.  I've known a few.  You work twice as hard to be a farmer as to be his hog.  I suppose it's thinking about trying to be good makes the crack run up the wall one night.  A man with high standards, too, the least hair falls on him sometimes wilts his spine.  He can't let himself alone, won't let himself off the hook if he falls just a breath from grace." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382649-i-would-not-say-i-am-looking-for-god-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382649-i-would-not-say-i-am-looking-for-god-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not say I am looking for God. Or, I am not looking for God precisely. I am not seeking the God I learned about as a Catholic child, as an 18-year-old novice in a religious community, as an agnostic graduate student, as - but who cares about my disguises? Or God's." -- Mary Rose O'Reilley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192242-he-read-it-for-the-same-reason-an-animal-tears</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 04:32:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Nathanael West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192242-he-read-it-for-the-same-reason-an-animal-tears]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He read it for the same reason an animal tears at a wounded foot: to hurt the pain." -- Nathanael West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236085-if-you-reveal-everything-bare-every-feeling-ask-for-understanding</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236085-if-you-reveal-everything-bare-every-feeling-ask-for-understanding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you reveal everything, bare every feeling, ask for understanding, you lose something crucial to your sense of yourself. You need to know things that others don't know. It's what no one knows about you that allows you to know yourself." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135948-years-after-i-d-seen-him-for-the-last-time-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135948-years-after-i-d-seen-him-for-the-last-time-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Years after I'd seen him for the last time I found myself thinking of him unexpectedly and often. You know how certain places grow powerful in the mind with passing time. In those early morning dreams when I come back to bed after a sleepy pee and fall quickly into the narrow end of the night, there is one set of streets I keep returning to, one dim mist of railroad rooms  and certain figures reappear, borderline ghosts." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684702-only-those-who-still-have-hope-can-benefit-from-tears</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 04:33:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Nathanael West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/684702-only-those-who-still-have-hope-can-benefit-from-tears]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only those who still have hope can benefit from tears. When they finish, they feel better. But to those without hope, whose anguish is basic and permanent, no good comes from crying. Nothing changes for them. They usually know this, but still can’t help crying." -- Nathanael West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71279-i-n-the-american-soul-there-is-a-lonely-individual-standing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71279-i-n-the-american-soul-there-is-a-lonely-individual-standing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[I]n the American soul there is a lonely individual standing in a vast landscape.  He is either on a horse or driving a car, depending, and either way he’s carrying a gun.  This is one of the essential images in American mythology." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33647-life-is-in-fact-a-battle-evil-is-insolent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 13:21:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33647-life-is-in-fact-a-battle-evil-is-insolent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is, in fact, a battle. Evil is insolent and strong; beauty enchanting, but rare; goodness very apt to be weak; folly very apt to be defiant; wickedness to carry the day; imbeciles to be in great places, people of sense in small, and mankind generally unhappy. But the world as it stands is no narrow illusion, no phantasm, no evil dream of the night; we wake up to it, forever and ever; and we can neither forget it nor deny it nor dispense with it." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326947-who-invented-the-human-heart-i-wonder-tell-me-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 13:32:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/326947-who-invented-the-human-heart-i-wonder-tell-me-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who invented the human heart, I wonder?  Tell me, and then show me the place where he was hanged." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236625-those-who-have-abandoned-belief-must-still-believe-in-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236625-those-who-have-abandoned-belief-must-still-believe-in-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who have abandoned belief must still believe in us. They are sure that they are right not to believe but they know belief must not fade completely. Hell is when no one believes. There must always be believers. Fools, idiots, those who hear voices, those who speak in tongues. We are your lunatics. We surrender our lives to make your nonbelief possible. You are sure that you are right but you don’t want everyone to think as you do. There is no truth without fools. We are your fools, your madwomen, rising at dawn to pray, lighting candles, asking statues for good health, long life." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460617-cities-were-built-to-measure-time-to-remove-time-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460617-cities-were-built-to-measure-time-to-remove-time-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cities were built to measure time, to remove time from nature. There’s an endless counting down, he said. When you strip away all the surfaces, when you see into it, what’s left is terror. This is the thing that literature was meant to cure." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 17:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The so-called ‘psychotically depressed’ person who tries to kill herself doesn’t do so out of quote ‘hopelessness’ or any abstract conviction that life’s assets and debits do not square. And surely not because death seems suddenly appealing. The person in whom Its invisible agony reaches a certain unendurable level will kill herself the same way a trapped person will eventually jump from the window of a burning high-rise. Make no mistake about people who leap from burning windows. Their terror of falling from a great height is still just as great as it would be for you or me standing speculatively at the same window just checking out the view; i.e. the fear of falling remains a constant. The variable here is the other terror, the fire’s flames: when the flames get close enough, falling to death becomes the slightly less terrible of two terrors. It’s not desiring the fall; it’s terror of the flames. And yet nobody down on the sidewalk, looking up and yelling ‘Don’t!’ and ‘Hang on!’, can understand the jump. Not really. You’d have to have personally been trapped and felt flames to really understand a terror way beyond falling." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431914-heaven-kiwi-thought-would-be-the-reading-room-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Karen Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431914-heaven-kiwi-thought-would-be-the-reading-room-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heaven, Kiwi thought, would be the reading room of a great library. But it would be private. Cozy. You wouldn’t have to worry about some squeaky-shoed librarian turning the lights off on you or gauging your literacy by reading the names on your book spines, and there wouldn’t be a single other patron. The whole place would hum with a library’s peace, filtering softly over you like white bars of light…" -- Karen Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39670-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39670-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No live organism can continue for long to exist sanely under conditions of absolute reality." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714352-toby-had-received-though-not-yet-digested-one-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 09:34:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Iris Murdoch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714352-toby-had-received-though-not-yet-digested-one-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Toby had received, though not yet digested, one of the earliest lessons of adult life: that one is never secure. At any moment one can be removed from a state of guileless serenity and plunged into its opposite, without any intermediate condition, so high about us do the waters rise of our own and other people's imperfection." -- Iris Murdoch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384465-hopes-were-wallflowers-hopes-hugged-the-perimeter-of-a-dance</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Karen Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384465-hopes-were-wallflowers-hopes-hugged-the-perimeter-of-a-dance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hopes were wallflowers.  Hopes hugged the perimeter of a dance floor in your brain, tugging at their party lace, all perfume and hems and doomed expectation. They fanned their dance cards, these guests that pressed against the walls of your heart." -- Karen Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213306-i-never-even-for-a-moment-doubted-what-they-d-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 17:49:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213306-i-never-even-for-a-moment-doubted-what-they-d-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never, even for a moment, doubted what they’d told me. This is why it is that adults and even parents can, unwittingly, be cruel: they cannot imagine doubt’s complete absence. They have forgotten." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401944-that-sometimes-human-beings-have-to-just-sit-in-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 17:49:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401944-that-sometimes-human-beings-have-to-just-sit-in-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That sometimes human beings have to just sit in one place and, like, hurt. That you will become way less concerned with what other people think of you when you realize how seldom they do. That there is such a thing as raw, unalloyed, agendaless kindness. That it is possible to fall asleep during an anxiety attack. That concentrating on anything is very hard work." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374107-people-are-mostly-layers-of-violence-and-tenderness-wrapped-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 17:32:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/374107-people-are-mostly-layers-of-violence-and-tenderness-wrapped-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are mostly layers of violence and tenderness wrapped like bulbs, and it is difficult to say what makes them onions or hyacinths." -- Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302501-now-helpless-in-the-hollow-of-an-unarmorial-age-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:59:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302501-now-helpless-in-the-hollow-of-an-unarmorial-age-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, helpless in the hollow of
An unarmorial age, a trough
Of smoke in slow suspended skeins
Above their scrap of history,
Only an attitude remains:

Time has transfigured them into
Untruth. The stone finality
They hardly meant has come to be
Their final blazon, and to prove
Our almost-instinct almost true:
What will survive of us is love." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18338-there-is-no-bad-whiskey-there-are-only-some-whiskeys</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 10:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18338-there-is-no-bad-whiskey-there-are-only-some-whiskeys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no bad whiskey.  There are only some whiskeys that aren't as good as others." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146716-everything-gets-horrible-everything-you-see-gets-ugly-lurid-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 05:15:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146716-everything-gets-horrible-everything-you-see-gets-ugly-lurid-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything gets horrible. Everything you see gets ugly. Lurid is the word. Doctor Garton said lurid, one time.  That's the right word for it. And everything sounds harsh, spiny and harsh sounding, like every sound you hear all of a sudden has teeth. And smelling like I smell bad even after I just got out of the shower. It's like what's the point of washing if everything smells like I need another shower" -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112783-what-can-a-character-come-to-know-of-himself-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 17:31:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Margot add a quote by from The Eye of the Story, by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112783-what-can-a-character-come-to-know-of-himself-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What can a character come to know, of himself and others, by working through a given situation?  That is what fiction asks, with an emotional urgency driving it all the way; and can he know it in time?
" -- from The Eye of the Story, by Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
