<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79453-nicole]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/79453-nicole" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 17:16:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76904-they-came-to-the-high-stone-shaft-with-the-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 17:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Joan Aiken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76904-they-came-to-the-high-stone-shaft-with-the-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They came to the high stone shaft with the face of Sul; they descended to the terrace below. And here Caradog waited, leaning on his silver-tipped rod and eying the horizon, until the delicate slip of the new moon moved out from behind the shoulder of Mount Damyake, with the mysterious, shadowy ghost of the old moon cradle inside it, like an egg inside its egg cup.

&quot;Now it is time,&quot; he said.

&quot;Blame it!&quot; expostulated Dido. &quot;It ain't &lt;i&gt;right&lt;/i&gt; for me to die! Have you thought of that, mister? You're and &lt;i&gt;old&lt;/i&gt; gager; you've lived nigh on fourscore years, I shouldn't wonder. You did a whole lot of things and learned a lot  o' stuff --- though mussy knows, you ain't put it to very good use. But I haven't hardly done &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt;! And I ain't learned much, neither, except the use of the globes that Mr. Holy taught me, and how to curtsy and cut up whales.&quot;

At the thought of Mr. Holystone her voice, to her shame, began to wobble dangerously; she stopped speaking and drew a deep breath.

&quot;Cease repining, child, and go down those steps,&quot; said Caradog. &quot;Do not quarrel with your destiny. If Sul wishes you to die, then it is your time.&quot;

Dido remembered the story that Bran had told about the man who picked up the necklace. Well, if it is my destiny, she thought, best not to make a pother about it." -- Joan Aiken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191699-moominvalley-in-november-chapter-5-the-hemulen-the-hemulen-woke</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 16:37:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191699-moominvalley-in-november-chapter-5-the-hemulen-the-hemulen-woke]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Moominvalley in November
Chapter 5, THE HEMULEN:

The hemulen woke up slowly and recognised himself and wished he had been someone he didn't know. He felt even tireder than when he went to bed, and here it was -- another day which would go on until evening and then there would be another one and another one which would be the same as all days are when they are lived by a hemulen.

He crept under the bedcover and buried his nose in the pillow, then he shifted his stomach to the edge of the bed where the sheets were cool. He took possession of the whole bed with outstretched arms and legs he was waiting for a nice dream that wouldn't come. He curled up and made himself small but it didn't help a bit. He tried being the hemulen that everybody like, he tried being the hemulen that no one liked. But however hard he tried he remained a hemulen doing his best without anything really coming off. In the end he got up and pulled on his trousers.

The Hemulen didn't like getting dressed and undressed, it gave him a feeling that the days passed without anything of importance happening. Even so, he spent the whole day arranging, organising and directing things from morning till night! All around him there were people living slipshod and aimless lives, wherever he looked there was something to be put to rights and he worked his fingers to the bone trying to get them to see how they ought to live.

It's as though they don't want to live well, the Hemulen thought sadly as he brushed his teeth. He looked at the photograph of himself with his boat which was been taken when the boat was launched. It was a beautiful picture but it made him feel even sadder.

I ought to learn how to sail, the Hemulen thought. But I've never got enough time..." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393754-taylor-clapped-her-hands-three-times-for-attention-ladies-ladies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 10:33:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393754-taylor-clapped-her-hands-three-times-for-attention-ladies-ladies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Taylor clapped her hands three times for attention. &quot;Ladies! Ladies! My stars! That's enough. Now. We all know Miss Arkansas's girls are fake, miss Ohio's easier than making cereal, and Miss Montana's dress is something my blind meemaw would wear to bingo night. And Miss New Mexico -- aren't you from the chill-out state? Maybe you can channel up some new-age-Whole-Foods-incense calm right about now, because we have a big job ahead called staying alive." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2011 06:20:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4566-in-vain-have-i-struggled-it-will-not-do-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In vain have I struggled. It will not do. My feelings will not be repressed. You must allow me to tell you how ardently I admire and love you." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 12:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Piglet sidled up to Pooh from behind. &quot;Pooh?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;Yes, Piglet?&quot;
&quot;Nothing,&quot; said Piglet, taking Pooh's hand. &quot;I just wanted to be sure of you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463890-there-is-no-sunrise-so-beautiful-that-it-is-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 16:56:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Mindy Kaling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/463890-there-is-no-sunrise-so-beautiful-that-it-is-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no sunrise so beautiful that it is worth waking me up to see it." -- Mindy Kaling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2012 16:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think... if it is true that 
there are as many minds as there 
are heads, then there are as many 
kinds of love as there are hearts." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460427-lie-on-the-bridge-and-watch-the-water-flowing-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2013 10:36:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460427-lie-on-the-bridge-and-watch-the-water-flowing-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lie on the bridge and watch the water flowing past.  Or run, or wade through the swamp in your red boots.  Or roll yourself up and listen to the rain falling on the roof.  It's very easy to enjoy yourself." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 11:22:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414466-some-people-say-never-let-them-see-you-cry-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people say, “Never let them see you cry.” I say, if you’re so mad you could just cry, then cry. It terrifies everyone." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955065-let-me-introduce-you-sophie-this-is-miss-eliot-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 08:29:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by Katherine Rundell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955065-let-me-introduce-you-sophie-this-is-miss-eliot-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me introduce you. Sophie, this is Miss Eliot, from the National Childcare Agency. Miss Eliot, this is Sophie, from the ocean." -- Katherine Rundell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637333-and-she-s-got-brains-enough-for-two-which-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2014 15:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[nicole add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637333-and-she-s-got-brains-enough-for-two-which-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And she's got brains enough for two, which is the exact quantity the girl who marries you will need." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
