<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/794950-jenna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/794950-jenna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 08:06:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49572-the-time-is-ripe-for-looking-back-over-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 08:06:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Frederick Buechner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49572-the-time-is-ripe-for-looking-back-over-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time is ripe for looking back over the day, the week, the year, and trying to figure out where we have come from and where we are going to, for sifting through the things we have done and the things we have left undone for a clue to who we are and who, for better or worse, we are becoming.  But again and again we avoid the long thoughts….We cling to the present out of wariness of the past.  And why not, after all?  We get confused.  We need such escape as we can find.  But there is a deeper need yet, I think, and that is the need—not all the time, surely, but from time to time—to enter that still room within us all where the past lives on as a part of the present, where the dead are alive again, where we are most alive ourselves to turnings and to where our journeys have brought us.  The name of the room is Remember—the room where with patience, with charity, with quietness of heart, we remember consciously to remember the lives we have lived." -- Frederick Buechner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49731-a-canon-is-a-guarded-catalogue-of-that-speech-music</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2008 18:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by George Steiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49731-a-canon-is-a-guarded-catalogue-of-that-speech-music]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A canon is a guarded catalogue of that speech, music and art which houses inside us, which is irrevocably familiar to our homecomings.  And this will include, if honestly arrived at and declared (even if solely to oneself), all manner of ephemera, trivial, and possibly mendacious matter…No manor woman need justify his personal anthology, his canonic welcomes.  Love does not argue its necessities." -- George Steiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50167-for-the-next-half-hour-or-so-there-was-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:23:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Gillian Linscott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50167-for-the-next-half-hour-or-so-there-was-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the next half-hour or so there was nothing to be done but sit and suffer it.  We had Madame Tetrazzini trilling about the hissing and sissing of the needle, like a princess at the back of a cave with the sea monster snuffling outside it.  We had Señor Caruso searching bravely for The Lost Chord in a forest of alien English vowel sounds.  We had McCormack’s &lt;i&gt;Kathleen Mavourneen&lt;/i&gt;, Clara Butt longing for her Ain Folk in accents suggesting that they might be found somewhere south of Hyde Park, a tenor whose name I forgot summoning Jerusalem, Jerusalem, and everybody looking devout over their empty teacups." -- Gillian Linscott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12009-yet-each-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-by-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 16:11:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12009-yet-each-man-kills-the-thing-he-loves-by-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet each man kills the thing he loves
By each let this be heard
Some do it with a bitter look
Some with a flattering word
The coward does it with a kiss
The brave man with a sword" -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58023-please-don-t-think-so-lightly-of-liking-someone-it-s-terribly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 16:12:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Anne Perry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58023-please-don-t-think-so-lightly-of-liking-someone-it-s-terribly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Please don’t think so lightly of liking someone.  It’s terribly important.  It is a kind of loving, you know, and one that frequently lasts a lot longer than romance.  You can fall out of love, as well in.  Most of us do, especially if you don’t actually like the person as well.  It doesn’t always grow into love by any means, but sometimes it does." -- Anne Perry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58271-but-unless-we-are-creators-we-are-not-fully-alive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 11:57:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58271-but-unless-we-are-creators-we-are-not-fully-alive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But unless we are creators we are not fully alive. What do I mean by creators? Not only artists, whose acts of creation are the obvious ones of working with paint of clay or words. Creativity is a way of living life, no matter our vocation or how we earn our living. Creativity is not limited to the arts, or having some kind of important career." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141164-war-is-not-two-great-armies-meeting-in-the-clash</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2009 17:23:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Mary Rinehart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141164-war-is-not-two-great-armies-meeting-in-the-clash]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is not two great armies meeting in the clash and frenzy of battle.  War is a boy being carried on a stretcher, looking up at God’s blue sky with bewildered eyes that are soon to close; war is a woman carrying a child that has been injured by a shell; war is spirited horses tied in burning buildings and waiting for death; war is the flower of a race, battered, hungry, bleeding, up to its knees in filthy water; war is an old woman burning a candle before the Mater Dolorsa for the son she has given." -- Mary Rinehart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147302-this-recognition-of-the-truth-we-get-in-the-artist-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 17:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147302-this-recognition-of-the-truth-we-get-in-the-artist-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This recognition of the truth we get in the artist’s work comes to us as a revelation of new truth.  I want to be clear about that.  I am not referring to the sort of patronizing recognition we give a writer by nodding our heads and observing, “Yes, yes, very good, very true—that’s just what I’m always saying.”  I mean the recognition of a truth that tells us something about ourselves that we had not been always saying, something that puts a new knowledge of ourselves withint our grasp.  It is new, startling, and perhaps shattering, and yet it comes to us with a sense of familiarity.  We did not know it before, but the moment the poet how shown it to us, we know that, somehow or other, we had always really known it." -- Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166192-history-as-it-was-purveyed-to-us-was-not-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2009 16:16:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Patricia Hampl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166192-history-as-it-was-purveyed-to-us-was-not-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History, as it was purveyed to us, was not so much a narrative, not even the detached observation of the rise and fall of fortunes and cultures.  It was the litany of loss, attended by the inevitable sympathy for the vanquished side.  The past was always the underdog, and we sensed it was only right to be on its side against the bully future.  We were left with the impression that our own grip was loosening on some essential pediment as one empire after another was swallowed up, and the centuries collapsed into our own." -- Patricia Hampl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181007-we-pass-and-leave-you-lying-no-need-for-rhetoric</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 07:57:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Richard Aldington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181007-we-pass-and-leave-you-lying-no-need-for-rhetoric]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We pass and leave you lying. No need for rhetoric, for funeral music, for melancholy bugle-calls.  No need for tears now, no need for regret.
We took our risk with you; you died and we live.  We take your noble gift, salute for the last time those lines of pitiable crosses, those solitary mounds, those unknown graves, and turn to live our lives out as we may.
Which of us were fortunate--who can tell?  For you there is silence and cold twilight drooping in awful desolation over those motionless lands.  For us sunlight and the sound of women's voices, song and hope and laughter, despair, gaiety, love--life.
Lost terrible silent comrades, we, who might have died, salute you." -- Richard Aldington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181869-how-fortunate-we-were-who-still-had-hope-i-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 08:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Vera Brittain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181869-how-fortunate-we-were-who-still-had-hope-i-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How fortunate we were who still had hope I did not then realise; I could not know how soon the time would come when we should have no more hope, and yet be unable to die" -- Vera Brittain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203278-the-war-said-a-soldier-proverb-will-last-a-hundred</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 06:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Preston William Slosson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203278-the-war-said-a-soldier-proverb-will-last-a-hundred]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The War,' said a soldier proverb, 'will last a hundred years--five years of fighting and ninety-give of winding up the barbed wire." -- Preston William Slosson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15200-war-is-what-happens-when-language-fails</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 12:47:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15200-war-is-what-happens-when-language-fails]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is what happens when language fails." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241133-to-be-ignorant-of-the-future-is-a-condition-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 20:09:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Frances J. Woodward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241133-to-be-ignorant-of-the-future-is-a-condition-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be ignorant of the future is a condition of mortal existence, with which one can make terms.  To be ignorant of the present, where it concerns the life of those one loves, is an additional burden almost beyond endurance." -- Frances J. Woodward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252593-in-1895-lady-londonberry-commented-acidly-on-a-bridegroom-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2010 08:56:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pamela Horn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252593-in-1895-lady-londonberry-commented-acidly-on-a-bridegroom-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In 1895 Lady Londonberry commented acidly on a bridegroom who had 'married the 10,000 a year as well as the lady." -- Pamela Horn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263638-we-are-all-living-history-and-it-s-hard-to-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 08:22:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Marilyn Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263638-we-are-all-living-history-and-it-s-hard-to-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all living history, and it’s hard to say now what will be important in the future.  One thing’s certain, though: if we throw it away, it’s gone." -- Marilyn Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
