<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/795024-erik]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/795024-erik" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 11:29:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 11:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3583-passion-makes-a-person-stop-eating-sleeping-working-feeling-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion makes a person stop eating, sleeping, working, feeling at peace. A lot of people are frightened because, when it appears, it demolishes all the old things it finds in its path. 

No one wants their life thrown into chaos. That is why a lot of people keep that threat under control, and are somehow capable of sustaining a house or a structure that is already rotten. They are the engineers of the superseded. 

Other people think exactly the opposite: they surrender themselves without a second thought, hoping to find in passion the solutions to all their problems. They make the other person responsible for their happiness and blame them for their possible unhappiness. They are either euphoric because something marvelous has happened or depressed because something unexpected has just ruined everything. 

Keeping passion at bay or surrendering blindly to it - which of these two attitudes is the least destructive? 

I don't know." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19826-we-must-be-willing-to-let-go-of-the-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2010 11:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19826-we-must-be-willing-to-let-go-of-the-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must be willing to let go of the life we planned so as to have the life that is waiting for us." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102507-he-had-never-wanted-to-know-anything-about-the-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 17:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102507-he-had-never-wanted-to-know-anything-about-the-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had never wanted to know anything about the part of her intimate life that he had not shared with her.  Why should he take an interest now, still less take offense at it?  Anyhow, he asked himself, what is an intimate secret?  Is that where we hide what's most mysterious, most singular, most original about a human being?  Are her intimate secrets what make Chantal the unique being he loves?  No.  What people keep secret is the most common, the most ordinary, the most prevalent thing, the same thing that everybody has: the body and its needs, its maladies, its manias-constipation for instance, or menstruation.  We ashamedly conceal these intimate matters not because they are so personal but on the contrary, they are so lamentably impersonal." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403781-you-were-unsure-which-pain-is-worse----the-shock</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 21:55:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Simon Van Booy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403781-you-were-unsure-which-pain-is-worse----the-shock]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You were unsure which pain is worse -- the shock of what happened or the ache for what never will." -- Simon Van Booy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
