<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/799856-brooke]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/799856-brooke" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 13:08:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2008 13:08:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/356-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned this, at least, by my experiment: that if one advances confidently in the direction of his dreams, and endeavors to live the life which he has imagined, he will meet with a success unexpected in common hours." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:05:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/929-whatever-you-can-do-or-dream-you-can-begin-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!" -- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14828-we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-excellence-then-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:06:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by William Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14828-we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-excellence-then-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit." -- William Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14830-these-are-the-times-in-which-a-genius-would-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:06:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Abigail Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14830-these-are-the-times-in-which-a-genius-would-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are the times in which a genius would wish to live. It is not in the still calm of life, or the repose of a pacific station, that great characters are formed. The habits of a vigorous mind are formed in contending with difficulties. Great necessities call out great virtues. When a mind is raised, and animated by scenes that engage the heart, then those qualities which would otherwise lay dormant, wake into life and form the character of the hero and the statesman." -- Abigail Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14831-it-is-a-small-soul-buried-beneath-the-weight-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:07:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Montaigne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14831-it-is-a-small-soul-buried-beneath-the-weight-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a small soul, buried beneath the weight of affairs, that does not know how to get clean away from them, that cannot put them aside and pick them up again." -- Montaigne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9178-chance-favors-the-prepared-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:08:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Louis Pasteur]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9178-chance-favors-the-prepared-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chance favors the prepared mind." -- Louis Pasteur]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770-the-love-of-learning-the-sequestered-nooks-and-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:09:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770-the-love-of-learning-the-sequestered-nooks-and-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The love of learning, the sequestered nooks,
And all the sweet serenity of books" -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14834-to-the-body-and-mind-which-have-been-cramped-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:09:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14834-to-the-body-and-mind-which-have-been-cramped-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the body and mind which have been cramped by noxious work or company, nature is medicinal and restores their tone. The tradesman, the attorney comes out of the din and craft of the street and sees the sky and the woods, and is a man again. In their eternal calm, he finds himself." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14836-men-cannot-abandon-their-religious-faith-without-a-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:10:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14836-men-cannot-abandon-their-religious-faith-without-a-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men cannot abandon their religious faith without a kind of aberration of intellect and a sort of violent distortion of their true nature; they are invincibly brought back to more pious sentiments. Unbelief is an accident, and faith is the only permanent state of mankind." -- Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14838-either-write-something-worth-reading-or-do-something-worth-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:11:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14838-either-write-something-worth-reading-or-do-something-worth-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14840-literature-takes-a-habit-of-mind-that-has-disappeared-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 19:12:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14840-literature-takes-a-habit-of-mind-that-has-disappeared-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature takes a habit of mind that has disappeared. It requires silence, some form of isolation, and sustained concentration in the presence of an enigmatic thing." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910764-one-of-my-greatest-concerns-for-the-young-women-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 09:04:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brooke add a quote by Robert D. Hales]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910764-one-of-my-greatest-concerns-for-the-young-women-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of my greatest concerns for the young women of the Church is that they will sell themselves short in dating and marriage by forgetting who they really are--daughters of a loving Heavenly Father. . . . Unfortunately, a young woman who lowers her standards far enough can always find temporary acceptance from immature and unworthy young men. . . .

At their best, daughters of God are loving, caring, understanding, and sympathetic. This does not mean they are also gullible, unrealistic, or easily manipulated. If a young man does not measure up to the standards a young woman has set, he may promise her that he will change if she will marry him first. Wise daughters of God will insist that young men who seek their hand in marriage change before the wedding, not after. (I am referring here to the kind of change that will be part of the lifelong growth of every disciple.) He may argue that she doesn't really believe in repentance and forgiveness. But one of the hallmarks of repentance is forsaking sin. Especially when the sin involves addictive behaviors or a pattern of transgression, wise daughters of God insist on seeing a sustained effort to forsake sin over a long period of time as true evidence of repentance. They do not marry someone because they believe they can change him. Young women, please do not settle for someone unworthy of your gospel standards.

On the other hand, young women should not refuse to settle down. There is no right age for young men or young women to marry, but there is a right attitude for them to have about marriage: &quot;Thy will be done&quot; . . . . The time to marry is when we are prepared to meet a suitable mate, not after we have done all the enjoyable things in life we hoped to do while we were single. . . .

When I hear some young men and young women set plans in stone which do not include marriage until after age twenty-five or thirty or until a graduate degree has been obtained, I recall Jacob's warning, &quot;Seek not to counsel the Lord, but to take counsel from his hand&quot; (Jacob 4:10). . . .

How we conduct ourselves in dating relationships is a good indication of how we will conduct ourselves in a marriage relationship. . . .

Individuals considering marriage would be wise to conduct their own prayerful due diligence--long before they set their hearts on marriage. There is nothing wrong with making a T-square diagram and on either side of the vertical line listing the relative strengths and weaknesses of a potential mate. I sometimes wonder whether doing more homework when it comes to this critical decision would spare some Church members needless heartache. I fear too many fall in love with each other or even with the idea of marriage before doing the background research necessary to make a good decision.

It is sad when a person who wants to be married never has the opportunity to marry. But it is much, much sadder to be married to the wrong person. If you do not believe me, talk with someone who has made that mistake. Think carefully about the person you are considering marrying, because marriage should last for time and for all eternity." -- Robert D. Hales]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
