<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/800645-keely]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/800645-keely" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 11:58:47 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 11:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456196-i-m-not-laughing-i-was-actually-crying-and-please-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m not laughing.” I was actually crying. “And please don’t laugh at me now, but I think the reason it’s so hard for me to get over this guy is because I seriously believed David was my soul mate. ”He probably was. Your problem is you don’t understand what that word means. People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that’s what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that’s holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life. A true soul mate is probably the most important person you’ll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake. But to live with a soul mate forever? Nah. Too painful. Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then they leave. And thank God for it. Your problem is, you just can’t let this one go. It’s over, Groceries. David’s purpose was to shake you up, drive you out of your marriage that you needed to leave, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light could get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you had to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master and beat it. That was his job, and he did great, but now it’s over. Problem is, you can’t accept that his relationship had a real short shelf life. You’re like a dog at the dump, baby – you’re just lickin’ at the empty tin can, trying to get more nutrition out of it. And if you’re not careful, that can’s gonna get stuck on your snout forever and make your life miserable. So drop it.“But I love him.”
“So love him.” “But I miss him.” “So miss him. Send him some love and light every time you think about him, then drop it. You’re just afraid to let go of the last bits of David because then you’ll be really alone, and Liz Gilbert is scared to death of what will happen if she’s really alone. But here’s what you gotta understand, Groceries. If you clear out all that space in your mind that you’re using right now to obsess about this guy, you’ll have a vacuum there, an open spot – a doorway. And guess what the universe will do with the doorway? It will rush in – God will rush in – and fill you with more love than you ever dreamed. So stop using David to block that door. Let it go." -- Elizabeth Gilbert in Eat, Pray, Love.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174145-this-is-a-good-sign-having-a-broken-heart-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 11:59:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174145-this-is-a-good-sign-having-a-broken-heart-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is a good sign, having a broken heart. It means we have tried for something." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 11:59:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244961-someday-you-re-gonna-look-back-on-this-moment-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 12:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244961-someday-you-re-gonna-look-back-on-this-moment-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someday you're gonna look back on this moment of your life as such a sweet time of grieving.  You'll see that you were in mourning and your heart was broken, but your life was changing..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393651-i-do-not-consider-myself-less-ignorant-than-most-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 12:04:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393651-i-do-not-consider-myself-less-ignorant-than-most-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not consider myself less ignorant than most people. I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books. I have begun to listen to the teachings my blood whispers to me. My story is not a pleasant one; it is neither sweet nor harmonious, as invented stories are; it has the taste of nonsense and chaos, of madness and dreams -- like the lives of all men who stop deceiving themselves." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139694-i-have-sometimes-told-people-probably-wrongly-that-there-s-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 20:53:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Scarlett Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1139694-i-have-sometimes-told-people-probably-wrongly-that-there-s-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have sometimes told people, probably wrongly, that there’s no point in writing at all if you don’t feel that there’s something you absolutely have to explore. The idea that someone may want ‘to be a writer’ but have no idea of what to write is quite paradoxical, in one way. After all, why write things down if you don’t have a burning desire to communicate something? But actually, most people who want to write do have things to communicate, they just don’t necessarily know what they are yet. I have themes and ideas in my mind constantly, as do many other people. I care about things in the world and I want to express this somehow. Part of becoming a writer is working out which of all the strange thoughts you have in a given day are worth exploring further." -- Scarlett Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1223303-confession-of-effort-chafes-against-the-notion-that-empathy-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 19:01:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Leslie Jamison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1223303-confession-of-effort-chafes-against-the-notion-that-empathy-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["confession of effort chafes against the notion that empathy should always rise unbidden, that genuine means the same thing as unwilled, that intentionality is the enemy of love. But I believe in intention and I believe in work. I believe in waking up in the middle of the night and packing our bags and leaving our worst selves for our better ones." -- Leslie Jamison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
