<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/800852-j-rogue]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/800852-j-rogue" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 12:12:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17678-many-persons-have-a-wrong-idea-of-what-constitutes-true</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 12:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Helen Keller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17678-many-persons-have-a-wrong-idea-of-what-constitutes-true]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many persons have a wrong idea of what constitutes true happiness. It is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose." -- Helen Keller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17680-last-will-prologue-we-sacco-and-vanzetti-sound-of-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 12:16:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Nicola Sacco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17680-last-will-prologue-we-sacco-and-vanzetti-sound-of-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Last Will

Prologue:
We, Sacco and Vanzetti, sound of body and mind,
Devise and bequeath to all we leave behind,
The worldly wealth we inherited at our birth,
Each one to share alike as we leave this earth.

To Wit:
To babies we will their mothers’ love,
To youngsters we will the sun above.
To spooners who wont to tryst the night,
We give the moon and stars that shine so bright.
To thrill them in their hours of joy,
When boy hugs maid and maid hugs boy.
To nature’s creatures we allot the spring and summer,
To the doe, the bear, the gold-finch and the hummer.
To the fishes we ascribe the deep blue sea,
The honey we apportion to the bustling bee.
To the pessimist—good cheer—his mind to sooth,
To the chronic liar we donate the solemn truth.

And Lastly:

To those who judge solely seeking renown,
With blaring trumpets of the fakir and clown;
To the prosecutor, persecutor, and other human hounds,
Who’d barter another’s honor, recognizing no bounds,
To the Governor, the Jury, who another’s life they’d sell—
We endow them with the fiery depths of HELL!

(Industrial Worker, Aug. 20, 1927)" -- Nicola Sacco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17687-i-don-t-believe-in-charity-i-believe-in-solidarity-charity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 12:25:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17687-i-don-t-believe-in-charity-i-believe-in-solidarity-charity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe in charity. I believe in solidarity. Charity is so vertical. It goes from the top to the bottom. Solidarity is horizontal. It respects the other person. I have a lot to learn from other people." -- Eduardo Galeano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 23:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66608-when-everything-goes-to-hell-the-people-who-stand-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 22:39:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66608-when-everything-goes-to-hell-the-people-who-stand-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When everything goes to hell, the people who stand by you without flinching -- they are your family. " -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125996-both-for-the-production-on-a-mass-scale-of-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 10:54:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[J. add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125996-both-for-the-production-on-a-mass-scale-of-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both for the production on a mass scale of this communist consciousness, and for the success of the cause itself, the alteration of men on a mass scale is necessary, an alteration which can only take place in a practical movement, a revolution; this revolution is necessary, therefore, not only because the ruling class cannot be overthrown in any other way, but also because the class overthrowing it can only in a revolution succeed in ridding itself of all the muck of ages and become fitted to found society anew." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
