<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/801248-david]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/801248-david" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 16:40:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411110-rather-than-seeing-himself-as-human-because-he-could-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 16:40:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411110-rather-than-seeing-himself-as-human-because-he-could-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rather than seeing himself as human because he could make economic calculations, the hunter insisted that being truly human meant &lt;i&gt;refusing&lt;/i&gt; to make such calculations, refusing to measure or remember who had given what to whom, for the precise reason that doing so would inevitably create a world where we began &quot;comparing power with power, measuring, calculating&quot; and reducing each other to slaves or dogs through debt." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593731-a-great-embarrassing-fact-haunts-all-attempts-to-represent-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593731-a-great-embarrassing-fact-haunts-all-attempts-to-represent-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[A] great embarrassing fact… haunts all attempts to represent the market as the highest form of human freedom: that historically, impersonal, commercial markets originate in theft." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465608-political-economy-tends-to-see-work-in-capitalist-societies-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465608-political-economy-tends-to-see-work-in-capitalist-societies-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Political economy tends to see work in capitalist societies as divided between two spheres: wage labor, for which the paradigm is always factories, and domestic labor – housework, childcare – relegated mainly to women. The first is seen primarily as a matter of creating and maintaining physical objects. The second is probably best seen as a matter of creating and maintaining people and social relations.
[...] This makes it easier to see the two as fundamentally different sorts of activity, making it hard for us to recognize interpretive labor, for example, or most of what we usually think of as women’s work, as labor at all. To my mind it would probably be better to recognize it as the primary form of labor. Insofar as a clear distinction can be made here, it’s the care, energy, and labor directed at human beings that should be considered fundamental. The things we care most about – our loves, passions, rivalries, obsessions – are always other people; and in most societies that are not capitalist, it’s taken for granted that the manufacture of material goods is a subordinate moment in a larger process of fashioning people. In fact, I would argue that one of the most alienating aspects of capitalism is the fact that it forces us to pretend that it is the other way around, and that societies exist primarily to increase their output of things." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526063-in-fact-this-is-precisely-the-logic-on-which-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526063-in-fact-this-is-precisely-the-logic-on-which-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact this is precisely the logic on which the Bank of England&amp;mdash;the first successful modern central bank&amp;mdash;was originally founded. In 1694, a consortium of English bankers made a loan of £1,200,000 to the king. In return they received a royal monopoly on the issuance of banknotes. What this meant in practice was they had the right to advance IOUs for a portion of the money the king now owed them to any inhabitant of the kingdom willing to borrow from them, or willing to deposit their own money in the bank&amp;mdash;in effect, to circulate or &quot;monetize&quot; the newly created royal debt. This was a great deal for the bankers (they got to charge the king 8 percent annual interest for the original loan and simultaneously charge interest on the same money to the clients who borrowed it) , but it only worked as long as the original loan remained outstanding. To this day, this loan has never been paid back. It cannot be. If it ever were, the entire monetary system of Great Britain would cease to exist." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543703-if-history-shows-anything-it-is-that-there-s-no-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543703-if-history-shows-anything-it-is-that-there-s-no-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If history shows anything, it is that there's no better way to justify relations founded on violence, to make such relations seem moral, than by reframing them in the language of debt&amp;mdash;above all, because it immediately makes it seem that it's the victim who's doing something wrong." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66180-traditional-hedonism-was-based-on-the-direct-experience-of-pleasure-wine</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66180-traditional-hedonism-was-based-on-the-direct-experience-of-pleasure-wine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Traditional hedonism...was based on the direct experience of pleasure: wine, women and song; sex, drugs and rock 'n' roll; or whatever the local variant. The problem, from a capitalist perspective, is that there are inherent limits to all this. People become sated, bored...Modern self-illusory hedonism solves this dilemma because here, what one is really consuming are fantasies and day-dreams about what having a certain product &lt;i&gt;would&lt;/i&gt; be like." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431372-freuchen-tells-how-one-day-after-coming-home-hungry-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431372-freuchen-tells-how-one-day-after-coming-home-hungry-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freuchen tells how one day, after coming home hungry from an unsuccessful walrus-hunting expedition, he found one of the successful hunters dropping off several hundred pounds of meat. He thanked him profusely. The man objected indignantly:
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Up in our country we are human!&quot; said the hunter. &quot;And since we are human we help each other. We don't like to hear anybody say thanks for that. What I get today you may get tomorrow. Up here we say that by gifts one makes slaves and by whips one makes dogs.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
... The refusal to calculate credits and debits can be found throughout the anthropological literature on egalitarian hunting societies. Rather than seeing himself as human &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/I&gt; he could make economic calculations, the hunter insisted that being truly human meant &lt;i&gt;refusing&lt;/i&gt; to make such calculations, refusing to measure or remember who had given what to whom, for the precise reason that doing so would inevitably create a world where we began &quot;comparing power with power, measuring, calculating&quot; and reducing each other to slaves or dogs through debt. It's not that he, like untold millions of similar egalitarian spirits throughout history, was unaware that humans have a propensity to calculate. If he wasn't aware of it, he could not have said what he did. Of course we have a propensity to calculate. We have all sorts of propensities. In any real-life situation, we have propensities that drive us in several different contradictory directions simultaneously. No one is more real than any other. The real question is which we take as the foundation of our humanity, and therefore, make the basis of our civilization." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626826-but-if-all-maximizing-models-are-really-arguing-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626826-but-if-all-maximizing-models-are-really-arguing-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if all maximizing models are really arguing is that “people will always seek to maximize something,” then they obviously can’t predict anything, which means employing them can hardly be said to make anthropology more scientific. All they really add to analysis is a set of assumptions about human nature. The assumption, most of all, that no one ever does anything primarily out of concern for others; that whatever one does, one is only trying to get something out of it for oneself. In common English, there is a word for this attitude. It’s called “cynicism.” Most of us try to avoid people who take it too much to heart. In economics, apparently, they call it “science." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552861-a-revolution-on-a-world-scale-will-take-a-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/552861-a-revolution-on-a-world-scale-will-take-a-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A revolution on a world scale will take a very long time. But it is also possible to recognize that it is already starting to happen. The easiest way to get our minds around it is to stop thinking about revolution as a thing — “the” revolution, the great cataclysmic break—and instead ask “what is revolutionary action?” We could then
suggest: revolutionary action is any collective action which rejects, and therefore confronts, some form of power or domination and in doing so, reconstitutes social relations—even within the collectivity—in that light. Revolutionary action does not necessarily have to aim to topple governments. Attempts to create autonomous communities in the face of power (using Castoriadis’ definition
here: ones that constitute themselves, collectively make their own rules or principles of operation, and continually reexamine them), would, for
instance, be almost by definition revolutionary acts. And history shows us that the continual accumulation
of such acts can change (almost) everything." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526259-as-it-turns-out-we-don-t-all-have-to-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526259-as-it-turns-out-we-don-t-all-have-to-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As it turns out, we don't &quot;all&quot; have to pay our debts. Only some of us do." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556501-the-theory-of-exodus-proposes-that-the-most-effective-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/556501-the-theory-of-exodus-proposes-that-the-most-effective-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The theory of exodus proposes that the most effective way of opposing capitalism and the liberal state is not through direct confrontation but by means of what Paolo Virno has called “engaged withdrawal,”mass defection by those wishing to create new forms of community. One need only glance at the historical record to confirm that most successful forms of popular resistance have taken precisely this form. They have not involved challenging power head on (this usually leads to being slaughtered, or if not, turning into some—often even uglier—variant of the
very thing one first challenged) but from one or another strategy of slipping away from its grasp, from flight, desertion, the founding of new communities." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526233-money-has-no-essence-it-s-not-really-anything-therefore-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526233-money-has-no-essence-it-s-not-really-anything-therefore-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["money has no essence. It's not &quot;really&quot; anything; therefore, its nature has always been and presumably always will be a matter of political conten­tion." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526049-say-a-king-wishes-to-support-a-standing-army-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526049-say-a-king-wishes-to-support-a-standing-army-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Say a king wishes to support a standing army of fifty thousand men. Under ancient or medieval conditions, feeding such a force was an enormous problem&amp;mdash;unless they were on the march, one would need to employ almost as many men and ani­mals just to locate, acquire, and transport the necessary provisions. On the other hand, if one simply hands out coins to the soldiers and then demands that every family in the kingdom was obliged to pay one of those coins back to you, one would, in one blow, turn one's entire national economy into a vast machine for the provisioning of soldiers, since now every family, in order to get their hands on the coins, must find some way to contribute to the general effort to provide soldiers with things they want. Markets are brought into existence as a side effect." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437473-at-this-point-we-can-finally-see-what-s-really-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437473-at-this-point-we-can-finally-see-what-s-really-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At this point we can finally see what's really at stake in our peculiar habit of defining ourselves simultaneously as master and slave, reduplicating the most brutal aspects of the ancient household in our very concept of ourselves, as masters of our freedoms, or as owners of our very selves. It is the only way that we can imagine ourselves as completely isolated beings. There is a direct line from the new Roman conception of liberty – not as the ability to form mutual relationships with others, but as the kind of absolute power of &quot;use and abuse&quot; over the conquered chattel who make up the bulk of a wealthy Roman man's household – to the strange fantasies of liberal philosophers like Hobbes, Locke, and Smith, about the origins of human society in some collection of thirty- or forty-year-old males who seem to have sprung from the earth fully formed, then have to decide whether to kill each other or begin to swap beaver pelts." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437493-thomas-jefferson-that-owner-of-many-slaves-chose-to-begin</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:26:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437493-thomas-jefferson-that-owner-of-many-slaves-chose-to-begin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thomas Jefferson, that owner of many slaves, chose to begin the Declaration of Independence by directly contradicting the moral basis of slavery, writing &quot;we hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, and that they are endowed by their Creator with certain inalienable Rights ...&quot; thus undercutting simultaneously any argument that Africans were racially inferior, and also that they or their ancestors could ever have been justly and legally deprived of their freedom. In doing so, however, he did not propose some radically new conception of rights and liberties. Neither have subsequent political philosophers. For the most part, we've just kept the old ones, but with the word &quot;not&quot; inserted here and there. Most of our most precious rights and freedoms are a series of exceptions to an overall moral and legal framework that suggests we shouldn't really have them in the first place." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785441-residents-of-the-squatter-community-of-christiana-denmark-for-example</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785441-residents-of-the-squatter-community-of-christiana-denmark-for-example]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Residents of the squatter community of Christiana, Denmark, for example, have a Christmastide ritual where they dress in Santa suits, take toys from department stores and distribute them to children on the street, partly just so everyone can relish the images of the cops beating down Santa and snatching the toys back from crying children." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785442-if-you-have-the-power-to-hit-people-over-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785442-if-you-have-the-power-to-hit-people-over-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have the power to hit people over the head whenever you want, you don’t have to trouble yourself too much figuring out what they think is going on, and therefore, generally speaking, you don’t. Hence the sure-fire way to simplify social arrangements, to ignore the incredibly complex play of perspectives, passions, insights, desires, and mutual understandings that human life is really made of, is to make a rule and threaten to attack anyone who breaks it. This is why violence has always been the favored recourse of the stupid: it is the one form of stupidity to which it is almost impossible to come up with an intelligent response. It is also of course the basis of the state." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785443-we-are-usually-told-that-democracy-originated-in-ancient-athens-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785443-we-are-usually-told-that-democracy-originated-in-ancient-athens-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are usually told that democracy originated in ancient Athens—like science, or philosophy, it was a Greek invention. It’s never entirely clear what this is supposed to mean. Are we supposed to believe that before the Athenians, it never really occurred to anyone, anywhere, to gather all the members of their community in order to make joint decisions in a way that gave everyone equal say?" -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785445-if-there-is-no-way-to-compel-those-who-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785445-if-there-is-no-way-to-compel-those-who-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no way to compel those who find a majority decision distasteful to go along with it, then the last thing one would want to do is to hold a vote: a public contest which someone will be seen to lose. Voting would be the most likely means to guarantee humiliations, resentments, hatreds, in the end, the destruction of communities. What is seen as an elaborate and difficult process of finding consensus is, in fact, a long process of making sure no one walks away feeling that their views have been totally ignored." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785446-in-other-words-if-a-man-is-armed-then-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/785446-in-other-words-if-a-man-is-armed-then-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In other words if a man is armed, then one pretty much has to take his opinions into account. One can see how this worked at its starkest in Xenophon’s Anabasis, which tells the story of an army of Greek mercenaries who suddenly find themselves leaderless and lost in the middle of Persia. They elect new officers, and then hold a collective vote to decide what to do next. In a case like this, even if the vote was 60/40, everyone could see the balance of forces and what would happen if things actually came to blows. Every vote was, in a real sense, a conquest." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675623-about-the-only-thing-we-can-imagine-is-catastrophe</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/675623-about-the-only-thing-we-can-imagine-is-catastrophe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["About the only thing we can imagine
is catastrophe." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526123-but-if-smith-was-right-and-gold-and-silver-became</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526123-but-if-smith-was-right-and-gold-and-silver-became]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But if Smith was right, and gold and silver became money through the natural workings of the market completely independently of governments, then wouldn't the obvious thing be to just grab control of the gold and silver mines?" -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565826-even-in-the-bible-the-admonition-in-the-ten-commandments</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565826-even-in-the-bible-the-admonition-in-the-ten-commandments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even in the Bible, the admonition in the Ten Commandments not to 'covet thy neighbor's wife' clearly referred not to lust in one's heart (adultery had already been covered in commandment number seven), but to the prospect of taking her as a debt-peon&amp;mdash;in other words, as a servant to sweep one's yard and hang out the laundry." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728397-for-me-this-is-exactly-what-s-so-pernicious-about-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/728397-for-me-this-is-exactly-what-s-so-pernicious-about-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, this is exactly what's so pernicious about the morality of debt: the way that financial imperatives constantly try to reduce us all, despite ourselves, to the equivalent of pillagers, eyeing the world simply for what can be turned into money -- and then tell us that it's only those who are willing to see the world as pillagers who deserve access to the resources required to pursue anything in life &lt;i&gt;other&lt;/i&gt; than money." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617634-but-in-the-years-since-the-neoliberal-project-really-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:27:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617634-but-in-the-years-since-the-neoliberal-project-really-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But in the years since the neoliberal project really has been stripped down to what was always its essence: not an economic project at all, but a political project, designed to devastate the imagination, and willing – with it’s cumbersome securitization and insane military projects – to destroy the capitalist order itself if that’s what it took to make it seem inevitable." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617639-what-it-mainly-revealed-was-that-one-of-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617639-what-it-mainly-revealed-was-that-one-of-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What it mainly revealed was that one of the most insidious of the “hidden injuries of class” in North American society was the denial of the right to do good, to be noble, to pursue any form of value other than money – or, at least, to do it and to gain any financial security or rewards for having done. The passionate hatred of the “liberal elite” among right-wing populists came down, in practice, to the utterly justified resentment towards a class that had sequestered, for its own children, every opportunity to pursue love, truth, beauty, honor, decency, and to be afforded the means to exist while doing so. The endless identification with soldiers (“support our troops!) – that is, with individuals who have, over the years, been reduced to little more than high tech mercenaries enforcing of a global regime of financial capital – lay in the fact that these are almost the only individuals of working class origin in the US who have figured out a way to get paid for pursuing some kind of higher ideal, or at least being able to imagine that’s what they’re doing. Obviously most would prefer to pursue higher ideals in way that did not involve the risk of having their legs blown off. The sense of rage, in fact, stems above all from the knowledge that all such jobs are taken by children of the rich." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776644-normally-when-you-challenge-the-conventional-wisdom-that-the-current-economic</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776644-normally-when-you-challenge-the-conventional-wisdom-that-the-current-economic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Normally, when you challenge the conventional wisdom—that the current economic and political system is the only possible one—the first reaction you are likely to get is a demand for a detailed architectural blueprint of how an alternative system would work, down to the nature of its financial instruments, energy supplies, and policies of sewer maintenance. Next, you are likely to be asked for a detailed program of how this system will be brought into existence. Historically, this is ridiculous. When has social change ever happened according to someone’s blueprint? It’s not as if a small circle of visionaries in Renaissance Florence conceived of something they called “capitalism,” figured out the details of how the stock exchange and factories would someday work, and then put in place a program to bring their visions into reality. In fact, the idea is so absurd we might well ask ourselves how it ever occurred to us to imagine this is how change happens to begin." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572899-the-criminalization-of-debt-then-was-the-criminalization-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:28:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/572899-the-criminalization-of-debt-then-was-the-criminalization-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The criminalization of debt, then, was the criminalization of the very basis of human society. It cannot be overemphasized that in a small community, everyone normally was both a lender and borrower. One can only imagine the tensions and temptations that must have existed in a community&amp;mdash;and communities, much though they are based on love, in fact &lt;i&gt;because&lt;/i&gt; they are based on love, will always also be full of hatred, rivalry and passion&amp;mdash;when it became clear that with sufficiently clever scheming, manipulation, and perhaps a bit of strategic bribery, they could arrange to have almost anyone they hated imprisoned or even hanged." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526065-tally-sticks-were-quite-explicitly-ious-both-parties-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 22:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/526065-tally-sticks-were-quite-explicitly-ious-both-parties-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tally sticks were quite explicitly IOUs: both parties to a transaction would take a hazelwood twig, notch it to indicate the amount owed, and then split it in half. The creditor would keep one half, called &quot;the stock&quot; (hence the origin of the term &quot;stock holder&quot;) and the debtor kept the other, called &quot;the stub&quot; (hence the origin of the term &quot;ticket stub.)" -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801598-i-would-like-then-to-end-by-putting-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2013 13:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Graeber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801598-i-would-like-then-to-end-by-putting-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would like, then, to end by putting in a good word for the non-industrious poor. At least they aren’t hurting anyone. Insofar as the time they are taking time off from work is being spent with friends and family, enjoying and caring for those they love, they’re probably improving the world more than we acknowledge." -- David Graeber]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
