<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/801350-becky-rose]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/801350-becky-rose" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 17:59:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830589-our-failure-to-be-a-peculiar-people-in-maintaining-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 17:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830589-our-failure-to-be-a-peculiar-people-in-maintaining-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our failure to be a &quot;peculiar&quot; people in maintaining our standards, despite the jeers and the criticisms of the crowd, will be our failure to be chosen for that calling to which we are called.

The Lord has told us, &quot;Behold, there are many called, but few are chosen&quot; (D&amp;C 121:34), and then in the same revelation points out two reasons why men fail of their blessings. The first reason he gives is that their hearts are set so much upon the things of this world, and the second is that they aspire so much to the honors of men. So then as Church members let us beware lest we set our hearts upon the things of this world and lest we aspire so much to the honors of men that we compromise our standards. If we do so, we will be cut off in the Day of Judgment and will lose our blessings. Our reward for daring to live the gospel despite the oppositions from the outside world will be to have blessings added upon our heads forever and forever." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830585-of-course-you-are-peculiar-if-the-world-continues-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 17:59:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830585-of-course-you-are-peculiar-if-the-world-continues-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course you are peculiar. If the world continues its present trend, and if you walk in obedience to the doctrines and principles of this church, you may become even more peculiar in the eyes of others." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830634-i-do-not-care-how-learned-a-man-may-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 17:59:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by John Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830634-i-do-not-care-how-learned-a-man-may-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not care how learned a man may be, or how extensively he may have traveled; I do not care what his talent, intellect or genius may be, at what college he may have studied, how comprehensive his views or what his judgment may be on other matters, he cannot understand certain things without the Spirit of God, and that necessarily introduces the principle . . . of revelation." -- John Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850905-today-we-have-a-rebirth-of-ancient-sodom-and-gomorrah</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 13:23:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850905-today-we-have-a-rebirth-of-ancient-sodom-and-gomorrah]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today we have a rebirth of ancient Sodom and Gomorrah. From seldom-read pages in dusty Bibles they come forth as real cities in a real world, depicting a real malady--pernicious permissiveness." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850788-a-man-is-saved-no-faster-than-he-gets-knowledge</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 13:23:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Joseph Smith Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850788-a-man-is-saved-no-faster-than-he-gets-knowledge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man is saved no faster than he gets knowledge, for if he does not get knowledge, he will be brought into captivity by some evil power in the other world, as evil spirits will have more knowledge, and consequently more power than many men who are on the earth. Hence it needs revelation to assist us, and give us knowledge of the things of God." -- Joseph Smith Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850092-knowledge-is-power-and-all-things-are-to-be-known</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 13:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/850092-knowledge-is-power-and-all-things-are-to-be-known]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge is power,&quot; and all things are to be known in due season. But premature knowledge--knowing at the wrong time--is fatal both to progress and to happiness." -- Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874327-we-gladly-conform-to-the-people-s-needs-in-all-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 17:33:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Johann Martin Boltzius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/874327-we-gladly-conform-to-the-people-s-needs-in-all-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We gladly conform to the people's needs in all things if it can be done in conformity with the word of God and for the sake of God's kingdom." -- Johann Martin Boltzius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93436-when-we-put-god-first-all-other-things-fall-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 11:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93436-when-we-put-god-first-all-other-things-fall-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we put God first, all other things fall into their proper place or drop out of our lives." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885322-through-your-dress-and-appearance-you-can-show-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 14:30:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by For the Strength of Youth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885322-through-your-dress-and-appearance-you-can-show-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through your dress and appearance, you can show that you know how precious your body is. . . .

Show respect for the Lord and yourself by dressing appropriately for Church meetings and activities. This is especially important when attending sacrament services. Young men should dress with dignity when officiating in the ordinance of the sacrament.

If you are not sure what is appropriate to wear, study the words of the prophets, pray for guidance, and ask your parents or leaders for help. Your dress and appearance now will help you prepare for the time when you will go to the temple to make sacred covenants with God. Ask yourself, “Would I feel comfortable with my appearance if I were in the Lord’s presence?" -- For the Strength of Youth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885320-the-expression-follow-the-brethren-has-a-broader-meaning-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 14:40:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/885320-the-expression-follow-the-brethren-has-a-broader-meaning-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The expression “follow the Brethren” has a broader meaning than some would apply to it. It means not only to agree with the counsel given to the Church by the Brethren, but also to follow their example in appearance and deportment." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/884099-i-have-always-been-impressed-with-the-love-and-respect</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 14:42:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Glenn L. Pace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/884099-i-have-always-been-impressed-with-the-love-and-respect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always been impressed with the love and respect our Savior bestowed upon the women in His life. As we read about these associations, our focus is generally on what He taught them and the love and understanding He gave them. Have you ever considered the possibility that these women provided immense comfort to His burdened soul?" -- Glenn L. Pace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/900627-during-the-sixteen-years-i-served-as-the-secretary-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 20:38:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Francis M. Gibbons]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/900627-during-the-sixteen-years-i-served-as-the-secretary-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["During the sixteen years I served as the secretary to the First Presidency, I attended hundreds of meetings where President Hunter was in attendance. In the course of these meetings, President Hunter's voice was heard less frequently than almost any other. That is quite amazing when one considers the popular perception of lawyers as being verbose, but it is not to suggest that he sat mute in these meetings. He was always actively involved; however, he did not feel the need to be heard on every subject under discussion. When he did speak, what he said was thoughtful and analytical." -- Francis M. Gibbons]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/900213-throughout-his-ministry-jesus-gave-commandments-and-he-taught-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 20:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Dallin H. Oaks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/900213-throughout-his-ministry-jesus-gave-commandments-and-he-taught-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Throughout His ministry Jesus gave commandments. And He taught, “If ye love me, keep my commandments” (John 14:15; see also verses 21, 23). He affirmed that keeping His commandments would require His followers to leave what He called “that which is highly esteemed among men” (Luke 16:15) and “the tradition of men” (Mark 7:8; see also verse 13). He also warned, “If ye were of the world, the world would love his own: but because ye are not of the world, but I have chosen you out of the world, therefore the world hateth you” (John 15:19). As the Apostle Peter later declared, the followers of Jesus were to be “a peculiar people” (1 Peter 2:9).

Latter-day Saints understand that we should not be “of the world” or bound to “the tradition of men,” but like other followers of Christ, we sometimes find it difficult to separate ourselves from the world and its traditions. Some model themselves after worldly ways because, as Jesus said of some whom He taught, “they loved the praise of men more than the praise of God” (John 12:43). These failures to follow Christ are too numerous and too sensitive to list here. They range all the way from worldly practices like political correctness and extremes in dress and grooming to deviations from basic values like the eternal nature and function of the family.

Jesus’s teachings were not meant to be theoretical. . . .

Following Christ is not a casual or occasional practice but a continuous commitment and way of life that applies at all times and in all places." -- Dallin H. Oaks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910764-one-of-my-greatest-concerns-for-the-young-women-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 18:47:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Robert D. Hales]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/910764-one-of-my-greatest-concerns-for-the-young-women-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of my greatest concerns for the young women of the Church is that they will sell themselves short in dating and marriage by forgetting who they really are--daughters of a loving Heavenly Father. . . . Unfortunately, a young woman who lowers her standards far enough can always find temporary acceptance from immature and unworthy young men. . . .

At their best, daughters of God are loving, caring, understanding, and sympathetic. This does not mean they are also gullible, unrealistic, or easily manipulated. If a young man does not measure up to the standards a young woman has set, he may promise her that he will change if she will marry him first. Wise daughters of God will insist that young men who seek their hand in marriage change before the wedding, not after. (I am referring here to the kind of change that will be part of the lifelong growth of every disciple.) He may argue that she doesn't really believe in repentance and forgiveness. But one of the hallmarks of repentance is forsaking sin. Especially when the sin involves addictive behaviors or a pattern of transgression, wise daughters of God insist on seeing a sustained effort to forsake sin over a long period of time as true evidence of repentance. They do not marry someone because they believe they can change him. Young women, please do not settle for someone unworthy of your gospel standards.

On the other hand, young women should not refuse to settle down. There is no right age for young men or young women to marry, but there is a right attitude for them to have about marriage: &quot;Thy will be done&quot; . . . . The time to marry is when we are prepared to meet a suitable mate, not after we have done all the enjoyable things in life we hoped to do while we were single. . . .

When I hear some young men and young women set plans in stone which do not include marriage until after age twenty-five or thirty or until a graduate degree has been obtained, I recall Jacob's warning, &quot;Seek not to counsel the Lord, but to take counsel from his hand&quot; (Jacob 4:10). . . .

How we conduct ourselves in dating relationships is a good indication of how we will conduct ourselves in a marriage relationship. . . .

Individuals considering marriage would be wise to conduct their own prayerful due diligence--long before they set their hearts on marriage. There is nothing wrong with making a T-square diagram and on either side of the vertical line listing the relative strengths and weaknesses of a potential mate. I sometimes wonder whether doing more homework when it comes to this critical decision would spare some Church members needless heartache. I fear too many fall in love with each other or even with the idea of marriage before doing the background research necessary to make a good decision.

It is sad when a person who wants to be married never has the opportunity to marry. But it is much, much sadder to be married to the wrong person. If you do not believe me, talk with someone who has made that mistake. Think carefully about the person you are considering marrying, because marriage should last for time and for all eternity." -- Robert D. Hales]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/945131-a-persistent-preoccupation-with-freedom-of-speech-to-the-neglect</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 17:00:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/945131-a-persistent-preoccupation-with-freedom-of-speech-to-the-neglect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A persistent preoccupation with &quot;freedom of speech&quot; to the neglect of other freedoms can diminish the shelter available for religion and other precious freedoms. The intertwining of all our freedoms is greater than we realize. . . . It may be true . . . that the people of Sodom and Gomorrah had absolute free speech, but did they have anything worth saying?" -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/946053-obviously-the-most-enduring-way-to-make-this-commitment-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 17:29:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by George Gilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/946053-obviously-the-most-enduring-way-to-make-this-commitment-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Obviously the most enduring way to make this commitment is through marriage. Yet because sexual liberals deny the differences between the sexes, their explanations of why there are marriages and why marriage is needed and desired ignore the central truth of marriage: that it is built on sex roles. Pressed to explain the institution, they respond vaguely that human beings want &quot;structure&quot; or desire &quot;intimacy.&quot; But however desirable in marriage, these values are not essential causes or explanations of it.

In many cultures, the wife and husband share very few one-to-one intimacies. Ties with others of the same sex--or even the opposite sex--often offer deeper companionship. The most intimate connections are between mothers and their children. In all societies, male groups provide men with some of their most emotionally gratifying associations. Indeed, intimacy can deter or undermine wedlock. In the kibbutz, for example, where unrelated boys and girls are brought up together and achieve a profound degree of companionate feeling, they never marry members of the same child-rearing group. In the many cultures where marriages are arranged, the desire for intimacy is subversive of marriage.

Similarly, man's &quot;innate need for structure&quot; can be satisfied in hundreds of forms of organization. The need for structure may explain all of them or none of them, but it does not tell us why, of all possible arrangements, marriage is the one most prevalent. It does not tell us why, in most societies, marriage alone is consecrated in a religious ceremony and entails a permanent commitment.

As most anthropologists see it, however, the reason is simple. The very essence of marriage, Bronislaw Malinowski wrote, is not structure and intimacy; it is &quot;parenthood and above all maternity.&quot; The male role in marriage, as Margaret Mead maintained, &quot;in every known human society, is to provide for women and children.&quot; In order to marry, in fact, Malinowski says that almost every human society first requires the man &quot;to prove his capacity to maintain the woman.&quot;

Marriage is not simply a ratification of an existing love. It is the conversion of that love into a biological and social continuity. . . . Regardless of what reasons particular couples may give for getting married, the deeper evolutionary and sexual propensities explain the persistence of the institution. All sorts of superficial variations--from homosexual marriage to companionate partnership--may be played on the primal themes of human life. But the themes remain. The natural fulfillment of love is a child; the fantasies and projects of the childless couple may well be considered as surrogate children." -- George Gilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/969609-permissiveness-cannot-sustain-true-liberty-for-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 07:55:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/969609-permissiveness-cannot-sustain-true-liberty-for-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Permissiveness cannot sustain true liberty for long. . . . In Sodom they probably had absolute free speech, but nothing worth saying! On the other hand, an otherwise permissive society, which tolerates almost everything, usually will not tolerate speech that challenges its iniquity. Evil is always intolerantly preoccupied with its own perpetuation." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970010-funeral-sermon-02-08-1880-how-is-it-with-this-young-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2013 15:22:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by John Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970010-funeral-sermon-02-08-1880-how-is-it-with-this-young-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Funeral sermon, 02/08/1880]
How is it with this young man here? Well, I wish it were otherwise; I wish he had lived a very good Saint, which, however, he did not do. We have not come here to indulge in any kind of false sentimentality. He was a drunkard; that is a truth and many of you know it. . . . His father lived up to the Gospel, and died strong in the faith; and his mother has been a very good woman, so far as I know; I have never known anything against her. This boy has caused her a great deal of trouble; and I have been sorry for him. Well, should we tell things? Yes, always; that day is not far distant when the coverings will be taken from the face of all people, and we shall all stand naked, as it were, before God--both you and I and this young man. Well this boy,--I call him a boy, he is a young man, and is a nephew of mine by marriage; and I would not want to say anything about him on that account, neither would I falsify the young man on that account; but let us tell things and understand them as they are. . . .

I would say, I do not utter these things to cause any unpleasant feeling in the bosom of the family; they cannot help it. If I could have helped it, I would; if the mother could have helped it, she would; if the sister could have helped it, she would; if the friends could have helped it, they would. . . .

We are now talking not to the dead, but to the living. I would say, Let us avoid these evils, they lead down to death; let us seek to live our religion, to obey the laws of God and keep his commandments. And in regard to the future, we leave that in the hands of the Almighty who doeth all things well; and we will do all we can to promote the comfort of the living and the dead." -- John Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540307-to-whatever-degree-he-may-have-desacralized-the-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 13:34:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becky add a quote by Mircea Eliade]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540307-to-whatever-degree-he-may-have-desacralized-the-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To whatever degree he may have desacralized the world, the man who has made his choice in favor of a profane life never succeeds in completely doing away with religious behavior." -- Mircea Eliade]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
