<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/803405-ben]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/803405-ben" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:18:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32013-a-fire-broke-out-backstage-in-a-theatre-the-clown</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:18:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32013-a-fire-broke-out-backstage-in-a-theatre-the-clown]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A fire broke out backstage in a theatre. The clown came out to warn the public; they thought it was a joke and applauded. He repeated it; the acclaim was even greater. I think that's just how the world will come to an end: to general applause from wits who believe it's a joke." -- Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32014-for-every-bourgeois-in-the-heat-of-youth-if-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:22:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32014-for-every-bourgeois-in-the-heat-of-youth-if-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For every bourgeois, in the heat of youth, if only for a day, for a minute, has believed himself capable of immense passions, of heroic enterprises.  The most mediocre libertine has dreamed of oriental princesses; every rotary carries about inside him the debris of a poet." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32015-a-man-feared-a-man-feared-that-he-might-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:24:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Stephen Crane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32015-a-man-feared-a-man-feared-that-he-might-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A MAN FEARED

A man feared that he might find an assassin;
Another that he might find a victim.
One was more wise than the other." -- Stephen Crane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32016-as-long-as-we-re-young-we-manage-to-find-excuses</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:30:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32016-as-long-as-we-re-young-we-manage-to-find-excuses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as we're young, we manage to find excuses for the stoniest indifference, the most blatant caddishness, we put them down to emotional eccentricity or some sort of romantic inexperience.  But later on, when life shows us how much cunning, cruelty, and malice are required just to keep the body at ninety-eight point six, we catch on, we know the scene, we begin to understand how much swinishness it takes to make up a past.  Just take a close look at yourself and the degree of rottenness you've come to.  There's no mystery about it, no more room for fairy tales; if you've lived this long, it's because you've squashed any poetry you had in you." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32018-i-m-an-old-man-now-and-a-lonesome-man-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:33:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32018-i-m-an-old-man-now-and-a-lonesome-man-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm an old man now, and a lonesome man in Kansas / but not afraid / to speak my lonesomeness in a car, / because not only my lonesomeness / it's Ours, all over America, / O tender fellows --/ &amp; spoken lonesomeness is Prophecy / in the moon 100 years ago or in / the middle of Kansas now." -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32020-beauty-is-desired-in-order-that-it-may-be-befouled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:35:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Georges Bataille]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32020-beauty-is-desired-in-order-that-it-may-be-befouled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is desired in order that it may be befouled; not for its own sake, but for the joy brought by the certainty of profaining it." -- Georges Bataille]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32026-art-altogether-is-nothing-but-a-survival-skill-we-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:48:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32026-art-altogether-is-nothing-but-a-survival-skill-we-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art altogether is nothing but a survival skill, we should never lose sight of this fact, it is, time and again, just an attempt -- an attempt that seems touching even to our intellect -- to cope with this world and its revolting aspects, which, as we know, is invariably possible only by resorting to lies and falsehoods, to hyprocrisy and self-deception, Reger said.  These pictures are full of lies and falsehoods and full of hypocrisy and self-deception, there is nothing else in them if we disregard their often inspired artistry.  All these pictures, moreover, are an expression of man's absolute helplessness in coping with himself and with what surrounds him all his life.  That is what all these pictures express, this helplessness which, on the one hand, embarasses the intellect and, on the other hand, bewilders the same intellect and moves it to tears, Reger said." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32030-i-detest-the-idea-that-love-between-two-persons-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 07:56:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32030-i-detest-the-idea-that-love-between-two-persons-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I detest the idea that love between two persons can lead to salvation.  All my life I have fought against this oppressive type of relationship.  Instead, I believe in searching for a kind of love that somehow involves all of humanity." -- Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32066-1-did-the-people-of-viet-nam-use-lanterns-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 09:49:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Denise Levertov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32066-1-did-the-people-of-viet-nam-use-lanterns-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["1) Did the people of Viet Nam
use lanterns of stone?
2) Did they hold ceremonies
to reverence the opening of buds?
3) Were they inclined to quiet laughter?
4) Did they use bone and ivory,
jade and silver, for ornament?
5) Had they an epic poem?
6) Did they distinguish between speech and singing?

1) Sir, their light hearts turned to stone.
It is not remembered whether in gardens
stone lanterns illumined pleasant ways.
2) Perhaps they gathered once to delight in blossom,
but after the children were killed
there were no more buds.
3) Sir, laughter is bitter to the burned mouth.
4) A dream ago, perhaps.  Ornament is for joy.
All the bones were charred.
5) It is not remembered.  Remember,
most were peasants; their life
was in rice and bamboo.
When peaceful clouds were reflected in the paddies
and the water buffalo stepped surely along terraces,
maybe fathers told their sons old tales.
When bombs smashed those mirrors
there was time only to scream.
6) There is an echo yet
of their speech which was like a song.
It was reported their singing resembled
the flight of moths in moonlight.
Who can say?  It is silent now." -- Denise Levertov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113497-it-is-cruel-to-discover-one-s-mediocrity-only-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 18:50:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113497-it-is-cruel-to-discover-one-s-mediocrity-only-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is cruel to discover one's mediocrity only when it is too late.  It does not improve the temper." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113500-lots-of-men-are-like-that-their-artistic-leanings-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 18:54:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113500-lots-of-men-are-like-that-their-artistic-leanings-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lots of men are like that, their artistic leanings never go beyond a weakness for shapely thighs." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113501-there-is-no-longer-any-class-outside-the-class-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 18:58:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Fanny Howe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113501-there-is-no-longer-any-class-outside-the-class-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no longer any class outside the class of character, and no history to put your faith in.
You can actually live as if you have no culture, no perspective particular to a date in time.
You are an individual whose prime and solitary property is your own body.
Dying becomes a hell beyond all reason or justice in this ahistorical context." -- Fanny Howe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113502-people-are-terrible-they-can-bear-anything-anything-people-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 18:59:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113502-people-are-terrible-they-can-bear-anything-anything-people-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are terrible.  They can bear anything.  Anything!  People are hard and brutal.  And everyone is disposable.  Everyone!  That's the lesson." -- Rainer Werner Fassbinder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113503-girl-s-story-7-the-hard-to-please-momma-momma-i-got-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:02:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Gabrielle Burton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113503-girl-s-story-7-the-hard-to-please-momma-momma-i-got-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["GIRL'S STORY #7: THE HARD-TO-PLEASE MOMMA

Momma, I got a B, the daughter said.
Who got an A? Momma answered.
Momma, I showed in the track meet.
Who placed? Momma answered.
Momma, I placed in the track meet.
Who won? Momma answered.
The daughter was chosen Homecoming Queen, the daughter ran all the way home, Momma, Momma, the most wonderful thing happened, I was chosen attendant to the Homecoming Queen.
Who's Queen? Momma answered.
I am, said the daughter." -- Gabrielle Burton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113506-the-idea-of-the-family-as-a-protective-haven-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:05:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Nicola Field]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113506-the-idea-of-the-family-as-a-protective-haven-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The idea of the family as a protective haven is a myth, the family unit cannot provide the haven it promises.  On the contrary, we can never isolate ourselves from social and political relationships in the world.  The places we choose to hide are alawys inseparably connected to the real world, the world they actually might encounter in school, and for some, in neighborhoods.  It is not the failure, or the breakdown, of the family which causes our alienation, but the ever-disappointed hopes instilled in us as children.  These hopes are false dreams of being cocooned and of belonging." -- Nicola Field]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113511-i-ve-thought-of-myself-a-girl-on-several-occasions-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:15:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113511-i-ve-thought-of-myself-a-girl-on-several-occasions-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've thought of myself a girl on several occasions because I like to polish shoes and find household tasks amusing.  There was once even a time when I insisted on mending a torn suit with my own hands.  And in winter I always light the heating stoves myself, as though this were the natural course of things.  But of course I'm not a real girl.  Please give me a moment to consider all this would entail.  The first thing that comes to mind is the question of whether I might possibly be a girl has never, never, not for a single moment, troubled me, rattled my bourgeois composure or made me unhappy.  An absolutely by no means unhappy person stands before you, I'd like to put quite special emphasis on this, for I have never experienced sexual torment or distress, for I was never at a loss for quite simple methods of freeing myself from pressures.  A rather curious, that is to say, important discovery for me was that it filled me with the most delightful gaiety to imagine myself someone's servant....  My nature, then, merely inclines me to treat people well, to be helpful and so forth.  Not long ago I carried with flabbergasting zeal a shopping bag full of new potatoes for a petit bourgeoise.  She's have been perfectly able to tote it herself.  Now my situation is this: my particular nature also sometimes seeks, I've discovered, a mother, a teacher, that is, to express myself better, an unapproachable entity, a sort of goddess.  At times I find the goddess in an instant, whereas at others it takes time before I'm able to imagine her, that is, find her bright, bountiful figure and sense her power.  And to achieve a moment of human happiness, I must always first think up a story containing an encounter between myself and another person, whereby I am always the subordinate, obedient, sacrificing, scrutinized, and chaperoned party.  There's more to it, of course, quite a lot, but this still sheds light on a few things.  Many conclude it must be terribly easy to carry out a course of treatment, as it were, upon my person, but they're all gravely mistaken.  For, the moment anyone seems ready to start lording and lecturing it over me, something within me begins to laugh, to jeer, and then, of course, respect is out of the question, and within the apparently worthless individual arises a superior one whom I never expel when he appears in me...." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113513-we-have-often-had-this-particular-exchange-about-climate-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:18:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Fanny Howe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113513-we-have-often-had-this-particular-exchange-about-climate-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have often had this particular exchange about climate and landscape and why we both feel so lonely here uprooted.  It was what each of us had wanted of course.

Besides wanting to experience a place we hated, we wanted to be insomniacs and loners, losers and drop-outs.  To know the sky was the only location of meaning and joy left to us." -- Fanny Howe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113514-and-this-moral-as-with-the-deformed-aesop-morals-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:24:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by William Carlos Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113514-and-this-moral-as-with-the-deformed-aesop-morals-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this moral?  As with the deformed Aesop, morals are the memory of success that no longer succeeds." -- William Carlos Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113515-electra-weeping-for-the-dead-orestes-if-we-love-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:27:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Simone Weil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113515-electra-weeping-for-the-dead-orestes-if-we-love-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Electra weeping for the dead Orestes.  If we love God while thinking that he does not exist, he will manifest his existence." -- Simone Weil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113519-27-july-rage-thought-to-live-by-in-the-general-buster</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:30:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Guy Maddin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113519-27-july-rage-thought-to-live-by-in-the-general-buster]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["27 July

Rage-thought to live by: in &lt;i&gt;The General&lt;/i&gt;, Buster gets so annoyed at his girlfriend's stupidity for stoking the engine with tiny pieces of wood, he facetiously gives her little toothpicks - which she dutifully feeds into the fire.  He then stares at her in disbelief, then delights in her anyway and leaps at her with a kiss.  Sweet axiom!" -- Guy Maddin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113523-if-they-plato-and-aristotle-wrote-about-politics-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:34:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Blaise Pascal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113523-if-they-plato-and-aristotle-wrote-about-politics-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If they [Plato and Aristotle] wrote about politics it was as if to lay down rules for a madhouse.

And if they pretended to treat it as something really important it was because they knew that the madmen they were talking to believed themselves to be kings and emperors.  They humored these beliefs in order to calm down their madness with as little harm as possible." -- Blaise Pascal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113524-six-lines-i-know-that-in-this-world-no-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:38:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Aaron Zeitlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113524-six-lines-i-know-that-in-this-world-no-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Six Lines

I know that in this world no one needs me,
me, a word-beggar in the Jewish graveyard
Who needs a poem, especially in Yiddish?

Only what is hopeless on this earth has beauty
and only the ephemeral is godly
and humility is the only true rebellion" -- Aaron Zeitlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113525-doctor-spielvogel-it-alleviates-nothing-fixing-the-blame---blaming</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 19:47:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113525-doctor-spielvogel-it-alleviates-nothing-fixing-the-blame---blaming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Doctor Spielvogel, it alleviates nothing fixing the blame - blaming is still ailing, of course, of course - but nonetheless, what &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; it with these Jewish parents, &lt;i&gt;what&lt;/i&gt;, that they were able to make us little Jewish boys believe ourselves to be princes on the one hand, unique as unicorns on the one hand, geniuses and brilliant like nobody has ever been brilliant and beautiful before in the history of childhood - saviors and sheer perfection on the one hand, and such bumbling, incompetent, thoughtless, helpless, selfish, evil little shits, little &lt;i&gt;ingrates&lt;/i&gt;, on the other!" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214052-she-saw-that-the-world-was-evil-and-yet-craved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 12:58:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Laura Riding Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214052-she-saw-that-the-world-was-evil-and-yet-craved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She saw that the world was evil and yet craved for happines in it, which she thought to get by being evil herself.  And she had no more happiness than I have had -- who chose the other way.  There was something that was the same in each of us: we were alike in that we hated the world, and yet saw that it could not have been otherwise.  And we both tried to love in spite of this hate: perhaps she was more successful than I.  Therefore do not talk lightly of a new start.  Evil as the old things were, they were all that we had.  And if you feel that they are gone now, be sorrowful -- for it will be a long time before new things come to replace them, and we cannot say how much better they will be." -- Laura Riding Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214054-the-usual-heresy-consists-in-denying-the-existence-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 13:05:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Lars Gustafsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214054-the-usual-heresy-consists-in-denying-the-existence-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["     The usual heresy consists in denying the existence of a god who has created us.  It is a much more interesting heresy to imagine that possibly a god has created us and then to say that there isn't the least reason for us to be impressed by that fact.  And certainly not to be thankful for it." -- Lars Gustafsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214056-on-land-i-have-too-much-time-i-m-overwhelmed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 13:08:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Alvaro Mutis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214056-on-land-i-have-too-much-time-i-m-overwhelmed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On land I have too much time, I'm overwhelmed by a boredom that eventually paralyzes me.  But this isn't really the main reason for my suicide.  Even if I had another chance to go to sea, I know that for a long time I've been storing up something I can only define as a weariness with being alive, with having to choose between one thing and another, with listening to people around me talk about things that basically don't interest them, that they really know nothing about.  The foolishness of our fellow humans knows no bounds, my dear Gaviero.  If it didn't sound absurd, I'd say I'm leaving because I can't stand the noise the living make." -- Alvaro Mutis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214058-you-will-find-yourself-among-people-there-is-no-help</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 13:13:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Paul Bowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214058-you-will-find-yourself-among-people-there-is-no-help]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will find yourself among people.
There is no help for this
nor should you want it otherwise.
The passages where no one waits are dark
and hard to navigate.
The wet walls touch your shoulders on each side.
When the trees were there I cared that they were there.
And now they are gone, does it matter?
The passages where no one waits go on
and give no promise of an end.
You will find yourself among people,
Faces, clothing, teeth and hair
and words, and many words
When there was life, I said that life was wrong.
What do I say now?  You understand?" -- Paul Bowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214062-the-bees-sit-so-slothfully-on-the-flowers-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 13:26:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Georg Büchner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214062-the-bees-sit-so-slothfully-on-the-flowers-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bees sit so slothfully on the flowers, and the sunshine lies so lazily on the ground.  A horrible idleness prevails. -- Idleness is the root of all vice. -- What people won't do out of boredom!  They study out of boredom, they pray out of boredom, they fall in love, marry, and multiply out of boredom and finally die out of boredom, and -- and that's the humor in it -- they do everything with the most serious faces, without realizing why and with God knows what intentions.  All these heroes, these geniuses, these idiots, these saints, these sinners, these fathers of families are basically nothing but refined idlers.  -- Why must &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; be the one to know this?  Why can't I take myself seriously and dress this poor puppet in tails and put an umbrella in its hand so that it will become very proper and very useful and very moral?  That man who just left me -- I envied him, I could have beaten him out of envy.  Oh, to be someone else for once!  Just for a minute. -- How that man runs!  If only I knew of one thing under the sun that could still make me run." -- Georg Büchner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214063-unfulfilled-wish-a-woman-in-atzbach-was-murdered-by-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2009 13:29:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ben add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214063-unfulfilled-wish-a-woman-in-atzbach-was-murdered-by-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unfulfilled Wish

A woman in Atzbach was murdered by her husband because, in his opinion, she had carried the wrong child with her to safety from their burning house.  She had not saved their eight-year old son, for whom the man had special plans, but had saved their daughter, who was not loved by the husband.  When the husband was asked, in the District Court in Wels, what plans he had had for his son, who had been completely consumed by the fire, the husband replied that he had intended him to be an anarchist and a mass murderer of dictatorships and thus a destroyer of the state." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
