<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/803559-muna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/803559-muna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 11:48:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80769-there-is-always-a-certain-hour-of-the-day-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 11:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80769-there-is-always-a-certain-hour-of-the-day-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always a certain hour of the day and of the night when a man’s courage is at its lowest ebb, and it was that hour only that he feared." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61802-and-he-knew-also-what-the-old-man-was-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 11:49:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61802-and-he-knew-also-what-the-old-man-was-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And he knew, also, what the old man was thinking as his tears flowed, and he, Rieux, thought it too: that a loveless world is a dead world, and always there comes an hour when one is weary of prisons, of one's work, and of devotion to duty, and all one craves for is a loved face, the warmth and wonder of a loving heart." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80772-in-different-degrees-in-every-part-of-the-town-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 11:50:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80772-in-different-degrees-in-every-part-of-the-town-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In different degrees, in every part of the town, men and women had been yearning for a reunion, not of the same kind for all, but for all alike ruled out. Most of them had longed intensely for an absent one, for the warmth of a body, for love, or merely a life that habit had endeared. Some, often without knowing it, suffered from being deprived of the company of friends and from their inability to get in touch with them through the usual channels of friendship—letters, trains, and boats. Others, fewer these... had desired a reunion with something they couldn’t have defined, but which seemed to them the only desirable thing on earth. For want of a better name, they sometimes called it peace." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12890-death-is-always-on-the-way-but-the-fact-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2008 11:55:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Paul Bowles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12890-death-is-always-on-the-way-but-the-fact-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death is always on the way, but the fact that you don't know when it will arrive seems to take away from the finiteness of life. It's that terrible precision that we hate so much. But because we don't know, we get to think of life as an inexhaustible well. Yet everything happens a certain number of times, and a very small number, really. How many more times will you remember a certain afternoon of your childhood, some afternoon that's so deeply a part of your being that you can't even conceive of your life without it? Perhaps four or five times more. Perhaps not even. How many more times will you watch the full moon rise? Perhaps twenty. And yet it all seems limitless." -- Paul Bowles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95311-metaphor-a-tightly-fitting-suit-of-metal-generally-tin-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2008 20:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Chris Ware]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95311-metaphor-a-tightly-fitting-suit-of-metal-generally-tin-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["METAPHOR: A tightly fitting suit of metal, generally tin, which entirely encloses the wearer, both impeding free movement and preventing emotional expression and/or social contact." -- Chris Ware]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118893-what-i-m-sure-of-is-that-you-can-t-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 21:08:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118893-what-i-m-sure-of-is-that-you-can-t-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I'm sure of is that you can't be happy without money. That's all. I don't like superficiality and I don't like romanticism. I like to be conscious. And what I've noticed is that there's a kind of spiritual snobbism in certain 'superior beings' who think that money isn't necessary for happiness. Which is stupid, which is false, and to a certain degree cowardly.... For a man who is well born, being happy is never complicated. It's enough to take up the general fate, only not with the will for renunciation like so many fake great men, but with the will for happiness. Only it takes time to be happy. A lot of time. Happiness, too, is a long patience. And in almost every case, we use up our lives making money, when we should be using our money to gain time. That's the only problem that's ever interested me.... To have money is to have time. That's my main point. Time can be bought. Everything can be bought. To be or to become rich is to have time to be happy, if you deserve it.... Everything for happiness, against the world which surrounds us with its violence and its stupidity.... All the cruelty of our civilization can be measured by this one axiom: happy nations have no history." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85145-i-do-not-believe-in-god-and-i-am-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 22:27:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85145-i-do-not-believe-in-god-and-i-am-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not believe in God and I am not an atheist." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137706-beauty-is-unbearable-drives-us-to-despair-offering-us-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 22:27:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137706-beauty-is-unbearable-drives-us-to-despair-offering-us-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is unbearable, drives us to despair, offering us for a minute the glimpse of an eternity that we should like to stretch out over the whole of time." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114850-the-only-way-to-deal-with-an-unfree-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 22:31:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114850-the-only-way-to-deal-with-an-unfree-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to deal with an unfree world is to become so absolutely free that your very existence is an act of rebellion." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14170-never-make-a-decision-when-you-need-to-pee</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2009 22:31:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14170-never-make-a-decision-when-you-need-to-pee]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never make a decision when you need to pee." -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 11:27:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Muna add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5606-ideally-what-should-be-said-to-every-child-repeatedly-throughout]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ideally, what should be said to every child, repeatedly, throughout his or her school life is something like this: 'You are in the process of being indoctrinated. We have not yet evolved a system of education that is not a system of indoctrination. We are sorry, but it is the best we can do. What you are being taught here is an amalgam of current prejudice and the choices of this particular culture. The slightest look at history will show how impermanent these must be. You are being taught by people who have been able to accommodate themselves to a regime of thought laid down by their predecessors. It is a self-perpetuating system. Those of you who are more robust and individual than others will be encouraged to leave and find ways of educating yourself — educating your own judgements. Those that stay must remember, always, and all the time, that they are being moulded and patterned to fit into the narrow and particular needs of this particular society." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
