<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80510-becca]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80510-becca" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 08:28:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 08:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83895-it-was-love-at-first-sight-at-last-sight-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was love at first sight, at last sight, at ever and ever sight." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 08:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51844-i-think-it-is-all-a-matter-of-love-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 08:28:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51844-i-think-it-is-all-a-matter-of-love-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think it is all a matter of love; the more you love a memory the stronger and stranger it becomes" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:39:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the rest is rust and stardust." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136723-he-broke-my-heart-you-merely-broke-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:39:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136723-he-broke-my-heart-you-merely-broke-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He broke my heart. You merely broke my life." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65051-all-at-once-we-were-madly-clumsily-shamelessly-agonizingly-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:39:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65051-all-at-once-we-were-madly-clumsily-shamelessly-agonizingly-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All at once we were madly, clumsily, shamelessly, agonizingly in love with each other; hopelessly, I should add, because that frenzy of mutual possession might have been assuaged only by our actually imbibing and assimilating every particle of each other's soul and flesh; but there we were, unable even to mate as slum children would have so easily found an opportunity to do so." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221548-i-recall-certain-moments-let-us-call-them-icebergs-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:40:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221548-i-recall-certain-moments-let-us-call-them-icebergs-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recall certain moments, let us call them icebergs in paradise, when after having had my fill of her –after fabulous, insane exertions that left me limp and azure-barred–I would gather her in my arms with, at last, a mute moan of human tenderness (her skin glistening in the neon light coming from the paved court through the slits in the blind, her soot-black lashes matted, her grave gray eyes more vacant than ever–for all the world a little patient still in the confusion of a drug after a major operation)–and the tenderness would deepen to shame and despair, and I would lull and rock my lone light Lolita in my marble arms, and moan in her warm hair, and caress her at random and mutely ask her blessing, and at the peak of this human agonized selfless tenderness (with my soul actually hanging around her naked body and ready to repent), all at once, ironically, horribly, lust would swell again–and 'oh, no,' Lolita would say with a sigh to heaven, and the next moment the tenderness and the azure–all would be shattered." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358936-i-knew-i-had-fallen-in-love-with-lolita-forever</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:40:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358936-i-knew-i-had-fallen-in-love-with-lolita-forever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knew I had fallen in love with Lolita forever; but I also knew she would not be forever Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247476-i-shall-be-dumped-where-the-weed-decays-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:40:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247476-i-shall-be-dumped-where-the-weed-decays-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall be dumped where the weed decays, And the rest is rust and stardust" -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331282-i-looked-and-looked-at-her-and-i-knew-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:41:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331282-i-looked-and-looked-at-her-and-i-knew-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I looked and looked at her, and I knew, as clearly as I know that I will die, that I loved her more than anything I had ever seen or imagined on earth. She was only the dead-leaf echo of the nymphet from long ago - but I loved her, this Lolita, pale and polluted and big with another man's child. She could fade and wither - I didn't care. I would still go mad with tenderness at the mere sight of her face." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134984-my-carmen-i-said-i-used-to-call-her-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 07:41:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134984-my-carmen-i-said-i-used-to-call-her-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My Carmen,&quot; I said (I used to call her that sometimes) &quot;we shall leave this raw sore town as soon as you get out of bed.&quot;
     &quot;... Because, really,&quot; I continued, &quot;there is no point in staying here.&quot;
     &quot;There is no point in staying anywhere,&quot; said Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45233-the-first-ten-lies-they-tell-you-in-high-school</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:39:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45233-the-first-ten-lies-they-tell-you-in-high-school]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["THE FIRST TEN LIES THEY TELL YOU IN HIGH SCHOOL 

1. We are here to help you. 
2. You will have time to get to your class before the bell rings. 
3. The dress code will be enforced. 
4. No smoking is allowed on school grounds. 
5. Our football team will win the championship this year. 
6. We expect more of you here. 
7. Guidance counselors are always available to listen. 
8. Your schedule was created with you in mind. 
9. Your locker combination is private. 
10. These will be the years you look back on fondly. 

TEN MORE LIES THEY TELL YOU IN HIGH SCHOOL 

1. You will use algebra in your adult lives. 
2. Driving to school is a privilege that can be taken away. 
3. Students must stay on campus during lunch. 
4. The new text books will arrive any day now. 
5. Colleges care more about you than your SAT scores. 
6. We are enforcing the dress code. 
7. We will figure out how to turn off the heat soon. 
8. Our bus drivers are highly trained professionals. 
9. There is nothing wrong with summer school. 
10. We want to hear what you have to say." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/618444-he-was-my-tormentor-and-my-solace-the-creator-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 12:22:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Becca add a quote by CJ Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/618444-he-was-my-tormentor-and-my-solace-the-creator-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was my tormentor and my solace; the creator of the dark and the light within." -- CJ Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
