<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805215-mabel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805215-mabel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:22:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:22:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:24:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:27:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11864-i-m-not-upset-that-you-lied-to-me-i-m-upset</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:28:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11864-i-m-not-upset-that-you-lied-to-me-i-m-upset]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not upset that you lied to me, I'm upset that from now on I can't believe you." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27312-going-to-church-doesn-t-make-you-a-christian-any-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:28:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Billy Sunday]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27312-going-to-church-doesn-t-make-you-a-christian-any-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Going to church doesn’t make you a Christian any more than going to a garage makes you an automobile." -- Billy Sunday]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:29:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:34:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 01:38:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108834-there-are-so-many-fragile-things-after-all-people-break]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are so many fragile things, after all.  People break so easily, and so do dreams and hearts." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573751-if-nothing-saves-us-from-death-at-least-love-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2012 04:15:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573751-if-nothing-saves-us-from-death-at-least-love-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If nothing saves us from death, at least love should save us from life" -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162092-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 05:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mabel add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162092-it-s-come-at-last-she-thought-the-time-when-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's come at last,&quot; she thought, &quot;the time when you can no longer stand between your children and heartache.  When there wasn't enough food in the house you pretended that you weren't hungry so they could have more.  In the cold of a winter's night you got up and put your blanket on their bed so they wouldn't be cold.  You'd kill anyone who tried to harm them - I tried my best to kill that man in the hallway.  Then one sunny day, they walk out in all innocence and they walk right into the grief that you'd give your life to spare them from." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
