<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805526-travis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805526-travis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 08:13:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20593-gentlemen-you-can-t-fight-in-here-this-is-the-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 08:13:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Travis add a quote by Peter Sellers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20593-gentlemen-you-can-t-fight-in-here-this-is-the-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gentlemen, you can't fight in here!  This is the WAR ROOM!!!" -- Peter Sellers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112670-i-have-to-do-this-as-long-as-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2008 07:56:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Travis add a quote by Karl Kraus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112670-i-have-to-do-this-as-long-as-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have to do this, as long as it is at all possible; for if those who are obliged to look after commas had always made sure they were in the right place, then Shanghai would not be burning." -- Karl Kraus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45438-vogon-poetry-is-of-course-the-third-worst-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 12:34:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Travis add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45438-vogon-poetry-is-of-course-the-third-worst-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vogon poetry is of course, the third worst in the universe. 
The second worst is that of the Azgoths of Kria. During a recitation by their poet master Grunthos the Flatulent of his poem &quot;Ode to a Small Lump of Green Putty I Found in My Armpit One Midsummer Morning&quot; four of his audience died of internal haemorrhaging and the president of the Mid-Galactic Arts Nobbling Council survived by gnawing one of his own legs off. Grunthos was reported to have been &quot;disappointed&quot; by the poem's reception, and was about to embark on a reading of his 12-book epic entitled &quot;My Favourite Bathtime Gurgles&quot; when his own major intestine, in a desperate attempt to save humanity, leapt straight up through his neck and throttled his brain. 
The very worst poetry of all perished along with its creator, Paul Neil Milne Johnstone of Redbridge, in the destruction of the planet Earth. Vogon poetry is mild by comparison." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7518-since-feeling-is-first-who-pays-any-attention-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 14:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Travis add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7518-since-feeling-is-first-who-pays-any-attention-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["since feeling is first
who pays any attention
to the syntax of things
will never wholly kiss you;

wholly to be a fool
while Spring is in the world

my blood approves,
and kisses are a far better fate
than wisdom
lady i swear by all flowers. Don't cry
--the best gesture of my brain is less than
your eyelids' flutter which says

we are for eachother: then
laugh, leaning back in my arms
for life's not a paragraph

And death i think is no parenthesis" -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540355-he-walked-straight-out-of-college-into-the-waiting-arms</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2012 10:14:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Travis add a quote by Neal Stephenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540355-he-walked-straight-out-of-college-into-the-waiting-arms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He walked straight out of college into the waiting arms of the Navy. 

They gave him an intelligence test. The first question on the math part had to do with boats on a river: Port Smith is 100 miles upstream of Port Jones. The river flows at 5 miles per hour. The boat goes through water at 10 miles per hour. How long does it take to go from Port Smith to Port Jones? How long to come back?

Lawrence immediately saw that it was a trick question. You would have to be some kind of idiot to make the facile assumption that the current would add or subtract 5 miles per hour to or from the speed of the boat. Clearly, 5 miles per hour was nothing more than the average speed. The current would be faster in the middle of the river and slower at the banks. More complicated variations could be expected at bends in the river. Basically it was a question of hydrodynamics, which could be tackled using certain well-known systems of differential equations. Lawrence dove into the problem, rapidly (or so he thought) covering both sides of ten sheets of paper with calculations. Along the way, he realized that one of his assumptions, in combination with the simplified Navier Stokes equations, had led him into an exploration of a particularly interesting family of partial differential equations. Before he knew it, he had proved a new theorem. If that didn't prove his intelligence, what would?

Then the time bell rang and the papers were collected. Lawrence managed to hang onto his scratch paper. He took it back to his dorm, typed it up, and mailed it to one of the more approachable math professors at Princeton, who promptly arranged for it to be published in a Parisian mathematics journal.

Lawrence received two free, freshly printed copies of the journal a few months later, in San Diego, California, during mail call on board a large ship called the U.S.S. Nevada. The ship had a band, and the Navy had given Lawrence the job of playing the glockenspiel in it, because their testing procedures had proven that he was not intelligent enough to do anything else." -- Neal Stephenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
