<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805590-alexander-popov]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805590-alexander-popov" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:15:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607031-a-book-is-a-machine-to-think-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:15:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by I.A. Richards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607031-a-book-is-a-machine-to-think-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book is a machine to think with." -- I.A. Richards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607032-great-short-stories-and-great-jokes-have-a-lot-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607032-great-short-stories-and-great-jokes-have-a-lot-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great short stories and great jokes have a lot in common. Both depend on what communication-theorists sometimes call “exformation,” which is a certain quantity of vital information removed from but evoked by a communication in such a way as to cause a kind of explosion of associative connections within the recipient. This is probably why the effect of both short stories and jokes often feels sudden and percussive, like the venting of a long-stuck valve." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607033-call-themselves-asked-yama-you-are-wrong-sam-godhood-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Roger Zelazny]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607033-call-themselves-asked-yama-you-are-wrong-sam-godhood-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Call themselves?&quot; asked Yama. &quot;You are wrong, Sam, Godhood is more than a name. It is a condition of being. One does not achieve it merely by being immortal, for even the lowliest laborer in the fields may achieve continuity of existence. Is it then the conditioning of an Aspect? No. Any competent hypnotist can play games with the self-image. Is it the raising up of an Attribute? Of course not. I can design machines more powerful and more accurate than any faculty a man may cultivate. Being a god is the quality of being able to be yourself to such an extent that your passions correspond with the forces of the universe, so that those who look upon you know this without hearing your name spoken. Some ancient poet said that the world is full of echoes and correspondences. Another wrote a long poem of an inferno, wherein each man suffered a torture which coincided in nature with those forces which had ruled his life. Being a god is being able to recognize within one's self these things that are important, and then to strike the single note that brings them into alignment with everything else that exists. Then, beyond morals or logic or esthetics, one is wind or fire, the sea, the mountains, rain, the sun or the stars, the flight of an arrow, the end of a day, the clasp of love. One rules through one's ruling passions. Those who look upon gods then say, without even knowing their names, 'He is Fire. She is Dance. He is Destruction. She is Love.' So, to reply to your statement, they do not call themselves gods. Everyone else does, though, everyone who beholds them.&quot;
&quot;So they play that on their fascist banjos, eh?&quot;
&quot;You choose the wrong adjective.&quot;
&quot;You've already used up all the others." -- Roger Zelazny]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607035-let-us-say-that-science-fiction-is-a-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Adam Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607035-let-us-say-that-science-fiction-is-a-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us say that science fiction is a kind of conceptual disorientation of the familiar." -- Adam Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607037</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:19:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Учебник по право]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607037]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Форфетингът е сконтиране на авалирани или акцептирани менителнични ефекти с ректа джиро за кредитиране на продавача с поемане на кредитния риск." -- Учебник по право]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607040-these-things-happen-one-day-you-run-everything-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:20:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Hunter Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607040-these-things-happen-one-day-you-run-everything-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These things happen. One day you run everything, and the next day
you run like a dog." -- Hunter Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369-a-human-being-is-a-part-of-the-whole-called</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/369-a-human-being-is-a-part-of-the-whole-called]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being is a part of the whole called by us universe, a part limited in time and space. He experiences himself, his thoughts and feeling as something separated from the rest, a kind of optical delusion of his consciousness. This delusion is a kind of prison for us, restricting us to our personal desires and to affection for a few persons nearest to us. Our task must be to free ourselves from this prison by widening our circle of compassion to embrace all living creatures and the whole of nature in its beauty." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607041-let-others-probe-the-mystery-if-they-can-time-harried-prisoners</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:22:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Theodore Roethke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607041-let-others-probe-the-mystery-if-they-can-time-harried-prisoners]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let others probe the mystery if they can. 
Time-harried prisoners of Shall and Will- 
The right thing happens to the happy man. 

The bird flies out, the bird flies back again; 
The hill becomes the valley, and is still; 
Let others delve that mystery if they can. 

God bless the roots! -Body and soul are one 
The small become the great, the great the small; 
The right thing happens to the happy man. 

Child of the dark, he can out leap the sun, 
His being single, and that being all: 
The right thing happens to the happy man. 

Or he sits still, a solid figure when 
The self-destructive shake the common wall; 
Takes to himself what mystery he can, 

And, praising change as the slow night comes on, 
Wills what he would, surrendering his will 
Till mystery is no more: No more he can. 
The right thing happens to the happy man." -- Theodore Roethke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22203-he-not-busy-being-born-is-busy-dying</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 03:22:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22203-he-not-busy-being-born-is-busy-dying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He not busy being born is busy dying." -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48084-so-in-america-when-the-sun-goes-down-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 04:49:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48084-so-in-america-when-the-sun-goes-down-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So in America when the sun goes down and I sit on the old broken-down river pier watching the long, long skies over New Jersey and sense all that raw land that rolls in one unbelievable huge bulge over to the West Coast, and all that road going, and all the people dreaming in the immensity of it, and in Iowa I know by now the children must be crying in the land where they let the children cry, and tonight the stars'll be out, and don't you know that God is Pooh Bear? the evening star must be drooping and shedding her sparkler dims on the prairie, which is just before the coming of complete night that blesses the earth, darkens all the rivers, cups the peaks and folds the final shore in, and nobody, nobody knows what's going to happen to anybody besides the forlorn rags of growing old, I think of Dean Moriarty, I even think of Old Dean Moriarty the father we never found, I think of Dean Moriarty." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607058-s-m-i-l-e</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 04:55:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Timothy Leary]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/607058-s-m-i-l-e]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["S.M.I.²L.E." -- Timothy Leary]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4413-we-look-for-the-secret---the-philosopher-s-stone-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:19:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4413-we-look-for-the-secret---the-philosopher-s-stone-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We look for the Secret - the Philosopher's Stone, the Elixir of the Wise, Supreme Enlightenment, 'God' or whatever...and all the time it is carrying us about...It is the human nervous system itself." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50980-i-don-t-believe-anything-but-i-have-many-suspicions</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:19:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50980-i-don-t-believe-anything-but-i-have-many-suspicions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't believe anything, but I have many suspicions." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79199-is-is-is-the-idiocy-of-the-word-haunts-me-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79199-is-is-is-the-idiocy-of-the-word-haunts-me-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is,&quot; &quot;is,&quot; &quot;is&quot;—the idiocy of the word haunts me. If it were abolished, human thought might begin to make sense. I don't know what anything &quot;is&quot;; I only know how it &lt;/i&gt;seems to me at this moment&lt;/i&gt;." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50983-human-beings-live-in-their-myths-they-only-endure-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:19:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50983-human-beings-live-in-their-myths-they-only-endure-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings live in their myths.  They only endure their realities." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62640-reality-is-what-you-can-get-away-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 03:20:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62640-reality-is-what-you-can-get-away-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is what you can get away with." -- Robert Anton Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615678-there-are-seven-levels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2012 13:51:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Paul McCartney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615678-there-are-seven-levels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are seven levels!" -- Paul McCartney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443071-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 03:09:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/443071-i-learned-this-at-least-by-my-experiment-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I learned this, at least, by my experiment: that if one advances confidently in the direction of his dreams, and endeavors to live the life which he has imagined, he will meet with a success unexpected in common hours. He will put some things behind, will pass an invisible boundary; new, universal, and more liberal laws will begin to establish themselves around and within him; or the old laws be expanded, and interpreted in his favor in a more liberal sense, and he will live with the license of a higher order of beings. In proportion as he simplifies his life, the laws of the universe will appear less complex, and solitude will not be solitude, nor poverty poverty, nor weakness weakness. If you have built castles in the air, your work need not be lost; that is where they should be. Now put the foundations under them." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82031-if-the-day-and-night-are-such-that-you-greet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2012 03:10:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82031-if-the-day-and-night-are-such-that-you-greet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the day and night are such that you greet them with joy, and life emits a fragrance like flowers and sweet-scented herbs, is more elastic, more starry, more immortal - that is your success." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690050-indeed-but-no-sand-this-time-so-the-lever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 02:26:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690050-indeed-but-no-sand-this-time-so-the-lever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed ... but no sand this time, so the lever goes up into fourth, and now there's no sound except wind. Screw
it all the way over, reach through the handlebars to raise the headlight beam, the needle leans down on a hundred, and wind-burned eyeballs strain to see down the centerline, trying to provide a margin for the reflexes.

But with the throttle screwed on there is only the barest margin, and no room at all for mistakes. It has to be done right ... and that's when the strange music starts, when you stretch your luck so far that fear becomes exhilaration and vibrates along your arms. You can barely see at a hundred; the tears blow back so fast that they vaporize before they get to your ears. The only sounds are wind and a dull roar floating back from the mufflers. You watch the white line and try to lean with it ... howling through a turn to the right, then to the left and down the long hill to Pacifica ... letting off now, watching for cops, but only until the next dark stretch and another few seconds on the edge ... The Edge ... There is no honest way to explain it because the only people who really know where it is are the ones who have gone over. The others --  the living -- are those who pushed their control as far as they felt they could handle it, and then pulled back, or slowed down, or did whatever they had to when it came time to choose between Now and Later.

But the edge is still Out there. Or maybe it's In. The association of motorcycles with LSD is no accident of publicity. They are both a means to an end, to the place of definitions." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 06:16:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5907-our-imagination-flies----we-are-its-shadow-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our imagination flies -- we are its shadow on the earth." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16110-the-only-important-elements-in-any-society-are-the-artistic</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 08:58:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Samuel R. Delany]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16110-the-only-important-elements-in-any-society-are-the-artistic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only important elements in any society are the artistic and the criminal, because they alone, by questioning the society’s values, can force it to change." -- Samuel R. Delany]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 03:08:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972701-one-can-distinguish-several-types-of-inspiration-which-intergrade-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 01:47:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972701-one-can-distinguish-several-types-of-inspiration-which-intergrade-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One can distinguish several types of inspiration, which intergrade, as all things do in this fluid and interesting world of ours, while yielding gracefully to a semblance of classification. A prefatory glow, not unlike some benign variety of the aura before an epileptic attack, is something the artist learns to perceive very early in life. This feeling of tickly well-being branches through him like the red and the blue in the picture of a skinned man under Circulation. As it spreads, it banishes all awareness of physical discomfort — youth’s toothache as well as the neuralgia of old age. The beauty of it is that, while completely intelligible (as if it were connected with a known gland or led to an expected climax), it has neither source nor object. It expands, glows, and subsides without revealing its secret. In the meantime, however, a window has opened, an auroral wind has blown, every exposed nerve has tingled. Presently all dissolves: the familiar worries are back and the eyebrow redescribes its arc
of pain; but the artist knows he is ready." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972823-you-are-right-sahara-there-are-no-mists-or-veils</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 06:09:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Leonard Cohen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972823-you-are-right-sahara-there-are-no-mists-or-veils]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are right, Sahara. There are no mists, or veils, or distances. But the mist is surrounded by a mist; and the veil is hidden behind a veil; and the distance continually draws away from the distance. That is why there are no mists, or veils, or distances. That is why it is called The Great Distance of Mist and Veils. It is here that The Traveler becomes The Wanderer, and The Wanderer becomes The One Who Is Lost, and The One Who Is Lost becomes The Seeker, and The Seeker becomes The Passionate Lover, and The Passionate Lover becomes The Beggar, and The Beggar becomes The Wretch, and The Wretch becomes The One Who Must Be Sacrificed, and The One Who Must Be Sacrificed becomes The Resurrected One and The Resurrected One becomes The One Who has Transcended The Great Distance of Mist and Veils. Then for a thousand years, or the rest of the afternoon, such a One spins in the Blazing Fire of Changes, embodying all the transformations, one after the other, and then beginning again, and then ending again, 86,000 times a second. Then such a one, if he is a man, is ready to love the woman Sahara; and such a one, if she is a woman, is ready to love the man who can put into song The Great Distance of Mist and Veils. Is it you who are waiting, Sahara, or is it I?" -- Leonard Cohen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 00:25:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135242-and-the-rest-is-rust-and-stardust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the rest is rust and stardust." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/550531-what-reconciles-me-to-my-own-death-more-than-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2014 02:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alexander add a quote by John Berger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/550531-what-reconciles-me-to-my-own-death-more-than-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What reconciles me to my own death more than anything else is the image of a place: a place where your bones and mine are buried, thrown, uncovered, together. They are strewn there pell-mell. One of your ribs leans against my skull. A metacarpal of my left hand lies inside your pelvis. (Against my broken ribs your breast like a flower.) The hundred bones of our feet are scattered like gravel. It is strange that this image of our proximity, concerning as it does mere phosphate of calcium, should bestow a sense of peace. Yet it does. With you I can imagine a place where to be phosphate of calcium is enough." -- John Berger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
