<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805933-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/805933-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 12:16:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15196-she-s-in-tenth-grade-he-said-i-hear-she-s-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 12:16:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15196-she-s-in-tenth-grade-he-said-i-hear-she-s-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She's in tenth grade,' he said. 'I hear she's been homeschooled till now.'
Maybe that explains it,' I said." -- Jerry Spinelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15197-a-kiss-about-apple-pie-a-la-mode-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 12:17:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15197-a-kiss-about-apple-pie-a-la-mode-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A kiss about apple pie a la mode with the vanilla creaminess melting in the pie heat. A kiss about chocolate, when you haven't eaten chocolate in a year. A kiss about palm trees speeding by, trailing pink clouds when you drive down the Strip sizzling with champagne. A kiss about spotlights fanning the sky and the swollen sea spilling like tears all over your legs." -- Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334-do-you-know-a-cure-for-me-why-yes-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 11:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Isak Dinesen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/334-do-you-know-a-cure-for-me-why-yes-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know a cure for me?&quot;

Why yes,&quot; he said, &quot;I know a cure for everything. Salt water.&quot;

Salt water?&quot; I asked him.

Yes,&quot; he said, &quot;in one way or the other. Sweat, or tears, or the salt sea." -- Isak Dinesen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8080-the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-adverbs</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 16:17:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8080-the-road-to-hell-is-paved-with-adverbs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road to hell is paved with adverbs." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494874-the-robin-flew-from-his-swinging-spray-of-ivy-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 16:00:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494874-the-robin-flew-from-his-swinging-spray-of-ivy-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The robin flew from his swinging spray of ivy on to the top of the wall and he opened his beak and sang a loud, lovely trill, merely to show off. Nothing in the world is quite as adorably lovely as a robin when he shows off - and they are nearly always doing it." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 16:50:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447207-the-world-will-know-and-understand-me-someday-but-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2012 15:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by George Sand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/447207-the-world-will-know-and-understand-me-someday-but-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world will know and understand me someday. But if that day does not arrive, it does not greatly matter. I shall have opened the way for other women." -- George Sand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827997-religion-may-not-be-something-you-approve-of-and-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 18:52:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Sharon Astyk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827997-religion-may-not-be-something-you-approve-of-and-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion may not be something you approve of, and that's just fine. But agrarian religious culture is going to be powerful.  If you think all religious people are the same, that religion is the cause of all problems and religious people are idiots, that's your privilege; but shut up about it.  As we’re less and less able to control our future, more and more people going to praying in their foxholes, maybe even you.  Get over it, and stop feeling superior.
And if you reject religion and don't want to see it flourish but you aren't working to provide community support, food for the hungry, care for the sick and dying, festivals of celebration and release, and a way to think about why the world of so screwed up, then expect to spend a lot of time wondering why you aren't as successful as religious groups.  Don't blame it on religion – blame it on the fact that you aren't very good a doing the things that religion does very well for many of us." -- Sharon Astyk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217302-the-most-confused-we-ever-get-is-when-we-re-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 21:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217302-the-most-confused-we-ever-get-is-when-we-re-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most confused we ever get is when we're trying to convince our heads of something our heart knows is a lie." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
