<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80608-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80608-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:32:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70023-clearly-the-secret-of-happiness-is-a-variation-on-the-general</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:32:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Stef Penney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70023-clearly-the-secret-of-happiness-is-a-variation-on-the-general]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clearly the secret of happiness...is a variation on the general principle of banging your head against a wall, and then stopping." -- Stef Penney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11475-nothing-thicker-than-a-knife-s-blade-separates-happiness-from-melancholy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:33:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11475-nothing-thicker-than-a-knife-s-blade-separates-happiness-from-melancholy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing thicker than a knife's blade separates happiness from melancholy." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160452-so-as-a-seventh-grader-no-you-weren-t-friends-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 08:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Lauren Myracle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160452-so-as-a-seventh-grader-no-you-weren-t-friends-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So as a seventh grader, no, you weren't friends with people you didn't like. But sometimes you also weren't friends with people you did like, which was complicated, and which didn't make any sense if you tried to explain it. Sometimes things just changed. That's where the sadness came in." -- Lauren Myracle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47078-i-went-to-a-tattoo-parlor-and-had-yes-written</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 08:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47078-i-went-to-a-tattoo-parlor-and-had-yes-written]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to a tattoo parlor and had YES written onto the palm of my left hand, and NO onto my right palm, what can I say, it hasn't made my life wonderful, its made life possible, when I rub my hands against each other in the middle of winter I am warming myself with the friction of YES and NO, when I clap my hands I am showing my appreciation through the uniting and parting of YES and NO, I signify &quot;book&quot; by peeling open my hands, every book, for me, is the balance of YES and NO, even this one, my last one, especially this one. Does it break my heart, of course, every moment of every day, into more pieces than my heart was made of, I never thought of myself as quiet, much less silent, I never thought about things at all, everything changed, the distance that wedged itself between me and my happiness wasn't the world, it wasn't the bombs and burning buildings, it was me, my thinking, the cancer of never letting go, is ignorance bliss, I don't know, but it's so painful to think, and tell me, what did thinking ever do for me, to what great place did thinking ever bring me? I think and think and think, I've thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10708-in-his-blue-gardens-men-and-girls-came-and-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:53:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10708-in-his-blue-gardens-men-and-girls-came-and-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his blue gardens men and girls came and went like moths among the whisperings and the champagne and the stars." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:53:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There must have been moments even that afternoon when Daisy tumbled short of his dreams -- not through her own fault, but because of the colossal vitality of his illusion. It had gone beyond her, beyond everything. He had thrown himself into it with a creative passion, adding to it all the time, decking it out with every bright feather that drifted his way. No amount of fire or freshness can challenge what a man will store up in his ghostly heart." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101795-think-how-you-love-me-she-whispered-i-don-t-ask</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 20:57:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101795-think-how-you-love-me-she-whispered-i-don-t-ask]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think how you love me,' she whispered. 'I don't ask you to love me always like this, but I ask you to remember.'

You'll always be like this to me.'

Oh no; but promise me you'll remember.' Her tears were falling. 'I'll be different, but somewhere lost inside me there'll always be the person I am tonight." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50199-i-do-not-so-much-write-a-book-as-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 13:27:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50199-i-do-not-so-much-write-a-book-as-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not so much write a book as sit up with it, as a dying friend.  I hold its hand and hope it will get better." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41083-many-writers-do-little-else-but-sit-in-small-rooms</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 13:27:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41083-many-writers-do-little-else-but-sit-in-small-rooms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many writers do little else but sit in small rooms recalling the real world." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25590-it-is-no-less-difficult-to-write-a-sentence-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 13:28:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25590-it-is-no-less-difficult-to-write-a-sentence-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is no less difficult to write a sentence in a recipe than sentences in Moby Dick.  So you might as well write Moby Dick." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50196-out-of-a-human-population-on-earth-of-four-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 13:31:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50196-out-of-a-human-population-on-earth-of-four-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of a human population on earth of four and a half billion, perhaps twenty people can write a book in a year.  Some people lift cars, too.  Some people enter week-long sled-dog races, go over Niagara Falls in a barrel, fly planes through the Arc de Triomphe.  Some people feel no pain in childbirth.  Some people eat cars.  There is no call to take human extremes as norms." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217111-there-is-neither-a-proportional-relationship-nor-an-inverse-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 13:32:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217111-there-is-neither-a-proportional-relationship-nor-an-inverse-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither a proportional relationship, nor an inverse one, between a writer’s estimation of a work in progress &amp; its actual quality. The feeling that the work is magnificent, &amp; the feeling that it is abominable, are both mosquitoes to be repelled, ignored, or killed, but not indulged." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179680-you-couldn-t-make-yourself-stop-feeling-a-certain-way-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 22:18:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179680-you-couldn-t-make-yourself-stop-feeling-a-certain-way-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You couldn't make yourself stop feeling a certain way, no matter what the other person did. You had to just wait. Eventually the feeling went away because others came along. Or sometimes it didn't go away but got squeezed into something tiny, and hung like a piece of tinsel in the back of your mind." -- Elizabeth Strout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 08:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Saul Bellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27147-you-never-have-to-change-anything-you-got-up-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never have to change anything you got up in the middle of the night to write." -- Saul Bellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22057-that-kind-of-thinking-that-writers-must-alleviate-their-guilt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 09:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ariel Gore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22057-that-kind-of-thinking-that-writers-must-alleviate-their-guilt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That kind of thinking [that writers must alleviate their guilt for leading a creative life] is based on the idea that the creative life is somehow self-indulgent. Artists and writers have to understand and live the truth that what we are doing is nourishing the world. William Carlos Williams said, &quot;It is difficult to get the news from poems yet men die miserably every day for lack of what is found there.&quot; You can't eat a book, right, but books have saved my life more often than sandwiches. And they've saved your life... But we don't say, oh, Maya Angelou should have silenced herself because other people have other destinies. It's interesting, because artists are always encouraged to feel guilty about their work. Why? Why don't we ask predatory bankers how they alleviate their guilt? " -- Ariel Gore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117992-a-guy-and-a-girl-can-be-just-friends-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 19:42:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117992-a-guy-and-a-girl-can-be-just-friends-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A guy and a girl can be just friends, but at one point or another, they will fall for each other...Maybe temporarily, maybe at the wrong time, maybe too late, or maybe forever" -- Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 18:54:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He awoke each morning with the desire to do right, to be a good and meaningful person, to be, as simple as it sounded and as impossible as it actually was, happy. And during the course of each day his heart would descend from his chest into his stomach. By early afternoon he was overcome by the feeling that nothing was right, or nothing was right for him, and by the desire to be alone. By evening he was fulfilled: alone in the magnitude of his grief, alone in his aimless guilt, alone even in his loneliness. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad,&lt;/i&gt; he would repeat to himself over and over, &lt;i&gt;I am not sad&lt;/i&gt;. As if he might one day convince himself. Or fool himself. Or convince others--the only thing worse than being sad is for others to know that you are sad. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad. I am not sad. &lt;/i&gt;Because his life had unlimited potential for happiness, insofar as it was an empty white room. He would fall asleep with his heart at the foot of his bed, like some domesticated animal that was no part of him at all. And each morning he would wake with it again in the cupboard of his rib cage, having become a little heavier, a little weaker, but still pumping. And by the midafternoon he was again overcome with the desire to be somewhere else, someone else, someone else somewhere else. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 18:57:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723-it-is-not-often-that-someone-comes-along-who-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 18:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723-it-is-not-often-that-someone-comes-along-who-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not often that someone comes along who is a true friend and a good writer." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130154-you-have-been-my-friend-that-in-itself-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 18:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by E. B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130154-you-have-been-my-friend-that-in-itself-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been my friend. That in itself is a tremendous thing. I wove my webs for you because I liked you. After all, what's a life, anyway? We're born, we live a little while, we die. A spider's life can't help being something of a mess, with all this trapping and eating flies. By helping you, perhaps I was trying to lift up my life a trifle. Heaven knows anyone's life can stand a little of that." -- E. B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161883-wilbur-never-forgot-charlotte-although-he-loved-her-children-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 19:00:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161883-wilbur-never-forgot-charlotte-although-he-loved-her-children-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wilbur never forgot Charlotte. Although he loved her children and grandchildren dearly, none of the new spiders ever quite took her place in his heart. She was in a class by herself. It is not often that someone comes along who is a true friend and a good writer. Charlotte was both." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154161-the-subtlest-change-in-new-york-is-something-people-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 19:01:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154161-the-subtlest-change-in-new-york-is-something-people-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The subtlest change in New York is something people don't speak much about but that is in everyone's mind. The city, for the first time in its long history, is destructible. A single flight of planes no bigger than a wedge of geese can quickly end this island fantasy, burn the towers, crumble the bridges, turn the underground passages into lethal chambers, cremate the millions. The intimation of mortality is part of New York now: in the sound of jets overhead, in the black headlines of the latest edition. (Written in 1949, 22 years before the World Trade Center was completed.)" -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24837-never-apologize-for-showing-feeling-when-you-do-so-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:11:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24837-never-apologize-for-showing-feeling-when-you-do-so-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never apologize for showing feeling. When you do so, you apologize for the truth." -- Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27526-i-have-lost-friends-some-by-death-others-by-sheer-inability</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27526-i-have-lost-friends-some-by-death-others-by-sheer-inability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have lost friends, some by death...others by sheer inability to cross the street." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22133-but-then-anyone-who-s-worth-anything-reads-just-what-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:23:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22133-but-then-anyone-who-s-worth-anything-reads-just-what-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But then anyone who's worth anything reads just what he likes, as the mood takes him, and with extravagant enthusiasm." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66784-the-beauty-of-the-world-has-two-edges-one-of-laughter</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:25:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66784-the-beauty-of-the-world-has-two-edges-one-of-laughter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beauty of the world...has two edges, one of laughter, one of anguish, cutting the heart asunder." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110359-dreams-are-always-crushing-when-they-don-t-come-true-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110359-dreams-are-always-crushing-when-they-don-t-come-true-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dreams are always crushing when they don't come true.  But it's the simple dreams that are often the most painful because they seem so personal, so reasonable, so attainable. You're always close enough to touch, but never quite close enough to hold and it's enough to break your heart." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:32:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82437-you-ll-get-over-it-it-s-the-clich-s-that-cause-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ll get over it…” It’s the clichés that cause the trouble. To lose someone you love is to alter your life for ever. You don’t get over it because ‘it” is the person you loved. The pain stops, there are new people, but the gap never closes. How could it? The particularness of someone who mattered enough to grieve over is not made anodyne by death. This hole in my heart is in the shape of you and no-one else can fit it. Why would I want them to?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10521-if-pain-must-come-may-it-come-quickly-because-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 09:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10521-if-pain-must-come-may-it-come-quickly-because-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If pain must come, may it come quickly. Because I have a life to live, and I need to live it in the best way possible. If he has to make a choice, may he make it now. Then I will either wait for him or forget him." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 20:47:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7139-do-not-let-your-fire-go-out-spark-by-irreplaceable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not let your fire go out, spark by irreplaceable spark in the hopeless swamps of the not-quite, the not-yet, and the not-at-all. Do not let the hero in your soul perish in lonely frustration for the life you deserved and have never been able to reach. The world you desire can be won. It exists.. it is real.. it is possible.. it's yours." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
