<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80638-b]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/80638-b" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 10:52:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385478-sarcasm-and-jokes-were-often-the-bottle-in-which-clinical</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2013 10:52:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[b add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385478-sarcasm-and-jokes-were-often-the-bottle-in-which-clinical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sarcasm and jokes were often the bottle in which clinical depressives sent out their most plangent screams for someone to care and help them." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268959-his-master-plan-to-get-them-all-out-the-door</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2013 16:42:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[b add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268959-his-master-plan-to-get-them-all-out-the-door]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His master plan to get them all out the door early met its first check of the day when he opened his closet door to discover that Zap the Cat, having penetrated the security of Vorkosigan House through Miles's quisling cook, had made a nest on the floor among his boots and fallen clothing to have kittens. Six of them.
Zap ignored his threats about the dire consequences of attacking an Imperial Auditor, and purred and growled from the dimness in her usual schizophrenic fashion. Miles gathered his nerve and rescued his best boots and House uniform, at a cost of some high Vor blood, and sent them downstairs for a hasty cleaning by the overworked Armsman Pym. The Countess, delighted as ever to find her biological empire increasing, came in thoughtfully bearing a cat-gourmet tray prepared by Ma Kosti that Miles would have had no hesitation in eating for his own breakfast. In the general chaos of the morning, however, he had to go down to the kitchen and scrounge his meal. The Countess sat on the floor and cooed into his closet for a good half-hour, and not only escaped laceration, but managed to pick up, sex, and name the whole batch of little squirming furballs before tearing herself away to hurry and dress." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568113-true-peace-required-the-presence-of-justice-not-just-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2014 11:51:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[b add a quote by N.K. Jemisin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568113-true-peace-required-the-presence-of-justice-not-just-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True peace required the presence of justice, not just the absence of conflict." -- N.K. Jemisin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
