<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807585-lisa-taylor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807585-lisa-taylor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:47:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:47:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:47:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:48:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:48:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:49:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:49:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes our light goes out, but is blown again into instant flame by an encounter with another human being." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9830-and-that-is-how-change-happens-one-gesture-one-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9830-and-that-is-how-change-happens-one-gesture-one-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And that is how change happens.  One gesture.  One person.  One moment at a time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1789-sometimes-the-slightest-things-change-the-directions-of-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:52:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Bryce Courtenay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1789-sometimes-the-slightest-things-change-the-directions-of-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the slightest things change the directions of our lives, the merest breath of a circumstance, a random moment that connects like a meteorite striking the earth.  Lives have swiveled and changed direction on the strength of a chance remark." -- Bryce Courtenay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10562-in-times-of-change-learners-inherit-the-earth-while-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 17:56:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Eric Hoffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10562-in-times-of-change-learners-inherit-the-earth-while-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In times of change, learners inherit the earth, while the learned find themselves beautifully equipped to deal with a world that no longer exists." -- Eric Hoffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7689-take-the-matter-as-you-find-it-ask-no-questions</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 18:03:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7689-take-the-matter-as-you-find-it-ask-no-questions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take the matter as you find it ask no questions, utter no remonstrances; it is your best wisdom. You expected bread and you have got a stone: break your teeth on it, and don't shriek because the nerves are martyrised; do not doubt that your mental stomach - if you have such a thing - is strong as an ostrich's; the stone will digest. You held out your hand for an egg, and fate put into it a scorpion. Show no consternation; close your fingers firmly upon the gift; let it sting through your palm. Never mind; in time, after your hand and arm have swelled and quivered long with torture, the squeezed scorpion will die, and you will have learned the great lesson how to endure without a sob." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23012-today-the-greatest-single-source-of-wealth-is-between-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 18:10:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Brian Tracy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23012-today-the-greatest-single-source-of-wealth-is-between-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today the greatest single source of wealth is between your ears." -- Brian Tracy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69058-you-should-never-be-surprised-when-someone-treats-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2009 18:12:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69058-you-should-never-be-surprised-when-someone-treats-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should never be surprised when someone treats you with respect, you should expect it." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
