<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807674-jack-smithee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807674-jack-smithee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:25:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5603-we-have-to-continually-be-jumping-off-cliffs-and-developing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:25:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5603-we-have-to-continually-be-jumping-off-cliffs-and-developing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to continually be jumping off cliffs and developing our wings on the way down." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2792-and-so-it-goes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:25:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2792-and-so-it-goes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so it goes..." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2308-one-of-the-few-good-things-about-modern-times-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:25:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2308-one-of-the-few-good-things-about-modern-times-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the few good things about modern times: If you die horribly on television, you will not have died in vain. You will have entertained us." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:26:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63-i-was-a-victim-of-a-series-of-accidents-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:27:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63-i-was-a-victim-of-a-series-of-accidents-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was a victim of a series of accidents, as are we all." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98330-of-all-the-words-of-mice-and-men-the-saddest</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:28:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98330-of-all-the-words-of-mice-and-men-the-saddest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the words of mice and men, the saddest are, &quot;It might have been." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27372-i-felt-after-i-finished-slaughterhouse-five-that-i-didn-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:29:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27372-i-felt-after-i-finished-slaughterhouse-five-that-i-didn-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt after I finished Slaughterhouse-Five that I didn’t have to write at all anymore if I didn’t want to. It was the end of some sort of career. I don’t know why, exactly. I suppose that flowers, when they’re through blooming, have some sort of awareness of some purpose having been served. Flowers didn’t ask to be flowers and I didn’t ask to be me. At the end of Slaughterhouse-Five…I had a shutting-off feeling…that I had done what I was supposed to do and everything was OK ." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1446-you-can-t-just-eat-good-food-you-ve-got-to-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:29:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1446-you-can-t-just-eat-good-food-you-ve-got-to-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't just eat good food. You've got to talk about it too. And you've got to talk about it to somebody who understands that kind of food." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158552-science-is-magic-that-works</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158552-science-is-magic-that-works]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is magic that works." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11870-the-practice-of-art-isn-t-to-make-a-living-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:36:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11870-the-practice-of-art-isn-t-to-make-a-living-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The practice of art isn't to make a living. It's to make your soul grow." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67388-the-waitress-brought-me-another-drink-she-wanted-to-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:37:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67388-the-waitress-brought-me-another-drink-she-wanted-to-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The waitress brought me another drink. She wanted to light my hurricane lamp again. I wouldn't let her.
&quot;Can you see anything in the dark, with your sunglasses on?&quot; she asked me.
&quot;The big show is inside my head,&quot; I said." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48275-novelists-have-on-the-average-about-the-same-iqs-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:41:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48275-novelists-have-on-the-average-about-the-same-iqs-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Novelists have, on the average, about the same IQs as the cosmetic consultants at Bloomingdale’s department store. Our power is patience. We have discovered that writing allows even a stupid person to seem halfway intelligent, if only that person will write the same thought over and over again, improving it just a little bit each time. It is a lot like inflating a blimp with a bicycle pump. Anybody can do it. All it takes is time." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76793-i-ve-often-thought-there-ought-to-be-a-manual-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:46:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76793-i-ve-often-thought-there-ought-to-be-a-manual-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've often thought there ought to be a manual to hand to little kids, telling them what kind of planet they're on, why they don't fall off it, how much time they've probably got here, how to avoid poison ivy, and so on. I tried to write one once. It was called Welcome to Earth. But I got stuck on explaining why we don't fall off the planet. Gravity is just a word. It doesn't explain anything. If I could get past gravity, I'd tell them how we reproduce, how long we've been here, apparently, and a little bit about evolution. I didn't learn until I was in college about all the other cultures, and I should have learned that in the first grade. A first grader should understand that his or her culture isn't a rational invention; that there are thousands of other cultures and they all work pretty well; that all cultures function on faith rather than truth; that there are lots of alternatives to our own society. Cultural relativity is defensible and attractive. It's also a source of hope. It means we don't have to continue this way if we don't like it." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13203-kilgore-trout-once-wrote-a-short-story-which-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:48:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13203-kilgore-trout-once-wrote-a-short-story-which-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kilgore Trout once wrote a short story which was a dialogue between two pieces of yeast. They were discussing the possible purposes of life as they ate sugar and suffocated in their own excrement. Because of their limited intelligence, they never came close to guessing that they were making champagne." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25806-every-character-should-want-something-even-if-it-is-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:48:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25806-every-character-should-want-something-even-if-it-is-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every character should want something, even if it is only a glass of water." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55218-life-happens-too-fast-for-you-ever-to-think-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 23:56:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55218-life-happens-too-fast-for-you-ever-to-think-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life happens too fast for you ever to think about it. If you could just persuade people of this, but they insist on amassing information." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47059-artists-use-frauds-to-make-human-beings-seem-more-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:01:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47059-artists-use-frauds-to-make-human-beings-seem-more-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Artists use frauds to make human beings seem more wonderful than they really are. Dancers show us human beings who move much more gracefully than human beings really move. Films and books and plays show us people talking much more entertainingly than people really talk, make paltry human enterprises seem important. Singers and musicians show us human beings making sounds far more lovely than human beings really make. Architects give us temples in which something marvelous is obviously going on. Actually, practically nothing is going on." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60358-as-i-approached-my-fiftieth-birthday-i-had-become-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:08:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60358-as-i-approached-my-fiftieth-birthday-i-had-become-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I approached my fiftieth birthday, I had become more and more enraged and mystified by the idiot decisions made by my countrymen. And then I had come suddenly to pity them, for I understood how innocent and natural it was for them to behave so abominably, and with such abominable results: They were doing their best to live like people invented in story books. This was the reason Americans shot each other so often: It was a convenient literary device for ending short stories and books.
Why were so many Americans treated by their government as though their lives were as disposable as paper facial tis-sues? Because that was the way authors customarily treated bit-part players in their made-up tales.
And so on.Once I understood what was making America such a dangerous, unhappy nation of people who had nothing to do with real life, I resolved to shun storytelling. I would write about life. Every person would be exactly as important as any other. All facts would also be given equal weightiness. Nothing would be left out. Let others bring order to chaos. I would bring chaos to order, instead, which I think I have done. If all writers would do that, then perhaps citizens not in the literary trades will understand that there is no order in the world around us, that we must adapt ourselves to the requirements of chaos instead. It is hard to adapt to chaos, but it can be done. I am living proof of that: It can be done." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73142-the-great-depression-was-going-on-so-that-the-station</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:21:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73142-the-great-depression-was-going-on-so-that-the-station]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Great Depression was going on, so that the station and the streets teemed with homeless people, just as they do today. The newspapers were full of stories of worker layoffs and farm foreclosures and bank failures, just as they are today. All that has changed, in my opinion, is that, thanks to television, we can hide a Great Depression. We may even be hiding a Third World War." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231652-write-to-please-just-one-person-if-you-open-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:30:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231652-write-to-please-just-one-person-if-you-open-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Write to please just one person. If you open a window and make love to the world, so to speak, your story will get pneumonia." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182702-somebody-gets-into-trouble-then-gets-out-of-it-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:39:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182702-somebody-gets-into-trouble-then-gets-out-of-it-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somebody gets into trouble, then gets out of it again. People love that story. They never get tired of it." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60119-i-m-a-doctor-of-cowshit-pigshit-and-chickenshit-when-you-doctors</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:41:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut, Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60119-i-m-a-doctor-of-cowshit-pigshit-and-chickenshit-when-you-doctors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm a doctor of cowshit, pigshit, and chickenshit.....when you doctors figure out what you want, you'll find me out in the barn shoveling my thesis." -- Kurt Vonnegut, Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221206-dear-sir-poor-sir-brave-sir-he-read-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:46:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221206-dear-sir-poor-sir-brave-sir-he-read-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dear Sir, poor sir, brave sir.&quot; he read, &quot;You are an experiment by the Creator of the Universe. You are the only creature in the entire Universe who has free will. You are the only one who has to figure out what to do next - and why. Everybody else is a robot, a machine.  Some persons seem to like you, and others seem to hate you, and you must wonder why.  They are simply liking machines and hating machines.  You are pooped and demoralized, &quot; read Dwayne.  &quot;Why wouldn't you be?  Of course it is exhausting, having to reason all the time in a universe which wasn't meant to be reasonable." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149825-i-told-him-that-if-we-doubted-that-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:51:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149825-i-told-him-that-if-we-doubted-that-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told him that if we doubted that we are demons in Hell, he should read The Mysterious Stranger, which Mark Twain wrote in 1898, long before the First World War (1914-1918). In the title story he proves to his own grim satisfaction, and to mine as well, that Satan and not God created the planet earth and &quot;the damned human race.&quot; If you doubt that, read your morning paper. Never mind what paper. Never mind the date." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243354-it-goes-against-the-american-storytelling-grain-to-have-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:52:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243354-it-goes-against-the-american-storytelling-grain-to-have-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It goes against the American storytelling grain to have someone in a situation he can't get out of, but I think this is very usual in life. [...] And it strikes me as gruesome and comical that in our culture we have an expectation that a man can always solve his problems. There is an implication that if you just have a little more energy, a little more fight, the problem can always be solved. That is so untrue that it makes me want to cry--or laugh." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117665-the-earthlings-behaved-at-all-times-as-though-there-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:52:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117665-the-earthlings-behaved-at-all-times-as-though-there-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Earthlings behaved at all times as though there were a big eye in the sky—as though that big eye were ravenous for entertainment." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226887-i-m-simply-interested-in-what-is-going-to-happen-next</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:55:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226887-i-m-simply-interested-in-what-is-going-to-happen-next]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm simply interested in what is going to happen next. I don't think I can control my life or my writing. Every other writer I know feels he is steering himself, and I don't have that feeling. I don't have that sort of control. I'm simply becoming. I'm startled that I became a writer." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178149-hi-ho</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 00:59:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178149-hi-ho]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hi ho" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313665-do-you-realize-that-all-great-literature-moby-dick</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 01:01:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313665-do-you-realize-that-all-great-literature-moby-dick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you realize that all great literature — &quot;Moby Dick,&quot; &quot;Huckleberry Finn,&quot; &quot;A Farewell to Arms,&quot; &quot;The Scarlet Letter,&quot; &quot;The Red Badge of Courage,&quot; &quot;The Iliad and The Odyssey,&quot; &quot;Crime and Punishment,&quot; the Bible, and &quot;The Charge of the Light Brigade&quot; — are all about what a bummer it is to be a ...human being?" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277573-i-didn-t-know-then-what-a-sperm-was-and-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2011 01:01:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jack add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277573-i-didn-t-know-then-what-a-sperm-was-and-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't know then what a sperm was, and so wouldn't understand his answer for several years. &quot;My boy,&quot; he said, &quot;you are descended from a long line of determined, resourceful, microscopic tadpoles-- champions every one." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
