<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807737-misti-rainwater-lites]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807737-misti-rainwater-lites" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:24:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559557-is-virgin-you-trying-to-fathom-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559557-is-virgin-you-trying-to-fathom-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is Virgin you trying to 
      fathom me" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:24:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it enough to see that a garden is beautiful without having to believe that there are fairies at the bottom of it too?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15346-ya-better-come-inside-when-you-re-ready-to-but-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 21:23:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Def Leppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15346-ya-better-come-inside-when-you-re-ready-to-but-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["ya better come inside 
when you're ready to
but no chance if ya don't wanna dance
you like four letter words when you're ready to
but then you won't 'cos you know that you can
" -- Def Leppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20571-i-found-god-in-myself-and-i-loved-her-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2008 01:47:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Ntozake Shange]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20571-i-found-god-in-myself-and-i-loved-her-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["i found god in myself
and i loved her
i loved her fiercely" -- Ntozake Shange]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:03:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1338-those-who-find-ugly-meanings-in-beautiful-things-are-corrupt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who find ugly meanings in beautiful things are corrupt without being charming. This is a fault. Those who find beautiful meanings in beautiful things are the cultivated. For these there is hope. They are the elect to whom beautiful things mean only Beauty. There is no such thing as a moral or an immoral book. Books are well written, or badly written. That is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6248-book-collecting-is-an-obsession-an-occupation-a-disease-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:04:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6248-book-collecting-is-an-obsession-an-occupation-a-disease-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Book collecting is an obsession, an occupation, a disease, an addiction, a fascination, an absurdity, a fate. It is not a hobby. Those who do it must do it. Those who do not do it, think of it as a cousin of stamp collecting, a sister of the trophy cabinet, bastard of a sound bank account and a weak mind." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1425-people-disappear-when-they-die-their-voice-their-laughter-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1425-people-disappear-when-they-die-their-voice-their-laughter-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People disappear when they die.  Their voice, their laughter, the warmth of their breath.  Their flesh.  Eventually their bones.  All living memory of them ceases.  This is both dreadful and natural.  Yet for some there is an exception to this annihilation.  For in the books they write they continue to exist.  We can rediscover them.  Their humor, their tone of voice, their moods.  Through the written word they can anger you or make you happy.  They can comfort you.  They can perplex you.  They can alter you.  All this, even though they are dead.  Like flies in amber, like corpses frozen in the ice, that which according to the laws of nature should pass away is, by the miracle of ink on paper, preserved.  It is a kind of magic." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/792-no-furniture-is-so-charming-as-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:05:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Sydney Smith ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/792-no-furniture-is-so-charming-as-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No furniture is so charming as books." -- Sydney Smith ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4567-the-books-are-to-remind-us-what-asses-and-fool</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:05:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4567-the-books-are-to-remind-us-what-asses-and-fool]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The books are to remind us what asses and fool we are. They're Caeser's praetorian guard, whispering as the parade roars down the avenue, &quot;Remember, Caeser, thou art mortal.&quot; Most of us can't rush around, talking to everyone, know all the cities of the world, we haven't time, money or that many friends. The things you're looking for, Montag, are in the world, but the only way the average chap will ever see ninety-nine per cent of them is in a book. Don't ask for guarantees. And don't look to be saved in any one thing, person, machine, or library. Do your own bit of saving, and if you drown, at least die knowing you were headed for shore." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798-books---the-best-antidote-against-the-marsh-gas-of-boredom</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by George Steiner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798-books---the-best-antidote-against-the-marsh-gas-of-boredom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books - the best antidote against the marsh-gas of boredom and vacuity" -- George Steiner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3395-the-failure-to-read-good-books-both-enfeebles-the-vision</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:06:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Allan Bloom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3395-the-failure-to-read-good-books-both-enfeebles-the-vision]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The failure to read good books both enfeebles the vision and strengthens our most fatal tendency -- the belief that the here and now is all there is." -- Allan Bloom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4941-properly-we-should-read-for-power-man-reading-should-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Ezra Pound]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4941-properly-we-should-read-for-power-man-reading-should-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Properly, we should read for power. Man reading should be man intensely alive. The book should be a ball of light in one's hand." -- Ezra Pound]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71772-a-wonderful-thing-about-a-book-in-contrast-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71772-a-wonderful-thing-about-a-book-in-contrast-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wonderful thing about a book, in contrast to a computer screen, is that you can take it to bed with you." -- Daniel J. Boorstin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69297-literature-simply-becomes-richer-after-you-ve-been-fired-rejected-stranded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:09:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Christian Bauman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69297-literature-simply-becomes-richer-after-you-ve-been-fired-rejected-stranded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature simply becomes richer after you've been fired, rejected, stranded, or had to change a few midnight diapers." -- Christian Bauman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74491-there-s-nothing-so-heavy-as-books-sir--unless-it-s-bricks</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 23:09:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Graham Greene]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74491-there-s-nothing-so-heavy-as-books-sir--unless-it-s-bricks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing so heavy as books, sir--unless it's bricks." -- Graham Greene]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559014-i-ve-got-a-rather-elegant-purplish-bruise-on-the-second</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:34:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559014-i-ve-got-a-rather-elegant-purplish-bruise-on-the-second]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve got a rather elegant purplish bruise on the second toe (which is longer than the first toe) of my left foot. I was standing in the shower. A bottle of shampoo fell from the towel rack and hit my toe. GODDAMN it HURT like a MOTHERFUCKING BITCH. I survived. If you would like a picture of my bruised toe, let me know. I sell specialty photographs via PayPal. Maybe a picture of my ass is more your style. I’ve got an ass, yes, and knees and elbows and hands and fingers and feet and toes and all the rest. The only thing I am missing is a uterus but I couldn’t photograph that for you even if I had one because I am not an x-ray technician. We all have fetishes to work through. My exact job title is Fetish Facilitator. Contact me." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559015-i-hit-the-goddamn-jackpot-with-celebrity-dreams-this-a-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:36:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559015-i-hit-the-goddamn-jackpot-with-celebrity-dreams-this-a-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hit the goddamn jackpot with celebrity dreams this a.m. In the latest dream I was in bed with Tom and Katie. I’ve never thought much of Tom Cruise but as I watched him fuck Katie fueled with insane lust and cocaine I murmured, 'God, Tom, I admire you so much.' Katie went to the bathroom to clean up and Tom fucked me. I was too happy to remember that I always preferred Ice Man to Maverick." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559016-yesterday-i-just-felt-like-eating-my-ass-off-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:37:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559016-yesterday-i-just-felt-like-eating-my-ass-off-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yesterday I just felt like eating my ass off so I did. I ate two Chef Boyardee pizzas, a Fifth Avenue candy bar, an entire package of fun size Snickers (that was fun!), several cherry sours (not the entire package, there are still a few left), an apple (apples don’t taste as good as they used to), several Slim Jims, a slice of burnt garlic toast, white cheddar popcorn and microwave popcorn. Today I will drink black coffee, eat a bowl of oatmeal (old school, boiled on the stove but no butter but lots of cinnamon and brown sugar) and dance to various YouTubes. I need to buy a pair of gloves, get my ass to the boxing gym and learn to love protein shakes. Also, I want to run a marathon. Then I want to get a backpack, stuff it with trail mix and the like and take to the road like the chick in that Wild book." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559017-i-dreamed-kim-kardashian-was-sobbing-but-her-makeup-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 18:38:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559017-i-dreamed-kim-kardashian-was-sobbing-but-her-makeup-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dreamed Kim Kardashian was sobbing but her makeup was still flawless. She stood on stage in a tight little cleavage squishing dress holding her award in her arms. Her out of focus, uninspired photograph of sunflowers and bluebonnets won Photograph of the Year in her church’s photography contest. I was kind of bitter about it but I didn’t attend her church and I didn’t enter the contest." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559018-that-night-lance-wants-to-rub-his-penis-as-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:22:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559018-that-night-lance-wants-to-rub-his-penis-as-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That night Lance wants to rub his penis as he thinks of Lexi but he refrains. He doesn’t want Lexi to be a masturbatory fantasy in the tradition of Cindy Crawford, Heather Locklear, Kate Hudson and Whoopi Goldberg. No. Hell no! As a matter of fact, hellll no with marshmallows on top. Lance wants Lexi to be his special lady, everything he needs and more. Lance has a gut feeling, an irritable bowel syndrome sensation, that Lexi is his Soul Mate, the one woman God made especially for him to enjoy. Lance wonders if Lexi is allergic to hyacinths. Roses are so common." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559021-many-american-women-over-forty-are-not-worried-about-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:22:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559021-many-american-women-over-forty-are-not-worried-about-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many American women over forty are not worried about their wrinkles and don’t give a rat’s ass about enhancing them. There’s this scientific fact called gravity. Gravity happens to us all, men and women. Some women and men over forty spend money fighting gravity with cosmetics and cosmetic surgery. That’s their ball game. That’s their parade. More power to them. There was once this woman named Gertrude Stein. She was the aesthetic opposite of Marilyn Monroe. I never knew Ms. Stein but from what I’ve read about her life I would venture to say that she was approximately (there’s no way of measuring such things…well, there are a couple of ways) a million times happier than Marilyn Monroe. Sexy on the outside doesn’t do much for ugly on the inside. This isn’t to say that Marilyn Monroe was ugly on the inside. I’m sure she was really fucking gorgeous on the inside, too. Bottom line: sparkle on the INSIDE can enhance ANYTHING on the outside." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559023-the-universe-gives-what-the-universe-gives-yes-cheap-thrills</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 22:21:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559023-the-universe-gives-what-the-universe-gives-yes-cheap-thrills]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe gives what the universe gives, yes. Cheap thrills, plenty of those, enough to get you through until Halloween when the Catholic school girls come out in full force and wink as they ask you to spank them (they’ve been very naughty). I’m going to sleep now and dream of deeper waters with treasure at the bottom. This junk has rendered me catatonic. I’m a mermaid, goddamn it, not the tooth fairy existing solely to place silver dollars beneath your crybaby pillow." -- Misti Rainwater-Lites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159279-what-do-women-want-i-want-a-red-dress-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 22:39:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Kim Addonizio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159279-what-do-women-want-i-want-a-red-dress-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What Do Women Want?&quot;
  	
  	I want a red dress.
I want it flimsy and cheap,
I want it too tight, I want to wear it
until someone tears it off me.
I want it sleeveless and backless,
this dress, so no one has to guess
what's underneath. I want to walk down
the street past Thrifty's and the hardware store
with all those keys glittering in the window,
past Mr. and Mrs. Wong selling day-old
donuts in their café, past the Guerra brothers
slinging pigs from the truck and onto the dolly,
hoisting the slick snouts over their shoulders.
I want to walk like I'm the only
woman on earth and I can have my pick.
I want that red dress bad.
I want it to confirm
your worst fears about me,
to show you how little I care about you
or anything except what
I want. When I find it, I'll pull that garment
from its hanger like I'm choosing a body
to carry me into this world, through
the birth-cries and the love-cries too,
and I'll wear it like bones, like skin,
it'll be the goddamned
dress they bury me in." -- Kim Addonizio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354260-love-me-like-a-wrong-turn-on-a-bad-road</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2012 22:40:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Kim Addonizio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354260-love-me-like-a-wrong-turn-on-a-bad-road]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love me like a wrong turn on a bad road
late at night." -- Kim Addonizio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244555-you-used-to-be-much-more-muchier-you-ve-lost-your-muchness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 22:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244555-you-used-to-be-much-more-muchier-you-ve-lost-your-muchness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You used to be much more...&quot;muchier.&quot; You've lost your muchness." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174673-after-a-year-of-therapy-my-psychiatrist-said-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 12:21:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Larry Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174673-after-a-year-of-therapy-my-psychiatrist-said-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After a year of therapy, my psychiatrist said to me, &quot;Maybe life isn't for everyone." -- Larry Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335457-sunday-just-came-down-like-a-nine-pound-hammer-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 12:21:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Larry Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/335457-sunday-just-came-down-like-a-nine-pound-hammer-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sunday just came down like a nine-pound hammer ... it was tainted with the closing-in feeling of the loss of freedom.  Because after the sun went down, it came back up on Monday morning.  And you had to go to work five more days.  And it sucked." -- Larry Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95059-i-didn-t-know-why-something-that-started-off-feeling-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 12:21:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Misti add a quote by Larry Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95059-i-didn-t-know-why-something-that-started-off-feeling-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't know why something that started off feeling so good had to wind up feeling so bad. Love was a big word and it covered a lot of territory. You could spend your whole life chasing after it and wind up with nothing, be an old bitter guy with long nose hair and ear hair and no teeth, hanging out in bars, looking for somebody your age, but the chances of success went down then. After a while you got too many strikes against you." -- Larry Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
