<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807910-jess70-lintott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/807910-jess70-lintott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 13:20:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3304-those-who-bring-sunshine-to-the-lives-of-others-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2008 13:20:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jess70 add a quote by J.M. Barrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3304-those-who-bring-sunshine-to-the-lives-of-others-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who bring sunshine to the lives of others cannot keep it from themselves." -- J.M. Barrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261187-nobody-can-avoid-falling-in-love-they-might-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 14:02:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jess70 add a quote by Stieg Larsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261187-nobody-can-avoid-falling-in-love-they-might-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody can avoid falling in love. They might want to deny it, but friendship is probably the most common form of love." -- Stieg Larsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213722-learn-to-like-what-doesn-t-cost-much-learn-to-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 12:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jess70 add a quote by Lowell Bennion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213722-learn-to-like-what-doesn-t-cost-much-learn-to-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Learn to like what doesn't cost much.
Learn to like reading, conversation, music.
Learn to like plain food, plain service, plain cooking.
Learn to like fields, trees, brooks, hiking, rowing, climbing hills.
Learn to like people, even though some of them may be different...different from you.
Learn to like to work and enjoy the satisfaction doing your job as well as it can be done.
Learn to like the song of birds, the companionship of dogs.
Learn to like gardening, puttering around the house, and fixing things.
Learn to like the sunrise and sunset, the beating of rain on the roof and windows, and the gentle fall of snow on a winter day.
Learn to keep your wants simple and refuse to be controlled by the likes and dislikes of others." -- Lowell Bennion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213724-if-we-thought-of-life-as-a-gift-we-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 12:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jess70 add a quote by Lowell Bennion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213724-if-we-thought-of-life-as-a-gift-we-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we thought of life as a gift, we might not demand nearly as much from it. And if we lived more graciously, giving of ourselves more freely to the well-being of others, many of our personal concerns would disappear, and life would become easier for all." -- Lowell Bennion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 06:10:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jess70 add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
