<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808183-jewel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808183-jewel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 03:37:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41513-once-a-king-in-narnia-always-a-king-in-narnia</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 03:37:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41513-once-a-king-in-narnia-always-a-king-in-narnia]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a King in Narnia, always a King in Narnia. But don't go trying to use the same route twice. Indeed, don't try to get there at all. It'll happen when you're not looking for it. And don't talk too much about it even among yourselves. And don't mention it to anyone else unless you find that they've had adventures of the same sort themselves. What's that? How will you know? Oh, you'll know all right. Odd things, they say-even their looks-will let the secret out. Keep your eyes open. Bless me, what do they teach them at these schools.&quot;
-The Profesor" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:10:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In each of us lie good and bad, light and dark, art and pain, choice and regret, cruelty and sacrifice. We’re each of us our own chiaroscuro, our own bit of illusion fighting to emerge into something solid, something real. We’ve got to forgive ourselves that. I must remember to forgive myself. Because there is a lot of grey to work with. No one can live in the light all the time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35863-i-know-because-i-read-your-mind-is-not-a-cage</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:10:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35863-i-know-because-i-read-your-mind-is-not-a-cage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know because I read...Your mind is not a cage. It's a garden. And it requires cultivating." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2286-you-can-never-really-know-someone-completely-that-s-why-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:10:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2286-you-can-never-really-know-someone-completely-that-s-why-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never really know someone completely. That’s why it’s the most terrifying thing in the world, really—taking someone on faith, hoping they’ll take you on faith too. It’s such a precarious balance, It’s a wonder we do it at all. And yet.." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36214-we-all-do-things-we-desperately-wish-we-could-undo</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:11:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36214-we-all-do-things-we-desperately-wish-we-could-undo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all do things we desperately wish we could undo. Those regrets just become part of who we are, along with everything else. To spend time trying to change that, well, it's like chasing clouds." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82101-we-re-all-strangers-connected-by-what-we-reveal-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:12:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82101-we-re-all-strangers-connected-by-what-we-reveal-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all strangers connected by what we reveal, what we share, what we take away--our stories. I guess that's what I love about books--they are thin strands of humanity that tether us to one another for a small bit of time, that make us feel less alone or even more comfortable with our aloneness, if need be." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:22:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:22:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:22:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:24:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44282-when-we-hold-each-other-in-the-darkness-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we hold each other, in the darkness, it doesn't make the darkness go away. The bad things are still out there. The nightmares still walking. When we hold each other we feel not safe, but better. &quot;It's all right&quot; we whisper, &quot;I'm here, I love you.&quot; and we lie: &quot;I'll never leave you.&quot; For just a moment or two the darkness doesn't seem so bad." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:24:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413047-everybody-has-a-secret-world-inside-of-them-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody has a secret world inside of them. I mean everybody. All of the people in the whole world, I mean everybody — no matter how dull and boring they are on the outside. Inside them they've all got unimaginable, magnificent, wonderful, stupid, amazing worlds... Not just one world. Hundreds of them. Thousands, maybe." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98938-you-get-ideas-from-daydreaming-you-get-ideas-from-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:27:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98938-you-get-ideas-from-daydreaming-you-get-ideas-from-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get ideas from daydreaming. You get ideas from being bored. You get ideas all the time. The only difference between writers and other people is we notice when we're doing it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82986-a-craven-can-be-as-brave-as-any-man-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2008 06:31:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82986-a-craven-can-be-as-brave-as-any-man-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A craven can be as brave as any man, when there is nothing to fear. And we all do our duty, when there is no cost to it. How easy it seems then, to walk the path of honor. Yet soon or late in every man's life comes a day when it is not easy, a day when he must choose. (Maester Aemon)" -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 23:37:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53166-the-best-fantasy-is-written-in-the-language-of-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best fantasy is written in the language of dreams. It is alive as dreams are alive, more real than real ... for a moment at least ... that long magic moment before we wake.

     Fantasy is silver and scarlet, indigo and azure, obsidian veined with gold and lapis lazuli. Reality is plywood and plastic, done up in mud brown and olive drab. Fantasy tastes of habaneros and honey, cinnamon and cloves, rare red meat and wines as sweet as summer. Reality is beans and tofu, and ashes at the end. Reality is the strip malls of Burbank, the smokestacks of Cleveland, a parking garage in Newark. Fantasy is the towers of Minas Tirith, the ancient stones of Gormenghast, the halls of Camelot. Fantasy flies on the wings of Icarus, reality on Southwest Airlines. Why do our dreams become so much smaller when they finally come true?

     We read fantasy to find the colors again, I think. To taste strong spices and hear the songs the sirens sang. There is something old and true in fantasy that speaks to something deep within us, to the child who dreamt that one day he would hunt the forests of the night, and feast beneath the hollow hills, and find a love to last forever somewhere south of Oz and north of Shangri-La.

     They can keep their heaven. When I die, I'd sooner go to middle Earth." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17466-we-all-need-to-be-mocked-from-time-to-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2008 23:37:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17466-we-all-need-to-be-mocked-from-time-to-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all need to be mocked from time to time, lest we take ourselves too seriously." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134025-i-have-no-idea-why-it-apparently-takes-three-grown</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 08:30:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134025-i-have-no-idea-why-it-apparently-takes-three-grown]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no idea why it apparently takes three grown men to cook some hamburgers.
One to cook, one to kibbitz, and one to insult the other two. " -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 07:32:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153144-so-many-vows-they-make-you-swear-and-swear-defend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many vows... they make you swear and swear. Defend the king. Obey the king. Keep his secrets. Do his bidding. Your life for his. But obey your father. Love your sister. Protect the innocent. Defend the weak. Respect the gods. Obey the laws. It’s too much. No matter what you do, you’re forsaking one vow or the other." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:13:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:13:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:14:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is unnecessary, like philosophy, like art.... It has no survival value; rather it is one of those things which give value to survival." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47924-some-day-you-will-be-old-enough-to-start-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:14:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47924-some-day-you-will-be-old-enough-to-start-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some day you will be old enough to start reading fairy tales again." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32548-whatever-comes-she-said-cannot-alter-one-thing-if-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:15:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32548-whatever-comes-she-said-cannot-alter-one-thing-if-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever comes,&quot; she said, &quot;cannot alter one thing.  If I am a princess in rags and tatters, I can be a princess inside.  It would be easy to be a princess if I were dressed in cloth of gold, but it is a great deal more of a triumph to be one all the time when no one knows it." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:21:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion. It lies in all of us. Sleeping... waiting... and though unwanted, unbidden, it will stir... open its jaws and howl. It speaks to us... guides us. Passion rules us all. And we obey. What other choice do we have? Passion is the source of our finest moments. The joy of love... the clarity of hatred... the ecstasy of grief. It hurts sometimes more than we can bear. If we could live without passion, maybe we'd know some kind of peace. But we would be hollow. Empty rooms, shuttered and dank. Without passion, we'd be truly dead." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101011-the-thing-about-a-hero-is-even-when-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2009 08:22:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101011-the-thing-about-a-hero-is-even-when-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The thing about a hero, is even when it doesn't look like there's a light at the end of the tunnel, he's going to keep digging, he's going to keep trying to do right and make up for what's gone before, just because that's who he is." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63346-stories-like-people-and-butterflies-and-songbirds-eggs-and-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 03:47:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63346-stories-like-people-and-butterflies-and-songbirds-eggs-and-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories, like people and butterflies and songbirds' eggs and human hearts and dreams, are also fragile things, made up of nothing stronger or more lasting than twenty-six letters and a handful of punctuation marks. Or they are words on the air, composed of sounds and ideas-abstract, invisible, gone once they've been spoken-and what could be more frail than that? But some stories, small, simple ones about setting out on adventures or people doing wonders, tales of miracles and monsters, have outlasted all the people who told them, and some of them have outlasted the lands in which they were created." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75237-life-is-like-topography-hobbes-there-are-summits-of-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 02:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75237-life-is-like-topography-hobbes-there-are-summits-of-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is like topography, Hobbes. There are summits of happiness and success, flat stretches of boring routine and valleys of frustration and failure." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153064-she-surrounded-herself-with-books-at-work-and-at-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 22:22:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153064-she-surrounded-herself-with-books-at-work-and-at-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She surrounded herself with books at work and at home. Her living space was a testament to her first and abiding love  with shelves jammed with books  tables crowded with them. She saw them not only as knowledge  entertainment  comfort  even sanity  but as a kind of artful decoration.    " -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182282-the-room-was-a-compact-informal-library-books-stood-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 22:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182282-the-room-was-a-compact-informal-library-books-stood-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The room was a compact, informal library. Books stood or were stacked on the shelves that ran along two walls from floor to ceiling, sat on the tables like knickknacks, trooped around the room like soldiers. They struck Malory as more than knowledge or entertainment, even more than stories or information. They were colour and texture, in a haphazard yet somehow intricate decorating scheme.
The short leg of the L-shaped room boasted still more books, as well as a small table that held the remains of Dana's breakfast.
With her hands on her hips, Dana watched Malory's perusal of her space. She'd seen the reaction before. 'No I haven't read them all, but I will.And no I don't know how many I have. Want coffee?'
Let me just ask this. Do you ever actually use the services of the library?'
Sure, but I need to own them. If I don't have twenty or thirty books right here, waiting to be read, I start jonesing. That's my compulsion." -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142998-bran-thought-about-it-can-a-man-still-be-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 22:28:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142998-bran-thought-about-it-can-a-man-still-be-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bran thought about it. 'Can a man still be brave if he's afraid?'
'That is the only time a man can be brave,' his father told him." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175402-what-is-honor-compared-to-a-woman-s-love-what-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2009 22:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jewel add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175402-what-is-honor-compared-to-a-woman-s-love-what-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is honor compared to a woman's love? What is duty against the feel of a newborn son in your arms . . . or the memory of a brother's smile? Wind and words. Wind and words. We are only human, and the gods have fashioned us for love. That is our great glory, and our great tragedy." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
