<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808320-sevada]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808320-sevada" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 05:57:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2416-the-major-problem-mdash-one-of-the-major-problems-for-there-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 05:57:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sevada add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2416-the-major-problem-mdash-one-of-the-major-problems-for-there-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The major problem&amp;mdash;&lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; of the major problems, for there are several&amp;mdash;one of the many major problems with governing people is that of whom you get to do it; or rather of who manages to get people to let them do it to them. 
To summarize: it is a well-known fact that those people who must &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to rule people are, ipso facto, those least suited to do it. 
To summarize the summary: anyone who is capable of getting themselves made President should on no account be allowed to do the job." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303458-one-of-the-problems-and-it-s-one-which-is-obviously</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2010 04:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sevada add a quote by Duglass Adamss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303458-one-of-the-problems-and-it-s-one-which-is-obviously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the problems, and it's one which is obviously going to get worse, is that all the people at the party are either the children or the grandchildren or the great-grandchildren of the people who wouldn't leave in the first place, and because of all the business about selective breeding and regressive genes and so on, it means that all the people now at the party are either absolutely fanatical partygoers, or gibbering idiots, or, more and more frequently, both." -- Duglass Adamss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306886-he-spent-a-lot-of-time-flying-he-learnt-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 04:50:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sevada add a quote by Duglass Adamss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306886-he-spent-a-lot-of-time-flying-he-learnt-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He spent a lot of time flying.

He learnt to communicate with birds and discovered that their conversation was fantastically boring. It was all to do with wind speed, wing spans, power-to-weight ratios and a fair bit about berries. Unfortunately, he discovered, once you have learnt birdspeak you quickly come to realize that the air is full of it the whole time, just inane bird chatter. There is no getting away from it." -- Duglass Adamss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309550-they-ve-discovered-how-to-turn-excess-body-fat-into-gold</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 02:17:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sevada add a quote by Duglass Adamss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309550-they-ve-discovered-how-to-turn-excess-body-fat-into-gold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They've discovered how to turn excess body fat into gold,&quot; he said, in a sudden blur of coherence.

&quot;You're kidding.&quot;

&quot;Oh yes,&quot; he said, &quot;no,&quot; he corrected himself, &quot;they have.&quot;

He rounded on the doubting part of his audience, which was all of it, and so it took a little while to round on it completely.

&quot;Have you been to California?&quot; he demanded. &quot;Do you know the sort of stuff they do there?&quot;

Three members of his audience said they had and that he was talking nonsense.

&quot;You haven't seen anything,&quot; insisted Arthur. &quot;Oh yes,&quot; he added, because someone was offering to buy another round." -- Duglass Adamss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308025-in-every-remote-corner-of-the-world-there-are-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2012 15:40:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sevada add a quote by Mark Carwardine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308025-in-every-remote-corner-of-the-world-there-are-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In every remote corner of the world there are people like Carl Jones and Don Merton who have devoted their lives to saving threatened species. Very often, their determination is all that stands between an endangered species and extinction.
But why do they bother? Does it really matter if the Yangtze river dolphin, or the kakapo, or the northern white rhino, or any other species live on only in scientists' notebooks?
Well, yes, it does. Every animal and plant is an integral part of its environment: even Komodo dragons have a major role to play in maintaining the ecological stability of their delicate island homes. If they disappear, so could many other species. And conservation is very much in tune with our survival. Animals and plants provide us with life-saving drugs and food, they pollinate crops and provide important ingredients or many industrial processes. Ironically, it is often not the big and beautiful creatures, but the ugly and less dramatic ones, that we need most.
Even so, the loss of a few species may seem irrelevant compared to major environmental problems such as global warming or the destruction of the ozone layer. But while nature has considerable resilience, there is a limit to how far that resilience can be stretched. No one knows how close to the limit we are getting. The darker it gets, the faster we're driving.
There is one last reason for caring, and I believe that no other is necessary. It is certainly the reason why so many people have devoted their lives to protecting the likes of rhinos, parakeets, kakapos, and dolphins. And it is simply this: the world would be a poorer, darker, lonelier place without them." -- Mark Carwardine]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
