<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808650-anuar-kassim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808650-anuar-kassim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 07:08:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308154-there-were-giants-in-the-earth-in-those-days-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 07:08:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308154-there-were-giants-in-the-earth-in-those-days-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were giants in the earth in those days; and also after that, when the sons of God came in unto the daughters of men, and they bore children to them." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/990030-i-think-i-was-a-pretty-decent-carer-but-five</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 13:57:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/990030-i-think-i-was-a-pretty-decent-carer-but-five]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I was a pretty decent carer. But five years felt about enough for me. I was like you, Tommy. I was pretty much ready when I became a donor. It felt right. After all, it’s what we’re supposed to be doing, isn’t it?" -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1031840-ibn-fadl-n-ibn-fadl-n-and-the-land-of-darkness-arab</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 03:09:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Ibn Fadlan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1031840-ibn-fadl-n-ibn-fadl-n-and-the-land-of-darkness-arab]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["IBN FADLĀN Ibn Fadlān and the Land of Darkness Arab Travellers in the Far North Translated with an Introduction by PAUL LUNDE and CAROLINE STONE" -- Ibn Fadlan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169629-numbers-are-unique-there-is-nothing-like-them-and-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 20:32:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Peter Michael Higgins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169629-numbers-are-unique-there-is-nothing-like-them-and-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Numbers are unique, there is nothing like them and this book reveals something of their mysterious nature. Numbers are familiar to everyone and are our mainstay when we feel the need to bring order to chaos. In our own minds they epitomize measured rationality and are the key tool for expressing it. However, do they really exist?" -- Peter Michael Higgins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1233911-the-malays-were-outstripped-economically-in-their-own-country-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 04:41:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1233911-the-malays-were-outstripped-economically-in-their-own-country-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Malays were outstripped economically in their own country by the immigrant races. In the words of historian Lennox Mills, “when the British came, the Malay was a poor man in a poor country; when they left he was a poor man in a rich country.” British attitudes and policies, what the Malays did for a living, the strengths of the immigrants and the nature of the Malay value system all contributed to their backward economic position." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1233943-an-often-used-assessment-of-present-day-singapore-is-that-the-people-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 05:13:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1233943-an-often-used-assessment-of-present-day-singapore-is-that-the-people-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An often-used assessment of present-day Singapore is that the People’s Action Party government transformed Singapore from a “colonial backwater” into a modern, prosperous global city. While it is true that the PAP transformed the city, it was certainly not a backwater. British Malaya was of great significance to global economic and political issues during the years between the two world wars." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1235232-the-ability-of-the-malay-political-leadership-through-umno-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 02:56:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1235232-the-ability-of-the-malay-political-leadership-through-umno-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ability of the Malay political leadership through UMNO to mobilize Malay public opinion caught the British by surprise. A people who only a decade earlier had seemed docile and apathetic were suddenly making their views known through mass demonstrations. The strength and emotion of the Malay reaction convinced the British that they had miscalculated. The British sat down with the Malay political leadership to come up with an alternative to the Malayan Union." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236399-the-british-legacy-was-mixed-the-british-left-behind-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 23:03:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236399-the-british-legacy-was-mixed-the-british-left-behind-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The British legacy was mixed. The British left behind a prosperous country with tremendous potential. A modern, Western-style democracy was in place with an infrastructure unmatched in the region. There was order and stability in the country, and the races seemed to be cooperating to lay the foundations for independence. Most saw a bright future for the new Federation of Malaya. On the other hand, there were forces at work beneath the surface that were also Britain’s legacy. Economic and political inequalities among the races were time bombs waiting to go off." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236542-in-1956-his-government-put-forward-a-proposal-to-bar</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 01:47:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236542-in-1956-his-government-put-forward-a-proposal-to-bar]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In 1956, his government put forward a proposal to bar student groups from political activities. The reaction was swift: militant Chinese students seized control of six Chinese-medium schools and barricaded themselves inside. Lim retaliated by sending the police to clear the schools. The students took to the streets, and almost two weeks of rioting led to the death of fifteen people and the injury of hundreds of others. The streets of Singapore became battlefields between security forces and Chinese radicals." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236604-in-the-eyes-of-many-malayans-it-was-a-zero-sum</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 03:10:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1236604-in-the-eyes-of-many-malayans-it-was-a-zero-sum]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the eyes of many Malayans, it was a zero-sum game. Help for one race was viewed as a loss for another. Loyalty to the country would be difficult to nurture among the immigrant races if they felt they were second-class citizens politically. Acceptance of the immigrants by the Malays would be hard since they felt they should be favored over the immigrants. Unity and equity – could they be reconciled? It has been said that “high tides raise all boats,” and perhaps rapid economic growth could help solve the racial problems." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237848-the-indonesians-had-been-told-that-the-malaysian-masses-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 04:18:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1237848-the-indonesians-had-been-told-that-the-malaysian-masses-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Indonesians had been told that the Malaysian masses would welcome their Indonesian brothers with open arms and that it was only their leaders and the British who believed in Malaysia. What followed was a debacle. Four planeloads of troops were involved in the “liberation.” One plane failed to get off the ground in Indonesia. A second plane crashed in the Straits of Melaka. A third dropped its troops in the wrong place. Stragglers from this plane flagged down a passing vehicle, and the Malaysian driver took his “liberators” to the nearest police station. The only commandos who were dropped on target were quickly rounded up by Commonwealth troops." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1239000-added-to-this-the-saf-had-adopted-a-defensive-israeli</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 04:16:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1239000-added-to-this-the-saf-had-adopted-a-defensive-israeli]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Added to this, the SAF had adopted a defensive Israeli model and had turned to Israeli defense forces to institute it. Indonesia and Malaysia wondered if Singapore, like Israel, saw itself as an embattled country in a world of enemies. Would it adopt the Israeli practice of attacking first and asking questions later? There was a religious dimension as well. As countries with large numbers of Muslims, Malaysia and Indonesia sympathized with the Arab and Palestinian causes. Having Israeli advisors in the neighborhood was a hard pill to swallow." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1240196-somehow-malaysia-must-find-a-way-to-create-racially-neutral</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 00:41:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1240196-somehow-malaysia-must-find-a-way-to-create-racially-neutral]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somehow Malaysia must find a way to create racially neutral space in the public sphere. This is not an easy task as most of the country’s social and political institutions are tied to racial identity. Because of the connection between race and religion, it would be virtually impossible to see religion as a vehicle. The educational system has proved to be an imperfect tool of national identity. For many, it remains a communalized institution that has powerful political symbolism." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1240197-two-opinion-pieces-written-by-local-author-catherine-lim-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2014 00:45:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1240197-two-opinion-pieces-written-by-local-author-catherine-lim-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two opinion pieces written by local author Catherine Lim in The Straits Times in 1994 were good examples of the political climate in the early years of Goh’s administration. The first article was titled “The PAP and the People: A Great Affective Divide.” Her thesis was that while the people of Singapore recognized the effective job the party did in running Singapore and providing for its prosperity, many of them did not like their leaders very much. For instance, on National Day, many Singaporeans did not fly the national flag because of the close connection between it and the PAP. Somehow flying the flag indicated you were a PAP supporter or liked the party, which in many minds was different from respecting what the leaders had done. In her second article, Lim questioned whether any significant political change had taken place with the handover of power from Lee Kuan Yew to Goh Chok Tong. She argued that the large salary increase for government officials that had been approved was an example of the continuing top-down style of government. In a way, the government’s response to these articles proved her correct. Its immediate reaction was to state that local writers had no business being involved in political issues. If they wanted to do so, they should join a political party and not give opinions from the sidelines. The argument was the same one used almost a decade earlier against the law society and against the churches. While there had been an attempt to obtain more feedback from people, there was still a deep feeling among PAP leaders that public political debate must be limited. Even in the mid-1990s, there was still a belief that too broad a discourse would threaten Singapore’s success." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248438-poverty-drove-their-parents-to-have-them-castrated-as-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 02:28:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Jung Chang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1248438-poverty-drove-their-parents-to-have-them-castrated-as-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poverty drove their parents to have them castrated as young children, hoping they would earn a better living at court. Usually the father would take the boy to a specialist castrator, who operated by the appointment of the court. After a contract was signed, absolving the castrator from any responsibility in case of death or failure (both highly likely outcomes), the unimaginably painful operation was performed. The castrator’s fee was huge and had to be paid from future earnings." -- Jung Chang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1252428-the-manchus-drank-tea-with-a-lot-of-milk-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 07:06:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Jung Chang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1252428-the-manchus-drank-tea-with-a-lot-of-milk-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Manchus drank tea with a lot of milk. In her case, the milk came from the breasts of a nurse. Cixi had been taking human milk since her prolonged illness in the early 1880s, on the recommendation of a renowned doctor. Several wet nurses were employed, and took turns to squeeze milk into a bowl for her. The nurses brought their sucking babies with them, and the woman who served her the longest stayed on in the palace, her son being given education and an office job." -- Jung Chang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253666-so-the-story-of-wild-fox-kang-s-attempted-coup-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 04:40:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Jung Chang]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253666-so-the-story-of-wild-fox-kang-s-attempted-coup-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So the story of Wild Fox Kang’s attempted coup and murder of Cixi lay in darkness and obscurity for nearly a century, until the 1980s, when Chinese scholars discovered in Japanese archives the testimony of the designated killer, Bi, which established beyond doubt the existence of the plot." -- Jung Chang]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274955-the-defeat-of-darwinism-in-the-face-of-science-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 01:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anuar add a quote by Harun Yahya]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274955-the-defeat-of-darwinism-in-the-face-of-science-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The defeat of Darwinism in the face of science can be reviewed under three basic topics: 1) The theory cannot explain how life originated on Earth. 2) No scientific finding shows that the “evolutionary mechanisms” proposed by the theory have any evolutionary power at all. 3) The fossil record proves the exact opposite of what the theory suggests. In this section, we will examine these three basic points in general outlines:" -- Harun Yahya]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
