<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808903-kristy-powers]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808903-kristy-powers" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 16:48:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205214-giving-birth-is-like-taking-your-lower-lip-and-forcing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 16:48:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Carol Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205214-giving-birth-is-like-taking-your-lower-lip-and-forcing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Giving birth is like taking your lower lip and forcing it over your head." -- Carol Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13681-humankind-cannot-bear-very-much-reality</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 16:48:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by T. S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13681-humankind-cannot-bear-very-much-reality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humankind cannot bear very much reality." -- T. S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 14:15:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995823-when-i-feel-the-ball-start-to-grow-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 15:57:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Nicholeen Peck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995823-when-i-feel-the-ball-start-to-grow-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I feel the ball start to grow in my stomach, I immediately do one of two things. I either change environments, by going to weed the garden or fold some laundry while taking deep breaths, or I start describing the situation which is bothering me, being very conscious that my words are only honest descriptions and not reactions. Sometimes, an issue is especially large to cope with, so I find a private place and pray. I pray until I feel a spirit of calmness, the spirit of God." -- Nicholeen Peck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008420-narnia-held-captive-by-the-post-christian-telmarines-cannot-be-rescued</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 05:19:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Louis A. Markos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1008420-narnia-held-captive-by-the-post-christian-telmarines-cannot-be-rescued]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Narnia, held captive by the “post-Christian” Telmarines, cannot be rescued and renewed until Peter and Edmund exercise their masculine gifts to defeat the Telmarine army while Susan and Lucy exercise their feminine gifts to wake up the trees from their deep slumber." -- Louis A. Markos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615-we-are-not-necessarily-doubting-that-god-will-do-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:44:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615-we-are-not-necessarily-doubting-that-god-will-do-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not necessarily doubting that God will do the best for us; we are wondering how painful the best will turn out to be." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103229-to-be-a-christian-means-to-forgive-the-inexcusable-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 19:44:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103229-to-be-a-christian-means-to-forgive-the-inexcusable-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a Christian means to forgive the inexcusable because God has forgiven the inexcusable in you." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033909-but-more-than-just-awakening-my-hunger-breathing-narnian-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 19:17:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Joe Rigney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1033909-but-more-than-just-awakening-my-hunger-breathing-narnian-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But more than just awakening my hunger, breathing Narnian air awakens a desire for a particular type of meal, one with tasty food, good conversation, lots of joy and laughter and revelry and strategizing about how to defeat the White Witch. It makes me want to eat my bread with joy and drink my wine with a merry heart, because God approves (Eccles. 9:7)." -- Joe Rigney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183394-adventures-are-never-fun-while-you-re-having-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 11:22:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183394-adventures-are-never-fun-while-you-re-having-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adventures are never fun while you're having them." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1140614-she-also-stirred-a-sort-of-envy-in-him-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 16:34:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1140614-she-also-stirred-a-sort-of-envy-in-him-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She also stirred a sort of envy in him by telling him that during the Two Minutes Hate her great difficulty was to avoid bursting out laughing. But she only questioned the teachings of the Party when they in some way touched upon her own life. Often she was ready to accept the official mythology, simply because the difference between truth and falsehood did not seem important to her." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1187477-i-am-rather-like-a-mosquito-in-a-nudist-camp</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 04:39:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by David Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1187477-i-am-rather-like-a-mosquito-in-a-nudist-camp]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am rather like a mosquito in a nudist camp; I know what I want to do, but I don’t know where to begin." -- David Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196956-ance-a-man-child-has-beaten-his-way-to-life-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 11:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196956-ance-a-man-child-has-beaten-his-way-to-life-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ance a man-child has beaten his way to life under the heart of a woman, she is mither to all men, for the hearts of mithers are everywhere the same." -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196990-love-her-i-cried-why-he-just-loves-her-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 12:06:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196990-love-her-i-cried-why-he-just-loves-her-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love her?&quot; I cried. &quot;Why he just loves her to death! He turns so white, and he suffers so, when her pain is the worst. Love her? And she him? Why, don't you remember the other day when he tipped her head against him and kissed her throat as he left the table; that he asked her if she 'loved him yet,' and she said right before all of us, 'Why Paul, I love you, until I scarcely can keep my fingers off you!" -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196992-my-mother-was-the-best-and-most-beautiful-woman-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 12:07:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196992-my-mother-was-the-best-and-most-beautiful-woman-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother was the best and most beautiful woman who ever lived. She was clean, and good, and always helped &quot;the poor and needy who cluster round your door,&quot; like it says in the poetry piece, and there never could have been a reason why God would want a woman to suffer herself, when she went flying on horseback even dark nights through rain or snow, to doctor other people's pain, and when she gave away things like she did—why, I've seen her take a big piece of meat from the barrel, and a sack of meal, and heaps of apples and potatoes to carry to Mandy Thomas—when she gave away food by the wagonload at a time, God couldn't have wanted her to be hungry, and yet she was that very minute almost crying for food;" -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196993-father-said-man-was-born-a-praying-animal-and-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 12:08:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196993-father-said-man-was-born-a-praying-animal-and-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Father said man was born a praying animal, and no matter how wicked he was, if he had an accident, or saw he had just got to die, he cried aloud to the Lord for help and mercy before he knew what he was doing." -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196995-when-it-grew-cold-enough-to-shut-the-doors-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 12:09:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristy add a quote by Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196995-when-it-grew-cold-enough-to-shut-the-doors-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When it grew cold enough to shut the doors, and have fire at night, first thing after supper all of us helped clear the table, then we took our slates and books and learned our lessons for the next day, and then father lined us against the wall, all in a row from Laddie down, and he pronounced words—easy ones that divided into syllables nicely, for me, harder for May, and so up until I might sit down. For Laddie, May and Leon he used the geography, the Bible, Roland's history, the Christian Advocate, and the Agriculturist. My, but he had them so they could spell! After that, as memory tests, all of us recited our reading lesson for the next day, especially the poetry pieces. I knew most of them, from hearing the big folks repeat them so often and practise the proper way to read them. I could do &quot;Rienzi's Address to the Romans,&quot; &quot;Casablanca,&quot; &quot;Gray's Elegy,&quot; or &quot;Mark Antony's Speech,&quot; but best of all, I liked &quot;Lines to a Water-fowl.&quot; When he was tired, if it were not bedtime yet, all of us, boys too, sewed rags for carpet and rugs. Laddie braided corn husks for the kitchen and outside door mats, and they were pretty, and &quot;very useful too,&quot; like the dog that got his head patted in McGuffey's Second." -- Gene Stratton-Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
