<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808977-amanda-winfree]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/808977-amanda-winfree" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:32:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15439-something-evil-i-said-ikstein-stands-outside-the-door-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:32:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Leonard Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15439-something-evil-i-said-ikstein-stands-outside-the-door-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something Evil

I said, &quot;Ikstein stands outside the door for a long time before he knocks.  Did you suspect that?  Did you suspect that he stands there listening to what we say before he knocks?&quot;  She said, &quot;Did you know you're crazy?&quot;  I said, &quot;I'm not crazy.  The expression on his face, when I open the door, is giddy and squirmy.  As if he'd been doing something evil, like listening outside our door before he knocked.&quot;  She said, &quot;That's Ikstein's expression.  Why do you invite him here?  Leave the door open.  He won't be able to listen to us.  You won't make yourself crazy imagining it.&quot;  I said, &quot;Brilliant, but he isn't due for an hour and I won't sit here with the door open.&quot;  She said, &quot;I hate to listen to you talk this way.  I won't be involved in your lunatic friendships.&quot;  She opened the door.  Ikstein stood there, giddy and squirmy." -- Leonard Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15440-march-6-1961-i-remembered-a-party-in-a-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:33:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Leonard Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15440-march-6-1961-i-remembered-a-party-in-a-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["March 6, 1961

I remembered a party in a house outside of Ann Arbor.  There was a jazz band -- piano, bass, drums, and sax -- playing in one of the large rooms.  A heavy odor of marijuana hung in the air.  The host appeared now and then looking pleased, as if he liked seeing strangers in every room, the party out of his control.  It wasn't wild, but with a constant flow of people, who knows what they're doing.  It became late and I was a little drunk, wandering from one part of the house to another.  I entered a long hall and was surprised by the silence, as if I had entered another house.  A girl at the other end of the hall was walking toward me.  I saw large blue eyes and very black hair.  She was about average height, doll-like features delicate as cut glass, extremely pretty, maybe the prettiest girl I'd ever seen.  When she came up to me I took her in my arms and kissed her.  She let it happen.  We were like creatures in a dream.  Holding her hand, I drew her with me and we passed through rooms where people stood about, and then left the house.  As we drove away, she said her name was Margo.  She was a freshman at the university, from a town in northern Michigan.  I took her home.  It was obvious she'd never gone home with a man.  She didn't seem fearful, only uncertain, the question in her eyes: &quot;What happens next?&quot;  What happened next was nothing much.  We fell asleep in our clothes.  I wasn't the one to make her no different from everyone." -- Leonard Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15442-a-knock-on-the-door-they-ask-me-if-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 07:34:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by James Tate]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15442-a-knock-on-the-door-they-ask-me-if-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Knock On The Door 

They ask me if I've ever thought about the end of 
the world, and I say, &quot;Come in, come in, let me 
give you some lunch, for God's sake.&quot; After a few 
bites it's the afterlife they want to talk about. 
&quot;Ouch,&quot; I say, &quot;did you see that grape leaf 
skeletonizer?&quot; Then they're talking about 
redemption and the chosen few sitting right by 
His side. &quot;Doing what?&quot; I ask. &quot;Just sitting?&quot; I 
am surrounded by burned up zombies. &quot;Let's 
have some lemon chiffon pie I bought yesterday 
at the 3 Dog Bakery.&quot; But they want to talk about 
my soul. I'm getting drowsy and see butterflies 
everywhere. &quot;Would you gentlemen like to take a 
nap, I know I would.&quot; They stand and back away 
from me, out the door, walking toward my 
neighbors, a black cloud over their heads and 
they see nothing without end. " -- James Tate]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402381-answers-i-began-two-hundred-hours-of-continuous-reading-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 12:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Leonard Michaels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402381-answers-i-began-two-hundred-hours-of-continuous-reading-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Answers
  
 I began two hundred hours of continuous reading in the twelve hours that remained before examinations. Melvin Bloom my roommate flipped the pages of his textbook in a sweet continuous trance. Reviewing the term's work was his pleasure. He went to sleep early. While he slept I bent into the night reading eating Benzedrine smoking cigarettes. Shrieking dwarfs charged across my notes. Crabs asked me questions. Melvin flipped a page blinked flipped another. He effected the same flipping and blinking with no textbook during examinations. For every question answers marched down his optical nerve neck arm and out onto his paper where they stopped in impeccable parade.  I'd look at my paper oily scratched by ratlike misery and I'd think of Melvin Bloom. I would think Oh God what is going to happen to me." -- Leonard Michaels]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
