<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/809150-mark-baker]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/809150-mark-baker" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 02:31:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83066-the-dream-by-mark-baker-a-man-lay-on-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 02:31:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Mark          Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83066-the-dream-by-mark-baker-a-man-lay-on-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Dream by Mark Baker

A man lay on his bed at the end of his life waiting to die.
His dream came to pay his last respects
and bid farewell to the man who had never used it.

As it entered the room the man looked down in shame.
&quot;Why did you not realize me?&quot; the dream asked.
&quot;Because I was afraid,&quot; the man said.
&quot;Afraid of what,&quot; said the dream.
&quot;I was afraid I would fail.&quot;

&quot;But haven't you failed by not attempting to use me?&quot;.
&quot;Yes I did, but I always thought there would be tomorrow.&quot;
&quot;You Fool!&quot; said the dream&quot; Did it never occur to you
that there was only ever today? the moment that you are in right now?

Do you think that now that death is here
that you can put it off until tomorrow?&quot;.
&quot;No&quot;, said the man, a tear gently rolling down his cheek.
The dream was softer now, because it knew that there were two types of pain,
the pain of discipline and the pain of regret,
and while discipline weighs ounces, regret weighs pounds.

Then the dream leant forward to gently wipe away the tear and said,
&quot; You need only have taken the first step
and I would have taken one to meet you,
for the only thing that ever separated us
was the belief in your mind that you couldn't have me&quot;.

Then they said goodbye and they both died." -- Mark          Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
