<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/810107-d-jennifer-dawson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/810107-d-jennifer-dawson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:14:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194795-it-s-not-all-bad-heightened-self-consciousness-apartness-an-inability-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:14:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Stephen Fry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194795-it-s-not-all-bad-heightened-self-consciousness-apartness-an-inability-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not all bad. Heightened self-consciousness, apartness, an inability to join in, physical shame and self-loathing—they are not all bad. Those devils have been my angels. Without them I would never have disappeared into language, literature, the mind, laughter and all the mad intensities that made and unmade me." -- Stephen Fry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130904-i-m-not-insecure-i-ve-been-through-way-too-much-f-king</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Drew Barrymore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130904-i-m-not-insecure-i-ve-been-through-way-too-much-f-king]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not insecure. I've been through way too much f**king sh*t to be insecure. I've got huge balls. But I've been humbled. That makes you grateful for every day you have." -- Drew Barrymore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431509-one-of-the-greatest-journeys-in-life-is-overcoming-insecurity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:14:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by J. A. Konrath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431509-one-of-the-greatest-journeys-in-life-is-overcoming-insecurity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the greatest journeys in life is overcoming insecurity and learning to truly not give a shit." -- J. A. Konrath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185900-everybody-sees-me-as-this-sullen-and-insecure-little-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:15:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Fiona Apple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185900-everybody-sees-me-as-this-sullen-and-insecure-little-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody sees me as this sullen and insecure little thing.  Those are just the sides of me that I feel necessary to show because no one else seems to be showing them." -- Fiona Apple]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247447-it-took-me-years-to-learn-to-sit-at-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:15:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Erica Jong]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247447-it-took-me-years-to-learn-to-sit-at-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It took me &lt;i&gt;years&lt;/i&gt; to learn to sit at my desk for more than two minutes at a time, to put up with the solitude and the terror of failure, and the godawful silence and the white paper. And now that I can take it . . . now that I can finally do it . . . I'm really raring to go. 

I was in my study writing. I was learning how to go down into myself and salvage bits and pieces of the past. I was learning how to sneak up on the unconscious and how to catch my seemingly random thoughts and fantasies. By closing me out of his world, Bennett had opened all sorts of worlds inside my own head. Gradually I began to realize that none of the subjects I wrote poems about engaged my deepest feelings, that there was a great chasm between what I cared about and what I wrote about. Why? What was I afraid of? Myself, most of all, it seemed.

&quot;Freedom is an illusion,&quot; Bennett would have said and, in a way, I too would have agreed. Sanity, moderation, hard work, stability . . . I believed in them too. But what was that other voice inside of me which kept urging me on toward zipless fucks, and speeding cars and endless wet kisses and guts full of danger? What was that other voice which kept calling me &lt;i&gt;coward!&lt;/i&gt; and egging me on to burn my bridges, to swallow the poison in one gulp instead of drop by drop, to go down into the bottom of my fear and see if I could pull myself up? Was it a voice? Or was it a thump? Something even more primitive than speech. A kind of pounding in my gut which I had nicknamed my &quot;hunger-thump.&quot; It was as if my stomach thought of itself as a heart. And no matter how I filled it—with men, with books, with food—it refused to be still. Unfillable—that's what I was. Nymphomania of the brain. Starvation of the heart." -- Erica Jong]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522538-the-hallmark-of-insecurity-is-bravado</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:17:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/522538-the-hallmark-of-insecurity-is-bravado]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The hallmark of insecurity is bravado." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405306-trust-and-faith-bring-joy-to-life-and-help-relationships</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:19:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Joyce Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405306-trust-and-faith-bring-joy-to-life-and-help-relationships]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trust and faith bring joy to life and help relationships grow to their maximum potential." -- Joyce Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405309-some-people-think-they-have-discernment-when-actually-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 05:19:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Joyce Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405309-some-people-think-they-have-discernment-when-actually-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people think they have discernment when actually they are just suspicious..

Suspicion comes out of the unrenewed mind; discernment comes out of the renewed spirit." -- Joyce Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217785-the-best-way-to-find-out-if-you-can-trust</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 08:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217785-the-best-way-to-find-out-if-you-can-trust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best way to find out if you can trust somebody is to trust them." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143093-follow-your-bliss-if-you-do-follow-your-bliss-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 20:56:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Joseph Campbell ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143093-follow-your-bliss-if-you-do-follow-your-bliss-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Follow your bliss.
If you do follow your bliss,
you put yourself on a kind of track
that has been there all the while waiting for you,
and the life you ought to be living
is the one you are living.
When you can see that,
you begin to meet people
who are in the field of your bliss,
and they open the doors to you.
I say, follow your bliss and don't be afraid,
and doors will open
where you didn't know they were going to be.
If you follow your bliss,
doors will open for you that wouldn't have opened for anyone else." -- Joseph Campbell ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331219-the-worst-part-of-life-is-waiting-the-best-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 04:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Jessica Brumley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/331219-the-worst-part-of-life-is-waiting-the-best-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part of life is waiting. The best part of life is having someone worth waiting for." -- Jessica Brumley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309542-a-rock-a-river-a-tree-hosts-to-species-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 10:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309542-a-rock-a-river-a-tree-hosts-to-species-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Rock, A River, A Tree
Hosts to species long since departed,
Mark the mastodon.
The dinosaur, who left dry tokens
Of their sojourn here
On our planet floor,
Any broad alarm of their of their hastening doom
Is lost in the gloom of dust and ages.
But today, the Rock cries out to us, clearly, forcefully,
Come, you may stand upon my
Back and face your distant destiny,
But seek no haven in my shadow.
I will give you no hiding place down here.
You, created only a little lower than
The angels, have crouched too long in
The bruising darkness,
Have lain too long
Face down in ignorance.
Your mouths spelling words
Armed for slaughter.
The rock cries out today, you may stand on me,
But do not hide your face.
Across the wall of the world,
A river sings a beautiful song,
Come rest here by my side.
Each of you a bordered country,
Delicate and strangely made proud,
Yet thrusting perpetually under siege.
Your armed struggles for profit
Have left collars of waste upon
My shore, currents of debris upon my breast.
Yet, today I call you to my riverside,
If you will study war no more.
Come, clad in peace and I will sing the songs
The Creator gave to me when I
And the tree and stone were one.
Before cynicism was a bloody sear across your brow
And when you yet knew you still knew nothing.
The river sings and sings on.
There is a true yearning to respond to
The singing river and the wise rock.
So say the Asian, the Hispanic, the Jew,
The African and Native American, the Sioux,
The Catholic, the Muslim, the French, the Greek,
The Irish, the Rabbi, the Priest, the Sheikh,
The Gay, the Straight, the Preacher,
The privileged, the homeless, the teacher.
They hear. They all hear
The speaking of the tree.
Today, the first and last of every tree
Speaks to humankind. Come to me, here beside the river.
Plant yourself beside me, here beside the river.
Each of you, descendant of some passed on
Traveller, has been paid for.
You, who gave me my first name,
You Pawnee, Apache and Seneca,
You Cherokee Nation, who rested with me,
Then forced on bloody feet,
Left me to the employment of other seekers--
Desperate for gain, starving for gold.
You, the Turk, the Swede, the German, the Scot...
You the Ashanti, the Yoruba, the Kru,
Bought, sold, stolen, arriving on a nightmare
Praying for a dream.
Here, root yourselves beside me.
I am the tree planted by the river,
Which will not be moved.
I, the rock, I the river, I the tree
I am yours--your passages have been paid.
Lift up your faces, you have a piercing need
For this bright morning dawning for you.
History, despite its wrenching pain,
Cannot be unlived, and if faced with courage,
Need not be lived again.
Lift up your eyes upon
The day breaking for you.
Give birth again
To the dream.
Women, children, men,
Take it into the palms of your hands.
Mold it into the shape of your most
Private need. Sculpt it into
The image of your most public self.
Lift up your hearts.
Each new hour holds new chances
For new beginnings.
Do not be wedded forever
To fear, yoked eternally
To brutishness.
The horizon leans forward,
Offering you space to place new steps of change.
Here, on the pulse of this fine day
You may have the courage
To look up and out upon me,
The rock, the river, the tree, your country.
No less to Midas than the mendicant.
No less to you now than the mastodon then.
Here on the pulse of this new day
You may have the grace to look up and out
And into your sister's eyes,
Into your brother's face, your country
And say simply
Very simply
With hope
Good morning." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199875-you-look-back-on-some-little-decision-you-made-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 03:33:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Mary Downing Hahn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/199875-you-look-back-on-some-little-decision-you-made-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You look back on some little decision you made and realize all the things that happened because of it, and you think to yourself &quot;if only I'd known,&quot; but, of course, you couldn't have known." -- Mary Downing Hahn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 13:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285424-the-first-week-of-august-hangs-at-the-very-top</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2013 19:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Natalie Babbitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285424-the-first-week-of-august-hangs-at-the-very-top]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first week of August hangs at the very top of the summer, the top of the live-long year, like the highest seat of a Ferris wheel when it pauses in its turning. The weeks that come before are only a climb from balmy spring, and those that follow a drop to the chill of autumn, but the first week of August is motionless, and hot. It is curiously silent, too, with blank white dawns and glaring noons, and sunsets smeared with too much color. Often at night there is lightning, but it quivers all alone. There is no thunder, no relieving rain. These are strange and breathless days, the dog days, when people are led to do things they are sure to be sorry for after." -- Natalie Babbitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/814183-it-was-far-better-he-thought-just-to-get-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2013 03:44:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[D. Jennifer add a quote by Anthony McDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/814183-it-was-far-better-he-thought-just-to-get-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was far better, he thought, just to get on with life yourself, to have your own adventures and make your own mistakes, without raising a banner over them that proclaimed: I'm this, or I'm that; of this party or of the other one." -- Anthony McDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
