<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/810965-patrick-nouhailler]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/810965-patrick-nouhailler" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:25:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319471-marriage-mating-and-love-are-socially-constructed-phenomena-that-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:25:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319471-marriage-mating-and-love-are-socially-constructed-phenomena-that-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marriage,&quot; &quot;mating,&quot; and &quot;love&quot; are socially constructed phenomena that have little or no transferable meaning outside any given culture. The examples we've noted of rampant ritualized group sex, mate-swapping, unrestrained casual affairs, and socially sanctioned sequential sex were all reported in cultures that anthropologists insist are monogamous simply because they've determined that something they call &quot;marriage&quot; takes place there. No wonder so many insist that marriage, monogamy, and the nuclear family are human universals. With such all-encompassing interpretations of the concepts, even the prairie vole, who &quot;sleeps with anyone,&quot; would qualify." -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305734-and-yet-despite-repeated-assurances-that-women-aren-t-particularly-sexual</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305734-and-yet-despite-repeated-assurances-that-women-aren-t-particularly-sexual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet, despite repeated assurances that women aren't particularly sexual creatures, in cultures around the world men have gone to extraordinary lengths to control female libido: female genital mutilation, head-to-toe chadors, medieval witch burnings, chastity belts, suffocating corsets, muttered insults about &quot;insatiable&quot; whores, pathologizing, paternalistic medical diagnoses of nymphomania or hysteria, the debilitating scorn heaped on any female who chooses to be generous with her sexuality...all parts of a worldwide campaign to keep the supposedly low-key female libido under control. Why the electrified high-security razor-wire fence to contain a kitty-cat?" -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305740-poverty-is-not-a-certain-small-amount-of-goods-nor</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:27:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305740-poverty-is-not-a-certain-small-amount-of-goods-nor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poverty is not a certain small amount of goods, nor is it just a relation between means and ends; above all it is a relation between people. Poverty is a social status. As such it is the invention of civilization. Socrates made the same point 2,400 years ago: &quot;He is richest who is content with least, for contentment is the wealth of nature." -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305747-though-many-strive-to-hide-their-human-libidinousness-from-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305747-though-many-strive-to-hide-their-human-libidinousness-from-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though many strive to hide their human libidinousness from themselves and each other, being a force of nature, it breaks through. Lots of uptight, proper Americans were scandalized by the way Elvis moved his hips when he sang &quot;rock and roll.&quot; But how many realized what the phrase rock and roll meant? Cultural historian Michael Ventura, investigating the roots of African-American music, found that rock 'n' roll was a term that originated in the juke joints of the South. Long in use by the time Elvis appeared, Ventura explains the phrase &quot;hadn't meant the name of a music, it meant 'to fuck.' 'Rock,' by itself, has pretty much meant that, in those circles, since the twenties at least.&quot; By the mid-1950s, when the phrase was becoming widely used in mainstream culture, Ventura says the disc jockeys &quot;either didn't know what they were saying or were too sly to admit what they knew." -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305735-nor-do-the-females-of-our-closest-primate-cousins-offer</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:29:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305735-nor-do-the-females-of-our-closest-primate-cousins-offer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor do the females of our closest primate cousins offer much reason to believe the human female should be sexually reluctant due to purely biological concerns. Instead, primatologist Meredith Small has noted that female primates are highly attracted to novelty in mating. Unfamiliar males appear to attract females more than known males with any other characteristic a male might offer (high status, large size, coloration, frequent grooming, hairy chest, gold chains, pinky ring, whatever). Small writes, &quot;The only consistent interest seen among the general primate population is an interest in novelty and variety...In fact,&quot; she reports, &quot;the search for the unfamiliar is documented as a female preference more often than is any other characteristic our human eyes can perceive." -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305745-as-attentive-readers-may-have-noted-the-standard-narrative-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305745-as-attentive-readers-may-have-noted-the-standard-narrative-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As attentive readers may have noted, the standard narrative of heterosexual interaction boils down to prostitution: a woman exchanges her sexual services for access to resources. Maybe mythic resonance explains part of the huge box-office appeal of a film like Pretty Woman, where Richard Gere's character trades access to his wealth in exchange for what Julia Roberts's character has to offer (she plays a hooker with a heart of gold, if you missed it). Please note that what she's got to offer is limited to the aforementioned heart of gold, a smile as big as Texas, a pair of long, lovely legs, and the solemn promise that they'll open only for him from now on. The genius of Pretty Woman lies in making explicit what's been implicit in hundreds of films and books. According to this theory, women have evolved to unthinkingly and unashamedly exchange erotic pleasure for access to a man's wealth, protection, status, and other treasures likely to benefit her and her children." -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352974-could-it-be-that-the-atomic-isolation-of-the-husband</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 23:30:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Patrick add a quote by Christopher Ryan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352974-could-it-be-that-the-atomic-isolation-of-the-husband]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Could it be that the atomic isolation of the husband and wife nucleus with an orbiting child or two is in fact a culturally imposed aberration for our species? As ill-suited to our evolved tendencies as corsets, chastity belts, and suits of armor? ...a distorted and distorting family structure inappropriate for our species?" -- Christopher Ryan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
