<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/811789-jeff-alan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/811789-jeff-alan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 15:30:24 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19468-bring-it-home-all-right-let-s-bring-it-home-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 15:30:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Sam Phillips]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19468-bring-it-home-all-right-let-s-bring-it-home-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bring it home? All right, let's bring it home. If you was hit by a truck and you was lying out there in that gutter dying, and you had time to sing &lt;i&gt;one&lt;/i&gt; song, one song that people would remember before you're dirt, one song that would let God know how you felt about your time here on Earth, one song that would sum you up -- you tellin' me that's the song you'd sing? That same Jimmy Davis tune we hear on the radio all day, about your peace within, and how it's real, and how you're gonna shout it? Or... would you sing somethin' different. Somethin' real. Somethin' &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; felt. Cause I'm tellin' you right now, that's the kind of song people want to hear. That's the kind of song that truly saves people." -- Sam Phillips]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19147-nobody-reads-poetry-we-are-told-at-every-inopportune-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2008 10:55:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by C.D. Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19147-nobody-reads-poetry-we-are-told-at-every-inopportune-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody reads poetry, we are told at every inopportune moment.  I read poetry.  I am somebody.  I am the people, too.  It can be allowed that an industrious quantity of contemporary American poetry is consciously written for a hermetic constituency; the bulk is written for the bourgeoisie, leaving a lean cut for labor.  Only the hermetically aimed has a snowball's chance in hell of reaching its intended ears.  One proceeds from this realization.  A staggering figure of vibrant, intelligent people can and do live without poetry, especially without the poetry of their time.  This figure includes the unemployed, the rank and file, the union brass, banker, scientist, lawyer, doctor, architect, pilot, and priest.  It also includes most academics, most of the faculty of the humanities, most allegedly literary editors and most allegedly literary critics.  They do so--go forward in their lives, toward their great reward, in an engulfing absence of poetry--without being perceived or perceiving themselves as hobbled or deficient in any significant way.  It is nearly true, though I am often reminded of a Transtromer broadside I saw in a crummy office building in San Francisco:

 

We got dressed and showed the house

You live well the visitor said

The slum must be inside you.

 

If I wanted to understand a culture, my own for instance, and if I thought such an understanding were the basis for a lifelong inquiry, I would turn to poetry first.  For it is my confirmed bias that the poets remain the most 'stunned by existence,' the most determined to redeem the world in words.." -- C.D. Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:06:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:06:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:11:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/512-there-is-no-greater-agony-than-bearing-an-untold-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978-whether-you-think-you-can-or-you-think-you-can-t--you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:13:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Henry Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/978-whether-you-think-you-can-or-you-think-you-can-t--you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether you think you can, or you think you can't--you're right." -- Henry Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:14:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
