<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/811818-luna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/811818-luna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 19:38:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 19:38:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93352-te-occidere-possunt-sed-te-edere-non-possunt-nefas-est]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Te Occidere Possunt Sed Te Edere Non Possunt Nefas Est&quot; (&quot;They can kill you, but the legalities of eating you are quite a bit dicier&quot;)." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258661---and-then-you-re-in-serious-trouble-very-serious-trouble-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 19:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258661---and-then-you-re-in-serious-trouble-very-serious-trouble-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["--and then you're in serious trouble, very serious trouble, and you know it, finally, deadly serious trouble, because this Substance you thought was your one true friend, that you gave up all for, gladly, that for so long gave you relief from the pain of the Losses your love of that relief caused, your mother and lover and god and compadre, has finally removed its smily-face mask to reveal centerless eyes and a ravening maw, and canines down to here, it's the Face In The Floor, the grinning root-white face of your worst nightmares, and the face is your own face in the mirror, now, it's you, the Substance has devoured or replaced and become you, and the puke-, drool- and Substance-crusted T-shirt you've both worn for weeks now gets torn off and you stand there looking and in the root-white chest where your heart (given away to It) should be beating, in its exposed chest's center and centerless eyes is just a lightless hole, more teeth, and a beckoning taloned hand dangling something irresistible, and now you see you've been had, screwed royal, stripped and fucked and tossed to the side like some stuffed toy to lie for all time in the posture you land in. You see now that It's your enemy and your worst personal nightmare and the trouble It's gotten you into is undeniable and you still can't stop. Doing the Substance now is like attending Black Mass but you still can't stop, even though the Substance no longer gets you high. You are, as they say, Finished. You cannot get drunk and you cannot get sober; you cannot get high and you cannot get straight. You are behind bars; you are in a cage and can see only bars in every direction. You are in the kind of a hell of a mess that either ends lives or turns them around." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 19:51:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29121-it-s-not-the-content-of-our-dreams-that-gives-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 14:01:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luna add a quote by Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29121-it-s-not-the-content-of-our-dreams-that-gives-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the content of our dreams that gives our second heart its dark color; it's the thoughts that go through our heads in those wakeful moments when sleep won't come. And those are the things we never tell anyone at all." -- Carolyn Parkhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
