<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/812008-cathy-pearl]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/812008-cathy-pearl" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 08:18:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146164-until-the-millennium-arrives-and-countries-cease-trying-to-enslave</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2012 08:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by E.B. Sledge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146164-until-the-millennium-arrives-and-countries-cease-trying-to-enslave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until the millennium arrives and countries cease trying to enslave others, it will be necessary to accept one's responsibilities and be willing to make sacrifices for one's country - as my comrades did. As the troops used to say, &quot;If the country is good enough to live in, it's good enough to fight for.&quot; With privilege goes responsibility." -- E.B. Sledge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473466-many-years-ago-when-i-used-to-smoke-my-lighter</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 17:50:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Stephanie Pearl-McPhee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473466-many-years-ago-when-i-used-to-smoke-my-lighter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many years ago, when I used to smoke, my lighter was often easier to find than my scissors. If I couldn't find the scissors, or was feeling too lazy to get up, I used the lighter to burn the yarn in one place to break it. Other than the smell, this worked fairly well. Later, when I found my scissors, I would cut off the little charred bits.

One day, I was knitting a cotton facecloth and needed to cut the end. I flicked my lighter, expecting to singe the one spot, thus breaking the yarn.

&lt;i&gt;I will remember that cotton is highly flammable, and that the knitting Fates punish laziness. I will also remember that a flaming facecloth can be extinguished with a cup of coffee...in a pinch." -- Stephanie Pearl-McPhee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473464-as-long-as-there-has-been-knitting-there-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 17:51:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cathy add a quote by Stephanie Pearl-McPhee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473464-as-long-as-there-has-been-knitting-there-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As long as there has been knitting there have been battles about it. There are self-declared &quot;yarn snobs,&quot; who frown on using anything but natural fibers; &quot;gauge snobs&quot;, who wouldn't be caught dead with chunky yarn; and &quot;experience snobs&quot;, who claim you can't declare yourself a real knitter until you abandon novelty yarns. The truth is that the knitting world is a tiny metaphor for the real world. It takes all kinds.

&lt;i&gt;I will not allow myself to feel bad if someone disapproves of my knitting. I will also resist the urge to stuff his mailbox full of chunky acrylic fun fur at 3:00 am.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Stephanie Pearl-McPhee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
