<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/813482-adina-cappell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/813482-adina-cappell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 22:38:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2531-i-am-no-king-and-i-am-no-lord-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 22:38:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2531-i-am-no-king-and-i-am-no-lord-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am no king, and I am no lord,
And I am no soldier at-arms,&quot; said he.
&quot;I'm none but a harper, and a very poor harper,
That am come hither to wed with ye.&quot;

&quot;If you were a lord, you should be my lord,
And the same if you were a thief,&quot; said she.
&quot;And if you are a harper, you shall be my harper,
For it makes no matter to me, to me,
For it makes no matter to me.&quot;

&quot;But what if it prove that I am no harper?
That I lied for your love most monstrously?&quot;

&quot;Why, then I'll teach you to play and sing,
For I dearly love a good harp,&quot; said she." -- Peter S. Beagle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4694-first-they-ignore-you-then-they-ridicule-you-then-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 17:02:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4694-first-they-ignore-you-then-they-ridicule-you-then-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First they ignore you, then they ridicule you, then they fight you, and then you win." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024915-richard-was-never-as-squeamish-as-he-thought-he-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 01:49:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Gaiman Neil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1024915-richard-was-never-as-squeamish-as-he-thought-he-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Richard was never as squeamish as he thought he was. Or rather, he was squeamish when it came to blood on screen: a good zombie movie or even an explicit medical drama would leave him huddled in a corner, hyperventilating, with his hands over his eyes, muttering things like &quot;Just tell me when it's over.&quot; But when it came to real blood, real pain, he simply did something about it." -- Gaiman Neil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2012 09:10:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6703-i-always-deserve-the-best-treatment-because-i-never-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 19:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6703-i-always-deserve-the-best-treatment-because-i-never-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always deserve the best treatment because I never put up with any other." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541995-she-found-out-that-having-something-to-do-prevented-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 18:58:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541995-she-found-out-that-having-something-to-do-prevented-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She found out that having something to do prevented you from feeling seasick, and that even a job like scrubbing a deck could be satisfying, if it was done in a seamanlike way. She was very taken with this notion, and later on she folded the blankets on her bunk in a seamanlike way, and put her possessions in the closet in a seamanlike way, and used 'stow' instead of 'tidy' for the process of doing so. After two days at sea, Lyra decided that this was the life for her." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9746-when-i-was-young-i-admired-clever-people-now-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 21:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9746-when-i-was-young-i-admired-clever-people-now-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was young, I admired clever people. Now that I am old, I admire kind people." -- Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20924-when-you-look-at-what-c-s-lewis-is-saying-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 18:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20924-when-you-look-at-what-c-s-lewis-is-saying-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you look at what C.S. Lewis is saying, his message is so anti-life, so cruel, so unjust. The view that the Narnia books have for the material world is one of almost undisguised contempt. At one point, the old professor says, ‘It’s all in Plato’ — meaning that the physical world we see around us is the crude, shabby, imperfect, second-rate copy of something much better. I want to emphasize the simple physical truth of things, the absolute primacy of the material life, rather than the spiritual or the afterlife.

[&lt;i&gt;The New York Times interview, 2000&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23834-april-is-the-cruelest-month-breeding-lilacs-out-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 02:56:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23834-april-is-the-cruelest-month-breeding-lilacs-out-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["April is the cruelest month, breeding
lilacs out of the dead land, mixing
memory and desire, stirring
dull roots with spring rain." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 02:56:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38534-april-is-the-cruelest-month-t-s-eliot-wrote-by-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["April is the cruelest month, T.S. Eliot wrote, by which I think he meant (among other things) that springtime makes people crazy. We expect too much, the world burgeons with promises it can't keep, all passion is really a setup, and we're doomed to get our hearts broken yet again. I agree, and would further add: Who cares? Every spring I go out there anyway, around the bend, unconditionally. ... Come the end of the dark days, I am more than joyful. I'm nuts. " -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543805-on-writing-there-s-a-great-quote-by-julius-irving-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 23:26:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by David Halberstam]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543805-on-writing-there-s-a-great-quote-by-julius-irving-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[On writing:] &quot;There's a great quote by Julius Irving that went, 'Being a professional is doing the things you love to do, on the days you don't feel like doing them.'&quot;

(&lt;i&gt;One On 1&lt;/i&gt;, interview with Budd Mishkin; &lt;i&gt;NY1&lt;/i&gt;, March 25, 2007.)" -- David Halberstam]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35055-a-facility-for-quotation-covers-the-absence-of-original-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 17:31:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Dorothy Sayers ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35055-a-facility-for-quotation-covers-the-absence-of-original-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A facility for quotation covers the absence of original thought." -- Dorothy Sayers ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545640-it-s-not-the-innocent-young-things-that-need-gentle-handling--it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 11:15:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/545640-it-s-not-the-innocent-young-things-that-need-gentle-handling--it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the innocent young things that need gentle handling--it's the ones that have been frightened and hurt." -- Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 23:35:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1928-if-you-re-looking-for-sympathy-you-ll-find-it-between-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're looking for sympathy you'll find it between shit and syphilis in the dictionary." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137080-if-you-aren-t-cute-you-may-as-well-be-clever</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2012 23:36:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137080-if-you-aren-t-cute-you-may-as-well-be-clever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you aren't cute, you may as well be clever." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 06:54:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 06:54:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4964-love-is-that-condition-in-which-the-happiness-of-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 06:22:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2409-and-now-cried-max-let-the-wild-rumpus-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 11:14:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2409-and-now-cried-max-let-the-wild-rumpus-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now,&quot; cried Max, &quot;let the wild rumpus start!" -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 16:49:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71624-there-was-a-girl-and-her-uncle-sold-her-put]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a girl, and her uncle sold her. Put like that it seems so simple.

No man, proclaimed Donne, is an island, and he was wrong. If we were not islands, we would be lost, drowned in each other's tragedies. We are insulated (a word that means, literally, remember, made into an island) from the tragedy of others, by our island nature and by the repetitive shape and form of the stories. The shape does not change: there was a human being who was born, lived and then by some means or other, died. There. You may fill in the details from your own experience. As unoriginal as any other tale, as unique as any other life. Lives are snowflakes- forming patterns we have seen before, as like one another as peas in a pod (and have you ever looked at peas in a pod? I mean, really looked at them? There's not a chance you'll mistake one for another, after a minute's close inspection) but still unique.

Without individuals we see only numbers, a thousand dead, a hundred thousand dead, &quot;casualties may rise to a million.&quot; With individual stories, the statistics become people- but even that is a lie, for the people continue to suffer in numbers that themselves are numbing and meaningless. Look, see the child's swollen, swollen belly and the flies that crawl at the corners of his eyes, this skeletal limbs: will it make it easier for you to know his name, his age, his dreams, his fears? To see him from the inside? And if it does, are we not doing a disservice to his sister, who lies in the searing dust beside him, a distorted distended caricature of a human child? And there, if we feel for them, are they now more important to us than a thousand other children touched by the same famine, a thousand other young lives who will soon be food for the flies' own myriad squirming children?

We draw our lines around these moments of pain, remain upon our islands, and they cannot hurt us. They are covered with a smooth, safe, nacreous layer to let them slip, pearllike, from our souls without real pain.

Fiction allows us to slide into these other heads, these other places, and look out through other eyes. And then in the tale we stop before we die, or we die vicariously and unharmed, and in the world beyond the tale we turn the page or close the book, and we resume our lives.

A life that is, like any other, unlike any other.

And the simple truth is this: There was a girl, and her uncle sold her." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2012 01:17:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Federico García Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To burn with desire and keep quiet about it is the greatest punishment we can bring on ourselves." -- Federico García Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 03:12:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569242-the-common-mistake-that-bullies-make-is-assuming-that-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 14:37:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Mary Elizabeth Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/569242-the-common-mistake-that-bullies-make-is-assuming-that-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The common mistake that bullies make is assuming that because someone is nice that he or she is weak. Those traits have nothing to do with each other. In fact, it takes considerable strength and character to be a good person." -- Mary Elizabeth Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66772-never-love-a-wild-thing-mr-bell-holly-advised-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2012 19:23:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66772-never-love-a-wild-thing-mr-bell-holly-advised-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never love a wild thing, Mr. Bell,' Holly advised him. 'That was Doc's mistake. He was always lugging home wild things. A hawk with a hurt wing. One time it was a full-grown bobcat with a broken leg. But you can't give your heart to a wild thing: the more you do, the stronger they get. Until they're strong enough to run into the woods. Or fly into a tree. Then a taller tree. Then the sky. That's how you'll end up, Mr. Bell. If you let yourself love a wild thing. You'll end up looking at the sky.&quot;
&quot;She's drunk,&quot; Joe Bell informed me. 
&quot;Moderately,&quot; Holly confessed....Holly lifted her martini. &quot;Let's wish the Doc luck, too,&quot; she said, touching her glass against mine. &quot;Good luck: and believe me, dearest Doc -- it's better to look at the sky than live there. Such an empty place; so vague. Just a country where the thunder goes and things disappear." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570565-her-pretty-name-of-adina-seemed-to-me-to-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:36:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570565-her-pretty-name-of-adina-seemed-to-me-to-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her pretty name of Adina seemed to me to have somehow a mystic fitness to her personality. 

Behind a cold shyness, there seemed to lurk a tremulous promise to be franker when she knew you better.

Adina is a strange child; she is fanciful without being capricious.

She was stout and fresh-coloured, she laughed and talked rather loud, and generally, in galleries and temples, caused a good many stiff British necks to turn round.

She had a mania for excursions, and at Frascati and Tivoli she inflicted her good-humoured ponderosity on diminutive donkeys with a relish which seemed to prove that a passion for scenery, like all our passions, is capable of making the best of us pitiless. 

Adina may not have the shoulders of the Venus of Milo...but I hope it will take more than a bauble like this to make her stoop.

Adina espied the first violet of the year glimmering at the root of a cypress. She made haste to rise and gather it, and then wandered further, in the hope of giving it a few companions. Scrope sat and watched her as she moved slowly away, trailing her long shadow on the grass and drooping her head from side to side in her charming quest. It was not, I know, that he felt no impulse to join her; but that he was in love, for the moment, with looking at her from where he sat. Her search carried her some distance and at last she passed out of sight behind a bend in the villa wall.

I don't pretend to be sure that I was particularly struck, from this time forward, with something strange in our quiet Adina. She had always seemed to me vaguely, innocently strange; it was part of her charm that in the daily noiseless movement of her life a mystic undertone seemed to murmur &quot;You don't half know me! Perhaps we three prosaic mortals were not quite worthy to know her: yet I believe that if a practised man of the world had whispered to me, one day, over his wine, after Miss Waddington had rustled away from the table, that there was a young lady who, sooner or later, would treat her friends to a first class surprise, I should have laid my finger on his sleeve and told him with a smile that he phrased my own thought. ..&quot;That beautiful girl,&quot; I said, &quot;seems to me agitated and preoccupied.&quot;

&quot;That beautiful girl is a puzzle. I don't know what's the matter with her; it's all very painful; she's a very strange creature. I never dreamed there was an obstacle to our happiness--to our union. She has never protested and promised; it's not her way, nor her nature; she is always humble, passive, gentle; but always extremely grateful for every sign of tenderness. Till within three or four days ago, she seemed to me more so than ever; her habitual gentleness took the form of a sort of shrinking, almost suffering, deprecation of my attentions, my petits soins, my lovers nonsense. It was as if they oppressed and mortified her--and she would have liked me to bear more lightly. I did not see directly that it was not the excess of my devotion, but my devotion itself--the very fact of my love and her engagement that pained her. When I did it was a blow in the face. I don't know what under heaven I've done! Women are fathomless creatures. And yet Adina is not capricious, in the common sense...

.So these are peines d'amour?&quot; he went on, after brooding a moment. &quot;I didn't know how fiercely I was in love!&quot; 

Scrope stood staring at her as she thrust out the crumpled note: that she meant that Adina--that Adina had left us in the night--was too large a horror for his unprepared sense....&quot;Good-bye to everything! Think me crazy if you will. I could never explain. Only forget me and believe that I am happy, happy, happy! Adina Beati.&quot;...

Love is said to be par excellence the egotistical passion; if so Adina was far gone. &quot;I can't promise to forget you,&quot; I said; &quot;you and my friend here deserve to be remembered!" -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578690-shut-up-let-me-tell-you-let-me-every-time-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 12:11:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Louis C.K.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578690-shut-up-let-me-tell-you-let-me-every-time-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Shut up…let me tell you, LET ME. Every time I look at your face or even remember it, it wrecks me. And the way you are with me and you’re just fun and you shit all over me and you make fun of me and you’re real. I don’t have enough time in any day to think about you enough...I don’t even think about women anymore. I think about you." -- Louis C.K.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 03:41:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144999-she-was-a-girl-who-knew-how-to-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 03:41:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144999-she-was-a-girl-who-knew-how-to-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a girl who knew how to be happy even when she was sad. And that’s important—you know " -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188073-you-believe-lies-so-you-eventually-learn-to-trust-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 03:41:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188073-you-believe-lies-so-you-eventually-learn-to-trust-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223913-like-all-of-my-friends-she-s-a-lousy-judge-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 14:41:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Adina add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223913-like-all-of-my-friends-she-s-a-lousy-judge-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all of my friends, she's a lousy judge of character." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
