<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/813888-suzy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/813888-suzy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:56:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20419-to-see-a-world-in-a-grain-of-sand-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:56:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20419-to-see-a-world-in-a-grain-of-sand-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To see a World in a Grain of Sand 
And a Heaven in a Wild Flower, 
Hold Infinity in the palm of your hand 
And Eternity in an hour." -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:57:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6766-i-can-listen-no-longer-in-silence-i-must-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can listen no longer in silence.  I must speak to you by such means as are within my reach.  You pierce my soul.  I am half agony, half hope.  Tell me not that I am too late, that such precious feelings are gone for ever.  I offer myself to you again with a heart even more your own than when you almost broke it, eight years and a half ago.  Dare not say that man forgets sooner than  woman, that his love has an earlier death.  I have loved none but you. Unjust I may have been, weak and resentful I have been, but never inconstant.  You alone have brought me to Bath. For you alone, I think and plan.  Have you not seen this? Can you fail to have understood my wishes?  I had not waited even these ten days, could I have read your feelings, as I think you must have penetrated mine.  I can hardly write.  I am every instant hearing something which overpowers me.  You sink your voice, but I can distinguish the tones of that voice when they would be lost on others. Too good, too excellent creature!  You do us justice, indeed. You do believe that there is true attachment and constancy among men. Believe it to be most fervent, most undeviating, in F. W.

I must go, uncertain of my fate; but I shall return hither, or follow your party, as soon as possible.  A word, a look, will be enough to decide whether I enter your father's house this evening or never." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13563-i-am-the-master-of-my-fate-i-am-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:57:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by William Ernest Henley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13563-i-am-the-master-of-my-fate-i-am-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the master of my fate;
I am the captain of my soul." -- William Ernest Henley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7838-veni-vidi-vici-i-came-i-saw-i-conquered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 20:59:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Julius Caesar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7838-veni-vidi-vici-i-came-i-saw-i-conquered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Veni, vidi, vici. (&lt;i&gt;I came, I saw, I conquered&lt;/i&gt;.)" -- Julius Caesar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750-fear-not-death-for-the-sooner-we-die-the-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 21:00:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750-fear-not-death-for-the-sooner-we-die-the-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fear not death for the sooner we die, the longer we shall be immortal." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6017-i-believe-that-the-most-important-single-thing-beyond-discipline</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 21:06:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6017-i-believe-that-the-most-important-single-thing-beyond-discipline]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that the most important single thing, beyond discipline and creativity is daring to dare." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11745-do-not-go-gentle-into-that-good-night-old-age</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:26:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Dylan Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11745-do-not-go-gentle-into-that-good-night-old-age]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not go gentle into that good night,
Old age should burn and rave at close of day;
Rage, rage against the dying of the light." -- Dylan Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7241-better-to-reign-in-hell-than-to-serve-in-heaven</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:34:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7241-better-to-reign-in-hell-than-to-serve-in-heaven]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to reign in Hell, than to serve in Heaven." -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3922-cogito-ergo-sum-i-think-therefore-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:35:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by René Descartes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3922-cogito-ergo-sum-i-think-therefore-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cogito ergo sum.    &lt;i&gt;(I think, therefore I am.)&lt;/i&gt;" -- René Descartes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145825-faith-n-belief-without-evidence-in-what-is-told-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:35:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145825-faith-n-belief-without-evidence-in-what-is-told-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Faith, n.&lt;/b&gt; Belief without evidence in what is told by one who speaks without knowledge, of things without parallel." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2008 17:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:50:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151-a-casual-stroll-through-the-lunatic-asylum-shows-that-faith</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:51:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1151-a-casual-stroll-through-the-lunatic-asylum-shows-that-faith]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A casual stroll through the lunatic asylum shows that faith does not prove anything." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053-to-you-i-m-an-atheist-to-god-i-m-the-loyal</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:51:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053-to-you-i-m-an-atheist-to-god-i-m-the-loyal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To you, I'm an atheist.
To God, I'm the loyal opposition." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4416-we-are-all-atheists-about-most-of-the-gods-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:52:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4416-we-are-all-atheists-about-most-of-the-gods-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all atheists about most of the gods that humanity has ever believed in. Some of us just go one god further." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2348-i-d-take-the-awe-of-understanding-over-the-awe-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:52:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2348-i-d-take-the-awe-of-understanding-over-the-awe-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd take the awe of understanding over the awe of ignorance any day." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:52:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All thinking men are atheists." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:53:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63481-religion-has-convinced-people-that-there-s-an-invisible-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion has convinced people that there's an invisible man ... living in the sky. Who watches everything you do every minute of every day. And the invisible man has a list of ten specific things he doesn't want you to do. And if you do any of these things, he will send you to a special place, of burning and fire and smoke and torture and anguish for you to live forever, and suffer, and suffer, and burn, and scream, until the end of time. But he loves you. He loves you. He loves you and he needs money." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16743-one-would-go-mad-if-one-took-the-bible-seriously</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:53:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Aleister Crowley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16743-one-would-go-mad-if-one-took-the-bible-seriously]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One would go mad if one took the Bible seriously; but to take it seriously one must be already mad." -- Aleister Crowley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:54:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9180-stood-in-firelight-sweltering-bloodstain-on-chest-like-map-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stood in firelight, sweltering. Bloodstain on chest like map of violent new continent. Felt cleansed. Felt dark planet turn under my feet and knew what cats know that makes them scream like babies in night.

Looked at sky through smoke heavy with human fat and God was not there. The cold, suffocating dark goes on forever and we are alone. Live our lives, lacking anything better to do. Devise reason later. Born from oblivion; bear children, hell-bound as ourselves, go into oblivion. There is nothing else.

Existence is random. Has no pattern save what we imagine after staring at it for too long. No meaning save what we choose to impose. This rudderless world is not shaped by vague metaphysical forces. It is not God who kills the children. Not fate that butchers them or destiny that feeds them to the dogs. It’s us. Only us. Streets stank of fire. The void breathed hard on my heart, turning its illusions to ice, shattering them. Was reborn then, free to scrawl own design on this morally blank world.

Was Rorschach.

Does that answer your Questions, Doctor?" -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:11:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75949-there-have-been-five-great-kisses-since-1642-b-c-before-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75949-there-have-been-five-great-kisses-since-1642-b-c-before-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There have been five great kisses since 1642 B.C...(before then couples hooked thumbs.) And the precise rating of kisses is a terribly difficult thing, often leading to great controversy.... Well, this one left them all behind." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10920-i-wanted-the-whole-world-or-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2008 00:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10920-i-wanted-the-whole-world-or-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted the whole world or nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67732-my-daughter-is-seven-and-some-of-the-other-second-grade</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 22:30:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Anne Fadiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67732-my-daughter-is-seven-and-some-of-the-other-second-grade]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My daughter is seven, and some of the other second-grade parents complain that their children don't read for pleasure. When I visit their homes, the children's rooms are crammed with expensive books, but the parent's rooms are empty. Those children do not see their parents reading, as I did every day of my childhood. By contrast, when I walk into an apartment with books on the shelves, books on the bedside tables, books on the floor, and books on the toilet tank, then I know what I would see if I opened the door that says 'PRIVATE--GROWNUPS KEEP OUT': a child sprawled on the bed, reading." -- Anne Fadiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8017-ireland-is-a-land-of-poets-and-legends-of-dreamers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 05:34:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8017-ireland-is-a-land-of-poets-and-legends-of-dreamers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ireland is a land of poets and legends, of dreamers and rebels. All of these have music woven through and around them. Tunes for dancing or for weeping, for battle or for love." -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8532-damn-me-to-hell-or-take-me-to-heaven-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 05:34:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8532-damn-me-to-hell-or-take-me-to-heaven-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Damn me to hell or take me to heaven, but for Gods sake, do it now...." -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63196-excuse-me-tonight-you-represent-every-dateless-woman-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 05:35:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63196-excuse-me-tonight-you-represent-every-dateless-woman-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Excuse me? Tonight you represent every dateless woman in this city, every woman who's about to sit down to a lonely meal of Weight Watchers past primavera she's just nuked in the microwave. Every woman who will get into bed tonight with a book or reruns of Sex and the City as her only companion. You are our shining hope....But no pressure." -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23825-why-couldn-t-the-merciful-god-turn-down-the-sunlight-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 05:35:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Nora Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23825-why-couldn-t-the-merciful-god-turn-down-the-sunlight-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why couldn't the merciful God turn down the sunlight so it wasn't blasting like a red furnace against his aching eyes? Because he'd worshipped the god of beer, thats why. He'd broken a commandment and worshipped the false and foamy god of beer. And now he was being punished." -- Nora Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95616-first-with-the-head-then-with-the-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 05:39:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Suzy add a quote by Bryce Courtenay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95616-first-with-the-head-then-with-the-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First with the head, then with the heart." -- Bryce Courtenay]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
