<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/815734-david]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/815734-david" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:31:05 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642973-but-the-fevers-are-on-me-now-the-virus-mad</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Monette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/642973-but-the-fevers-are-on-me-now-the-virus-mad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the fevers are on me now, the virus mad to ravage my last fifty T cells. It's hard to keep the memory at full dazzle, with so much loss to mock it. Roger gone, Craig gone, Cesar gone, Stevie gone. And this feeling that I'm the last one left, in a world where only the ghosts still laugh. But at least they're the ghosts of full-grown men, proof that all of us got that far, free of the traps and the lies. And from that moment on the brink of summer's end, no one would ever tell me again that men like me couldn't love." -- Paul Monette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440993-don-t-let-anyone-tell-you-that-the-truth-can-t-disappear</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:31:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Monette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440993-don-t-let-anyone-tell-you-that-the-truth-can-t-disappear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't let anyone tell you that the truth can't disappear. If I believe in anything, rather than God, is that I am part of something that goes all the way back to Antigone, and that whatever speaks the truth of our hearts can only make us stronger. Can only give us the power to counter the hate and bigotry and heal this addled world.
Just remember: You are not alone." -- Paul Monette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440992-the-struggle-for-true-openness-and-intimacy-is-a-lifelong</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:31:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Monette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440992-the-struggle-for-true-openness-and-intimacy-is-a-lifelong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The struggle for true openness and intimacy is a lifelong struggle for all of us, gay and straight alike. And besides, a difficult life brings you to the core of yourself, where you learn what justice is and how it has to be fought for." -- Paul Monette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690426-grief-is-a-sword-or-it-is-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:31:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Paul Monette]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/690426-grief-is-a-sword-or-it-is-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief is a sword, or it is nothing." -- Paul Monette]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71634-few-will-have-the-greatness-to-bend-history-itself-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:32:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71634-few-will-have-the-greatness-to-bend-history-itself-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few will have the greatness to bend history itself, but each of us can work to change a small portion of events.  It is from numberless diverse acts of courage and belief that human history is shaped. Each time a man stands up for an ideal, or acts to improve the lot of others, or strikes out against injustice, he sends forth a tiny ripple of hope, and crossing each other from a million different centers of energy and daring those ripples build a current which can sweep down the mightiest walls of oppression and resistance." -- Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15709-lets-dedicate-ourselves-to-what-the-ancient-greeks-wrote-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:32:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert F. Kennedy ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15709-lets-dedicate-ourselves-to-what-the-ancient-greeks-wrote-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lets dedicate ourselves to what the ancient greeks wrote so many years ago, to tame the savageness of man and make gentle the life of this world. Let us dedicate ourselves to that" -- Robert F. Kennedy ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35953-let-no-one-be-discouraged-by-the-belief-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:33:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35953-let-no-one-be-discouraged-by-the-belief-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let no one be discouraged by the belief there is nothing one person can do against the enormous array of the world's ills, misery, ignorance, and violence.  Few will have the greatness to bend history, but each of us can work to change a small portion of events.  And in the total of all those acts will be written the history of a generation." -- Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106459-we-can-move-in-that-direction-as-a-country-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 16:33:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106459-we-can-move-in-that-direction-as-a-country-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can move in that direction as a country, in greater polarization - black people amongst blacks, and white amongst whites, filled with hatred toward one another. Or we can make an effort, as Martin Luther King did, to understand and to comprehend, and replace that violence, that stain of bloodshed that has spread across our land, with an effort to understand, compassion and love.... What we need in the United States is not division; what we need in the United States is not hatred; what we need in the United States is not violence and lawlessness, but is love and wisdom, and compassion toward one another, and a feeling of justice toward those who still suffer within our country, whether they be white or whether they be black." -- Robert F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799808-i-can-certainly-throw-out-some-observation-about-the-process</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:24:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/799808-i-can-certainly-throw-out-some-observation-about-the-process]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can certainly throw out some observation about the process of creating which may be of use. Firstly, it's the best &amp; the worst of worlds, because the only fuel you have to make the fire blaze on the page / screen is the stuff of your own being. An artist consumes his or herself in the act of making art. I can feel that consumption even now, sitting here at my desk at the end of a working day. In order to generate the ideas that I have set on the page for the last 10 or 11 hours I have burned the fuel of my own history. This is, obviously a double-edged sword. In order to give, the artist must take from himself. That's the deal. And it's very important to me that the work I do is the best I can make it, because I know what is being burned up to create. As the villain of Sacrament says: &quot;living &amp; dying, we feed the fire." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801848-the-world-had-seen-so-many-ages-the-age-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801848-the-world-had-seen-so-many-ages-the-age-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world had seen so many Ages: the Age of Enlightenment; of Reformation; of Reason. Now, at last, the Age of Desire. And after this, an end to Ages; an end, perhaps, to everything." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822827-she-wanted-nothing-that-he-could-offer-her-except-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:27:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822827-she-wanted-nothing-that-he-could-offer-her-except-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wanted nothing that he could offer her, except perhaps his absence." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go to heaven for the climate and hell for the company." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:50:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all the dragons in our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us act, just once, with beauty and courage. Perhaps everything that frightens us is, in its deepest essence, something helpless that wants our love." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3511-throw-your-dreams-into-space-like-a-kite-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 03:50:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3511-throw-your-dreams-into-space-like-a-kite-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Throw your dreams into space like a kite, and you do not know what it will bring back, a new life, a new friend, a new love, a new country." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723448-according-to-my-previous-belief-system-being-a-christian-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 22:23:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723448-according-to-my-previous-belief-system-being-a-christian-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to my previous belief system, being a Christian and homosexual was not only incompatible; like heaven and hell, they were in absolute opposition. The constant conflict of being one person inside but presenting another on the outside for twenty-two years eventually took its toll. 

The messages I got were loud and clear. Never ever admit to yourself or anyone who you are. Hide it, kill it, eradicate it, heal it, deliver it, break it, suppress it, deny it, marry it to a woman, heterosexualize it, therapy it, anything and everything, but whatever you do don’t stand up one day and say “I am gay” because that will mean the end.  I spent most of my life trying to destroy the real me, doing all I could to ensure he never found expression. A suicide of the soul, identity and meaning. When you finally embrace the gift of your sexual orientation it IS the end; the end of shame, fear and oppression. You leave the darkness of the closet and begin a life of honesty, authenticity and freedom." -- Anthony Venn-Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217070-keep-your-face-always-toward-the-sunshine---and-shadows</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 23:21:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217070-keep-your-face-always-toward-the-sunshine---and-shadows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Keep your face always toward the sunshine - and shadows will fall behind you." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
