<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816153-sharon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816153-sharon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:37:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21216-you-can-tempt-me-desert-me-or-cause-me-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:37:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Chris Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21216-you-can-tempt-me-desert-me-or-cause-me-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can tempt me, desert me, or cause me great pain; you can create a dark world that my cause me to fear; you can rule your world with blood and terror, that's true.
But you can't win. And I know that. Weak as I am, with my imperfections and sins, even with all of my failing, I am stronger than you.
I will soon have a body. And I have my agency now. I will increase in my faith and knowledge and power. I am not perfect, but I will be, and there's not a thing you can do! I will become like the Father if I follow the Son. You are powerless to stop me. You can threaten and tempt and whisper lies in my ear, but you can't stop me, Satan; I see that so clearly now! I can stop myslef, yes, but only if I follow you.
And I reject you temptations. I reject your whispered lies. I reject you, Lucifer, and your entire plan. You have no power to control me. I am in control of myself. And try as you might, you won't control me on earth. We will defeat you in heaven, and we will deafeat you on earth. Here, or the earth, it doesn't matter; I am always stronger than you." -- Chris Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21215-in-the-time-you-will-live-there-will-be-heroes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:37:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Chris Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21215-in-the-time-you-will-live-there-will-be-heroes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the time you will live, there will be heroes around. Simple men, honest men who work two jobs, go to school, raise a family, and serve our God. An older couple who have the courage to seek out the truth while enduring the scorn and ridicule of their children and friends. A young man, a special spirit, who will take on a body that is deformed- and yet you will never see hime unhappy or without a smile on his face. A young mother who will care for a daughter while she suffers a painful death, and yet never doubt or loose faith that her Father loves them both.
In your worl famous people will be hard to find. But you will be surrounded by heroes, you will meet them everyday. They will be the simple people who struggle but never give up, those who strive to be happy despite the cares of the physical world, those who dream of the day when they will find the truth, those who search for understanding as to why they were born, why there is pain, or what it all means, and yet continure to endure, knowing in their soul, somewhere deep inside, that there has to be an answer.
These are the heroes that our Father needs down on earth. And you will be a hero. We already know that." -- Chris Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21214-all-men-will-die-all-men-will-be-called-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 00:37:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Chris Stewart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21214-all-men-will-die-all-men-will-be-called-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men will die. All men will be called upon to pass through the veil. But only a few, only a few special men, only those who have been worthy to answer a calling from God, are given the honor to die for a cause.
And in this life, in these times, all of us will be called on to make a sacrifice. When, or in what manner that sacrifice may be required, only God knows. All we can do is wait and prepare and pray that when our time comes, we will be ready to complete the task that he gives, so that when it is over, when we have done all we could, we might look to the Lord and say the same words he said : 'I have fought my way through, I have finished the work Thou didst give me to do." -- Chris Stewart]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
