<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816260-kathleen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816260-kathleen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:45:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485214-what-would-white-people-become-if-they-we-actually-confronted</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Steve Martinot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485214-what-would-white-people-become-if-they-we-actually-confronted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would white people become if they (we) actually confronted the fact that being white was not inherent in a person, in ourselves and others, but actually a demand that others make on us, a role we must play to fulfill a certain responsibility? Part of what is demanded is that we see others as different, yet attribute that difference to those others and not to ourselves, who are told to see it.  Who would white people become if they saw their own eye as an active agent in the production of race though that eye's attribution to others?  The so-called colorblindness that has become a prevalent notion these days would be impossible.  Is the essence of race, for which color is a symbol (of the imposed categorization), exists in the eye itself and not in the object seen by the eye, which has its own qualities, to what could the eye be blinding itself?  Who would we become if we saw those others not as different but as living under an imposition of difference?  Who would we become if we saw that imposition as something in which we were not only implicated but active agents in producing?  Who would we become if we sought to interpose ourselves in that process of imposition, to obstruct it in its primordial moment?  Who would white people become if they saw themselves through the eyes of those on whom they impose themselves?" -- Steve Martinot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235769-i-don-t-feel-that-it-is-necessary-to-know-exactly</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Michel Foucault]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235769-i-don-t-feel-that-it-is-necessary-to-know-exactly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t feel that it is necessary to know exactly what I am. The main interest in life and work is to become someone else that you were not in the beginning. If you knew when you began a book what you would say at the end, do you think that you would have the courage to write it?
What is true for writing and for love relationships is true also for life. The game is worthwhile insofar as we don’t know where it will end." -- Michel Foucault]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424867-w-e-must-recognize-that-ethics-requires-us-to-risk-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:46:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424867-w-e-must-recognize-that-ethics-requires-us-to-risk-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[W]e must recognize that ethics requires us to risk ourselves precisely at moments of unknowingness, when what forms us diverges from what lies before us, when our willingness to become undone in relation to others constitutes our chance of becoming human.  To be undone by another is a primary necessity, an anguish, to be sure, but also a chance--to be addressed, claimed, bound to what is not me, but also to be moved, to be prompted to act, to address myself elsewhere, and so to vacate the self-sufficient &quot;I&quot; as a kind of possession.  If we speak and try to give an account from this place, we will not be irresponsible, or, if we are, we will surely be forgiven." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442335-we-need-instead-to-ask-what-possibilities-of-mobilization-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:46:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442335-we-need-instead-to-ask-what-possibilities-of-mobilization-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We need instead to ask, what possibilities of mobilization are produced on the basis of existing configurations of discourse and power? What are the possibilities of reworking that very matrix of power by which we are constituted, of reconstituting the legacy of that constitution, and of working against each other process of regulation that can destabilize existing power regimes?  For if the subject is constituted by power, that power does not cease at the moment the subject is constituted, for that subject is never fully constituted, but is subjected and produced time and again.  That subject is neither a ground nor a product, but the permanent possibility of a certain resignifying process, one which gets detoured and stalled through other mechanisms of power, but which is power's own possibility of being reworked.  It is not enough to say that the subject is invariably engaged in a political field; that phenomenological phrasing misses the point that the subject is an accomplishment regulated and produced in advance.  And is as such fully political; indeed, perhaps most political as the point in which it is claimed to be prior to politics itself.  To perform this kind of Foucaultian critique of the subject is not to do away with the subject or to pronounce it's death, but merely to claim that certain versions of the subject are politically insidious." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456492-maybe-the-target-nowadays-is-not-to-discover-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Michel Foucault]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456492-maybe-the-target-nowadays-is-not-to-discover-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe the target nowadays is not to discover what we are but to refuse what we are." -- Michel Foucault]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616070-when-i-was-twelve-i-was-interviewed-by-a-doctoral</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 09:46:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616070-when-i-was-twelve-i-was-interviewed-by-a-doctoral]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was twelve, I was interviewed by a doctoral candidate in education and asked what I wanted to be when I grew up.  I said that I either wanted to be a philosopher or a clown, and I understood then, I think, that much depended on whether or not I found the world worth philosophizing about, and what the price of seriousness might be." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869131-ecologically-considered-it-is-not-primarily-our-verbal-statements-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2013 19:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by David Abram]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869131-ecologically-considered-it-is-not-primarily-our-verbal-statements-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ecologically considered, it is not primarily our verbal statements that are &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false,&quot; but rather the kind of relations that we sustain with the rest of nature. A human community that lives in a mutually beneficial relation with the surrounding earth is a community, we might say, that lives in truth. The ways of speaking common to that community—the claims and beliefs that enable such reciprocity to perpetuate itself—are, in this important sense, &lt;i&gt;true&lt;/i&gt;. They are in accord with a right relation between these people and their world. Statements and beliefs, meanwhile, that foster violence toward the land, ways of speaking that enable the impairment or ruination of the surrounding field of beings, can be described as &lt;i&gt;false&lt;/i&gt; ways of speaking—ways that encourage an unsustainable relation with the encompassing earth. A civilization that relentlessly destroys the living land it inhabits is not well acquainted with truth, regardless of how many supported facts it has amassed regarding the calculable properties of its world." -- David Abram]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
