<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816836-gary-kay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/816836-gary-kay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 08:46:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39486-my-experiences-of-men-has-neither-disposed-me-to-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 08:46:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gary add a quote by Robert E. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39486-my-experiences-of-men-has-neither-disposed-me-to-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experiences of men has neither disposed me to think worse of them nor be indisposed to serve them: nor, in spite of failures which I lament, of errors which I now see and acknowledge, or the present aspect of affairs, do I despair of the future. The truth is this: The march of Providence is so slow and our desires so impatient; the work of progress so immense and our means of aiding it so feeble; the life of humanity is so long, that of the individual so brief, that we often see only the ebb of the advancing wave and are thus discouraged. It is history that teaches us to hope. " -- Robert E. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 08:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gary add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
