<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/818075-william]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/818075-william" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 19:11:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 19:11:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in my father's bookshop, I heard a regular customer say that few things leave a deeper mark on a reader than the first book that finds its way into his heart.  Those first images, the echo of words we think we have left behind, accompany us throughout our lives and sculpt a palace in our memory to which, sooner or later—no matter how many books we read, how many worlds we discover, or how much we learn or forget—we will return." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13472-i-still-remember-the-day-my-father-took-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 19:11:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13472-i-still-remember-the-day-my-father-took-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I still remember the day my father took me to the Cemetery of Forgotten Books for the first time." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232215-your-friends-are-all-the-dullest-dogs-i-know-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 10:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232215-your-friends-are-all-the-dullest-dogs-i-know-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your friends are all the dullest dogs I know. They are not beautiful: they are only decorated. They are not clean: they are only shaved and starched. They are not dignified: they are only fashionably dressed. They are not educated: they are only college passmen. They are not religious: they are only pewrenters. They are not moral: they are only conventional. They are not virtuous: they are only cowardly. They are not even vicious: they are only “frail.” They are not artistic: they are only lascivious. They are not prosperous: they are only rich. They are not loyal, they are only servile; not dutiful, only sheepish; not public spirited, only patriotic; not courageous, only quarrelsome; not determined, only obstinate; not masterful, only domineering; not self-controlled, only obtuse; not self-respecting, only vain; not kind, only sentimental; not social, only gregarious; not considerate, only polite; not intelligent, only opinionated; not progressive, only factious; not imaginative, only superstitious; not just, only vindictive; not generous, only propitiatory; not disciplined, only cowed; and not truthful at all: liars every one of them, to the very backbone of their souls." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
