<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/818280-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/818280-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 18:21:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15327-in-the-end-though-maybe-we-must-all-give-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2009 18:21:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15327-in-the-end-though-maybe-we-must-all-give-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, though, maybe we must all give up trying to pay back the people in this world who sustain our lives. In the end, maybe it's wiser to surrender before the miraculous scope of human generosity and to just keep saying thank you, forever and sincerely, for as long as we have voices." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151159-the-best-musicians-know-this-music-isn-t-about-schools-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 21:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Wynton Marsalis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151159-the-best-musicians-know-this-music-isn-t-about-schools-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best musicians know this music isn't about &quot;schools&quot; at all. Like my father says, &quot;There's only one school, the school of 'Can you play?" -- Wynton Marsalis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176070-she-was-beautiful-in-the-quiet-way-that-lonely-unnoticed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 21:12:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jedediah Berry ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176070-she-was-beautiful-in-the-quiet-way-that-lonely-unnoticed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was beautiful, in the quiet way that lonely, unnoticed people are beautiful to those who notice them." -- Jedediah Berry ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248970-because-there-is-no-nation-so-powerful-it-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 12:27:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Carmen Agra Deedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248970-because-there-is-no-nation-so-powerful-it-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because there is no nation so powerful it cannot be wounded, nor a people so small they cannot offer mighty comfort." -- Carmen Agra Deedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2010 19:50:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270708-this-is-a-book-about-questioning-what-others-believe-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2010 10:22:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Marc Aronson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270708-this-is-a-book-about-questioning-what-others-believe-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is a book about questioning what others believe to be true, not accepting ideas just because famous people say they are right. I think knowledge is more like a wave than a switch. Only very rarely do we go from being totally wrong to totally right--as a light turns off and on. Instead, what we learned before allows us to move on to what we can see next. We can surf ahead, but there will always be another challenge, another crest, another setp. We must always keep thinking and asking new questions." -- Marc Aronson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303285-i-do-not-pretend-to-understand-the-moral-universe-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 19:29:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Theodore Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303285-i-do-not-pretend-to-understand-the-moral-universe-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not pretend to understand the moral universe; the arc is a long one, my eye reaches but little ways; I cannot calculate the curve and complete the figure by the experience of sight, I can divine it by conscience. And from what I see I am sure it bends towards justice." -- Theodore Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350882-doesn-t-matter-what-the-press-says-doesn-t-matter-what-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 21:13:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by J. Michael Straczynski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350882-doesn-t-matter-what-the-press-says-doesn-t-matter-what-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Doesn't matter what the press says. Doesn't matter what the politicians or the mobs say.Doesn't matter if the whole country decides that something wrong is something right. 
&lt;br&gt;
This nation was founded on one principle above all else: The requirement that we stand up for what we believe, no matter the odds or the consequences. When the mob and the press and the whole world tell you to move, your job is to plant yourself like a tree beside the river of truth, and tell the whole world -- &quot;No, YOU move." -- J. Michael Straczynski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
