<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820032-schuyler]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820032-schuyler" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 10:12:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518653-this-according-to-the-fellows-who-saw-me-as-fit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 10:12:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518653-this-according-to-the-fellows-who-saw-me-as-fit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This, according to the fellows who saw me as fit for a Service career, put me ahead of the curve, to understand this truth at an age when most guys are starting only to suspect the basics of adulthood--that life owes you nothing; that suffering takes many forms; that no one will ever care for you as your mother did; that the human heart is a chump." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44258-writing-is-a-concentrated-form-of-thinking-a-young-writer-sees</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44258-writing-is-a-concentrated-form-of-thinking-a-young-writer-sees]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is a concentrated form of thinking...a young writer sees that with words he can place himself more clearly into the world.  Words on a page, that's all it takes to help him separate himself from the forces around him, streets and people and pressures and feelings.  He learns to think about these things, to ride his own sentences into new perceptions." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44259-as-technology-advances-in-complexity-and-scope-fear-becomes-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:05:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44259-as-technology-advances-in-complexity-and-scope-fear-becomes-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As technology advances in complexity and scope, fear becomes more primitive." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44264-everybody-gets-told-to-write-about-what-they-know-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:09:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44264-everybody-gets-told-to-write-about-what-they-know-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody gets told to write about what they know.  The trouble with many of us is that at the earlier stages of life we think we know everything- or to put it more usefully, we are often unaware of the scope and structure of our ignorance." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44268-the-role-of-the-artist-is-to-ask-questions-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:16:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44268-the-role-of-the-artist-is-to-ask-questions-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The role of the artist is to ask questions, not answer them." -- Anton Pavlovich Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44270-i-do-not-speak-as-i-think-i-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:22:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44270-i-do-not-speak-as-i-think-i-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not speak as I think, I do not think as I should, and so it all goes on in helpless darkness." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44271-before-pop-art-there-was-such-a-thing-as-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44271-before-pop-art-there-was-such-a-thing-as-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before pop art, there was such a thing as bad taste.  Now there's kitsch, schlock, camp, and porn." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44273-it-is-simply-wrong-to-begin-with-a-theme-symbol</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44273-it-is-simply-wrong-to-begin-with-a-theme-symbol]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is simply wrong to begin with a theme, symbol or other abstract unifying agent, and then try to force characters and events to conform to it." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44276-if-money-is-the-bond-binding-me-to-human-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:46:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44276-if-money-is-the-bond-binding-me-to-human-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If &lt;i&gt;money&lt;/i&gt; is the bond binding me to &lt;i&gt;human&lt;/i&gt; life, binding society to me, connecting me with nature and man, is not money the bond of all &lt;i&gt;bonds&lt;/i&gt;? Can it not dissolve and bind all ties? Is it not, therefore, also the universal &lt;i&gt;agent&lt;/i&gt; of &lt;i&gt;separation&lt;/i&gt;?" -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44283-the-pen-will-never-be-able-to-move-fast-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 10:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44283-the-pen-will-never-be-able-to-move-fast-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pen will never be able to move fast enough to write down every word discovered in the space of memory. Some things have been lost forever, other things will perhaps be remembered again, and still other things have been lost and found and lost again.  There is no way to be sure of any this." -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47925-literary-fiction-and-poetry-are-real-marginalized-right-now-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 15:39:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47925-literary-fiction-and-poetry-are-real-marginalized-right-now-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literary fiction and poetry are real marginalized right now. There's a fallacy that some of my friends sometimes fall into, the ol' &quot;The audience is stupid. The audience only wants to go this deep. Poor us, we're marginalized because of TV, the great hypnotic blah, blah.&quot; You can sit around and have these pity parties for yourself. Of course this is bullshit. If an art form is marginalized it's because it's not speaking to people. One possible reason is that the people it's speaking to have become too stupid to appreciate it. That seems a little easy to me." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 15:40:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49697-she-had-nothing-in-this-world-but-her-two-hands</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 17:09:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Denis Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49697-she-had-nothing-in-this-world-but-her-two-hands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had nothing in this world but her two hands and her crazy love for Jesus, who seemed, for his part, never to have heard of her." -- Denis Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29533-we-have-advantages-we-have-a-cushion-to-fall-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 17:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29533-we-have-advantages-we-have-a-cushion-to-fall-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have advantages. We have a cushion to fall back on. This is abundance. A luxury of place and time. Something rare and wonderful. It's almost historically unprecedented. We must do extraordinary things. We have to. It would be absurd not to." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2008 17:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4819-when-you-consider-things-like-the-stars-our-affairs-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you consider things like the stars, our affairs don't seem to matter very much, do they?" -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 11:23:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62349-in-dark-times-the-definition-of-good-art-would-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In dark times, the definition of good art would seem to be art that locates and applies CPR to those elements of what's human and magical that still live and glow despite the times' darkness. Really good fiction could have as dark a worldview as it wished, but it'd find a way both to depict this world and to illuminate the possibilities for being alive and human in it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89748-i-don-t-go-back-and-look-at-my-early-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 08:57:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Lorrie Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89748-i-don-t-go-back-and-look-at-my-early-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t go back and look at my early work, because the last time I did, many years ago, it left me cringing. If one publishes, then one is creating a public record of Learning to Write." -- Lorrie Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110432-dr-ambrose-himself-told-mark-nechtr-that-the-problem-with-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:47:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110432-dr-ambrose-himself-told-mark-nechtr-that-the-problem-with-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dr. Ambrose himself told Mark Nechtr...that the problem with young people, starting sometime in about the 1960s, is that they tend to live too intensely inside their own social moment, and thus tend to see all existence past age thirty or so as somehow postcoital. It's then that they'll relax, settle back, sad animals, to watch- and learn, as Ambrose himself said he learned from hard artistic and academic experience- that life instead of being rated a hard R, or even a soft R, actually rarely even makes it into distribution. Tends to be too slow." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139685-ivanov-s-fear-was-of-a-literary-nature-that-is-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 16:30:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139685-ivanov-s-fear-was-of-a-literary-nature-that-is-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ivanov's fear was of a literary nature. That is, it was the fear that afflicts most citizens who, one fine (or dark) day, choose to make the practice of writing, and especially the practice of fiction writing, an integral part of their lives. Fear of being no good. Also fear of being overlooked. But above all, fear of being no good. Fear that one's efforts and striving will come to nothing. Fear of the step that leaves no trace. Fear of the forces of chance and nature that wipe away shallow prints. Fear of dining alone and unnoticed. Fear of going unrecognized. Fear of failure and making a spectacle of oneself. But above all, fear of being no good. Fear of forever dwelling in the hell of bad writers." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142047-if-anyone-is-unwilling-to-descend-into-himself-because-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 14:37:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142047-if-anyone-is-unwilling-to-descend-into-himself-because-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If anyone is unwilling to descend into himself, because this is too painful, he will remain superficial in his writing. . . If I perform to myself, then it’s this that the style expresses. And then the style cannot be my own. If you are unwilling to know what you are, your writing is a form of deceit." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165392-and-make-no-mistake-irony-tyrannizes-us-the-reason-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2009 17:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Schuyler add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165392-and-make-no-mistake-irony-tyrannizes-us-the-reason-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And make no mistake: irony tyrannizes us. The reason why our pervasive cultural irony is at once so powerful and so unsatisfying is that an ironist is impossible to pin down. All U.S. irony is based on an implicit &quot;I don’t really mean what I’m saying.&quot; So what does irony as a cultural norm mean to say? That it’s impossible to mean what you say? That maybe it’s too bad it’s impossible, but wake up and smell the coffee already? Most likely, I think, today’s irony ends up saying: &quot;How totally banal of you to ask what I really mean." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
