<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820225-katiesuzanne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820225-katiesuzanne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:20:34 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3060-i-am-the-lorax-i-speak-for-the-trees-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:20:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3060-i-am-the-lorax-i-speak-for-the-trees-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the Lorax. I speak for the trees. I speak for the trees for the trees have no tongues." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:20:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One final paragraph of advice: do not burn yourselves out. Be as I am - a reluctant enthusiast....a part-time crusader, a half-hearted fanatic. Save the other half of yourselves and your lives for pleasure and adventure. It is not enough to fight for the land; it is even more important to enjoy it. While you can. While it’s still here. So get out there and hunt and fish and mess around with your friends, ramble out yonder and explore the forests, climb the mountains, bag the peaks, run the rivers, breathe deep of that yet sweet and lucid air, sit quietly for a while and contemplate the precious stillness, the lovely, mysterious, and awesome space. Enjoy yourselves, keep your brain in your head and your head firmly attached to the body, the body active and alive, and I promise you this much; I promise you this one sweet victory over our enemies, over those desk-bound men and women with their hearts in a safe deposit box, and their eyes hypnotized by desk calculators. I promise you this; You will outlive the bastards." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:20:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/869-benedicto-may-your-trails-be-crooked-winding-lonesome-dangerous-leading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Benedicto: May your trails be crooked, winding, lonesome, dangerous, leading to the most amazing view. May your mountains rise into and above the clouds. May your rivers flow without end, meandering through pastoral valleys tinkling with bells, past temples and castles and poets towers into a dark primeval forest where tigers belch and monkeys howl, through miasmal and mysterious swamps and down into a desert of red rock, blue mesas, domes and pinnacles and grottos of endless stone, and down again into a deep vast ancient unknown chasm where bars of sunlight blaze on profiled cliffs, where deer walk across the white sand beaches, where storms come and go as lightning clangs upon the high crags, where something strange and more beautiful and more full of wonder than your deepest dreams waits  for you -- beyond that next turning of the canyon walls." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 21:20:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173194-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:21:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Arthur O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173194-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the music-makers,
And we are the dreamers of dreams,
Wandering by lone sea-breakers,
And sitting by desolate streams.
World-losers and world-forsakers,
Upon whom the pale moon gleams;
Yet we are the movers and shakers,
Of the world forever, it seems." -- Arthur O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:21:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:20:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4994-we-are-the-music-makers-and-we-are-the-dreamers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the music makers, and we are the dreamers of dreams." -- Arthur William Edgar O'Shaughnessy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 09:20:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[KatieSuzanne add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21627-the-best-thing-for-being-sad-replied-merlin-beginning-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best thing for being sad,&quot; replied Merlin, beginning to puff and blow, &quot;is to learn something. That's the only thing that never fails. You may grow old and trembling in your anatomies, you may lie awake at night listening to the disorder of your veins, you may miss your only love, you may see the world about you devastated by evil lunatics, or know your honour trampled in the sewers of baser minds. There is only one thing for it then — to learn. Learn why the world wags and what wags it. That is the only thing which the mind can never exhaust, never alienate, never be tortured by, never fear or distrust, and never dream of regretting. Learning is the only thing for you. Look what a lot of things there are to learn." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
