<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820273-victoria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820273-victoria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 12:41:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506731-stupidity-is-one-of-the-two-things-we-see-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 12:41:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/506731-stupidity-is-one-of-the-two-things-we-see-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...stupidity is one of the two things we see most clearly in retrospect. The other is missed chances." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456084-in-our-twenties-when-there-is-still-so-much-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 12:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Amor Towles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/456084-in-our-twenties-when-there-is-still-so-much-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our twenties, when there is still so much time ahead of us, time that seems ample for a hundred indecisions, for a hundred visions and revisions—we draw a card, and we must decide right then and there whether to keep that card and discard the next, or discard the first card and keep the second. And before we know it, the deck has been played out and the decisions we have just made will shape our lives for decades to come." -- Amor Towles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225608-everything-ends-and-everything-matters-everything-matters-not-in-spite</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2012 12:44:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Ron Currie Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225608-everything-ends-and-everything-matters-everything-matters-not-in-spite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything ends, and Everything matters.  

Everything matters not in spite of the end of you and all that you love, but because of it.  Everything is all you’ve got…and after Everything is nothing.  So you were wise to welcome Everything, the good and the bad alike, and cling to it all.  Gather it in.  Seek the meaning in sorrow and don’t ever turn away, not once, from here until the end.  Because it is all the same, it is all unfathomable, and it is all infinitely preferable to the one dreadful alternative." -- Ron Currie Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478611-all-i-know-is-that-i-ve-wasted-all-these-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 13:25:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Victoria add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478611-all-i-know-is-that-i-ve-wasted-all-these-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All I know is that I've wasted all these years looking for something, a sort of trophy I'd get only if I really, really did enough to deserve it. But I don't want it anymore, I want something else now, something warm and sheltering, something I can turn to, regardless of what I do, regardless of who I become. Something that will just be there, always, like tomorrow's sky. That's what I want now, and I think it's what you should want too. But it will be too late soon. We'll become too set to change. If we don't take our chance now, another may never come for either of us." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
