<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820741-annalee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820741-annalee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:27:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:27:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how close we are to another person, few human relationships are as free from strife, disagreement, and frustration as is the relationship you have with a good dog. Few human beings give of themselves to another as a dog gives of itself. I also suspect that we cherish dogs because their unblemished souls make us wish - consciously or unconsciously - that we were as innocent as they are, and make us yearn for a place where innocence is universal and where the meanness, the betrayals, and the cruelties of this world are unknown." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498915-once-you-have-had-a-wonderful-dog-a-life-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498915-once-you-have-had-a-wonderful-dog-a-life-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have had a wonderful dog, a life without one, is a life diminished." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287988-when-you-have-dogs-you-witness-their-uncomplaining-acceptance-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287988-when-you-have-dogs-you-witness-their-uncomplaining-acceptance-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you have dogs, you witness their uncomplaining acceptance of suffering, their bright desire to make the most of life in spite of the limitations of age and disease, their calm awareness of the approaching end when their final hours come. They accept death with a grace that I hope I will one day be brave enough to muster." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227753-in-each-little-life-we-can-see-great-truth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227753-in-each-little-life-we-can-see-great-truth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In each little life, we can see great truth and beauty, and in each little life we glimpse the way of all things in the universe. If we alow ourselves to be enchanted by the beauty of the ordinary, we begin to see that all things extraordinary. " -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498913-one-of-the-greatest-gifts-we-receive-from-dogs-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498913-one-of-the-greatest-gifts-we-receive-from-dogs-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the greatest gifts we receive from dogs is the tenderness they evoke in us. The disappointments of life, the injustices, the battering events that are beyond our control, and the betrayals we endure, from those we befriended and loved, can make us cynical and turn our hearts into flint – on which only the matches of anger and bitterness can be struck into flame. By their delight in being with us, the reliable sunniness of their disposition, the joy they bring to playtime, the curiosity with which they embrace each new experience, dogs can melt cynicism,and sweeten the bitter heart." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498910-truth-is-always-stranger-than-fiction-we-craft-fiction-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498910-truth-is-always-stranger-than-fiction-we-craft-fiction-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth is always stranger than fiction. We craft fiction to match our sense of how things ought to be, but truth cannot be crafted. Truth is, and truth has a way of astonishing us to our knees. Reminding us, that the universe does not exist to fulfill our expectations. Because we are imperfect beings who are self-blinded to the truth of the world’s stunning complexity, we shave reality to paper thin theories and ideologies that we can easily grasp – and we call them truths. But the truth of a sea in all it’s immensity cannot be embodied in one tidewashed pebble." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672940-a-man-and-a-woman-cannot-live-together-without-having</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:28:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/672940-a-man-and-a-woman-cannot-live-together-without-having]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man and a woman cannot live together without having against each other a kind of everlasting joke. Each has discovered that the other is not only a fool, but a great fool." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715425-too-many-of-us-die-without-knowing-transcendent-joy-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 13:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[annalee add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715425-too-many-of-us-die-without-knowing-transcendent-joy-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Too many of us die without knowing transcendent joy, in part because we pursue one form or another of materialism. We seek meaning in possessions, in pursuit of cosmic justice for earthly grievances, in the acquisition of power over others. But one day Death reveals that life is wasted in these cold passions, because zealotry of any kind precludes love except of the thing that is idolized." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
