<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820986-amena]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/820986-amena" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 20:45:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170631-time-is-not-the-great-teacher-experience-is-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 20:45:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lynsay Sands]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170631-time-is-not-the-great-teacher-experience-is-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is not the great teacher. Experience is. A man may live a whole life, but if he never leaves his home to experience that life, he dies knowing nothing. A mere child who has suffered and lived can be the wiser of the two." -- Lynsay Sands]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118962-christmas-renews-our-youth-by-stirring-our-wonder-the-capacity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 06:18:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Ralph Sockman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118962-christmas-renews-our-youth-by-stirring-our-wonder-the-capacity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christmas renews our youth by stirring our wonder. The capacity for wonder has been called our most pregnant human faculty, for in it are born our art, our science, our religion.&quot; 
~ (1889-1970), American religious leader. " -- Ralph Sockman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328188-i-will-love-you-with-no-regard-to-the-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you with no regard to the actions of our enemies or the jealousies of actors. I will love you with no regard to the outrage of certain parents or the boredom of certain friends. I will love you no matter what is served in the world’s cafeterias or what game is played at each and every recess. I will love you no matter how many fire drills we are all forced to endure, and no matter what is drawn upon the blackboard in blurry, boring chalk. I will love you no matter how many mistakes I make when trying to reduce fractions, and no matter how difficult it is to memorize the periodic table.
I will love you no matter what your locker combination was, or how you decided to spend your time during study hall. I will love you no matter how your soccer team performed in the tournament or how many stains I received on my cheerleading uniform. I will love you if I never see you again, and I will love you if I see you every Tuesday. I will love you if you cut your hair and I will love you if you cut the hair of others. I will love you if you abandon your baticeering, and I will love you if you if you retire from the theater to take up some other, less dangerous occupation. I will love you if you drop your raincoat on the floor instead of hanging it up and I will love you if you betray your father. I will love you even if you announce that the poetry of Edgar Guest is the best in the world and even if you announce that the work of Zilpha Keatley Snyder is unbearably tedious. I will love you if you abandon the theremin and take up the harmonica and I will love you if you donate your marmosets to the zoo and your tree frogs to M. I will love you as a starfish loves a coral reef and as a kudzu loves trees, even if the oceans turn to sawdust and the trees fall in the forest without anyone around to hear them. I will love you as the pesto loves the fettuccini and as the horseradish loves the miyagi, as the tempura loves the ikura and the pepperoni loves the pizza.
I will love you as the manatee loves the head of lettuce and as the dark spot loves the leopard, as the leech loves the ankle of a wader and as a corpse loves the beak of the vulture. I will love you as the doctor loves his sickest patient and a lake loves its thirstiest swimmer. I will love you as the beard loves the chin, and the crumbs love the beard, and the damp napkin loves the crumbs, and the precious document loves the dampness in the napkin, and the squinting eye of the reader loves the smudged print of the document, and the tears of sadness love the squinting eye as it misreads what is written. I will love you as the iceberg loves the ship, and the passengers love the lifeboat, and the lifeboat loves the teeth of the sperm whale, and the sperm whale loves the flavor of naval uniforms. i will love you as a child loves to overhear the conversations of its parents, and the parents love the sound of their own arguing voices, and as the pen loves to write down the words these voices utter in a notebook for safekeeping. I will love you as a shingle loves falling off a house on a windy day and striking a grumpy person across the chin, and as an oven loves malfunctioning in the middle of roasting a turkey.
I will love you as an airplane loves to fall from a clear blue sky and as an escalator loves to entangle expensive scarves in its mechanisms. I will love you as a wet paper towel loves to be crumpled into a ball and thrown at a bathroom ceiling and as an eraser loves to leave dust in the hairdos of people who talk too much. I will love you as a cufflink loves to drop from its shirt and explore the party for itself and as a pair of white gloves loves to slip delicately into the punchbowl. I will love you as the taxi loves the muddy splash of a puddle and as a library loves the patient tick of a clock." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278402-one-of-the-remarkable-things-about-love-is-that-despite</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:33:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278402-one-of-the-remarkable-things-about-love-is-that-despite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the remarkable things about love is that, despite very irritating people writing poems and songs about how pleasant it is, it really is quite pleasant." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133486-instead-of-the-word-love-there-was-an-enormous-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:33:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133486-instead-of-the-word-love-there-was-an-enormous-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of the word 'love' there was an enormous heart, a symbol sometimes used by people who have trouble figuring out the difference between words and shapes." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36690-if-you-have-ever-lost-a-loved-one-then-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36690-if-you-have-ever-lost-a-loved-one-then-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have ever lost a loved one, then you know exactly how it feels. And if you have not, then you cannot possibly imagine it." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368994-it-is-a-sad-truth-in-life-that-when-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:34:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368994-it-is-a-sad-truth-in-life-that-when-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["it is a sad truth in life that when someone has lost a loved one, friends sometimes avoid the person, just when the presence of friends is most needed." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265995-for-beatrice--my-love-for-you-shall-live-forever-you-however</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:34:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265995-for-beatrice--my-love-for-you-shall-live-forever-you-however]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Beatrice--My love for you shall live forever. You, however, did not." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568290-i-will-love-you-as-misfortune-loves-orphans-as-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:35:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568290-i-will-love-you-as-misfortune-loves-orphans-as-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as misfortune loves orphans, as fire loves innocence, and as justice loves to sit and watch while everything goes wrong." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429029-for-beatrice-when-we-first-met-i-was-lonely-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:35:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429029-for-beatrice-when-we-first-met-i-was-lonely-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Beatrice, when we first met, 
I was lonely, and you were pretty.
Now I am pretty lonely." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429028-for-beatrice-our-love-broke-my-heart-and-stopped-yours</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:35:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429028-for-beatrice-our-love-broke-my-heart-and-stopped-yours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Beatrice, our love broke my heart,
and stopped yours." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428871-for-beatrice-when-we-met-my-life-began-soon-afterwards</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:36:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/428871-for-beatrice-when-we-met-my-life-began-soon-afterwards]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Beatrice, when we met, my life began. Soon afterwards, yours ended." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926802-i-t-was-the-color-of-someone-buying-you-an-ice</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:36:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926802-i-t-was-the-color-of-someone-buying-you-an-ice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[I]t was the color of someone buying you an ice cream cone for no reason at all." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972204-when-you-read-as-many-books-as-klaus-baudelaire-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:38:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972204-when-you-read-as-many-books-as-klaus-baudelaire-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you read as many books as Klaus Baudelaire, you are going to learn a great deal of information that might not become useful for a long time. You might read a book that would teach you all about the exploration of outer space, even if you do not become an astronaut until you are eighty years old. You might read a book about how to preform tricks on ice skates, and then not be forced to preform these tricks for a few weeks. You might read a book on how to have a successful marriage, when the only women you will ever love has married someone else and then perished one terrible afternoon." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77445-the-heart-is-a-the-thousand-stringed-instrument-that-can-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:39:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by شمس الدین محمد حافظ / Khwāja Šams ud-Dīn Muhammad Hāfez-e Šīrāzī]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77445-the-heart-is-a-the-thousand-stringed-instrument-that-can-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heart is a
The thousand-stringed instrument

That can only be tuned with
Love." -- شمس الدین محمد حافظ / Khwāja Šams ud-Dīn Muhammad Hāfez-e Šīrāzī]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77439-there-are-so-many-positions-of-love-each-curve-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:42:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amena add a quote by شمس الدین محمد حافظ / Khwāja Šams ud-Dīn Muhammad Hāfez-e Šīrāzī]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77439-there-are-so-many-positions-of-love-each-curve-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are
So many positions of 
Love:

Each curve on a branch,

The thousand different ways
Your eyes can embrace us,

The infinite shapes your
Mind can draw,

The spring 
Orchestra of scents,

The currents of light combusting
Like passionate lips,

The revolution of Existence's skirt
Whose folds contain other worlds.

Your every sigh that falls against
His inconceivable
Omnipresent
Body." -- شمس الدین محمد حافظ / Khwāja Šams ud-Dīn Muhammad Hāfez-e Šīrāzī]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
