<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/821335-addie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/821335-addie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 16:04:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100236-to-care-only-for-well-being-seems-to-me-positively-ill-bred</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 16:04:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100236-to-care-only-for-well-being-seems-to-me-positively-ill-bred]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To care only for well-being seems to me positively ill-bred. Whether it’s good or bad, it is sometimes very pleasant, too, to smash things." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 16:10:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129697-you-are-using-your-own-moral-intuitions-to-authenticate-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are using your own moral intuitions to authenticate the wisdom of the Bible - and then, in the next moment, you assert that we human beings cannot possibly rely upon our own intuitions to rightly guide us in the world." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47149-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2008 08:13:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Tim O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47149-a-true-war-story-is-never-moral-it-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true war story is never moral. It does not instruct, nor encourage virtue, nor suggest models of proper human behavior, nor restrain men from doing the things men have always done. If a story seems moral, do not believe it. If at the end of a war story you feel uplifted, or if you feel that some small bit of rectitude has been salvaged from the larger waste, then you have been made the victim of a very old and terrible lie. There is no rectitude whatsoever. There is no virtue. As a first rule of thumb, therefore, you can tell a true war story by its absolute and uncompromising allegiance to obscenity and evil. " -- Tim O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 19:34:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All thinking men are atheists." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123922-no-that-is-the-great-fallacy-the-wisdom-of-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 19:42:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123922-no-that-is-the-great-fallacy-the-wisdom-of-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, that is the great fallacy: the wisdom of old men. They do not grow wise. They grow careful." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 12:53:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4502-the-president-of-the-united-states-has-claimed-on-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The president of the United States has claimed, on more than one occasion, to be in dialogue with God. If he said that he was talking to God through his hairdryer, this would precipitate a national emergency. I fail to see how the addition of a hairdryer makes the claim more ridiculous or offensive." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72135-i-know-of-no-society-in-human-history-that-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:35:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72135-i-know-of-no-society-in-human-history-that-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know of no society in human history that ever suffered because its people became too desirous of evidence in support of their core beliefs." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12508-when-considering-the-truth-of-a-proposition-one-is-either</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:36:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12508-when-considering-the-truth-of-a-proposition-one-is-either]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When considering the truth of a proposition, one is either engaged in an honest appraisal of the evidence and logical arguments, or one isn't. Religion is one area of our lives where people imagine that some other standard of intellectual integrity applies." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96324-it-is-merely-an-accident-of-history-that-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:36:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96324-it-is-merely-an-accident-of-history-that-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is merely an accident of history that it is considered normal in our society to believe that the Creator of the universe can hear your thoughts while it is demonstrative of mental illness to believe that he is communicating with you by having the rain tap in Morse code on your bedroom window." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96411-it-is-time-we-admitted-from-kings-and-presidents-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:37:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96411-it-is-time-we-admitted-from-kings-and-presidents-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is time we admitted, from kings and presidents on down, that there is no evidence that any of our books was authored by the Creator of the universe. The Bible, it seems certain, was the work of sand-strewn men and women who thought the earth was flat and for whom a wheelbarrow would have been a breathtaking example of emerging technology. To rely on such a document as the basis for our worldview-however heroic the efforts of redactors- is to repudiate two thousand years of civilizing insights that the human mind has only just begun to inscribe upon itself through secular politics and scientific culture. We will see that the greatest problem confronting civilization is not merely religious extremism: rather, it is the larger set of cultural and intellectual accommodations we have made to faith itself." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:40:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129692-the-moral-truth-here-is-obvious-anyone-who-feels-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moral truth here is obvious: anyone who feels that the interests of a blastocyst just might supersede the interests of a child with a spinal cord injury has had his moral sense blinded by religious metaphysics." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:41:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45103-said-during-a-debate-when-his-opponent-ridiculously-asserted-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[&lt;i&gt;Said during a debate when his opponent ridiculously asserted that atheism and belief in evolution leads to Nazism&lt;/i&gt;:]

Atheism by itself is of course not a moral position or a political one of any kind, it simply is the refusal to believe in a supernatural dimension. For you to say of Naziism, that it was the implementation of the work of [author:Charles Darwin|12793] is a filthy slander, undeserving of you, and an insult to this audience.  [author:Darwin|12793]’s thought was not taught in Germany; [author:Darwinism|12793] was derided in Germany along with every other form of unbelief that all the great modern atheists, [author:Darwin|12793], [author:Einstein|9810] and [author:Freud|10017] were alike despised by the National Socialist regime.

Now, just to take the most notorious of the 20th century totalitarianisms, the most finished example, the most perfected one, the most ruthless and refined one, that of National Socialism, the one that fortunately allowed the escape of all these great atheists, thinkers and many others, to the United States, a country of separation of church and state, that gave them welcome, if it’s an atheistic regime, then how come that in the first chapter of Mein Kampf, that [author:Hitler|30691] says that he’s doing God’s work and executing God’s will in destroying the Jewish people?  How come the fuhrer oath that every officer of the Party and the Army had to take, making [author:Hitler|30691] into a minor god, begins “I swear in the name of almighty God, my loyalty to the Fuhrer?” How come that on the belt buckle of every Nazi soldier it says Gott mit uns, God on our side? How come that the first treaty made by the Nationalist Socialist dictatorship, the very first is with the Vatican? It’s exchanging political control of Germany for Catholic control of German education. How come that the church has celebrated the birthday of the Fuhrer every year, on that day until democracy put an end to this filthy, quasi-religious, superstitious, barbarous, reactionary system. Again, this is not a difference of emphasis between us to suggest that there’s something fascistic about me and about my beliefs is something I won't hear said and you shouldn't believe." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12042-that-which-can-be-asserted-without-evidence-can-be-dismissed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:42:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12042-that-which-can-be-asserted-without-evidence-can-be-dismissed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which can be asserted without evidence, can be dismissed without evidence." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129693-author-mt-838305-mother-teresa-was-not-a-friend-of-the-poor</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:44:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129693-author-mt-838305-mother-teresa-was-not-a-friend-of-the-poor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[author:MT|838305] &lt;i&gt;[Mother Teresa]&lt;/i&gt; was not a friend of the poor. She was a friend of &lt;i&gt;poverty&lt;/i&gt;. She said that suffering was a gift from God. She spent her life opposing the only known cure for poverty, which is the empowerment of women and the emancipation of them from a livestock version of compulsory reproduction." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129696-recently-crowds-of-thousands-gathered-throughout-the-muslim-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:46:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129696-recently-crowds-of-thousands-gathered-throughout-the-muslim-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Recently , crowds of thousands gathered throughout the Muslim world - burning European embassies, issuing threats, taking hostages, even killing people - in protest over twelve cartoons depicting the Prophet Muhammad that were first published in a Danish newspaper. When was the last atheist riot?" -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129700-we-can-either-have-a-twenty-first-century-conversation-about-morality-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:52:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129700-we-can-either-have-a-twenty-first-century-conversation-about-morality-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can either have a twenty-first-century conversation about morality and the human well-being - a conversation in which we avail ourselves of all scientific insights and philosophical arguments that have accumulated in the last two thousand years of human discourse - or we can confine ourselves to a first-century conversation as it is preserved in the Bible." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:54:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129701-in-fact-atheism-is-a-term-that-should-not-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact, &quot;atheism&quot; is a term that should not even exist. No one ever needs to identify himself as a &quot;non-astrologer&quot; or a &quot;non-alchemist.&quot; We do not have words for people who doubt that Elvis is still alive or that aliens have traversed the galaxy only to molest ranchers and their cattle. Atheism is nothing more than the noises reasonable people make in the presence of unjustified religious beliefs." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129702-it-is-time-that-we-admitted-that-faith-is-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 08:56:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129702-it-is-time-that-we-admitted-that-faith-is-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is time that we admitted that faith is nothing more than the license religious people give one another to keep believing when reasons fail." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129704-religious-moderation-is-the-direct-result-of-taking-scripture-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 09:00:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129704-religious-moderation-is-the-direct-result-of-taking-scripture-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religious moderation is the direct result of taking scripture less and less seriously. So why not take it less seriously still? Why not admit the the Bible is merely a collection of imperfect books written by highly fallible human beings." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 19:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36026-if-you-don-t-know-the-thing-to-do-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 19:54:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36026-if-you-don-t-know-the-thing-to-do-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't know, the thing to do is not to get scared, but to learn." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30409-what-is-important-is-the-story-because-when-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2009 17:59:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30409-what-is-important-is-the-story-because-when-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is important is the story. Because when we are all dust and teeth and kicked-up bits of skin - when we're dancing with our own skeletons - our words might be all that's left of us." -- Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145091-it-s-a-long-day-s-drive-any-way-you-look-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2009 18:01:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145091-it-s-a-long-day-s-drive-any-way-you-look-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a long day's drive any way you look at it. With a man who has taken your sins - real and imagined - and stitched them onto the sackcloth of his own soul, it is endless." -- Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143684-how-you-see-a-country-depends-on-whether-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2009 18:02:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143684-how-you-see-a-country-depends-on-whether-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How you see a country depends on whether you are driving through it, or live in it.  How you see a country depends on whether or not you can leave it, if you have to." -- Alexandra Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120061-happy-as-a-clam-is-what-my-mother-says-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2009 14:26:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120061-happy-as-a-clam-is-what-my-mother-says-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happy as a clam, is what my mother says for happy. I am happy as a clam: hard-shelled, firmly closed." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48841-it-seems-to-me-i-am-trying-to-tell-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 16:36:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48841-it-seems-to-me-i-am-trying-to-tell-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me I am trying to tell you a dream--making a vain attempt, because no relation of a dream can convey the dream-sensation, that commingling of absurdity, surprise, and bewilderment in a tremor of struggling revolt, that notion of being captured by the incredible which is of the very essence of dreams...No, it is impossible; it is impossible to convey the life-sensation of any given epoch of one's existence--that which makes its truth, its meaning--its subtle and penetrating essence. It is impossible. We live, as we dream-alone..." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114360-writing-in-english-is-like-throwing-mud-at-a-wall</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 16:37:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114360-writing-in-english-is-like-throwing-mud-at-a-wall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing in English is like throwing mud at a wall." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149297-i-couldn-t-have-felt-more-of-lonely-desolation-somehow-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2009 16:40:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149297-i-couldn-t-have-felt-more-of-lonely-desolation-somehow-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't have felt more of lonely desolation somehow, had I been robbed of a belief or had missed my destiny in life..." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55845-you-must-not-fall-when-you-lose-your-balance</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 17:11:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Philippe Petit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55845-you-must-not-fall-when-you-lose-your-balance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must not fall. / When you lose your balance, resist for a long time before turning yourself toward the earth.  Then jump. / You must not force yourself to stay steady.  You must move forward." -- Philippe Petit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126147-the-essential-thing-is-to-etch-movements-in-the-sky</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2009 17:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Addie add a quote by Philippe Petit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126147-the-essential-thing-is-to-etch-movements-in-the-sky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The essential thing is to etch movements in the sky, movements so still they leave no trace.  The essential thing is simplicity. / That is why the long path to perfection is horizontal." -- Philippe Petit]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
