<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/822082-kathleen-heuer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/822082-kathleen-heuer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 14:50:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 14:50:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 14:51:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2008 16:39:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 16:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 16:32:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 17:14:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5543-insanity-is-doing-the-same-thing-over-and-over-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insanity is doing the same thing, over and over again, but expecting different results." -- Narcotics Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 18:02:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/806-it-takes-courage-to-grow-up-and-become-who-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 18:09:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by E.E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/806-it-takes-courage-to-grow-up-and-become-who-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are." -- E.E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 18:11:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619-it-is-never-too-late-to-be-what-you-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is never too late to be what you might have been." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184199-my-future-starts-when-i-wake-up-every-morning-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2012 09:58:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Miles Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184199-my-future-starts-when-i-wake-up-every-morning-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My future starts when I wake up every morning. Every day I find something creative to do with my life." -- Miles Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422993-treat-a-man-as-he-is-and-he-will-remain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 13:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/422993-treat-a-man-as-he-is-and-he-will-remain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Treat a man as he is and he will remain as he is. Treat a man as he can and should be and
he will become as he can and should be." -- Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507868-if-you-want-to-have-a-more-pleasant-cooperative-teenager-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 13:42:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/507868-if-you-want-to-have-a-more-pleasant-cooperative-teenager-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to have a more pleasant,cooperative teenager, be a more understanding, emphatic, consistent, loving parent." -- Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813504-rule-1-no-cut-or-compromise-should-be-suggested-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:18:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by John Benham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813504-rule-1-no-cut-or-compromise-should-be-suggested-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rule #1: No cut or compromise should be suggested by ANY member of the community. This includes the music coalition, music educators, and the music supervisor. 

Suggest a cut or compromise, and you become responsible for the decision." -- John Benham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819599-volunteering-to-help-others-is-the-right-thing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 13:37:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Gretchen Rubin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819599-volunteering-to-help-others-is-the-right-thing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Volunteering to help others is the right thing to do, and it also boosts personal happiness; a review of research by the Corporation for National and Community Service shows that those who aid the causes they value tend to be happier and in better health. They show fewer signs of physical and mental aging. And it's not just that helpful people also tend to be healthier and happier; helping others causes happiness. &quot;Be selfless, if only for selfish reasons,&quot; as one of my happiness paradoxes holds. About one-quarter of Americans volunteer, and of those, a third volunteer for more than a hundred hours each year." -- Gretchen Rubin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542925-i-tried-to-go-to-sleep-with-my-headphones-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 17:12:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542925-i-tried-to-go-to-sleep-with-my-headphones-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tried to go to sleep with my headphones still on, but then after a while my mom and dad came in, and my mom grabbed Bluie from the shelf and hugged him to her stomach, and my dad sat down in my desk chair, and without crying he said, 'You are not a grenade, not to us. Thinking about you dying makes us sad, Hazel, but you are not a grenade. You are amazing. You can't know, sweetie, because you've never had a baby become a brilliant young reader with a side interest in horrible television shows, but the joy you bring us is so much greater than the sadness we feel about your illness.'

'Okay,' I said.

'Really,' my dad said. 'I wouldn't bullshit you about this. If you were more trouble than you're worth, we'd just toss you out on the streets.'

'We're not sentimental people,' Mom added, deadpan. 'We'd leave you at an orphanage with a note pinned to your pajamas." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435188-the-rule-of-agreement-reminds-you-to-respect-what-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 15:56:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Tina Fey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435188-the-rule-of-agreement-reminds-you-to-respect-what-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the Rule of Agreement reminds you to “respect what your partner has created” and to at least start from an open-minded place. Start with a YES and see where that takes you." -- Tina Fey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345916-i-was-obliged-to-be-industrious-whoever-is-equally-industrious</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 15:04:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Johannes Sebastian Bach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345916-i-was-obliged-to-be-industrious-whoever-is-equally-industrious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was obliged to be industrious. Whoever is equally industrious will succeed equally well." -- Johannes Sebastian Bach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304209-art-isn-t-only-a-painting-art-is-anything-that-s-creative</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 11:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathleen add a quote by Seth Godin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304209-art-isn-t-only-a-painting-art-is-anything-that-s-creative]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art isn't only a painting.  Art is anything that's creative, passionate, and personal.  And great art resonates with the viewer, not only with the creator.

What makes someone an artist?  I don't think is has anything to do with a paintbrush.  There are painters who follow the numbers, or paint billboards, or work in a small village in China, painting reproductions.  These folks, while swell people, aren't artists.  On the other hand, Charlie Chaplin was an artist, beyond a doubt.  So is Jonathan Ive, who designed the iPod.  You can be an artists who works with oil paints or marble, sure.  But there are artists who work with numbers, business models, and customer conversations.  Art is about intent and communication, not substances.

An artists is someone who uses bravery, insight, creativity, and boldness to challenge the status quo.  And an artists takes it personally.

That's why Bob Dylan is an artist, but an anonymous corporate hack who dreams up Pop 40 hits on the other side of the glass is merely a marketer.  That's why Tony Hsieh, founder of Zappos, is an artists, while a boiler room of telemarketers is simply a scam.

Tom Peters, corporate gadfly and writer, is an artists, even though his readers are businesspeople.  He's an artists because he takes a stand, he takes the work personally, and he doesn't care if someone disagrees.  His art is part of him, and he feels compelled to share it with you because it's important, not because he expects you to pay him for it.

Art is a personal gift that changes the recipient.  The medium doesn't matter.  The intent does.

Art is a personal act of courage, something one human does that creates change in another." -- Seth Godin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
