<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/822477-e]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/822477-e" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 17:44:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846266-he-looked-at-them-and-saw-their-faces-did-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 17:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Alasdair Gray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/846266-he-looked-at-them-and-saw-their-faces-did-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He looked at them and saw their faces did not fit. The skin on the skulls crawled and twitched like half-solid paste. All the heads in his angle of vision seemed irregular lumps, like potatoes but without a potato’s repose: potatoes with crawling surfaces punctured by holes which opened and shut, holes blocked with coloured jelly or fringed with bone stumps, elastic holes through which air was sucked or squirted, holes secreting salt, wax, spittle and snot. He grasped a pencil in his trouser pocket, wishing it were a knife he could thrust through his cheek and use to carve his face down to the clean bone. But that was foolish. Nothing clean lay under the face. He thought of sectioned brains, palettes, eyeballs and ears seen in medical diagrams and butcher’s shops. He thought of elastic muscle, pulsing tubes, gland sacks full of lukewarm fluid, the layers of cellular and fibrous and granular tissues inside a head. What was felt as tastes, caresses, dreams and thoughts could be seen as a cleverly articulated mass of garbage." -- Alasdair Gray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327964-no-i-don-t-mean-love-when-i-say-patriotism-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 18:41:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/327964-no-i-don-t-mean-love-when-i-say-patriotism-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No, I don't mean love, when I say patriotism. I mean fear. The fear of the other. And its expressions are political, not poetical: hate, rivalry, aggression." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18354-the-louder-he-talked-of-his-honor-the-faster-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 20:51:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18354-the-louder-he-talked-of-his-honor-the-faster-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The louder he talked of his honor, the faster we counted our spoons." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4667-to-photograph-is-to-hold-one-s-breath-when-all-faculties</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 20:38:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Henri Cartier-Bresson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4667-to-photograph-is-to-hold-one-s-breath-when-all-faculties]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To photograph is to hold one's breath, when all faculties converge to capture fleeting reality. It's at that precise moment that mastering an image becomes a great physical and intellectual joy." -- Henri Cartier-Bresson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339966-being-unable-to-make-people-more-reasonable-i-preferred-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 18:21:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339966-being-unable-to-make-people-more-reasonable-i-preferred-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being unable to make people more reasonable, I preferred to be happy away from them" -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857892-in-heathrow-a-vast-chunk-of-memory-detached-itself-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 21:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857892-in-heathrow-a-vast-chunk-of-memory-detached-itself-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Heathrow a vast chunk of memory detached itself from a blank bowl of airport sky and fell on him. He vomited into a blue plastic canister without breaking stride." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302564-colonies-are-the-outhouses-of-the-european-soul-where-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 00:31:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302564-colonies-are-the-outhouses-of-the-european-soul-where-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Colonies are the outhouses of the European soul, where a fellow can let his pants down and relax, enjoy the smell of his own shit." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 09:31:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158499-without-turning-the-pharmacist-answered-that-he-liked-books-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without turning, the pharmacist answered that he liked books like The Metamorphosis, Bartleby, A Simple Heart, A Christmas Carol.  And then he said that he was reading Capote's Breakfast at Tiffany's. Leaving aside the fact that A Simple Heart and A Christmas Carol were stories, not books, there was something revelatory about the taste of this bookish young pharmacist, who ... clearly and inarguably preferred minor works to major ones.  He chose The Metamorphosis over The Trial, he chose Bartleby over Moby Dick, he chose A Simple Heart over Bouvard and Pecouchet, and A Christmas Carol over A Tale of Two Cities or The Pickwick Papers. What a sad paradox, thought Amalfitano.  Now even bookish pharmacists are afraid to take on the great, imperfect, torrential works, books that blaze a path into the unknown.  They choose the perfect exercises of the great masters.  Or what amounts to the same thing: they want to watch the great masters spar, but they have no interest in real combat, when the great masters struggle against that something, that something that terrifies us all, that something that cows us and spurs us on, amid blood and mortal wounds and stench." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1092640-hotel-waldhaus-we-had-no-luck-with-the-weather-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 09:34:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1092640-hotel-waldhaus-we-had-no-luck-with-the-weather-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hotel Waldhaus

We had no luck with the weather and the guests at our table were repellent in every respect. They even ruined Nietzsche for us. Even after they had had a fatal car accident and had been laid out in the church in Sils, we still hated them." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577706-of-the-not-very-many-ways-known-of-shedding-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 23:29:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577706-of-the-not-very-many-ways-known-of-shedding-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of the not very many ways known of shedding one's body, falling, falling, falling is the supreme method, but you have to select your sill or ledge very carefully so as not to hurt yourself or others. Jumping from a high bridge is not recommended even if you cannot swim, for wind and water abound in weird contingencies, and tragedy ought not to culminate in a record dive or a policeman's promotion. If you rent a cell in the luminous waffle, room 1915 or 1959, in a tall business centre hotel browing the star dust, and pull up the window, and gently - not fall, not jump - but roll out as you should for air comfort, there is always the chance of knocking clean through into your own hell a pacific noctambulator walking his dog; in this respect a back room might be safer, especially if giving on the roof of an old tenacious normal house far below where a cat may be trusted to flash out of the way. Another popular take-off is a mountaintop with a sheer drop of say 500 meters but you must find it, because you will be surprised how easy it is to miscalculate your deflection offset, and have some hidden projection, some fool of a crag, rush forth to catch you, causing you to bounce off it into the brush, thwarted, mangled and unnecessarily alive. The ideal drop is from an aircraft, your muscles relaxed, your pilot puzzled, your packed parachute shuffled off, cast off, shrugged off - farewell, shootka (little chute)! Down you go, but all the while you feel suspended and buoyed as you somersault in slow motion like a somnolent tumbler pigeon, and sprawl supine on the eiderdown of the air, or lazily turn to embrace your pillow, enjoying every last instant of soft, deep, death-padded life, with the earth's green seesaw now above, now below, and the voluptuous crucifixion, as you stretch yourself in the growing rush, in the nearing swish, and then your loved body's obliteration in the Lap of the Lord." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
