<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/824071-val]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/824071-val" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 19:53:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40139-we-who-lived-in-concentration-camps-can-remember-the-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 19:53:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40139-we-who-lived-in-concentration-camps-can-remember-the-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We who lived in concentration camps can remember the men who walked through the huts comforting others, giving away their last piece of bread. They may have been few in number, but they offer sufficient proof that everything can be taken from a man but one thing: the last of the human freedoms -- to choose one's attitude in any given set of circumstances, to choose one's own way." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67974-but-there-was-no-need-to-be-ashamed-of-tears</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 19:54:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67974-but-there-was-no-need-to-be-ashamed-of-tears]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there was no need to be ashamed of tears, for tears bore witness that a man had the greatest of courage, the courage to suffer." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27504-it-did-not-really-matter-what-we-expected-from-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 19:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27504-it-did-not-really-matter-what-we-expected-from-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It did not really matter what we expected from life, but rather what life expected from us. We needed to stop asking about the meaning of life, and instead to think of ourselves as those who were being questioned by life—daily and hourly. Our answer must consist, not in talk and meditation, but in right action and in right conduct. Life ultimately means taking the responsibility to find the right answer to its problems and to fulfill the tasks which it constantly sets for each individual." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60409-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-saw-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2008 19:59:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60409-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-saw-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first time in my life I saw the truth as it is set into song by so many poets, proclaimed as the final wisdom by so many thinkers. The truth - that Love is the ultimate and highest goal to which man can aspire. Then I grasped the meaning of the greatest secret that human poetry and human thought and belief have to impart: The salvation of man is through love and in love." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64063-a-man-who-becomes-conscious-of-the-responsibility-he-bears</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 05:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Victor Frankl (Man's Search For Meaning)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64063-a-man-who-becomes-conscious-of-the-responsibility-he-bears]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who becomes conscious of the responsibility he bears toward a human being who affectionately waits for him, or to an unfinished work, will never be able to throw away his life. He knows the &quot;why&quot; for his existence, and will be able to bear almost any &quot;how." -- Victor Frankl (Man's Search For Meaning)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170475-being-human-always-points-and-is-directed-to-something-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 06:01:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170475-being-human-always-points-and-is-directed-to-something-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...being human always points, and is directed, to something, or someone, other than oneself—be it meaning to fulfill or another human being to encounter. The more one forgets himself—by giving himself to a cause to serve or another person to love—the more human he is and the more he actualizes himself.... What is called self-actualization is not an attainable aim at all, for the simple reason that the more one would strive for it, the more he would miss it. In other words, self-actualization is possible only as a side-effect of self-transcendence." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69391-love-is-the-only-way-to-grasp-another-human-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 16:49:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69391-love-is-the-only-way-to-grasp-another-human-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the only way to grasp another human being in the innermost core of his personality. No one can become fully aware of the very essence of another human being unless he loves him. By his love he is enabled to see the essential traits and features in the beloved person; and even more, he sees that which is potential in him, which is not yet actualized but yet ought to be actualized. Furthermore, by his love, the loving person enables the beloved person to actualize these potentialities. By making him aware of what he can be and of what he should become, he makes these potentialities come true." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69392-usually-to-be-sure-man-considers-only-the-stubble-field</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 16:58:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69392-usually-to-be-sure-man-considers-only-the-stubble-field]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually, to be sure, man considers only the stubble field of transitoriness and overlooks the full granaries of the past, wherein he had salvaged once and for all his deeds, his joys and also his sufferings. Nothing can be undone, and nothing can be done away with. I should say having been is the surest kind of being." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21406-so-live-as-if-you-were-living-already-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 16:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21406-so-live-as-if-you-were-living-already-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So live as if you were living already for the second time and as if you had acted the first time as wrongly as you are about to act now!" -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69394-it-is-not-freedom-from-conditions-but-it-is-freedom</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 17:02:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69394-it-is-not-freedom-from-conditions-but-it-is-freedom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not freedom from conditions, but it is freedom to take a stand toward the conditions." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69396-i-recommend-that-the-statue-of-liberty-on-the-east</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 17:06:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69396-i-recommend-that-the-statue-of-liberty-on-the-east]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recommend that the Statue of Liberty on the East Coast be supplemented by a Statue of Responsiblity on the West Coast." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69398-a-human-being-is-not-one-thing-among-others-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 17:09:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69398-a-human-being-is-not-one-thing-among-others-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being is not one thing among others; things determine each other, but man is ultimately self-determining. What he becomes - within the limits of endowment and environment- he has made out of himself. In the concentration camps, for example, in this living laboratory and on this testing ground, we watched and witnessed some of our comrades behave like swine while others behaved like saints. Man has both potentialities within himself; which one is actualized depends on decisions but not on conditions." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121244-we-are-up-against-the-unseen-power-that-controls-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 19:41:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121244-we-are-up-against-the-unseen-power-that-controls-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are up against the unseen power that controls this dark world and the spiritual agents are from the very headquarters of evil. Therefore, we must wear the &quot;whole armour of God,&quot; that we may be able to resist evil in its day of power, and that even when we have fought to a standstill, we may still stand our ground." -- Corrie Ten Boom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2009 08:05:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65903-some-things-don-t-matter-much-like-the-color-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["some things don't matter much. Like the color of a house. How big is that in the overall scheme of life? But lifting a person's heart--now, that matters. The whole problem with people is...they know what matters, but they don't choose it...The hardest thing on earth is choosing what matters." -- Sue Monk Kidd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109653-the-trouble-with-anger-is-it-gets-hold-of-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 12:07:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Val add a quote by Jeanne Duprau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109653-the-trouble-with-anger-is-it-gets-hold-of-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with anger is, it gets hold of you. And then you aren't the master of yourself anymore. Anger is. And when anger is the boss, you get unintended consequences." -- Jeanne Duprau]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
