<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82624-melanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82624-melanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 10:18:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366999-i-envied-his-inspiration-his-optimism-in-focusing-back-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 10:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Bao Ninh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366999-i-envied-his-inspiration-his-optimism-in-focusing-back-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I envied his inspiration, his optimism in focusing back on the painful but glorious days. They were caring days, when we knew what we were living and fighting for and why we needed to suffer and sacrifice.
Those were the days when all of us were young, very pure and very sincere." -- Bao Ninh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364997-o-what-a-world-of-unseen-visions-and-heard-silences</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2011 01:53:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Julian Jaynes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/364997-o-what-a-world-of-unseen-visions-and-heard-silences]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O, what a world of unseen visions and heard silences, this insubstantial country of the mind! What ineffable essences, these touchless rememberings and unshowable reveries! And the privacy of it all! A secret theater of speechless monologue and prevenient counsel, an invisible mansion of all moods, musings, and mysteries, an infinite resort of disappointments and discoveries. A whole kingdom where each of us reigns reclusively alone, questioning what we will, commanding what we can. A hidden hermitage where we may study out the troubled book of what we have done and yet may do. An introcosm that is more myself than anything I can find in a mirror. This consciousness that is myself of selves, that is everything, and yet is nothing at all - what is it?
And where did it come from?
And why?" -- Julian Jaynes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367157-i-mean-i-have-the-feeling-that-something-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2011 06:00:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367157-i-mean-i-have-the-feeling-that-something-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, I have the feeling that something in my mind is poisoning everything else." -- Vladimir Nabokov ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73653-you-know-some-people-say-life-is-short-and-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2013 19:44:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Chris Rock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73653-you-know-some-people-say-life-is-short-and-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, some people say life is short and that you could get hit by a bus at any moment and that you have to live each day like it's your last. Bullshit. Life is long. You're probably not gonna get hit by a bus. And you're gonna have to live with the choices you make for the next fifty years." -- Chris Rock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259240-i-m-not-telling-you-to-make-the-world-better-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 15:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/259240-i-m-not-telling-you-to-make-the-world-better-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not telling you to make the world better, because I don't think that progress is necessarily part of the package. I'm just telling you to live in it. Not just to endure it, not just to suffer it, not just to pass through it, but to live in it. To look at it. To try to get the picture. To live recklessly. To take chances. To make your own work and take pride in it. To seize the moment. And if you ask me why you should bother to do that, I could tell you that the grave's a fine and private place, but none I think do there embrace. Nor do they sing there, or write, or argue, or see the tidal bore on the Amazon, or touch their children. And that's what there is to do and get it while you can and good luck at it." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555768-and-in-the-end-the-logical-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 13:14:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555768-and-in-the-end-the-logical-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . and in the end the logical thing would be to give up and I would give up if I were laboring for a reader today, but as there is in the world not a single human who can speak my language; or, more simply, not a single human who can speak; or, even more simply, not a single human; I must think only of myself, of that force which urges me to express myself. I repeat: there is something I know, there is something I know, there is something..." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967578-nostalgia-seems-something-like-the-pain-of-ignorance-of-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 00:43:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melanie add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/967578-nostalgia-seems-something-like-the-pain-of-ignorance-of-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Nostalgia seems something like the pain of ignorance, of not knowing. You are far away, and I don't know what has become of you. My country is far away, and I don't know what is happening there." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
