<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/826699-ryan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/826699-ryan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 09:12:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115373-i-want-to-throw-up-because-we-re-supposed-to-quietly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2008 09:12:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by David Wojnarowicz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115373-i-want-to-throw-up-because-we-re-supposed-to-quietly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to throw up because we're supposed to quietly and politely make house in this killing machine called America and pay taxes to support our own slow murder and I'm amazed we're not running amok in the streets, and that we can still be capable of gestures of loving after lifetimes of all this." -- David Wojnarowicz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 06:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We die containing a richness of lovers and tribes, tastes we have swallowed, bodies we have plunged into and swum up as if rivers of wisdom, characters we have climbed into as if trees, fears we have hidden in as if caves. 

I wish for all this to be marked on by body when I am dead.  I believe in such cartography - to be marked by nature, not just to label ourselves on a map like the names of rich men and women on buildings.  We are communal histories, communal books.  We are not owned or monogamous in our taste or experience." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261014-sure-nothing-succeeds-like-success-fact-is-dearest-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 10:21:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/261014-sure-nothing-succeeds-like-success-fact-is-dearest-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure, nothing succeeds like success. Fact is, dearest, we are fools.  We cling to an ideal no one wants or cares about. I am the greater fool of the two of us. I go on eating out my heart and poisoning every moment of my life in the attempt to rouse people's sensibilities. At least if I could do it with closed eyes. The irony is I see the futility of my efforts and yet I can't let go." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 07:33:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473751-to-engage-in-activism-that-envisions-alternatives-ways-of-organizing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 14:40:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Deborah B. Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473751-to-engage-in-activism-that-envisions-alternatives-ways-of-organizing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To engage in activism that envisions alternatives ways of organizing society and alternative ways of being is to risk membership in society, a sense of belonging, however partial it may be.  Activism can make us vulnerable because it is so obviously about wanting something beyond what is, and to have a political desire often is construed as wanting too much." -- Deborah B. Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204921-if-god-really-existed-it-would-be-necessary-to-abolish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 10:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Mikhail Bakunin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204921-if-god-really-existed-it-would-be-necessary-to-abolish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If God really existed, it would be necessary to abolish Him." -- Mikhail Bakunin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
