<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/827348-monica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/827348-monica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Miss Piggy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and it may be necessary from time to time to give a stupid or misinformed beholder a black eye." -- Miss Piggy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 11:56:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 12:05:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55076-i-ll-be-looking-for-you-will-every-moment-every-single</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:21:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55076-i-ll-be-looking-for-you-will-every-moment-every-single]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll be looking for you, Will, every moment, every single moment. And when we do find each other again, we'll cling together so tight that nothing and no one'll ever tear us apart. Every atom of me and every atom of you... We'll live in birds and flowers and dragonflies and pine trees and in clouds and in those little specks of light you see floating in sunbeams... And when they use our atoms to make new lives, they wont' just be able to take one, they'll have to take two, one of you and one of me, we'll be joined so tight..." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4714-i-write-almost-always-in-the-third-person-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4714-i-write-almost-always-in-the-third-person-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write almost always in the third person, and I don't think the narrator is male or female anyway. They're both, and young and old, and wise and silly, and sceptical and credulous, and innocent and experienced, all at once. Narrators are not even human - they're sprites." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5323-but-it-gradually-seemed-to-me-that-i-d-made-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5323-but-it-gradually-seemed-to-me-that-i-d-made-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...But it gradually seemed to me that I'd made myself believe something that wasn't true. I'd made myself believe that I was fine and happy and fulfilled on my own without the love of anyone else. Being in love was like China: you knew it was there, and no doubt it was very interesting, and some people went there, but I never would. I'd spend all my life without ever going to China, but it wouldn't matter, because there was all the rest of the world to visit... And I thought: am I really going to spend the rest of my life without feeling that again? I thought: I &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to go to China. It's full of treasures and strangeness and mysteries and joy." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:24:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132361-oh-will-she-said-what-can-we-do-whatever-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, Will,&quot; she said, &quot;What can we do? Whatever can we do? I want to live with you forever. I want to kiss you and lie down with you and wake up with you every day of my life till I die, years and years and years away. I don't want a memory, just a memory...&quot;

&quot;No,&quot; he said. &quot;Memory's a poor thing to have. It's your own real hair and mouth and arms and eyes and hands I want. I didn't know I could ever love anything so much. Oh, Lyra, I wish this night would never end! If only we could stay here like this, and the world could stop turning, and everyone else could fall into a sleep...&quot;

&quot;Everyone except us! And you and I could live here forever and just love each other.&quot;

&quot;I will love you forever; whatever happens. Till I die and after I die, and when I find my way out of the land of the dead, I'll drift about forever, all my atoms, till I find you again...&quot;

&quot;I'll be looking for you, Will, every moment, every single moment. And when we do find each other again, we'll cling together so tight that nothing and no one'll ever tear us apart. Every atom of me and every atom of you...We'll live in birds and flowers and dragonflies and pin trees and in clouds and in those little specks of light you see floating in sunbeams...And when they use our atoms to make new lives, they won't just be able to take one, they'll have to take two, one of you and one of me, we'll be joined so tight...&quot;

They lay side by side, hand in hand, looking at the sky." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110270-even-if-it-means-oblivion-friends-i-ll-welcome-it-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:25:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110270-even-if-it-means-oblivion-friends-i-ll-welcome-it-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if it means oblivion, friends, I'll welcome it, because it won't be nothing.  We'll be alive again in a thousand blades of grass, and a million leaves; we'll be falling in the raindrops and blowing in the fresh breeze; we'll be glittering in the dew under the stars and the moon out there in the physical world, which is our true home and always was." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26365-i-have-stolen-ideas-from-every-book-i-have-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:25:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26365-i-have-stolen-ideas-from-every-book-i-have-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have stolen ideas from every book I have ever read." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415352-awake-love-think-speak-be-walking-trees-be-talking-beasts</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:28:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/415352-awake-love-think-speak-be-walking-trees-be-talking-beasts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Awake. Love. Think. Speak. Be walking trees. Be talking beasts. Be divine waters." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70275-the-term-is-over-the-holidays-have-begun-the-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:29:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70275-the-term-is-over-the-holidays-have-begun-the-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The term is over: the holidays have begun. The dream is ended: this is the morning." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350927-and-as-he-spoke-he-no-longer-looked-to-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 10:30:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Monica add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350927-and-as-he-spoke-he-no-longer-looked-to-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And as He spoke, He no longer looked to them like a lion; but the things that began to happen after that were so great and beautiful that I cannot write them. And for us this the end of all the stories, and we can most truly say that they all lived happily ever after. But for them it was only the beginning of the real story. All their life in this world and all their adventures in Narnia had only been the cover and the title page: now at last they were beginning Chapter One of the Great Story which no one on earth has read: which goes on for ever: in which every chapter is better than the one before." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
