<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/828261-carol]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/828261-carol" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:25:09 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393930-i-have-learned-something-of-what-the-spirit-has-taught</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393930-i-have-learned-something-of-what-the-spirit-has-taught]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have learned something of what the Spirit has taught, and I know now that the place of safety in this world is not in any given place; it doesn't make so much difference where we live, and I have found that security can come to Israel only when they keep the commandments, when they live so that they can enjoy the companionship, the direction, the comfort, and the guidance of the Holy Spirit of the Lord." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840382-it-was-to-accomplish-this-lofty-purpose-basic-to-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:25:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840382-it-was-to-accomplish-this-lofty-purpose-basic-to-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was to accomplish this lofty purpose basic to all liberty that God “established the Constitution of this land by the hands of wise men whom (he) raised up unto this very purpose” (D&amp;C 101:77–80). Contained within the principles of that great heaven-inspired document is the message of this Church to the world in this fateful hour. Except the spirit of the Gospel of Jesus Christ and principles contained within the Constitution of the United States are inherent in world plans now being formulated, they are but building on sand and the Lord is not in that building." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830589-our-failure-to-be-a-peculiar-people-in-maintaining-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:25:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830589-our-failure-to-be-a-peculiar-people-in-maintaining-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our failure to be a &quot;peculiar&quot; people in maintaining our standards, despite the jeers and the criticisms of the crowd, will be our failure to be chosen for that calling to which we are called.

The Lord has told us, &quot;Behold, there are many called, but few are chosen&quot; (D&amp;C 121:34), and then in the same revelation points out two reasons why men fail of their blessings. The first reason he gives is that their hearts are set so much upon the things of this world, and the second is that they aspire so much to the honors of men. So then as Church members let us beware lest we set our hearts upon the things of this world and lest we aspire so much to the honors of men that we compromise our standards. If we do so, we will be cut off in the Day of Judgment and will lose our blessings. Our reward for daring to live the gospel despite the oppositions from the outside world will be to have blessings added upon our heads forever and forever." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399336-happiness-does-not-depend-on-what-happens-outside-of-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/399336-happiness-does-not-depend-on-what-happens-outside-of-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness does not depend on what happens outside of you but on what happens inside of you; it is measured by the spirit with which you meet the problems of life. - 1974" -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311332-the-path-to-exaltation-is-rugged-and-steep-many-stumble</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:26:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311332-the-path-to-exaltation-is-rugged-and-steep-many-stumble]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The path to [exaltation] is rugged and steep. Many stumble and fall, and through discouragement never pick themselves up to start again. The forces of evil cloud the path with many foggy deterrents, often trying to detour us in misleading trails. But through all this journey there is the calming assurance that if we choose the
right, success will be ours, and the achievement of it will have molded and formed and created us into the kind of person qualified to be accepted into the presence of God." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295428-the-one-who-confidently-looks-forward-to-an-eternal-reward</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:26:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295428-the-one-who-confidently-looks-forward-to-an-eternal-reward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one who confidently looks forward to an eternal reward for his efforts in mortality is constantly sustained through his deepest trials. When he is disappointed in love, he does not commit suicide. When loved ones die, he doesn’t despair; when he loses a coveted contest, he doesn’t falter; when war and destruction dissipate his future, he doesn’t sink into a depression. He lives above his world and never loses sight of the goal of his salvation." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66151-just-as-a-flood-lighted-temple-is-more-beautiful-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66151-just-as-a-flood-lighted-temple-is-more-beautiful-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just as a flood-lighted temple is more beautiful in a severe storm or in a heavy fog, so the gospel of Jesus Christ is more glorious in times of inward storm and of personal sorrow and tormenting conflict." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111033-you-cannot-lift-another-soul-until-you-are-standing-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:27:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111033-you-cannot-lift-another-soul-until-you-are-standing-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot lift another soul until you are standing on higher ground than he is.  You cannot light a fire in another soul unless it is burning in your own soul." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184862-life-is-fragile-handle-with-prayer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 17:27:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carol add a quote by Harold B. Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184862-life-is-fragile-handle-with-prayer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is fragile, handle with prayer." -- Harold B. Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
