<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82919-wesley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82919-wesley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 20:20:44 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51952-he-wanted-to-tell-her-from-the-greater-perspective-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 20:20:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by Mary Robison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51952-he-wanted-to-tell-her-from-the-greater-perspective-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He wanted to tell her, from the greater perspective he had, that to own only a little talent, like his, was an awful, plaguing thing; that being only a little special meant you expected too much, most of the time, and liked yourself too little. He wanted to assure her that she had missed nothing" -- Mary Robison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85992-a-new-degree-of-anger-came-over-him-what-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 14:15:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85992-a-new-degree-of-anger-came-over-him-what-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A new degree of anger came over him. What did it all matter? What did it matter if the mother talked Polish and cried in labour, if this child were stiff with resistance, and crying?Why take it to heart?Let the mother cry in labour, let the child cry in resistance, since they would do so. Why should he fight against it, why resist? Let it be, if it were so. Let them be as they were, if they insisted." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53376-what-good-are-insights-they-only-make-things-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 20:21:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53376-what-good-are-insights-they-only-make-things-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What good are insights?  They only make things worse." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187599-my-ideal-life-is-a-quiet-one-i-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 17:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by Charles D'Ambrosio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187599-my-ideal-life-is-a-quiet-one-i-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ideal life is a quiet one. I like to read, to sit still in the same chair, with the lampshade at a certain angle, alone, or with Meagan nearby, and now and then, if I'm lucky, I'll come across a lovely phrase or fine sentiment, look up from my book, and feel the harmony of some notion, the justice of it, and know that everything is there. That's life to me, those privately discovered moments. " -- Charles D'Ambrosio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2011 18:44:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by George Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165931-you-know-that-feeling-at-the-end-of-the-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know that feeling at the end of the day, when the anxiety of that-which-I-must-do falls away and, for maybe the first time that day, you see, with some clarity, the people you love and the ways you have, during that day, slightly ignored them, turned away from them to get back to what you were doing, blurted out some mildly hurtful thing, projected, instead of the deep love you really feel, a surge of defensiveness or self-protection or suspicion?  That moment when you think, Oh God, what have I done with this day?  And what am I doing with my life?  And how must I change to avoid catastrophic end-of-life regrets?

I feel like that now: tired of the Me I've always been, tired of making the same mistakes, repetitively stumbling after the same small ego strokes, being caught in the same loops of anxiety and defensiveness.  At the end of my life, I know I won't be wishing I'd held more back, been less effusive, more often stood on ceremony, forgiven less, spent more days oblivious to the secret wishes and fears of the people around me...  

--&quot;Buddha Boy" -- George Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293478-oh-god-it-s-wonderful-to-get-out-of-bed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 19:28:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by Frank O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293478-oh-god-it-s-wonderful-to-get-out-of-bed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["oh god it’s wonderful 
to get out of bed 
and drink too much coffee 
and smoke too many cigarettes 
and love you so much" -- Frank O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513621-it-was-like-that-class-at-school-where-the-teacher</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 22:27:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Wesley add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/513621-it-was-like-that-class-at-school-where-the-teacher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was like that class at school where the teacher talks about Realization, about how you could realize something big in a commonplace thing. The example he gave--and the liar said it really happened--was that once while drinking orange juice, he'd realized he would be dead someday. He wondered if we, his students, had had similar 'realizations.'
Is he kidding? I thought.
Once I cashed a paycheck and I realized it wasn't enough.
Once I had food poisoning, and realized I was trapped inside my body." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
