<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82930-sarita]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/82930-sarita" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 12:15:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56843-let-me-make-a-clean-breast-of-it-here-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 12:15:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56843-let-me-make-a-clean-breast-of-it-here-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me make a clean breast of it here, and frankly admit that I kept but sorry guard. With the problem of the universe revolving in me, how could I- being left completely to myself at such a thought-engendering altitude- how could I but lightly hold my obligations to observe all whaleships' standing orders, &quot;Keep your weather eye open, and sing out every time.&quot; 

     And let me in this place movingly admonish you, ye ship-owners of Nantucket! Beware of enlisting in your vigilant fisheries any lad with lean brow and hollow eye; given to unseasonable meditativeness...: your whales must be seen before they can be killed; and this sunken-eyed young Platonist will tow you ten wakes round the world, and never make you one pint of sperm the richer. 

Nor are these monitions at all unneeded. For nowadays, the whale-fishery furnishes an asylum for many romantic, melancholy, and absent-minded young men, disgusted with the corking care of earth, and seeking sentiment in tar and blubber. Childe Harold not unfrequently perches himself upon the mast-head of some luckless disappointed whale-ship, and in moody phrase ejaculates:- &quot;Roll on, thou deep and dark blue ocean, roll! Ten thousand blubber-hunters sweep over thee in vain. &quot;

... &quot;Why, thou monkey,&quot; said a harpooneer to one of these lads, &quot;we've been cruising now hard upon three years, and thou hast not raised a whale yet. Whales are scarce as hen's teeth whenever thou art up here.&quot; Perhaps they were; or perhaps there might have been shoals of them in the far horizon; but lulled into such an opium-like listlessness of vacant, unconscious reverie is this absent-minded youth by the blending cadence of waves with thoughts, that at last he loses his identity; takes the mystic ocean at his feet for the visible image of that deep, blue, bottomless soul, pervading mankind and nature; and every strange, half-seen, gliding, beautiful thing that eludes him; every dimly-discovered, uprising fin of some undiscernible form, seems to him the embodiment of those elusive thoughts that only people the soul by continually flitting through it. In this enchanted mood, thy spirit ebbs away to whence it came; becomes diffused through time and space; like Crammer's sprinkled Pantheistic ashes, forming at last a part of every shore the round globe over. 

     There is no life in thee, now, except that rocking life imparted by a gentle rolling ship; by her, borrowed from the sea; by the sea, from the inscrutable tides of God. But while this sleep, this dream is on ye, move your foot or hand an inch; slip your hold at all; and your identity comes back in horror. Over Descartian vortices you hover. And perhaps, at midday, in the fairest weather, with one half-throttled shriek you drop through that transparent air into the summer sea, no more to rise for ever. Heed it well, ye Pantheists! " -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57886-all-great-literature-is-one-of-two-stories-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 09:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Leo Tolstoy ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57886-all-great-literature-is-one-of-two-stories-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All great literature is one of two stories; a man goes on a journey or a stranger comes to town." -- Leo Tolstoy ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166676-from-wonder-into-wonder-existence-opens</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:44:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Lao Tsu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166676-from-wonder-into-wonder-existence-opens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["from wonder into wonder 
existence opens" -- Lao Tsu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19119-of-all-the-preposterous-assumptions-of-humanity-over-humanity-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:45:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19119-of-all-the-preposterous-assumptions-of-humanity-over-humanity-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the preposterous assumptions of humanity over humanity, nothing exceeds most of the criticisms made on the habits of the poor by the well-housed, well- warmed, and well-fed." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289281-from-john-hay-s-diary-the-president-never-appeared-to-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 13:40:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289281-from-john-hay-s-diary-the-president-never-appeared-to-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(from John Hay's diary) “The President never appeared to better advantage in the world,” Hay proudly noted in his diary. “Though He knows how immense is the danger to himself from the unreasoning anger of that committee, he never cringed to them for an instant.  He stood where he thought he was right and crushed them with his candid logic." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139840-well-then-however-the-old-sea-captains-may-order-me-about--however</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:44:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139840-well-then-however-the-old-sea-captains-may-order-me-about--however]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, then, however the old sea-captains may order me about--however they may thump and punch me about, I have the satisfaction of knowing that it is all right; that everybody else is one way or other served in much the same way--either in a physical or metaphysical point of view, that is; and so the universal thump is passed round, and all hands should rub each other's shoulder-blades, and be content." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:44:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are more things in Heaven and Earth, Horatio, than are dreamt of in your philosophy." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:43:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154489-what-thou-lovest-well-remains-the-rest-is-dross-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:43:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Ezra Pound]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154489-what-thou-lovest-well-remains-the-rest-is-dross-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What thou lovest well remains,

the rest is dross

What thou lov’st well shall not be reft from thee

What thou lov’st well is thy true heritage" -- Ezra Pound]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289284-elizabeth-blair-of-brother-frank-he-could-not-let-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 13:36:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289284-elizabeth-blair-of-brother-frank-he-could-not-let-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elizabeth Blair of brother Frank: he could “not let even a great man set his small dogs on him without kicking the dog &amp; giving his master some share of the resentment." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289287-lincoln-understood-the-importance-as-one-delegate-put-it-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:44:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289287-lincoln-understood-the-importance-as-one-delegate-put-it-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lincoln understood the importance, as one delegate put it, of integrating “all the elements of the Republican party—including the impracticable, the Pharisees, the better-than-thou declaimers, the long-haired men and the short-haired women." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289286-lincoln-reflecting-on-george-washington-s-words-it-is-of-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2011 06:44:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289286-lincoln-reflecting-on-george-washington-s-words-it-is-of-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(Lincoln reflecting on) George Washington's words: “It is of infinite moment  that you should properly estimate the immense value of your national union to your collective and individual happiness; that you should cherish a cordial, habitual, and immovable attachment to it; accustoming yourselves to think and speak of it as of the palladium of your political safety and prospertiy.  Washington advised vigilance against “the first dawning of every attempt to alienate any portion of our country from the rest or to enfeeble the sacred ties which now link together the various parts." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289288-simon-cameron-i-loved-my-brother-as-only-the-poor</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 13:39:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289288-simon-cameron-i-loved-my-brother-as-only-the-poor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Simon Cameron: “I loved my brother, as only the poor and lonely can love those with whom they have toiled and struggled up the rugged hill of life’s success—but he died bravely in the discharge of his duty." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54815-a-good-laugh-is-a-mighty-good-thing-and-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 10:13:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54815-a-good-laugh-is-a-mighty-good-thing-and-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good laugh is a mighty good thing, and rather too scarce a good thing; the more's the pity. So, if any one man, in his own proper person, afford stuff for a good joke to anybody, let him not be backward, but let him cheerfully allow himself to spend and be spent in that way. And the man that has anything bountifully laughable about him, be sure there is more in that man than you perhaps think for." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2011 10:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:28:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been given questions to which you cannot be given answers. You will have to live them out - perhaps a little at a time.'
And how long is that going to take?'
I don't know. As long as you live, perhaps.'
That could be a long time.'
I will tell you a further mystery,' he said. 'It may take longer." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434554-i-could-die-in-peace-i-think-if-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:29:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434554-i-could-die-in-peace-i-think-if-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could die in peace, I think, if the world was beautiful. To know it's being ruined is hard." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368185-as-i-have-read-the-gospels-over-the-years-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:29:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368185-as-i-have-read-the-gospels-over-the-years-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As I have read the Gospels over the years, the belief has grown in me that Christ did not come to found an organized religion but came instead to found an unorganized one. He seems to have come to carry religion out of the temples into the fields and sheep pastures, onto the roadsides and the banks of the rivers, into the houses of sinners and publicans, into the town and the wilderness, toward the membership of all that is here. Well, you can read and see what you think." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414260-history-overflows-time-love-overflows-the-allowance-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:31:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414260-history-overflows-time-love-overflows-the-allowance-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["History overflows time. Love overflows the allowance of the world. All the vessels overflow, and no end or limit stays put. Every shakable thing has got to be shaken. In a sense, nothing that was ever lost in Port William ever has been replaced. In another sense, nothing is ever lost, and we are compacted together forever, even by our failures, our regrets, and our longings." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425395-the-music-while-it-lasted-brought-a-new-world-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:31:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425395-the-music-while-it-lasted-brought-a-new-world-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The music, while it lasted, brought a new world into being." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414264-my-vision-of-the-gathered-church-that-had-come-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:32:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414264-my-vision-of-the-gathered-church-that-had-come-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My vision of the gathered church that had come to me... had been replaced by a vision of the gathered community. What I saw now was the community imperfect and irresolute but held together by the frayed and always fraying, incomplete and yet ever-holding bonds of the various sorts of affection. There had maybe never been anybody who had not been loved by somebody, who had been loved by somebody else, and so on and on... It was a community always disappointed in itself, disappointing its members, always trying to contain its divisions and gentle its meanness, always failing and yet always preserving a sort of will toward goodwill. I knew that, in the midst of all the ignorance and error, this was a membership; it was the membership of Port William and of no other place on earth. My vision gathered the community as it never has been and never will be gathered in this world of time, for the community must always be marred by members who are indifferent to it or against it, who are nonetheless its members and maybe nonetheless essential to it. And yet I saw them all as somehow perfected, beyond time, by one another's love, compassion, and forgiveness, as it is said we may be perfected by grace." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425423-new-grief-when-it-came-you-could-feel-filling-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:33:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/425423-new-grief-when-it-came-you-could-feel-filling-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["New grief, when it came, you could feel filling the air. It took up all the room there was. The place itself, the whole place, became a reminder of the absence of the hurt or the dead or the missing one. I don't believe that grief passes away. It has its time and place forever. More time is added to it; it becomes a story within a story. But grief and griever alike endure." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24670-the-complexity-of-our-present-trouble-suggests-as-never-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 13:35:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarita add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24670-the-complexity-of-our-present-trouble-suggests-as-never-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The complexity of our present trouble suggests as never before that we need to change our present concept of education. Education is not properly an industry, and its proper use is not to serve industries, either by job-training or by industry-subsidized research. It's proper use is to enable citizens to live lives that are economically, politically, socially, and culturally responsible. This cannot be done by gathering or &quot;accessing&quot; what we now call &quot;information&quot; - which is to say facts without context and therefore without priority. A proper education enables young people to put their lives in order, which means knowing what things are more important than other things; it means putting first things first." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
