<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/829470-kemireads]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/829470-kemireads" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 15:38:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2012 15:38:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kemireads! add a quote by David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100888-because-here-s-something-else-that-s-weird-but-true-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because here's something else that's weird but true: in the day-to day trenches of adult life, there is actually no such thing as atheism. There is no such thing as not worshipping. Everybody worships. The only choice we get is what to worship. And the compelling reason for maybe choosing some sort of god or spiritual-type thing to worship -- be it JC or Allah, be it YHWH or the Wiccan Mother Goddess, or the Four Noble Truths, or some inviolable set of ethical principles -- is that pretty much anything else you worship will eat you alive. If you worship money and things, if they are where you tap real meaning in life, then you will never have enough, never feel you have enough. It's the truth. Worship your body and beauty and sexual allure and you will always feel ugly. And when time and age start showing, you will die a million deaths before they finally grieve you. On one level, we all know this stuff already. It's been codified as myths, proverbs, clichés, epigrams, parables; the skeleton of every great story. The whole trick is keeping the truth up front in daily consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 08:44:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kemireads! add a quote by Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32978-recognize-that-the-very-molecules-that-make-up-your-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Recognize that the very molecules that make up your body, the atoms that construct the molecules, are traceable to the crucibles that were once the centers of high mass stars that exploded their chemically rich guts into the galaxy, enriching pristine gas clouds with the chemistry of life.  So that we are all connected to each other biologically, to the earth chemically and to the rest of the universe atomically.  That’s kinda cool!  That makes me smile and I actually feel quite large at the end of that.  It’s not that we are better than the universe, we are part of the universe.  We are in the universe and the universe is in us." -- Neil deGrasse Tyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345798-livid-adj-fuck-you-for-cheating-on-me-fuck-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2013 21:32:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kemireads! add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/345798-livid-adj-fuck-you-for-cheating-on-me-fuck-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["livid, &lt;i&gt;adj.&lt;/i&gt;

Fuck You for cheating on me.  Fuck you for reducing it to the word cheating.  As if this were a card game, and you sneaked a look at my hand.  Who came up with the term &lt;i&gt;cheating,&lt;/i&gt; anyway?  A cheater, I imagine.  Someone who thought &lt;i&gt;liar&lt;/i&gt; was too harsh.  Someone who thought &lt;i&gt;devastator&lt;/i&gt; was too emotional.  The same person who thought, oops, he’d gotten &lt;i&gt;caught with his hand in the cookie jar.&lt;/i&gt;  Fuck you.  This isn’t about slipping yourself an extra twenty dollars of Monopoly money.  These are our lives.  You went and broke our lives.  You are so much worse than a cheater.  You killed something.  And you killed it when its back was turned." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543639-i-am-the-happiest-man-alive-i-have-that-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 11:44:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kemireads! add a quote by Thomas Browne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/543639-i-am-the-happiest-man-alive-i-have-that-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the happiest man alive.  I have that in me that can convert poverty to riches, adversity to prosperity, and I am more invulnerable than Archilles;  Fortune hath not one place to hit me." -- Thomas Browne]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
