<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/830683-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/830683-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 18:52:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79460-when-you-look-into-your-mother-s-eyes-you-know-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 18:52:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79460-when-you-look-into-your-mother-s-eyes-you-know-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you look into your mother’s eyes, you know that is the purest love you can find on this earth." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18297-be-a-mother-who-is-committed-to-loving-her-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Marjorie Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18297-be-a-mother-who-is-committed-to-loving-her-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be a Mother who is committed to loving her children into standing on higher ground than the enviroment surrounding them. Mothers are endowed with a love that is unlike any other love on the face of the earth." -- Marjorie Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Brenda Ueland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73427-in-fact-that-is-why-the-lives-of-most-women]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact that is why the lives of most women are so vaguely unsatisfactory. They are always doing secondary and menial things (that do not require all their gifts and ability) for others and never anything for themselves. Society and husbands praise them for it (when they get too miserable or have nervous breakdowns) though always a little perplexedly and half-heartedly and just to be consoling. The poor wives are reminded that that is just why wives are so splendid -- because they are so unselfish and self-sacrificing and that is the wonderful thing about them! But inwardly women know that something is wrong. They sense that if you are always doing something for others, like a servant or nurse, and never anything for yourself, you cannot do others any good. You make them physically more comfortable. But you cannot affect them spiritually in any way at all. For to teach, encourage, cheer up, console, amuse, stimulate or advise a husband or children or friends, you have to be something yourself. [...]&quot;If you would shut your door against the children for an hour a day and say; 'Mother is working on her five-act tragedy in blank verse!' you would be surprised how they would respect you. They would probably all become playwrights." -- Brenda Ueland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159330-my-mother-taught-me-some-basic-philosophies-of-rearing-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:12:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley/Small and Simple Things]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159330-my-mother-taught-me-some-basic-philosophies-of-rearing-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother taught me some basic philosophies of rearing children.  One is that you have to trust them.  I tried hard never to say &quot;no&quot; if I could possibly say &quot;yes&quot;.  I think that worked well because it gave my children the feeling that I trusted them and they were responsible to do the best they could." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley/Small and Simple Things]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108479-a-mother-s-nurturing-love-arouses-in-children-from-their-earliest</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:14:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by M. Russell Ballard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108479-a-mother-s-nurturing-love-arouses-in-children-from-their-earliest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mother's nurturing love arouses in children, from their earliest days on earth, an awakening of the memories of love and goodness they experience in their premortal existence,  Because our mothers love us, we learn, or more accurately remember, that God also loves us" -- M. Russell Ballard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50956-mother-is-the-name-for-god-in-the-lips-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50956-mother-is-the-name-for-god-in-the-lips-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mother is the name for God in the lips and hearts of little children." -- William Makepeace Thackeray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:15:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No pain that we suffer, no trial that we experience is wasted. It ministers to our education, to the development of such qualities as patience, faith, fortitude and humility. All that we suffer and all that we endure, especially when we endure it patiently, builds up our characters, purifies our hearts, expands our souls, and makes us more tender and charitable, more worthy to be called the children of God . . . and it is through sorrow and suffering, toil and tribulation, that we gain the education that we come here to acquire and which will make us more like our Father and Mother in heaven." -- Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194434-even-if-i-m-setting-myself-up-for-failure-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ayelet Waldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194434-even-if-i-m-setting-myself-up-for-failure-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even if i'm setting myself up for failure, I think it's worth trying to be a mother who delights in who her children are, in their knock-knock jokes and earnest questions. A mother who spends less time obseessing about what will happen, or what has happened, and more time reveling in what is.  A mother who doesn't fret over failings and slights, who realizes her worries and anxieties are just thoughts, the continuous chattering and judgement of a too busy mind. A mother who doesn't worry so much about being bad or good but just recognizes that she's both, and neither. A mother who does her best, and for whom that is good enough, even if, in the end, her best turns out to be, simply, not bad. " -- Ayelet Waldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72476-if-i-cannot-give-my-children-a-perfect-mother-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:16:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ruth Bell Graham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72476-if-i-cannot-give-my-children-a-perfect-mother-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I cannot give my children a perfect mother I can at least give them more of the one they've got--and make that one more loving.  I will be available.  I will take time to listen, time to play, time to be home when they arrive from school, time to counsel and encouerage." -- Ruth Bell Graham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51624-i-was-also-told-that-there-is-no-greater-prayer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:19:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Betty J. Eadie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51624-i-was-also-told-that-there-is-no-greater-prayer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was also told that there is no greater prayer than that of a mother for her children.  These are the purest prayers because of their intense desire and, at times, sense of desperation.  A mother has the ability to give her heart to her children and to implore mightily before God for them." -- Betty J. Eadie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104171-any-woman-who-has-devoted-herself-to-raising-children-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 19:20:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ann Crittenden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104171-any-woman-who-has-devoted-herself-to-raising-children-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any woman who has devoted herself to raising children has experienced the hollow praise that only thinly conceals smug dismissal.  In a culture that measures worth and achievement almost solely in terms of money, the intensive work of rearing responsible adults counts for little.  One of the most intriguing questions in economic history is how this came to be; how mothers came to be excluded from the ranks of productive citizens.  How did the demanding job of rearing a modern child come to be termed baby-sitting?  When did caring for children become a 'labor of love,;' smothered under a blanket of sentimentality that hides its economic importance?" -- Ann Crittenden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25798-the-art-of-mothering-is-to-teach-the-art-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:00:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Elaine Heffner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25798-the-art-of-mothering-is-to-teach-the-art-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of mothering is to teach the art of living to children." -- Elaine Heffner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205560-i-d-tell-my-mother-to-you-know-go-you-know-what-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 20:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gregg Olsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205560-i-d-tell-my-mother-to-you-know-go-you-know-what-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd tell my mother to, you know,  go you-know-what herself and I would go help those children. They're in an orphanage and they've got family! That's sickening. What does John do? Nothing. His kids are in an orphanage... and he does nothing.
~ Michelle Jarvis" -- Gregg Olsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153929-you-can-t-use-up-creativity-the-more-you-use-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 15:36:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153929-you-can-t-use-up-creativity-the-more-you-use-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't use up creativity. The more you use, the more you have." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122527-creativity-is-a-continual-surprise</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 15:40:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122527-creativity-is-a-continual-surprise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Creativity is a continual surprise." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58124-remember-goals-are-stars-to-steer-by-not-sticks-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 07:23:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Barbara Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58124-remember-goals-are-stars-to-steer-by-not-sticks-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, goals are stars to steer by, not sticks with which to beat ourselves." -- Barbara Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
