<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/83139-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/83139-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:59:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134436-in-any-case-frequent-punishments-are-a-sign-of-weakness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 11:59:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jean-Jacques Rousseau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134436-in-any-case-frequent-punishments-are-a-sign-of-weakness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In any case, frequent punishments are a sign of weakness or slackness in the government. There is no man so bad that he cannot be made good for something. No man should be put to death, even as an example, if he can be left to live without danger to society." -- Jean-Jacques Rousseau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470266-the-words-consent-of-the-governed-have-become-an-empty</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 16:16:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Chris Hedges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470266-the-words-consent-of-the-governed-have-become-an-empty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The words &lt;i&gt;consent of the governed&lt;/i&gt; have become an empty phrase. Our textbooks on political science and economics are obsolete. Our nation has been hijacked by oligarchs, corporations, and a narrow, selfish, political, and economic elite, a small and privileged group that governs, and often steals, on behalf of moneyed interests. This elite, in the name of patriotism and democracy, in the name of all the values that were once part of the American system and defined the Protestant work ethic, has systematically destroyed our manufacturing sector, looted the treasury, corrupted our democracy, and trashed the financial system. During this plundering we remained passive, mesmerized by the enticing shadows on the wall, assured our tickets to success, prosperity, and happiness were waiting around the corner." -- Chris Hedges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470267-washington-has-become-our-versailles-we-are-ruled-entertained-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 16:19:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Chris Hedges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470267-washington-has-become-our-versailles-we-are-ruled-entertained-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Washington has become our Versailles. We are ruled, entertained, and informed by courtiers -- and the media has evolved into a class of courtiers. The Democrats, like the Republicans, are mostly courtiers. Our pundits and experts, at least those with prominent public platforms, are courtiers. We are captivated by the hollow stagecraft of political theater as we are ruthlessly stripped of power. It is smoke and mirrors, tricks and con games, and the purpose behind it is deception." -- Chris Hedges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 18:34:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822771-it-takes-a-heavy-commitment-to-quality-education-for-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 11:24:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by William H. Calvin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/822771-it-takes-a-heavy-commitment-to-quality-education-for-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a heavy commitment to quality education for all to avoid that stratification of society, those needless degrees of separation. But even the present-day United States has lost what commitment it used to have to free education of high quality. Anyone reading the annual surveys of science literacy (another example: fewer than half of Americans know that the earth orbits the sun once a year) has to wonder how badly most people are going to be left behind, further along into the 21st century, whether they too will become &quot;stubborn, apathetic, and perverse&quot; toward a scientific and technological world they must view as magical, beyond their comprehension, accessible only via the right incantations." -- William H. Calvin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/601222-organization-is-the-devil-s-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 20:13:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Linda Medley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/601222-organization-is-the-devil-s-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Organization is the Devil's work." -- Linda Medley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108752-whoever-it-is-you-fall-in-love-with-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:59:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108752-whoever-it-is-you-fall-in-love-with-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever it is you fall in love with for the first time, not just love but be in love with, is the one who will always make you angry, the one you can't be logical about." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
