<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/831657-graeme-s-houston]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/831657-graeme-s-houston" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 13:32:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26643-what-is-a-man-if-his-chief-good-and-market</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 13:32:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26643-what-is-a-man-if-his-chief-good-and-market]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a man, if his chief good and market of his time be but to sleep and feed? a beast, no more. Sure he that made us with such large discourse, looking before and after, gave us not that capability and god-like reason to fust in us unused." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 13:37:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sky above the port was the color of television, tuned to a dead channel." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10371-find-out-what-your-hero-or-heroine-wants-and-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 13:40:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10371-find-out-what-your-hero-or-heroine-wants-and-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Find out what your hero or heroine wants, and when he or she wakes up in the morning, just follow him or her all day.." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26657-it-s-all-that-the-young-can-do-for-the-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 13:40:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26657-it-s-all-that-the-young-can-do-for-the-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's all that the young can do for the old, to shock them and keep them up to date." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11669-had-i-the-heavens-embroidered-cloths-enwrought-with-golden-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 14:47:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11669-had-i-the-heavens-embroidered-cloths-enwrought-with-golden-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Had I the heavens' embroidered cloths,
Enwrought with golden and silver light,
The blue and the dim and the dark cloths
Of night and light and the half light,
I would spread the cloths under your feet:
But I, being poor, have only my dreams;
I have spread my dreams under your feet;
Tread softly because you tread on my dreams." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26676-on-the-seashore-of-endless-worlds-children-meet-the-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 15:00:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Graeme add a quote by Rabindranath Tagore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26676-on-the-seashore-of-endless-worlds-children-meet-the-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the seashore of endless worlds children meet.

The infinite sky is motionless overhead and the restless water is boisterous. On the seashore of endless worlds the children meet with shouts and dances.

They build their houses with sand, and they play with empty shells. With withered leaves they weave their boats and smilingly float them on the vast deep. Children have their play on the seashore of worlds.

They know not how to swim, they know not how to cast nets. Pearl-fishers dive for pearls, merchants sail in their ships, while children gather pebbles and scatter them again. They seek not for hidden treasures, they know not how to cast nets.

The sea surges up with laughter, and pale gleams the smile of the sea-beach. Death-dealing waves sing meaningless ballads to the children, even like a mother while rocking her baby’s cradle. The sea plays with children, and pale gleams the smile of the sea-beach.

On the seashore of endless worlds children meet. Tempest roams in the pathless sky, ships are wrecked in the trackless water, death is abroad and children play. On the seashore of endless worlds is the great meeting of children." -- Rabindranath Tagore]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
