<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/831792-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/831792-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 10:59:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181632-a-number-of-months-ago-i-read-in-the-newspaper</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 10:59:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kate add a quote by David Wojnarowicz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181632-a-number-of-months-ago-i-read-in-the-newspaper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A number of months ago I read in the newspaper that there was a supreme court ruling which states that homosexuals in america have no constitutional rights against the government's invasion of their privacy.  The paper states that homosexuality is traditionally condemned in america &amp; only people who are heterosexual or married or who have families can expect those constitutional rights.  There were no editorials.  Nothing.  Just flat cold type in the morning paper informing people of this.  In most areas of the u.s.a it is possible to murder a man &amp; when one is brought to trial, one has only to say that the victim was a queer &amp; that he tried to touch you &amp; the courts will set you free.  When I read the newspaper article I felt something stirring in my hands; I felt a sensation like seeing oneself from miles above the earth or looking at one's reflection in a mirror through the wrong end of a telescope. Realizing that I have nothing left to lose in my actions I let my hands become weapons, my teeth become weapons, every bone &amp; muscle &amp; fiber &amp; ounce of blood become weapons, &amp; I feel prepared for the rest of my life." -- David Wojnarowicz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25300-belize-hell-or-heaven-roy-indicates-heaven-through-a-glance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 11:00:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kate add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25300-belize-hell-or-heaven-roy-indicates-heaven-through-a-glance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Belize: Hell or heaven? 

[Roy indicates &quot;Heaven&quot; through a glance]

Belize: Like San Francisco.

Roy Cohn: A city. Good. I was worried... it'd be a garden. I hate that shit.

Belize: Mmmm. Big city. Overgrown with weeds, but flowering weeds. On every corner a wrecking crew and something new and crooked going up catty corner to that. Windows missing in every edifice like broken teeth, fierce gusts of gritty wind, and a gray high sky full of ravens.

Roy Cohn: Isaiah.

Belize: Prophet birds, Roy. Piles of trash, but lapidary like rubies and obsidian, and diamond-colored cowspit streamers in the wind. And voting booths.

Roy Cohn: And a dragon atop a golden horde.

Belize: And everyone in Balencia gowns with red corsages, and big dance palaces full of music and lights and racial impurity and gender confusion. And all the deities are creole, mulatto, brown as the mouths of rivers. Race, taste and history finally overcome. And you ain't there.

Roy Cohn: And Heaven?

Belize: That was Heaven, Roy." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42686-big-ben-struck-the-half-hour-how-extraordinary-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2009 10:59:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[kate add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42686-big-ben-struck-the-half-hour-how-extraordinary-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Big Ben struck the half hour.

How extraordinary it was, strange, yes, touching, to see the old lady (they had been neighbors ever so many years) move away from the window, as if she were attached to that sound, that string. Gigantic as it was, it had something to do with her. Down, down, into the midst of ordinary things the finger fell making the moment solemn. She was forced, so Clarissa imagined, by that sound, to move, to go - but where? Clarissa tried to follow her as she turned and disappeared, and could still just see her white cap moving at the back of the bedroom. She was still there moving about at the other end of the room. Why creeds and prayers and mackintoshes? when, thought Clarissa, that's the miracle, that's the mystery; that old lady, she meant, whom she could see going from chest of drawers to dressing table. She could still see her. And the supreme mystery, which Kilman might say she had solved, or Peter might say he had solved, but Clarissa didn't believe either of them had the ghost of an idea of solving, was simply this: here was one room, there another. Did religion solve that, or love?" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
