<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/832026-scott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/832026-scott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 12:30:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98120-the-worst-part-is-wondering-how-you-ll-find-the-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 12:30:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98120-the-worst-part-is-wondering-how-you-ll-find-the-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part is wondering how you’ll find the strength tomorrow
to go on doing what you did today and have been doing for much
too long, where you’ll find the strength for all that stupid running around, those projects that come to nothing, those attempts to escape from crushing necessity, which always founder and serve only to convince you one more time that destiny is implacable, that every night will find you down and out, crushed by the dread of more and more sordid and insecure tomorrows. And maybe it’s treacherous old age coming on, threatening the worst. Not much music left inside us for life to dance to. Our youth has gone to the ends of the earth to die in the silence of the truth. And where, I ask you, can a man escape to, when he hasn’t enough madness left inside him? The truth is an endless death agony. The truth is death. You have to choose: death or lies. I’ve never been able to kill myself." -- Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148706-everybody-knows-that-aristotelian-two-value-logic-is-fucked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 12:58:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148706-everybody-knows-that-aristotelian-two-value-logic-is-fucked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody knows that Aristotelian two-value logic is fucked." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36874-sometimes-you-just-have-to-pee-in-the-sink</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 13:03:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36874-sometimes-you-just-have-to-pee-in-the-sink]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you just have to pee in the sink." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165289-irony-and-cynicism-were-just-what-the-u-s-hypocrisy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 20:29:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165289-irony-and-cynicism-were-just-what-the-u-s-hypocrisy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Irony and cynicism were just what the U.S. hypocrisy of the fifties and sixties called for. That’s what made the early postmodernists great artists. The great thing about irony is that it splits things apart, gets up above them so we can see the flaws and hypocrisies and duplicates. The virtuous always triumph? Ward Cleaver is the prototypical fifties father? &quot;Sure.&quot; Sarcasm, parody, absurdism and irony are great ways to strip off stuff’s mask and show the unpleasant reality behind it. The problem is that once the rules of art are debunked, and once the unpleasant realities the irony diagnoses are revealed and diagnosed, &quot;then&quot; what do we do? Irony’s useful for debunking illusions, but most of the illusion-debunking in the U.S. has now been done and redone. Once everybody knows that equality of opportunity is bunk and Mike Brady’s bunk and Just Say No is bunk, now what do we do? All we seem to want to do is keep ridiculing the stuff. Postmodern irony and cynicism’s become an end in itself, a measure of hip sophistication and literary savvy. Few artists dare to try to talk about ways of working toward redeeming what’s wrong, because they’ll look sentimental and naive to all the weary ironists. Irony’s gone from liberating to enslaving. There’s some great essay somewhere that has a line about irony being the song of the prisoner who’s come to love his cage." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172808-we-re-all-especially-those-of-us-who-are-educated-and-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 20:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172808-we-re-all-especially-those-of-us-who-are-educated-and-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all—especially those of us who are educated and have read a lot and have watched TV critically—in a very self-conscious and sort of worldly and sophisticated time, but also a time when we seem terribly afraid of other people's reactions to us and very desperate to control how people interpret us. Everyone is extremely conscious of manipulating how they come off in the media; they want to structure what they say so that the reader or audience will interpret it in the way that is most favorable to them. What's interesting to me is that this isn't all that new. This was the project of the Sophists in Athens, and this is what Socrates and Plato thought was so completely evil. The Sophists had this idea: Forget this idea of what's true or not—what you want to do is rhetoric; you want to be able to persuade the audience and have the audience think you're smart and cool. And Socrates and Plato, basically their whole idea is, &quot;Bullshit. There is such a thing as truth, and it's not all just how to say what you say so that you get a good job or get laid, or whatever it is people think they want." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 20:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200381-the-so-called-psychotically-depressed-person-who-tries-to-kill-herself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The so-called ‘psychotically depressed’ person who tries to kill herself doesn’t do so out of quote ‘hopelessness’ or any abstract conviction that life’s assets and debits do not square. And surely not because death seems suddenly appealing. The person in whom Its invisible agony reaches a certain unendurable level will kill herself the same way a trapped person will eventually jump from the window of a burning high-rise. Make no mistake about people who leap from burning windows. Their terror of falling from a great height is still just as great as it would be for you or me standing speculatively at the same window just checking out the view; i.e. the fear of falling remains a constant. The variable here is the other terror, the fire’s flames: when the flames get close enough, falling to death becomes the slightly less terrible of two terrors. It’s not desiring the fall; it’s terror of the flames. And yet nobody down on the sidewalk, looking up and yelling ‘Don’t!’ and ‘Hang on!’, can understand the jump. Not really. You’d have to have personally been trapped and felt flames to really understand a terror way beyond falling." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105183-probably-i-dont-believe-in-a-lot-of-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 20:57:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105183-probably-i-dont-believe-in-a-lot-of-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Probably I dont believe in a lot of things that I used to believe in but that doesnt mean I dont believe in anything." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 21:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249420-i-had-two-dreams-about-him-after-he-died-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had two dreams about him after he died.  I dont remember the first one all that well but it was about meetin him in town somewheres and he give me some money and I think I lost it.  But the second one it was like we was both back in older times and I was on horseback goin through the mountains of a night.  Goin through this pass in the mountains.  It was cold and there was snow on the ground and he rode past me and kept on goin.  Never said nothin.  He just rode on past and he had this blanket wrapped around him and he had his head down and when he rode past I seen he was carryin fire in a horn the way people used to do and I could see the horn from the light inside of it.  About the color of the moon.  And in the dream I knew that he was goin on ahead and that he was fixin to make a fire somewhere out there in all that dark and all that cold and I knew that whenever I got there he would be there.  And then I woke up." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328033-a-legion-of-horribles-hundreds-in-number-half-naked-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 21:11:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328033-a-legion-of-horribles-hundreds-in-number-half-naked-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A legion of horribles, hundreds in number, half naked or clad in costumes attic or biblical or wardrobed out of a fevered dream with the skins of animals and silk finery and pieces of uniform still tracked with the blood of prior owners, coats of slain dragoons, frogged and braided cavalry jackets, one in a stovepipe hat and one with an umbrella and one in white stockings and a bloodstained wedding veil and some in headgear or cranefeathers or rawhide helmets that bore the horns of bull or buffalo and one in a pigeontailed coat worn backwards and otherwise naked and one in the armor of a Spanish conquistador, the breastplate and pauldrons deeply dented with old blows of mace or sabre done in another country by men whose very bones were dust and many with their braids spliced up with the hair of other beasts until they trailed upon the ground and their horses' ears and tails worked with bits of brightly colored cloth and one whose horse's whole head was painted crimson red and all the horsemen's faces gaudy and grotesque with daubings like a company of mounted clowns, death hilarious, all howling in a barbarous tongue and riding down upon them like a horde from a hell more horrible yet than the brimstone land of Christian reckoning, screeching and yammering and clothed in smoke like those vaporous beings in regions beyond right knowing where the eye wanders and the lip jerks and drools." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287119-chin-up-ferdinand-i-kept-saying-to-myself-to-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 22:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287119-chin-up-ferdinand-i-kept-saying-to-myself-to-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chin up, Ferdinand,&quot; I kept saying to myself, to keep up my courage. &quot;What with being chucked out of everywhere, you're sure to find whatever it is that scares all those bastards so. It must be at the end of the night, and that's why they're so dead set against going to the end of the night." -- Louis-Ferdinand Céline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320643-all-our-misery-comes-from-wanting-at-all-costs-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 22:43:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320643-all-our-misery-comes-from-wanting-at-all-costs-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All our misery comes from wanting at all costs to go on being Tom, Dick, or Harry, year in, year out.  This body of ours, this disguise put on my common jumping molecules, is in constant revolt against the abominable farce of having to endure.  Our molecules, the dears, want to get lost in the universe as fast as they can!  It makes them miserable to be nothing but &quot;us,&quot; the jerks of infinity.  We'd burst if we had the courage, day after day we come very close to it.  The atomic torture we love so is locked up inside us by our pride." -- Louis-Ferdinand Celine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8114-you-begin-saving-the-world-by-saving-one-man-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 22:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8114-you-begin-saving-the-world-by-saving-one-man-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You begin saving the world by saving one man at a time; all else is grandiose romanticism or politics." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166220-i-was-sentimental-about-many-things-a-woman-s-shoes-under</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 22:51:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166220-i-was-sentimental-about-many-things-a-woman-s-shoes-under]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was sentimental about many things: a woman’s shoes under the bed; one hairpin left behind on the dresser; the way they said, 'I’m going to pee.' hair ribbons; walking down the boulevard with them at 1:30 in the afternoon, just two people walking together; the long nights of drinking and smoking; talking; the arguments; thinking of suicide; eating together and feeling good; the jokes; the laughter out of nowhere; feeling miracles in the air; being in a parked car together; comparing past loves at 3am; being told you snore; hearing her snore; mothers, daughters, sons, cats, dogs; sometimes death and sometimes divorce; but always carring on, always seeing it through; reading a newspaper alone in a sandwich joint and feeling nausea because she’s now married to a dentist with an I.Q. of 95; racetracks, parks, park picnics; even jails; her dull friends; your dull friends; your drinking, her dancing; your flirting, her flirting; her pills, your fucking on the side and her doing the same; sleeping together" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291536-ann-i-love-you-i-hope-my-car-starts-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 23:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291536-ann-i-love-you-i-hope-my-car-starts-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ann, I love you. I hope my car starts. I hope the sink isn't plugged up. I'm glad I didn't fuck a groupie. I'm glad I'm not very good at getting into bed with strange females. I'm glad I'm an idiot. I'm glad I don't know anything. I'm glad I haven't been murdered. When I look at my hands and they are still on my wrists, I think to myself, I am lucky." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170345-wherever-you-look-there-s-meanness-and-corruption-this-room-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 23:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170345-wherever-you-look-there-s-meanness-and-corruption-this-room-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever you look there’s meanness and corruption. This room, this bottle of grape wine, these fruits in the basket, are all products of profit and loss. A fellow can’t live without giving his passive acceptance to meanness. Somebody wears his tail to a frazzle for every mouthful we eat and every stitch we wear—and nobody seems to know. Everybody is blind, dumb, and blunt-headed—stupid and mean." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238695-masks-beneath-masks-until-suddenly-the-bare-bloodless-skull</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 23:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Scott add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/238695-masks-beneath-masks-until-suddenly-the-bare-bloodless-skull]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Masks beneath masks until suddenly the bare bloodless skull." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
