<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/832637-josh]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/832637-josh" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 19:01:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 19:01:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17892-the-absence-of-the-will-to-live-is-alas-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The absence of the will to live is, alas, not sufficient to make one want to die." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 07:52:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing was ever in tune. People just blindly grabbed at whatever there was: communism, health foods, zen, surfing, ballet, hypnotism, group encounters, orgies, biking, herbs, Catholicism, weight-lifting, travel, withdrawal, vegetarianism, India, painting, writing, sculpting, composing, conducting, backpacking, yoga, copulating, gambling, drinking, hanging around, frozen yogurt, Beethoven, Back, Buddha, Christ, TM, H, carrot juice, suicide, handmade suits, jet travel, New York City, and then it all evaporated and fell apart. People had to find things to do while waiting to die. I guess it was nice to have a choice." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1965-all-fled-all-done-so-lift-me-on-the-pyre-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 07:53:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Robert E. Howard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1965-all-fled-all-done-so-lift-me-on-the-pyre-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All fled—all done, so lift me on the pyre—&lt;br&gt;
The Feast is over, and the lamps expire." -- Robert E. Howard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22201-the-total-amount-of-suffering-per-year-in-the-natural</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 07:54:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22201-the-total-amount-of-suffering-per-year-in-the-natural]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The total amount of suffering per year in the natural world is beyond all decent contemplation. During the minute that it takes me to compose this sentence, thousands of animals are being eaten alive, many others are running for their lives, whimpering with fear, others are slowly being devoured from within by rasping parasites, thousands of all kinds are dying of starvation, thirst, and disease. It must be so. If there ever is a time of plenty, this very fact will automatically lead to an increase in the population until the natural state of starvation and misery is restored. In a universe of electrons and selfish genes, blind physical forces and genetic replication, some people are going to get hurt, other people are going to get lucky, and you won't find any rhyme or reason in it, nor any justice. The universe that we observe has precisely the properties we should expect if there is, at bottom, no design, no purpose, no evil, no good, nothing but pitiless indifference." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51878-knowledge-subverts-love-in-proportion-as-we-penetrate-our-secrets</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 18:24:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51878-knowledge-subverts-love-in-proportion-as-we-penetrate-our-secrets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge subverts love: in proportion as we penetrate our secrets, we come to loathe our kind, precisely because they resemble us." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51882-the-multiplication-of-our-kind-borders-on-the-obscene-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 18:27:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51882-the-multiplication-of-our-kind-borders-on-the-obscene-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The multiplication of our kind borders on the obscene; the duty to love them, on the preposterous." -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22359-and-between-whiles-you-boast-of-having-managed-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 08:15:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Louis Ferdinance Celine ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22359-and-between-whiles-you-boast-of-having-managed-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And between whiles you boast of having managed to be rid of your unhappiness, but everyone knows, don't they, that you've not done any such thing but are just as miserable as you well can be. As you grow uglier and uglier and more repulsive, playing this game as you grow old, you can't even conceal your unhappiness any longer, your failure; and in the end your face has become only an ugly expression which takes twenty, thirty or more years to come up from your stomach onto your face. That is what a man will achieve, that and that alone, -- an ugly expression which he has spent a lifetime making and often even then hasn't managed to finish off properly, because of how difficult and complicated an expression it would have to be to reflect his real soul without missing anything out. " -- Louis Ferdinance Celine ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102031-few-beings-have-ever-been-so-impregnated-pierced-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 06:35:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102031-few-beings-have-ever-been-so-impregnated-pierced-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few beings have ever been so impregnated, pierced to the core, by the conviction of the absolute futility of human aspiration. The universe is nothing but a furtive arrangement of elementary particles. A figure in transition toward chaos. That is what will finally prevail. The human race will disappear. Other races in turn will appear and disappear.  The skies will be glacial and empty, traversed by the feeble light of half-dead stars. These too will disappear. Everything will disappear. And human actions are as free and as stripped of meaning as the unfettered movements of the elementary particles. Good, evil, morality, sentiments? Pure ‘Victorian fictions.’ All that exists is egotism. Cold, intact, and radiant." -- Michel Houellebecq]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 09:07:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44274-people-speak-sometimes-about-the-bestial-cruelty-of-man-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People speak sometimes about the &quot;bestial&quot; cruelty of man, but that is terribly unjust and offensive to beasts, no animal could ever be so cruel as a man, so artfully, so artistically cruel." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247485-only-optimists-commit-suicide-optimists-who-no-longer-succeed-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 09:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josh add a quote by Emil Cioran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247485-only-optimists-commit-suicide-optimists-who-no-longer-succeed-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only optimists commit suicide, optimists who no longer succeed at being optimists. The others, having no reason to live, why would they have any to die?" -- Emil Cioran]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
