<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/833119-hoser]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/833119-hoser" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 09:54:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 09:54:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[hoser add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if the point of life has nothing to do with the creation of an ever-expanding region of control? What if the point is not to keep at bay all those people, beings, objects and emotions that we so needlessly fear? What if the point instead is to let go of that control? What if the point of life, the primary reason for existence, is to lie naked with your lover in a shady grove of trees? What if the point is to taste each other's sweat and feel the delicate pressure of finger on chest, thigh on thigh, lip on cheek? What if the point is to stop, then, in your slow movements together, and listen to the birdsong, to watch the dragonflies hover, to look at your lover's face, then up at the undersides of leaves moving together in the breeze? What if the point is to invite these others into your movement, to bring trees, wind, grass, dragonflies into your family and in so doing abandon any attempt to control them? What if the point all along has been to get along, to relate, to experience things on their own terms? What if the point is to feel joy when joyous, love when loving, anger when angry, thoughtful when full of thought? What if the point from the beginning has been to simply be?" -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134969-one-of-the-fables-we-live-by-is-that-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 09:54:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[hoser add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134969-one-of-the-fables-we-live-by-is-that-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the fables we live by is that some day the killing will stop. If only we rid ourselves of Chinese, white men will have jobs and white women will have virtue, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Indians, we will fulfill our Manifest Destiny, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Canaanites, we will live in the Promised Land, and then we can stop killing. If only we rid ourselves of Jews, we can build and maintain a Thousand Year Reich, and then we can stop killing. If only we stop the Soviet Union, we can stop the killing (remember the Peace Dividend that never materialized?). If only we can take out the worldwide terrorist network of bin Laden and others like him. If only. But the killing never stops. Always a new enemy to be hated is found." -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
