<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/834915-brandon-s]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/834915-brandon-s" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 12:41:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20955-sure-it-was-your-idea-and-your-fly-but-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 12:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon S. add a quote by John Gierach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20955-sure-it-was-your-idea-and-your-fly-but-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure, it was your idea and your fly, but he caught the big fish. Remember, fairness is a human idea largely unknown in nature." -- John Gierach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119455-she-lived-upstairs-in-the-farmhouse-guests-and-visitors-occupied</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:17:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon S. add a quote by Jon Katz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119455-she-lived-upstairs-in-the-farmhouse-guests-and-visitors-occupied]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She lived upstairs in the farmhouse; guests and visitors occupied the B&amp;B rooms downstairs. She kept crates tucked all over the house, in which herding dogs-border collies and shepherds-slept while waiting to work, exercise, or play. 

These working dogs, I'd come to learn, led lives very different from my dogs'. Carolyn let them out several times a day to exercise and eliminate, but generally, they were out of crates only to train or herd sheep. While they were out, Carolyn tossed a cup of kibble into their crates for them to eat when they returned. I asked her once if she left the lights on for the dogs when she went out, and she looked at me curiously. &quot;Why? They don't read... 

Still, they were everywhere. If you bumped into a sofa it might growl or thump. Some of her crew were puppies; some were strange rescue dogs." -- Jon Katz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119457-the-true-heart-of-carolyn-s-farm-was-her-kitchen-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 00:23:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brandon S. add a quote by Jon Katz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119457-the-true-heart-of-carolyn-s-farm-was-her-kitchen-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true heart of Carolyn's farm was her kitchen, where sausages and pungent dog treats lay scattered over they counters, along with collars, magazines and books, trial application forums, checks from her students (Carolyn, not big on details, often left them lying around for months), leashes, and dog toys. 

Pots of coffee were always brewing, and dog people could be found sitting around her big wooden table at all hours. Devon and I were always welcome there, and he grew to love going around the table from person to person, collecting pats and treats. Troubled dogs were familiar at the table, and appreciated. If we couldn't bring our dogs many places, we could always bring them here." -- Jon Katz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
