<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/836085-asma]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/836085-asma" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 13:43:20 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218565-in-our-travels-we-have-come-across-many-equations--math-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 13:43:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218565-in-our-travels-we-have-come-across-many-equations--math-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our travels, we have come across many equations--math for understanding the universe, for making music, for mapping stars, and also for tipping, which is important. Here is our favorite equation: Us plus Them equals All of Us. It is very simple math. Try it sometime. You probably won’t even need a pencil." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15307-sometimes-people-are-beautiful-not-in-looks-not-in-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 13:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15307-sometimes-people-are-beautiful-not-in-looks-not-in-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes people are beautiful.
Not in looks.
Not in what they say.
Just in what they are." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97041-i-understand-that-some-people-find-god-after-misfortune-although</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 22:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Andrew Davidson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97041-i-understand-that-some-people-find-god-after-misfortune-although]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I understand that some people find God after misfortune, although this seems to me even more ridiculous than finding Him in good times. 'God smote me. He must love me.' It's like not wanting a romantic relationship until a member of the opposite sex punches you in the face. My 'miraculous survival' will not change my opinion that Heaven is an idea constructed by man to help him cope with the fact that life on earth is both brutally short, and paradoxically, far too long. " -- Andrew Davidson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128778-is-it-possible-in-the-final-analysis-for-one-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 12:51:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128778-is-it-possible-in-the-final-analysis-for-one-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it possible, in the final analysis, for one human being to achieve perfect understanding of another?
We can invest enormous time and energy in serious efforts to know another person, but in the end, how close can we come to that person's essence? We convince ourselves that we know the other person well, but do we really know anything important about anyone?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:40:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:41:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:42:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:42:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:43:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:43:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54-don-t-walk-behind-me-i-may-not-lead-don-t-walk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't walk behind me; I may not lead. Don't walk in front of me; I may not follow. Just walk beside me and be my friend." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:43:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1598-you-only-live-once-but-if-you-do-it-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:44:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:44:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:45:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:46:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:46:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:46:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4583-always-forgive-your-enemies-nothing-annoys-them-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:46:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4583-always-forgive-your-enemies-nothing-annoys-them-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3929-yesterday-is-history-tomorrow-is-a-mystery-today-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2010 12:47:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Bill Keane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3929-yesterday-is-history-tomorrow-is-a-mystery-today-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, today is a gift of God, which is why we call it the present." -- Bill Keane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306928-and-what-does-she-mean-by-love-anyway-people-use</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 09:34:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Jude Morgan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/306928-and-what-does-she-mean-by-love-anyway-people-use]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what does she mean by love, anyway? People use that word and mean all sorts of things by it." -- Jude Morgan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 12:15:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267274-do-you-love-me-westley-is-that-it-he-couldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 12:19:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267274-do-you-love-me-westley-is-that-it-he-couldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you love me, Westley? Is that it?’
	He couldn’t believe it. ‘Do I love you? My God, if your love were a grain of sand, mine would be a universe of beaches. If your love were—‘
	‘I don’t understand the first one yet,’ Buttercup interrupted. She was starting to get very excited now. ‘Let me get this straight. Are you saying my love is the size of a grain of sand and yours is this other thing? Images just confuse me so—is this universal business of yours bigger than my sand? Help me, Westley. I have the feeling we’re on the verge of something just terribly important.’
	‘I have stayed these years in my hovel because of you. I have taught myself languages because of you. I have made my body strong because I thought you might be pleased by a strong body. I have lived my life with only the prayer that some sudden dawn you might glance in my direction. I have not known a moment in years when the sight of you did not send my heart careening against my rib cage. I have not known a night when your visage did not accompany me to sleep. There has not been a morning when you did not flutter behind my waking eyelids….Is any of this getting through to you, Buttercup, or do you want me to go on for a while?’
	‘Never stop.’
	‘There has not been—‘
	‘If you’re teasing me, Westley, I’m just going to kill you.’
	‘How can you even dream I might be teasing?’
	‘Well, you haven’t once said you loved me.’
	‘That’s all you need? Easy. I love you. Okay? Want it louder? I love you. Spell it out, should I? I ell-oh-vee-ee why-oh-you. Want it backward? You love I.’
	‘You are teasing now; aren’t you?’
	‘A little maybe; I’ve been saying it so long to you, you just wouldn’t listen. Every time you said ‘Farm boy do this’ you thought I was answering ‘As you wish’ but that’s only because you were hearing wrong. ‘I love you’ was what it was, but you never heard, and you never heard." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378531-romance-is-the-sweetening-of-the-soul-with-fragrance-offered</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 08:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Wole Soyinka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378531-romance-is-the-sweetening-of-the-soul-with-fragrance-offered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Romance is the sweetening of the soul
With fragrance offered by the stricken heart." -- Wole Soyinka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632563-he-was-mastered-by-the-sheer-surging-of-life-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 02:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Jack London]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/632563-he-was-mastered-by-the-sheer-surging-of-life-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was mastered by the sheer surging of life, the tidal wave of being, the perfect joy of each separate muscle, joint, and sinew in that it was everything that was not death, that it was aglow and rampant, expressing itself in movement, flying exultantly under the stars." -- Jack London]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 07:55:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292065-despite-your-best-efforts-people-are-going-to-be-hurt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 08:01:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292065-despite-your-best-efforts-people-are-going-to-be-hurt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite your best efforts, people are going to be hurt when it's time for them to be hurt." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126951-everyone-may-be-ordinary-but-they-re-not-normal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 08:02:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126951-everyone-may-be-ordinary-but-they-re-not-normal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone may be ordinary, but they're not normal." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599087-i-could-disappear-from-the-face-of-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2012 08:08:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/599087-i-could-disappear-from-the-face-of-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could disappear from the face of the earth, and the world would go on moving without the slightest twinge. Things were tremendously complicated, to be sure, but one thing was clear: no one needed me." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258688</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 09:52:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Asma add a quote by محمود درويش]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258688]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["سجِّل! أنا عربي 
ورقمُ بطاقتي خمسونَ ألفْ 
وأطفالي ثمانيةٌ 
وتاسعهُم.. سيأتي بعدَ صيفْ! 
فهلْ تغضبْ؟ 
سجِّلْ! 
أنا عربي 
وأعملُ مع رفاقِ الكدحِ في محجرْ 
وأطفالي ثمانيةٌ 
أسلُّ لهمْ رغيفَ الخبزِ، 
والأثوابَ والدفترْ 
من الصخرِ 
ولا أتوسَّلُ الصدقاتِ من بابِكْ 
ولا أصغرْ 
أمامَ بلاطِ أعتابكْ 
فهل تغضب؟ 
سجل 
أنا عربي 
أنا اسم بلا لقبِ 
صبورٌ في بلادٍ كلُّ ما فيها 
يعيشُ بفورةِ الغضبِ 
جذوري... 
قبلَ ميلادِ الزمانِ رستْ 
وقبلَ تفتّحِ الحقبِ 
وقبلَ السّروِ والزيتونِ 
.. وقبلَ ترعرعِ العشبِ 
أبي.. من أسرةِ المحراثِ 
لا من سادةٍ نجبِ 
وجدّي كانَ فلاحاً 
بلا حسبٍ.. ولا نسبِ! 
يعلّمني شموخَ الشمسِ قبلَ قراءةِ الكتبِ 
وبيتي كوخُ ناطورٍ 
منَ الأعوادِ والقصبِ 
فهل ترضيكَ منزلتي؟ 
أنا اسم بلا لقبِ 
سجل 
أنا عربي 
ولونُ الشعرِ.. فحميٌّ 
ولونُ العينِ.. بنيٌّ 
وميزاتي:
على رأسي عقالٌ فوقَ كوفيّه 
وكفّي صلبةٌ كالصخرِ 
تخمشُ من يلامسَها 
وعنواني:
أنا من قريةٍ عزلاءَ منسيّهْ 
شوارعُها بلا أسماء 
وكلُّ رجالها في الحقلِ والمحجرْ 
فهل تغضبْ؟ 
سجِّل 
أنا عربي 
سلبتَ كرومَ أجدادي 
وأرضاً كنتُ أفلحُها 
أنا وجميعُ أولادي 
ولم تتركْ لنا.. ولكلِّ أحفادي 
سوى هذي الصخورِ.. 
فهل ستأخذُها 
حكومتكمْ.. كما قيلا؟
إذن
سجِّل.. برأسِ الصفحةِ الأولى 
أنا لا أكرهُ الناسَ 
ولا أسطو على أحدٍ 
ولكنّي.. إذا ما جعتُ 
آكلُ لحمَ مغتصبي 
حذارِ.. حذارِ.. من جوعي 
ومن غضبي" -- محمود درويش]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
