<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/837226-annie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/837226-annie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 17:09:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17839-being-an-icon-is-overrated-remember-an-icon-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 17:09:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by William Shatner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17839-being-an-icon-is-overrated-remember-an-icon-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being an icon is overrated, remember an icon can be moved by a mouse" -- William Shatner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17840-cry-havoc-and-let-slip-the-dogs-of-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 17:11:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17840-cry-havoc-and-let-slip-the-dogs-of-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cry havoc and let slip the dogs of war!" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18077-what-is-a-friend-a-single-soul-dwelling-in-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 23:53:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18077-what-is-a-friend-a-single-soul-dwelling-in-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a friend? A single soul dwelling in two bodies." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1629-it-is-the-mark-of-an-educated-mind-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 12:14:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Aristotle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1629-it-is-the-mark-of-an-educated-mind-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it." -- Aristotle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4093-the-most-beautiful-experience-we-can-have-is-the-mysterious</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 05:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4093-the-most-beautiful-experience-we-can-have-is-the-mysterious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most beautiful experience we can have is the mysterious - the fundamental emotion which stands at the cradle of true art and true science." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 08:14:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 08:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 08:17:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 22:51:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23222-let-us-tenderly-and-kindly-cherish-therefore-the-means-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 09:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23222-let-us-tenderly-and-kindly-cherish-therefore-the-means-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us tenderly and kindly cherish therefore, the means of knowledge. Let us dare to read, think, speak, and write ." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16208-sex-is-an-emotion-in-motion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 17:33:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Annie add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16208-sex-is-an-emotion-in-motion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex is an emotion in motion." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
