<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/837385-kim-bongiorno]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/837385-kim-bongiorno" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 19:36:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1059233-she-stared-at-the-faded-tile-floor-before-her-feet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 19:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1059233-she-stared-at-the-faded-tile-floor-before-her-feet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She stared at the faded tile floor before her feet, but knew his every step around her small kitchen.  When Martin touched the coffee cup patterned curtains he must assume she’d made, her fingers throbbed. When his eyes slid across the flowery aluminum water bottle at the table, her throat cracked with thirst.

The radio clicked off.

The silence of the room soaked up her raspy breaths, her pounding heart, her ache, and stirred them around the one man she ever longed for in a way that changes how you taste the world.

Her desire swirled in a pulsing, betraying, blurry hook, and encouraged him to move closer.

Martin obeyed." -- Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541674-be-so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 18:41:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/541674-be-so-good-they-can-t-ignore-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be so good they can't ignore you." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1019046-hey-melissa-is-there-anything-i-should-know-about-having-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 09:10:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1019046-hey-melissa-is-there-anything-i-should-know-about-having-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hey, Melissa-is there anything I should know about having this kid that isn't in the books I've been reading?&quot;
Sunlight streamed through the window, making the golden, hormone-induced mutton chops glisten upon my cheeks. As I waited for her answer, I thumbed through the glossy parenting magazines on her kitchen table.
A candle flickered by the sink, adding sweetness to the spit-up scented air that was gutting punched in the face by a diaper change..." -- Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1029547-from-the-moment-i-was-first-pregnant-and-those-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 06:37:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1029547-from-the-moment-i-was-first-pregnant-and-those-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the moment I was first pregnant, and those around me insisted that treats such as cold cuts and nail polish could cut my unborn child's potential IQ in half, I got into the habit of NOT seeking out the little things that brought me joy. Like soft cheese. And getting too close to a Starbucks.

Then my son came, and I was too busy crying while searching for his User Manual to consider a manicure or massage.

I lasted about a week as a new mom before reaching out to others in my situation online. As exhausted, cranky, and confused as I was, I needed friends. 

It didn't take long for this gaggle of desperate, sleepless women to meet up in person..." -- Kim Bongiorno]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1029920-nine-months-ago-my-mother-died-this-was-the-saddest</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 16:45:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kim add a quote by Meredith Spidel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1029920-nine-months-ago-my-mother-died-this-was-the-saddest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nine months ago, my mother died. This was the saddest, most painful time of my life, but somehow unexpected laughter managed to eke its way into the days and moments following her death...after determining she was, in fact, dead, my father, a very practical man, took the opportunity to finish up some laundry he has been working on" -- Meredith Spidel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
