<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/838294-marie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/838294-marie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 23:44:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125450-i-believe-that-today-more-than-ever-a-book-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 23:44:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125450-i-believe-that-today-more-than-ever-a-book-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that today more than ever a book should be sought after even if it has only one great page in it: we must search for fragments, splinters, toenails, anything that has ore in it, anything that is capable of resuscitating the body and soul. It may be that we are doomed, that there is no hope for us, any of us, but if that is so then let us set up a last agonizing, bloodcurdling howl, a screech of defiance, a war whoop! Away with lamentation! Away with elegies and dirges! Away with biographies and histories, and libraries and museums! Let the dead eat the dead. Let us living ones dance about the rim of the crater, a last expiring dance. But a dance!" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256682-we-clutter-the-earth-with-our-inventions-never-dreaming-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 23:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/256682-we-clutter-the-earth-with-our-inventions-never-dreaming-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We clutter the earth with our inventions, never dreaming that possibly they are unnecessary — or disadvantageous. We devise astounding means of communication, but do we communicate with one another? We move our bodies to and fro and incredible speeds, but do we really leave the spot we started from? Mentally, morally, spiritually, we are fettered. What have we achieved in mowing down mountain ranges, harnessing the energy of mighty rivers, or moving whole populations about like chess pieces, if we ourselves remain the same restless, miserable, frustrated creatures we were before? To call such activity progress is utter delusion. We may succeed in altering the face of the earth until it is unrecognizable even to the Creator, but if we are unaffected wherein lies the meaning?" -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36323-time-is-a-created-thing-to-say-i-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 20:11:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36323-time-is-a-created-thing-to-say-i-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is a created thing. To say 'I don't have time,' is like saying, 'I don't want to." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 21:17:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8329-if-after-i-depart-this-vale-you-ever-remember-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 13:05:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by H. L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8329-if-after-i-depart-this-vale-you-ever-remember-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If, after I depart this vale, you ever remember me and have thought to please my ghost, forgive some sinner and wink your eye at some homely girl." -- H. L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
