<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/840178-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/840178-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:32:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18369-love-would-never-leave-us-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:32:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18369-love-would-never-leave-us-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love would never leave us alone" -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:34:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25-we-are-all-in-the-gutter-but-some-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:36:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:40:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:43:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164-it-is-one-of-the-blessings-of-old-friends-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 21:45:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164-it-is-one-of-the-blessings-of-old-friends-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is one of the blessings of old friends that you can afford to be stupid with them." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2010 09:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The foundation of irreligious criticism is: Man makes religion, religion does not make man. Religion is, indeed, the self-consciousness and self-esteem of man who has either not yet won through to himself, or has already lost himself again. But man is no abstract being squatting outside the world. Man is the world of man – state, society. This state and this society produce religion, which is an inverted consciousness of the world, because they are an inverted world...

Religious suffering is, at one and the same time, the expression of real suffering and a protest against real suffering. Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people.

The abolition of religion as the illusory happiness of the people is the demand for their real happiness. To call on them to give up their illusions about their condition is to call on them to give up a condition that requires illusions. The criticism of religion is, therefore, in embryo, the criticism of that vale of tears of which religion is the halo.

Criticism has plucked the imaginary flowers on the chain not in order that man shall continue to bear that chain without fantasy or consolation, but so that he shall throw off the chain and pluck the living flower. The criticism of religion disillusions man, so that he will think, act, and fashion his reality like a man who has discarded his illusions and regained his senses, so that he will move around himself as his own true Sun. Religion is only the illusory Sun which revolves around man as long as he does not revolve around himself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 08:42:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 08:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198-i-am-so-clever-that-sometimes-i-don-t-understand-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
