<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/84023-keely]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/84023-keely" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8323-truth-would-quickly-cease-to-be-stranger-than-fiction-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by H. L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8323-truth-would-quickly-cease-to-be-stranger-than-fiction-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth would quickly cease to be stranger than fiction, once we got as used to it." -- H. L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119798-if-a-man-were-to-look-over-the-fence-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Quentin Crisp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119798-if-a-man-were-to-look-over-the-fence-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a man were to look over the fence on one side of his garden and observe that the neighbor on his left had laid his garden path round a central lawn; and were to look over the fence on the other side of his garden and observe that the neighbor on his right had laid his path down the middle of the lawn, and were then to lay his own garden path diagonally from one corner to the other, that man's soul would be lost. Originality is only to be praised when not prefaced by the look to right and left." -- Quentin Crisp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2122-i-would-believe-only-in-a-god-that-knows-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2122-i-would-believe-only-in-a-god-that-knows-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would believe only in a God that knows how to dance." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73437-the-man-whose-whole-life-is-spent-in-performing-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Adam Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73437-the-man-whose-whole-life-is-spent-in-performing-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man whose whole life is spent in performing a few simple operations, of which the effects are perhaps always the same, or very nearly the same, has no occasion to exert his understanding or to exercise his invention in finding out expedients for removing difficulties which never occur. He naturally loses, therefore, the habit of such exertion, and generally becomes as stupid and ignorant as it is possible for a human creature to become. " -- Adam Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103552-if-one-could-conclude-as-to-the-nature-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by J.B.S. Haldane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103552-if-one-could-conclude-as-to-the-nature-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one could conclude as to the nature of the Creator from a study of creation  it would appear that God has an inordinate fondness for stars and beetles." -- J.B.S. Haldane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8356-it-seems-to-me-that-the-idea-of-a-personal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8356-it-seems-to-me-that-the-idea-of-a-personal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that the idea of a personal God is an anthropological concept which I cannot take seriously. I also cannot imagine some will or goal outside the human sphere... Science has been charged with undermining morality, but the charge is unjust. A man's ethical behavior should be based effectually on sympathy, education, and social ties and needs; no religious basis is necessary. Man would indeed be in a poor way if he had to be restrained by fear of punishment and hope of reward after death." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2119-he-was-born-with-a-gift-of-laughter-and-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2119-he-was-born-with-a-gift-of-laughter-and-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was born with a gift of laughter and a sense that the world was mad." -- Rafael Sabatini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2120-hither-came-conan-the-cimmerian-black-haired-sullen-eyed-sword-in-hand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Robert E. Howard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2120-hither-came-conan-the-cimmerian-black-haired-sullen-eyed-sword-in-hand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hither came Conan, the Cimmerian, black-haired, sullen-eyed, sword in hand, a thief, a reaver, a slayer, with gigantic melancholies and gigantic mirth, to tread the jeweled thrones of the Earth under his sandaled feet." -- Robert E. Howard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2121-it-is-hard-enough-to-remember-my-opinions-without-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 00:29:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2121-it-is-hard-enough-to-remember-my-opinions-without-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard enough to remember my opinions, without also remembering my reasons for them!" -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2123-no-one-hath-seen-beauty-in-its-highest-lustre-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 08:38:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Henry Fielding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2123-no-one-hath-seen-beauty-in-its-highest-lustre-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one hath seen beauty in its highest lustre who hath never seen it in distress." -- Henry Fielding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 08:54:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Warren Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2125-did-you-ever-want-to-set-someone-s-head-on-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you ever want to set someone's head on fire, just to see what it looked like? Did you ever stand in the street and think to yourself, I could make that nun go blind just by giving her a kiss? Did you ever lay out plans for stitching babies and stray cats into a Perfect New Human? Did you ever stand naked surrounded by people who want your gleaming sperm, squirting frankincense, soma and testosterone from every pore? If so, then you're the bastard who stole my drugs Friday night. And I'll find you. Oh, yes." -- Warren Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2135-all-is-mystery-but-he-is-a-slave-who-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 10:05:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2135-all-is-mystery-but-he-is-a-slave-who-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All is mystery; but he is a slave who will not struggle to penetrate the dark veil." -- Benjamin Disraeli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 10:13:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2136-the-covers-of-this-book-are-too-far-apart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The covers of this book are too far apart." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2175-the-easy-confidence-with-which-i-know-another-man-s-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2007 13:15:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2175-the-easy-confidence-with-which-i-know-another-man-s-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The easy confidence with which I know another man's religion is folly teaches me to suspect that my own is also." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:34:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it so bad, then, to be misunderstood? Pythagoras was misunderstood, and Socrates, and Jesus, and Luther, and Copernicus, and Galileo, and Newton, and every pure and wise spirit that ever took flesh. To be great is to be misunderstood." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27042-as-democracy-is-perfected-the-office-of-president-represents-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 19:35:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by H.L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27042-as-democracy-is-perfected-the-office-of-president-represents-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As democracy is perfected, the office of president represents, more and more closely, the inner soul of the people. On some great and glorious day the plain folks of the land will reach their heart's desire at last and the White House will be adorned by a downright moron." -- H.L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8329-if-after-i-depart-this-vale-you-ever-remember-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 19:37:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by H. L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8329-if-after-i-depart-this-vale-you-ever-remember-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If, after I depart this vale, you ever remember me and have thought to please my ghost, forgive some sinner and wink your eye at some homely girl." -- H. L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18468-first-they-came-for-the-communists-and-i-did-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2008 13:44:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Martin Niemöller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18468-first-they-came-for-the-communists-and-i-did-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First they came for the communists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a communist;
Then they came for the socialists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a socialist;
Then they came for the trade unionists, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a trade unionist;
Then they came for the Jews, and I did not speak out—
    because I was not a Jew;
Then they came for me—
    and there was no one left to speak out for me." -- Martin Niemöller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25280-here-follows-the-substance-of-what-i-said-written-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 10:38:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Wilkie Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25280-here-follows-the-substance-of-what-i-said-written-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here follows the substance of what I said, written out entirely for your benefit. Pay attention to it, or you will be all abroad, when we get deeper into the story. Clear your mind of the children, or the dinner, or the new bonnet, or what not. Try if you can't forget politics, horses, prices in the city and grievances at the club. I hope you won't take this freedom on my part amiss; it's only a way I have of appealing to a gentle reader. Lord! haven't I seen you with the greatest authors in your hands, and don't I know how ready your attention is to wander when it's a book that asks for it, instead of a person?" -- Wilkie Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44591-at-the-age-when-we-are-all-of-us-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 10:47:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by William Wilkie Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44591-at-the-age-when-we-are-all-of-us-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the age when we are all of us most apt to take our colouring, in the form of a reflection from the colouring of other people, he had been sent abroad, and had been passed on from one nation to another, before there was time for any one colouring more than another to settle itself on him firmly. As a consequence of this, he had come back with so many different sides to his character, all more or less jarring with each other, that he seemed to pass his life in a state of perpetual contradiction with himself. He could be a busy man, and a lazy man; cloudy in the head, and clear in the head; a model of determination, and a spectacle of helplessness, all together. He had his French side, and his German side, and his Italian side--the original English foundation showing through, every now and then, as much as to say, &quot;Here I am, sorely transmogrified, as you see, but there's something of me left at the bottom of him still." -- William Wilkie Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49398-m-an-has-been-accustomed-ever-since-he-was-a-boy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 14:42:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49398-m-an-has-been-accustomed-ever-since-he-was-a-boy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[M]an has been accustomed, ever since he was a boy, to having a dozen incompatible philosophies dancing about together inside his head. He doesn't think of doctrines as primarily &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false,&quot; but as &quot;academic&quot; or &quot;practical,&quot; &quot;outworn&quot; or &quot;contemporary,&quot; &quot;conventional&quot; or &quot;ruthless.&quot; Jargon, not argument, is your best ally in keeping him from the Church. Don't waste time trying to make him think that materialism is true! Make him think it is strong or stark or courageous—that it is the philosophy of the future. That's the sort of thing he cares about." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62993-i-have-forgotten-my-umbrella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 09:58:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62993-i-have-forgotten-my-umbrella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have forgotten my umbrella. " -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73445-oscar-wilde-i-wish-i-had-said-that-whistler-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 10:34:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by James McNeill Whistler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73445-oscar-wilde-i-wish-i-had-said-that-whistler-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oscar Wilde: &quot;I wish I had said that.&quot; Whistler: &quot;You will, Oscar; you will." -- James McNeill Whistler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81378-the-maker-of-the-universe-with-stars-a-hundred-thousand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2008 14:04:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81378-the-maker-of-the-universe-with-stars-a-hundred-thousand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Maker of the universe with stars a hundred thousand light-years apart was interested, furious, and very personal about it if a small boy played baseball on Sunday afternoon." -- Sinclair Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107517-the-clothes-have-no-emperor</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 12:14:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Stewart Elliott Guthrie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107517-the-clothes-have-no-emperor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The clothes have no emperor." -- Stewart Elliott Guthrie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5880-the-key-is-never-never-work-nothing-is-more-aging</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2008 22:59:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Quentin Crisp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5880-the-key-is-never-never-work-nothing-is-more-aging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The key is never, never work. Nothing is more aging than work. It's not only the strain of getting up in the morning for work, but it's the resentment that settles on your face" -- Quentin Crisp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 16:23:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8076-this-tower-patched-unevenly-with-black-ivy-arose-like-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 04:35:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Mervyn Peake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8076-this-tower-patched-unevenly-with-black-ivy-arose-like-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This tower, patched unevenly with black ivy, arose like a mutilated finger from among the fists of knuckled masonry and pointed blasphemously at heaven. At night the owls made of it an echoing throat; by day it stood voiceless and cast its long shadow." -- Mervyn Peake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148928-everyone-believes-very-easily-whatever-he-fears-or-desires</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 21:25:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by Jean de La Fontaine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148928-everyone-believes-very-easily-whatever-he-fears-or-desires]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone believes very easily whatever he fears or desires." -- Jean de La Fontaine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4082-now-my-own-suspicion-is-that-the-universe-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 21:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Keely add a quote by J. B. S. Haldane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4082-now-my-own-suspicion-is-that-the-universe-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now, my own suspicion is that the universe is not only queerer than we suppose, but queerer than we can suppose. I have read and heard many attempts at a systematic account of it, from materialism and theosophy to the Christian system or that of Kant, and I have always felt that they were much too simple. I suspect that there are more things in heaven and earth that are dreamed of, or can be dreamed of, in any philosophy. That is the reason why I have no philosophy myself, and must be my excuse for dreaming." -- J. B. S. Haldane]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
