<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841143-kristen-ringman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841143-kristen-ringman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:06:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18309-they-say-that-every-snowflake-is-different-if-that-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:06:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18309-they-say-that-every-snowflake-is-different-if-that-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say that every snowflake is different.  If that were true, how could the world go on?  How could we ever get up off our knees? How could we ever recover from the wonder of it?" -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7996-human-beings-are-not-born-once-and-for-all-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:28:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7996-human-beings-are-not-born-once-and-for-all-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings are not born once and for all on the day their mothers give birth to them, but ... life obliges them over and over again to give birth to themselves." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18311-his-examination-revealed-that-he-had-no-fever-no-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:30:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18311-his-examination-revealed-that-he-had-no-fever-no-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["his examination revealed that he had no fever, no pain anywhere, and that his only concrete feeling was an urgent desire to die.  All that was needed was shrewd questioning...to conclude once again that the symptoms of love were the same as those of cholera." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7313-what-you-risk-reveals-what-you-value</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:31:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7313-what-you-risk-reveals-what-you-value]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you risk reveals what you value." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18312-huddled-around-the-fire-of-the-alphabet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 18:33:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Carole Maso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18312-huddled-around-the-fire-of-the-alphabet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Huddled around the fire of the alphabet..." -- Carole Maso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353605-the-struggle-is-inner-chicano-indio-american-indian-mojado-mexicano</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 18:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353605-the-struggle-is-inner-chicano-indio-american-indian-mojado-mexicano]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The struggle is inner: Chicano, indio, American Indian, mojado, mexicano, immigrant Latino, Anglo in power, working class Anglo, Black, Asian--our psyches resemble the bordertowns and are populated by the same people. The struggle has always been inner, and is played out in outer terrains. Awareness of our situation must come before inner changes, which in turn come before changes in society. Nothing happens in the &quot;real&quot; world unless it first happens in the images in our heads. (G. Anzaldua   Tejana Chicana poet, 1942- )" -- Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282275-i-can-t-seem-to-stay-out-of-my-own-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 18:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282275-i-can-t-seem-to-stay-out-of-my-own-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't seem to stay out of my own way." -- Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527862-i-sit-here-before-my-computer-amiguita-my-altar-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 18:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/527862-i-sit-here-before-my-computer-amiguita-my-altar-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sit here before my computer, Amiguita, my altar on top of the monitor with the Virgen de Coatlalopeuh candle and copal incense burning. My companion, a wooden serpent staff with feathers, is to my right while I ponder the ways metaphor and symbol concretize the spirit and etherealize the body. The Writing is my whole life, it is my obsession. This vampire which is my talent does not suffer other suitors. Daily I court it, offer my neck to its teeth. This is the sacrifice that the act of creation requires, a blood sacrifice. For only through the body, through the pulling of flesh, can the human soul be transformed. And for images, words, stories to have this transformative power, they must arise from the human body--flesh and bone--and from the Earth's body--stone, sky, liquid, soil. This work, these images, piercing tongue or ear lobes with cactus needle, are my offerings, are my Aztecan blood sacrifices." -- Gloria Anzaldua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129352-love-be-it-man-be-it-woman-it-must-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 21:33:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129352-love-be-it-man-be-it-woman-it-must-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love? Be it man. Be it woman.
It must be a wave you want to glide in on,
give your body to it, give your laugh to it,
give, when the gravelly sand takes you,
your tears to the land. To love another is something
like prayer and can't be planned, you just fall
into its arms because your belief undoes your disbelief." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117884-i-have-gone-out-a-possessed-witch-haunting-the-black</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 21:33:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117884-i-have-gone-out-a-possessed-witch-haunting-the-black]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have gone out, a possessed witch,
haunting the black air, braver at night;
dreaming evil, I have done my hitch
over the plain houses, light by light:
lonely thing, twelve-fingered, out of mind.
A woman like that is not a woman, quite.
I have been her kind.

I have found the warm caves in the woods,
filled them with skillets, carvings, shelves,
closets, silks, innumerable goods;
fixed the suppers for the worms and the elves:
whining, rearranging the disaligned.
A woman like that is misunderstood.
I have been her kind.

I have ridden in your cart, driver,
waved my nude arms at villages going by,
learning the last bright routes, survivor
where your flames still bite my thigh
and my ribs crack where your wheels wind.
A woman like that is not ashamed to die.
I have been her kind." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 22:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26900-tenderness-and-kindness-are-not-signs-of-weakness-and-despair</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 22:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26900-tenderness-and-kindness-are-not-signs-of-weakness-and-despair]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tenderness and kindness are not signs of weakness and despair, but manifestations of strength and resolution." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55784-kindness-before-you-know-what-kindness-really-is-you-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2012 22:07:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55784-kindness-before-you-know-what-kindness-really-is-you-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kindness

Before you know what kindness really is
you must lose things,
feel the future dissolve in a moment
like salt in a weakened broth.
What you held in your hand,
what you counted and carefully saved,
all this must go so you know
how desolate the landscape can be
between the regions of kindness.
How you ride and ride
thinking the bus will never stop,
the passengers eating maize and chicken
will stare out the window forever.

Before you learn the tender gravity of kindness,
you must travel where the Indian in a white poncho
lies dead by the side of the road.
You must see how this could be you,
how he too was someone
who journeyed through the night with plans
and the simple breath that kept him alive.

Before you know kindness as the deepest thing
   inside,
you must know sorrow as the other deepest thing.
You must wake up with sorrow.
You must speak to it till your voice
catches the thread of all sorrows
and you see the size of the cloth.

Then it is only kindness that makes sense anymore,
only kindness that ties your shoes
and sends you out into the day to mail letters and
   purchase bread,
only kindness that raises its head
from the crowd of the world to say
It is I you have been looking for,
and then goes with you everywhere
like  a shadow or a friend.


Colombia" -- Naomi Shihab Nye]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288821-i-am-two-women-one-wants-to-have-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 20:47:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288821-i-am-two-women-one-wants-to-have-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am two women: one wants to have all the joy, passion and adventure that life can give me. The other wants to be a slave to routine, to family life, to the things that can be planned and achieved. I'm a housewife and a prostitute, both of us living in the same body and doing battle with each other." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 13:27:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19778-the-secret-of-the-great-stories-is-that-they-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the secret of the Great Stories is that they &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; no secrets. The Great Stories are the ones you have heard and want to hear again. The ones you can enter anywhere and inhabit comfortably. They don’t deceive you with thrills and trick endings. They don’t surprise you with the unforeseen. They are as familiar as the house you live in. Or the smell of your lover’s skin. You know how they end, yet you listen as though you don’t. In the way that although you know that one day you will die, you live as though you won’t. In the Great Stories you know who lives, who dies, who finds love, who doesn’t. And yet you want to know again.

&lt;i&gt;That&lt;/i&gt; is their mystery and their magic." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 13:30:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78990-all-stories-are-about-wolves-all-worth-repeating-that-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All stories are about wolves. All worth repeating, that is. Anything else is sentimental drivel.

All of them?

Sure, he says. Think about it. There's escaping from the wolves, fighting the wolves, capturing the wolves, taming the wolves. Being thrown to the wolves, or throwing others to the wolves so the wolves will eat them instead of you. Running with the wolf pack. Turning into a wolf. Best of all, turning into the head wolf. No other decent stories exist." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
