<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841891-katie-kenig]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841891-katie-kenig" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 17:35:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31686-at-some-point-in-life-the-world-s-beauty-becomes-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 17:35:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31686-at-some-point-in-life-the-world-s-beauty-becomes-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point in life the world's beauty becomes enough.  You don't need to photograph, paint, or even remember it.  It is enough." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 08:50:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438134-the-universe-is-always-speaking-to-us-sending-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:44:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Nancy Thayer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438134-the-universe-is-always-speaking-to-us-sending-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The universe is always speaking to us. ... Sending us little messages, causing coincidences and serendipities, reminding us to stop, to look around, to believe in something else, something more." -- Nancy Thayer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241284-i-believe-in-being-strong-when-everything-seems-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241284-i-believe-in-being-strong-when-everything-seems-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day, and I believe in miracles" -- Audrey Hepburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437556-think-about-our-bodies-we-re-a-chain-of-veins-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:44:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Katie Kacvinsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437556-think-about-our-bodies-we-re-a-chain-of-veins-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think about our bodies.  We're a chain of veins and organs and tehy're all interconnected.  If something isn't going right in one area, the whole system can get out of whack.  That's teh way I see the world.  We're all connected.  I don't see myself as this separate entity.  I see things in a much larger scale.  Everything I do directly affects another person, all the way down the chain.  Every person I help can help another; we're all connected.  Change happens one person at a time.  And I want to commit my life to seeing that through." -- Katie Kacvinsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:45:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4959-you-don-t-have-to-burn-books-to-destroy-a-culture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2011 16:47:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1930-think-of-all-the-beauty-still-left-around-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of all the beauty still left around you and be happy." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398463-secrets-have-power-and-that-power-diminishes-when-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2012 01:19:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398463-secrets-have-power-and-that-power-diminishes-when-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Secrets have power. And that power diminishes when they are shared, so they are best kept and kept well. Sharing secrets, real secrets, important ones, with even one other person, will change them. Writing them down is worse, because who can tell how many eyes might see them inscribed on paper, no matter how careful you might be with it. So it's really best to keep your secrets when you have them, for their own good, as well as yours." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6379-despite-my-ghoulish-reputation-i-really-have-the-heart-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 22:08:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Robert Bloch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6379-despite-my-ghoulish-reputation-i-really-have-the-heart-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite my ghoulish reputation, I really have the heart of a small boy. I keep it in a jar on my desk." -- Robert Bloch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 13:48:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1404-if-you-don-t-have-time-to-read-you-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't have time to read, you don't have the time (or the tools) to write. Simple as that." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565511-she-is-her-odd-self-the-kiln-has-been-fired</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2012 02:05:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/565511-she-is-her-odd-self-the-kiln-has-been-fired]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is her odd self. The kiln has been fired.  She is a person persnickity about keeping her house clean, but not above spitting on her desk to rub out a coffee stain.  She will never be an athlete, or a mathematician, or a skinny person, or someone whose heart isn't snagged by the sight of fireflies on a summer night and the lilting cadence of a few good lines of poetry." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561529-o-to-be-sure-we-laugh-less-and-play-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 11:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Leo Rosten]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/561529-o-to-be-sure-we-laugh-less-and-play-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O, to be sure, we laugh less and play less and wear uncomfortable disguises like adults, but beneath the costume is the child we always are, whose needs are simple, whose daily life is still best described by fairy tales." -- Leo Rosten]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570563-i-just-want-to-say-one-thing-if-i-ever</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 00:09:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570563-i-just-want-to-say-one-thing-if-i-ever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I just want to say one thing.  If I ever write a novel again, it's going to be in defense of weak women, inept and codependent women.  I'm going to talk about all the great movies and songs and poetry that focus on such women.  I'm going to toast Blanche DuBois.  I'm going to celebrate women who aren't afraid to show their need and their vulnerabilities.  To be honest about how hard it can be to plow your way through a life that offers no guarantees about anything.  I'm going to get on my metaphorical knees and thank women who fall apart, who cry and carry on and wail and wring their hands because you know what, Midge? We all need to cry.  Thank God for women who can articulate their vulnerabilities and express what probably a lot of other people want to say and feel they can't. Those peoples' stronghold against falling apart themselves is the disdain they feel for women who do it for them. Strong.  I'm starting to think that's as much a party line as anything else ever handed to women for their assigned roles.  When do we get respect for our differences from men?  Our strength is our weakness. Our ability to feel is our humanity. You know what?  I'll bet if you talk to a hundred strong women, 99 of them would say 'I'm sick of being strong.  I would like to be cared for. I would like someone else to make the goddamn decisions, I'm sick of making decisions.'  I know this one woman who's a beacon of strength.  A single mother who can do everything - even more than you, Midge.  I ran into her not long ago and we went and got a coffee and you know what she told me?  She told me that when she goes out to dinner with her guy, she asks him to order everything for her.  Every single thing, drink to dessert.  Because she just wants to unhitch.  All of us dependent, weak women have the courage to do all the time what she can only do in a restaurant." -- Elizabeth Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 09:30:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Irving Stone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241462-there-are-no-faster-or-firmer-friendships-than-those-formed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no faster or firmer friendships than those formed between people who love the same books." -- Irving Stone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130823-nothing-in-life-is-fair-fair-is-a-dirty-word</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 09:35:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130823-nothing-in-life-is-fair-fair-is-a-dirty-word]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing in life is fair.  Fair is a dirty word and I'll thank you not to use that language around me." -- Jeff Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49141-if-you-show-someone-something-you-ve-written-you-give-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2012 11:26:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49141-if-you-show-someone-something-you-ve-written-you-give-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you show someone something you've written, you give them a sharpened stake, lie down in your coffin, and say, ‘When you’re ready’." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438902-what-is-straight-a-line-can-be-straight-or-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 08:46:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Tennessee Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/438902-what-is-straight-a-line-can-be-straight-or-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is straight? A line can be straight, or a street, but the human heart, oh, no, it's curved like a road through mountains." -- Tennessee Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67727-what-a-blessing-it-is-to-love-books-as-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 18:13:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Thomas Babington Macaulay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67727-what-a-blessing-it-is-to-love-books-as-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a blessing it is to love books as I love them;- to be able to converse with the dead, and to live amidst the unreal!" -- Thomas Babington Macaulay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480561-tonight-s-december-thirty-first-something-is-about-to-burst-the-clock</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 23:25:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Ogden Nash]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480561-tonight-s-december-thirty-first-something-is-about-to-burst-the-clock]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tonight’s December thirty-first,
Something is about to burst.
The clock is crouching, dark and small,
Like a time bomb in the hall.
Hark, it's midnight, children dear.
Duck! Here comes another year!" -- Ogden Nash]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
