<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841857-nicol-s]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/841857-nicol-s" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 10:18:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181721-libertarianism-is-good-because-it-helps-conservatives-pass-off-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 10:18:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicolás add a quote by Thomas Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181721-libertarianism-is-good-because-it-helps-conservatives-pass-off-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Libertarianism is good because it helps conservatives pass off a patently probusiness political agenda as a noble bid for human freedom.  Whatever we may think of libertarianism as a set of ideas, practically speaking, it is a doctrine that owes its visibility to the obvious charms it holds for the wealthy and the powerful.  The reason we have so many well-funded libertarians in American these days is not because libertarianism suddenly acquired an enormous grassroots following, but because it appeals to those who are able to fund ideas.  Like social Darwinism and Christian Science before it, libertarianism flatters the successful and rationalizes their core beliefs about the world.  They warm to the libertarian idea that taxation is theft because they themselves don’t like to pay taxes.  They fancy the libertarian notion that regulation is communist because they themselves find regulation intrusive and annoying.  Libertarianism is a politics born to be subsidized.  In the “free market of ideas,” it is a sure winner." -- Thomas Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1745-everyone-is-entitled-to-his-own-opinion-but-not-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 10:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicolás add a quote by Daniel Patrick Moynihan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1745-everyone-is-entitled-to-his-own-opinion-but-not-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone is entitled to his own opinion, but not to his own facts." -- Daniel Patrick Moynihan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
