<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/84282-alana]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/84282-alana" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 07:12:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 07:12:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193773-he-stared-and-talked-at-the-girl-s-red-hair-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 11:18:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193773-he-stared-and-talked-at-the-girl-s-red-hair-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He stared and talked at the girl's red hair and amused face for what seemed to be a few minutes; and then, feeling that the groups in such a place should mix, rose to his feet. To his astonishment, he discovered the whole garden empty. Everyone had gone long ago, and he went himself with a rather hurried apology. He left with a sense of champagne in his head, which he could not afterwards explain. In the wild events which were to follow, this girl had no part at all; he never saw her again until all his tale was over. And yet, in some indescribable way, she kept recurring like a motive in music through all his mad adventures afterwards, and the glory of her strange hair ran like a red thread through those dark and ill-drawn tapestries of the night. For what followed was so improbable that it might well have been a dream." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193774-oh-most-unhappy-man-he-cried-try-to-be-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 11:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193774-oh-most-unhappy-man-he-cried-try-to-be-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, most unhappy man,' he cried, 'try to be happy! You have red hair like your sister.'
My red hair, like red flames, shall burn up the world,' said Gregory." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195085-none-but-the-most-blindly-credulous-will-imaging-the-characters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 11:34:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Edmund Crispin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195085-none-but-the-most-blindly-credulous-will-imaging-the-characters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["None but the most blindly credulous will imaging the characters and events in this story to be anything but fictitious. It is true that the ancient and noble city of Oxford is, of all the towns of England, the likeliest progenitor of unlikely events and persons. But there are limits." -- Edmund Crispin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299197-he-went-on-for-some-time-while-i-sat-listening</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299197-he-went-on-for-some-time-while-i-sat-listening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He went on for some time while I sat listening in silence because I knew he was right, and like two people who have loved each other however imperfectly, who have tried to make a life together, however imperfectly, who have lived side by side and watched the wrinkles slowly form at the corner of the other's eyes, and watched a little drop of gray, as if poured from a jug, drop into the other's skin and spread itself evenly, listening to the other's coughs and sneezes and little collected mumblings, like two people who'd had one idea together and slowly allowed that idea to be replaced with two separate, less hopeful, less ambitious ideas, we spoke deep into the night, and the next day, and the next night. For forty days and forty nights, I want to say, but the fact of the matter is it only took three. One of us had loved the other more perfectly, had watched the other more closely, and one of us listened and the other hadn't, and one of us held on to the ambition of the one idea far longer than was reasonable, whereas the other, passing a garbage can one night, had casually thrown it away." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299200-once-or-twice-a-year-i-attended-the-english-romantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:13:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299200-once-or-twice-a-year-i-attended-the-english-romantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once or twice a year I attended the English Romantic conferences held throughout Europe, brief gatherings perhaps not dissimilar in feeling for the participants than the feeling Jews have when they get off the plane in Israel: the relief of at last being surrounded on all sides by your own kind--the relief and the horror." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299201-after-all-who-isn-t-a-survivor-from-the-wreck-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299201-after-all-who-isn-t-a-survivor-from-the-wreck-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...after all, who isn't a survivor from the wreck of childhood?" -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299204-all-my-life-i-have-arrived-early-only-to-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:15:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299204-all-my-life-i-have-arrived-early-only-to-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All my life I have arrived early only to find myself standing self-consciously on a corner, outside a door, in an empty room, but the closer I get to death the earlier I arrive, the longer I am content to wait, perhaps to give myself the false sensation that there is too much time rather than not enough." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299205-i-smiled-back-the-importance-of-manners-my-mother-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 20:16:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299205-i-smiled-back-the-importance-of-manners-my-mother-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I smiled back, the importance of manners, my mother always said, is inversely related to how inclined one is to use them, or, in other words, sometimes politeness is all that stands between oneself and madness." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 07:40:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 19:53:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71213-once-upon-a-time-there-was-a-boy-who-loved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time there was a boy who loved a girl, and her laughter was a question he wanted to spend his whole life answering." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 19:54:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3420-even-now-all-possible-feelings-do-not-yet-exist-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even now, all possible feelings do not yet exist, there are still those that lie beyond our capacity and our imagination.  From time to time, when a piece of music no one has ever written or a painting no one has ever painted, or something else impossible to predict, fathom or yet describe takes place, a new feeling enters the world.  And then, for the millionth time in the history of feeling, the heart surges and absorbs the impact." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 19:54:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the end, all that's left of you are your possessions.  Perhaps that's why I've never been able to throw anything away.  Perhaps that's why I hoarded the world:  with the hope that when I died, the sum total of my things would suggest a life larger than the one I lived." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79859-we-are-all-more-intelligent-than-we-are-capable-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 19:57:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Alain De Botton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79859-we-are-all-more-intelligent-than-we-are-capable-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all more intelligent than we are capable, and awareness of the insanity of love has never saved anyone from the disease." -- Alain De Botton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 11:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2567-the-queen-s-pride-was-his-ship-and-he-loved-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 11:06:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2567-the-queen-s-pride-was-his-ship-and-he-loved-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Queen's Pride was his ship, and he loved her. (That was the way his sentences always went: It is raining today and I love you. My cold is better and I love you. Say hello to Horse and I love you. Like that.)" -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188642-love-is-many-things-none-of-them-logical</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 11:06:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188642-love-is-many-things-none-of-them-logical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is many things none of them logical." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386960-it-was-the-hat-he-looked-sweet-in-the-hat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 07:17:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386960-it-was-the-hat-he-looked-sweet-in-the-hat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the hat. He looked sweet in the hat. How could a man in a fuzzy blue hat have used human bones to pave his roads?" -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395532-in-this-life-we-love-who-we-love-there-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 05:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395532-in-this-life-we-love-who-we-love-there-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this life we love who we love. There were some stories in which facts were very nearly irrelevant." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 05:56:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It makes you wonder. All the brilliant things we might have done with our lives if only we suspected we knew how." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411114-mathias-shrugged-after-all-a-criminal-lawyer-is-not-concerned</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 10:29:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Richard Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411114-mathias-shrugged-after-all-a-criminal-lawyer-is-not-concerned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mathias shrugged. After all, a criminal lawyer is not concerned with facts. He is concerned with probabilities. It is the novelist who is concerned with facts, whose job it is to say what a particular man did do on a particular occasion: the lawyer does not, cannot be expected to go further than show what the ordinary man would be most likely to do under presumed circumstances." -- Richard Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429357-you-may-tell-a-tale-that-takes-up-residence-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 09:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429357-you-may-tell-a-tale-that-takes-up-residence-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You may tell a tale that takes up residence in someone's soul, becomes their blood and self and purpose. That tale will move them and drive them and who knows that they might do because of it, because of your words. That is your role, your gift." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 09:14:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone needs to tell those tales.  When the battles are fought and won and lost, when the pirates find their treasures and the dragons eat their foes for breakfast with a nice cup of Lapsang souchong, someone needs to tell their bits of overlapping narrative.  There's magic in that.  It's in the listener, and for each and every ear it will be different, and it will affect them in ways they can never predict.  From the mundane to the profound.  You may tell a tale that takes up residence in someone's soul, becomes their blood and self and purpose.  That tale will move them and drive them and who knows what they might do because of it, because of your words.  That is your role, your gift.  Your sister may be able to see the future, but you yourself can shape it, boy.  Do not forget that... there are many kinds of magic, after all." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 09:14:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/446427-we-lead-strange-lives-chasing-our-dreams-around-from-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We lead strange lives, chasing our dreams around from place to place." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255269-sir-topher-finally-looked-up-because-any-hope-beyond-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 09:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255269-sir-topher-finally-looked-up-because-any-hope-beyond-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sir Topher finally looked up. “Because any hope beyond that, my boy, would be too much. I feared we would drown in it.”
&quot;Then I choose to drown,” Finnikin said. “In hope. Rather than float into nothing." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287031-this-hand-says-you-spend-the-rest-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 09:16:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Melina Marchetta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287031-this-hand-says-you-spend-the-rest-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This hand says you spend the rest of your life with me,&quot; he said, holding out his left hand, &quot;and this one says I spend the rest of my life with you. Choose.&quot;

She bit her lip, tears welling in her eyes. She took both of his hands in hers and he shuddered. &quot;I will die protecting you,&quot; he says.

There was a look of dismay on her face. &quot;Just like a man of this kingdom, Finnikin. Talking of death, yours or mine, is not a good way to begin a-&quot;

Isaboe gave a small gasp when he leaned forward, his lips an inch away from hers. &quot;I will die for you,&quot; he whispered.

She cupped his face in her hands. &quot;But promise me you'll live first. Because nothing we are about to do is going to be easy and I need you by my side." -- Melina Marchetta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 20:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14050-red-hair-sir-in-my-opinion-is-dangerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 07:54:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14050-red-hair-sir-in-my-opinion-is-dangerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Red hair, sir, in my opinion, is dangerous." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64588-once-in-his-life-every-man-is-entitled-to-fall</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 07:54:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by Lucille Ball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64588-once-in-his-life-every-man-is-entitled-to-fall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once in his life, every man is entitled to fall madly in love with a gorgeous redhead." -- Lucille Ball]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82842-if-you-re-betwixt-and-between-trust-the-one-with-red</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 07:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alana add a quote by O.R. Melling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82842-if-you-re-betwixt-and-between-trust-the-one-with-red]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're betwixt and between, trust the one with red hair." -- O.R. Melling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
