<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/843424-tiff]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/843424-tiff" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 21:11:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40707-take-time-slow-down-be-still-be-awake-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 21:11:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiff add a quote by Edward Hays]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40707-take-time-slow-down-be-still-be-awake-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take time, slow down, be still, be awake to the Divine Mystery that looks so common and so ordinary yet is wondrously present." -- Edward Hays]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40708-the-sculptor-produces-the-beautiful-statue-by-chipping-away-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2008 21:13:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiff add a quote by Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40708-the-sculptor-produces-the-beautiful-statue-by-chipping-away-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sculptor produces the beautiful statue by chipping away such parts of the marble block as are not needed - it is a process of elimination." -- Elbert Hubbard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1134-and-this-our-life-exempt-from-public-haunt-finds-tongues</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 15:44:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiff add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1134-and-this-our-life-exempt-from-public-haunt-finds-tongues]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this our life, exempt from public haunt, finds tongues in trees, books in the running brooks, sermons in stones, and good in everything.  I would not change it." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 07:46:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiff add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198832-it-doesn-t-matter-what-the-manifest-problem-was-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2013 19:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tiff add a quote by M. Catherine Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198832-it-doesn-t-matter-what-the-manifest-problem-was-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't matter what the manifest problem was in our childhood family. In a home where a child is emotionally deprived for one reason or another that child will take some personal emotional confusion into his or her adult life. We may spin our spiritual wheels in trying to make up for childhood's personal losses, looking for compensation in the wrong places and despairing that we can find it. But the significance of spiritual rebirth through Jesus Christ is that we can mature spiritually under His parenting and receive healing compensation for these childhood deprivations. Three emotions that often grow all out of proportion in the emotionally deprived child are fear, guilt, and anger. The fear grows out of the child's awareness of the uncontrollable nature of her fearful environment, of overwhelming negative forces around her. Her guilt, her profound feelings of inadequacy, intensify when she is unable to put right what is wrong, either in the environment or in another person, no matter how hard she tries to be good. If only she could try harder or be better, she could correct what is wrong, she thinks. She may carry this guilt all her life, not knowing where it comes from, but just always feeling guilty. She often feels too sorry for something she has done that was really not all that serious. Her anger comes from her frustration, perceived deprivation, and the resultant self-pity. She has picked up an anger habit and doesn't know how much trouble it is causing her. A fourth problem often follows in the wake of the big three: the need to control others and manipulate events in order to feel secure in her own world, to hold her world together- to make happen what she wants to happen. She thinks she has to run everything. She may enter adulthood with an illusion of power and a sense of authority to put other people right, though she has had little success with it. She thinks that all she has to do is try harder, be worthier, and then she can change, perfect, and save other people. But she is in the dark about what really needs changing.&quot;I thought I would drown in guilt and wanted to fix all the people that I had affected so negatively. But I learned that I had to focus on getting well and leave off trying to cure anyone around me.&quot; Many of those around - might indeed get better too, since we seldom see how much we are a key part of a negative relationship pattern. I have learned it is a true principle that I need to fix myself before I can begin to be truly helpful to anyone else. I used to think that if I were worthy enough and worked hard enough, and exercised enough anxiety (which is not the same thing as faith), I could change anything. My power and my control are illusions. To survive emotionally, I have to turn my life over to the care of that tender Heavenly Father who was really in charge. It is my own spiritual superficiality that makes me sick, and that only profound repentance, that real change of heart, would ultimately heal me. My Savior is much closer than I imagine and is willing to take over the direction of my life: &quot;I am the vine, ye are the branches: He that abideth in me, and I in him, the same bringeth forth much fruit: for without me, ye can do nothing.&quot; (John 15:5). As old foundations crumble, we feel terribly vulnerable. Humility, prayer and flexibility are the keys to passing through this corridor of healthy change while we experiment with truer ways of dealing with life. Godly knowledge, lovingly imparted, begins deep healing, gives tools to live by and new ways to understand the gospel." -- M. Catherine Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
