<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/843957-stuart]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/843957-stuart" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 08:08:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973939-the-house-adjourned-without-voting-on-the-bill-but-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 08:08:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by H.W. Brands]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973939-the-house-adjourned-without-voting-on-the-bill-but-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The House adjourned without voting on the bill, but the following year a similar bill—mandating equality in hotels and restaurants open to the public, in transportation facilities, in theaters and other public amusements and in the selection of juries—passed both chambers. The measure reached the White House about the time the two sides in Louisiana cobbled a compromise that allowed Grant to withdraw Sheridan and most of the federal troops. On March 1, 1875, the president signed the Civil Rights Act, the most ambitious affirmation of racial equality in American history until then (a distinction it would retain until the 1960s)." -- H.W. Brands]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974382-what-white-southerners-called-redemption-and-others-deemed-simply-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 16:44:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by H.W. Brands]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974382-what-white-southerners-called-redemption-and-others-deemed-simply-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what white Southerners called “redemption” and others deemed simply the return to power of the Democrats, who sufficiently intimidated, cheated and otherwise discouraged Republicans, including most of the freedmen, that they counted for little in Southern politics. With any Democratic presidential nominee guaranteed the South, any Republican had to perform overwhelmingly in the North." -- H.W. Brands]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975760-thus-began-the-long-process-of-transforming-jesus-from-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 22:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Reza Aslan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/975760-thus-began-the-long-process-of-transforming-jesus-from-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus began the long process of transforming Jesus from a revolutionary Jewish nationalist into a peaceful spiritual leader with no interest in any earthly matter. That was a Jesus the Romans could accept, and in fact did accept three centuries later when the Roman emperor Flavius Theodosius (d. 395) made the itinerant Jewish preacher’s movement the official religion of the state, and what we now recognize as orthodox Christianity was born." -- Reza Aslan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/984040-there-is-no-evidence-that-jesus-himself-openly-advocated-violent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 17:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Reza Aslan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/984040-there-is-no-evidence-that-jesus-himself-openly-advocated-violent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no evidence that Jesus himself openly advocated violent actions. But he was certainly no pacifist. “Do not think that I have come to bring peace on earth. I have not come to bring peace, but the sword” (Matthew 10:34 | Luke 12:51)." -- Reza Aslan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1048830-because-david-s-mother-loretta-refused-to-sign-up-for-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 12:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Lawrence Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1048830-because-david-s-mother-loretta-refused-to-sign-up-for-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because David’s mother, Loretta, refused to sign up for that, she and Ron agreed to divorce. She continued in Scientology, rising to the summit as an OT VIII. She worked as an accountant for the law firm of Greta Van Susteren, the television commentator, and her husband, John Coale, both Scientologists, who maintain a mansion on Clearwater Beach." -- Lawrence Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1051414-however-twelve-former-sea-org-members-told-me-that-miscavige</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 20:07:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Lawrence Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1051414-however-twelve-former-sea-org-members-told-me-that-miscavige]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However, twelve former Sea Org members told me that Miscavige had assaulted them; twenty-one have told me or testified in court that they have witnessed one or more assaults on other church staff members by their leader." -- Lawrence Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1162123-if-these-biochemical-phenomena-sound-similar-to-those-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 12:05:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Ray Kurzweil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1162123-if-these-biochemical-phenomena-sound-similar-to-those-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If these biochemical phenomena sound similar to those of the fight-or-flight syndrome, they are, except that here we are running toward something or someone; indeed, a cynic might say toward rather than away from danger. The changes are also fully consistent with those of the early phases of addictive behavior. The Roxy Music song “Love Is the Drug” is quite accurate in describing this state (albeit the subject of the song is looking to score his next fix of love)." -- Ray Kurzweil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1162949-although-i-m-not-prepared-to-move-up-my-prediction-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 11:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Ray Kurzweil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1162949-although-i-m-not-prepared-to-move-up-my-prediction-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although I’m not prepared to move up my prediction of a computer passing the Turing test by 2029, the progress that has been achieved in systems like Watson should give anyone substantial confidence that the advent of Turing-level AI is close at hand. If one were to create a version of Watson that was optimized for the Turing test, it would probably come pretty close." -- Ray Kurzweil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169000-and-at-last-becoming-a-complete-misanthrope-he-used-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 14:53:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stuart add a quote by Diogenes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1169000-and-at-last-becoming-a-complete-misanthrope-he-used-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And at last, becoming a complete misanthrope, he used to live, spending his time in walking about the mountains; feeding on grasses and plants, and in consequence of these habits, he was attacked by the dropsy, and so then he returned to the city, and asked the physicians, in a riddle, whether they were able to produce a drought after wet weather. And as they did not understand him, he shut himself up in a stable for oxen, and covered himself with cow-dung, hoping to cause the wet to evaporate from him, by the warmth that this produced. And as he did himself no go good in this way, he died, having lived seventy years;" -- Diogenes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
