<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/844096-jen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/844096-jen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 17:34:23 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105450-the-devil-knows-that-if-the-elders-of-israel-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 17:34:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105450-the-devil-knows-that-if-the-elders-of-israel-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The devil knows that if the elders of Israel should ever wake up, they could step forth and help preserve freedom and extend the gospel. Therefore the devil has concentrated, and to a large extent successfully, in neutralizing much of the priesthood. He has reduced them to Sleeping Giants." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295100-the-declaration-of-independence-is-much-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 17:36:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295100-the-declaration-of-independence-is-much-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Declaration of Independence . . . is much more than a political document. It constitutes a spiritual manifesto—revelation, if you will—declaring not for this nation only, but for all nations, the source of man's rights. Nephi, a Book of Mormon prophet, foresaw over 2,300 years ago that this event would transpire. The colonies he saw would break with Great Britain and that 'the power of the Lord was with [the colonists],' that they 'were delivered by the power of God out of the hands of all other nations' (1 Nephi 13:16, 19).  &quot;The Declaration of Independence was to set forth the moral justification of a rebellion against a long-recognized political tradition—the divine right of kings. At issue was the fundamental question of whether men's rights were God-given or whether these rights were to be dispensed by governments to their subjects. This document proclaimed that all men have certain inalienable rights. In other words, these rights came from God." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316708-one-of-the-marks-of-an-educated-man-today-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 17:37:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316708-one-of-the-marks-of-an-educated-man-today-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the marks of an educated man today is to know what not to read--what not to see or what not to listen to." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187184-the-central-issue-in-that-pre-mortal-council-was-shall-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 18:44:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187184-the-central-issue-in-that-pre-mortal-council-was-shall-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The central issue in that pre-mortal council was: Shall the children of God have untrammeled agency to choose the course they should follow, whether good or evil, or shall they be coerced and forced to be obedient? Christ and all who followed Him stood for the former proposition—freedom of choice; Satan stood for the latter—coercion and force. The war that began in heaven over this issue is not yet over. The conflict continues on the battlefield of mortality. And one of Lucifer’s primary strategies has been to restrict our agency through the power of earthly governments.” (BYU devotional held Tuesday, 16 September 1986, President Ezra Taft Benson)" -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
