<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/844196-russ-lyon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/844196-russ-lyon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 09:58:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 09:58:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russ add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24440-and-it-came-to-me-then-that-we-were-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And it came to me then. That we were wonderful traveling companions but in the end no more than lonely lumps of metal in their own separate orbits.  From far off they look like beautiful shooting stars, but in reality they're nothing more than prisons, where each of us is locked up alone, going nowhere. When the orbits of these two satellites of ours happened to cross paths, we could be together. Maybe even open our hearts to each other. But that was only for the briefest moment. In the next instant we'd be in absolute solitude. Until we burned up and became nothing." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38829-bolivia-is-a-striking-example-the-mostly-white-europeanized-elite</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 16:28:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russ add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38829-bolivia-is-a-striking-example-the-mostly-white-europeanized-elite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bolivia is a striking example. The mostly white, Europeanized elite, which is a minority, happens to be sitting on most of the hydrocarbon reserves. For the first time Bolivia is becoming democratic. So it's therefore bitterly hated by the West, which despises democracy, because it's much too dangerous." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573339-i-am-by-nature-a-person-suspicious-of-the-economic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2012 09:23:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russ add a quote by Charles Bowden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573339-i-am-by-nature-a-person-suspicious-of-the-economic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am by nature a person suspicious of the economic machine that feeds me.  And yet I am a captive of that economic machine, and my mind is structured by its lessons and demands.  I consume its wealth with zest.  I drive a truck, watch a color television, and write on a computer, but I cannot overcome the feeling that these objects and the industrial culture that produced them are temporary things, a kind of fat beast feeding on the bounty of the earth that will starve to death within the next century, or at least be severely diminished." -- Charles Bowden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373705-do-you-see-that-tree-it-is-dead-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2014 10:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russ add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373705-do-you-see-that-tree-it-is-dead-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you see that tree? It is dead but it still sways in the wind with the others. I think it would be like that with me. That if I died I would still be part of life in one way or another." -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
