<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/846212-anna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/846212-anna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 20:11:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7457-we-think-that-the-point-is-to-pass-the-test</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 20:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7457-we-think-that-the-point-is-to-pass-the-test]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We think that the point is to pass the test or to overcome the problem, but the truth is that things don't really get solved. They come together and they fall apart." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197776-the-most-fundamental-aggression-to-ourselves-the-most-fundamental-harm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 20:12:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197776-the-most-fundamental-aggression-to-ourselves-the-most-fundamental-harm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most fundamental aggression to ourselves, the most fundamental harm we can do to ourselves, is to remain ignorant by not having the courage and the respect to look at ourselves honestly and gently." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165429-life-is-glorious-but-life-is-also-wretched-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 20:13:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Pema Chödrön]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165429-life-is-glorious-but-life-is-also-wretched-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is glorious, but life is also wretched. It is both. Appreciating the gloriousness inspires us, encourages us, cheers us up, gives us a bigger perspective, energizes us. We feel connected. But if that's all that's happening, we get arrogant and start to look down on others, and there is a sense of making ourselves a big deal and being really serious about it, wanting it to be like that forever. The gloriousness becomes tinged by craving and addiction. On the other hand, wretchedness--life's painful aspect--softens us up considerably. Knowing pain is a very important ingredient of being there for another person. When you are feeling a lot of grief, you can look right into somebody's eyes because you feel you haven't got anything to lose--you're just there. The wretchedness humbles us and softens us, but if we were only wretched, we would all just go down the tubes. We'd be so depressed, discouraged, and hopeless that we wouldn't have enough energy to eat an apple. Gloriousness and wretchedness need each other. One inspires us, the other softens us. They go together." -- Pema Chödrön]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
