<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/846531-arlene]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/846531-arlene" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 12:28:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20204-there-is-no-need-to-search-achievement-leads-to-nowhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 12:28:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arlene add a quote by Dan Millman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20204-there-is-no-need-to-search-achievement-leads-to-nowhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no need to search; achievement leads to nowhere. It makes no difference at all, so just be happy now! Love is the only reality of the world, because it is all One, you see. And the only laws are paradox, humor and change. There is no problem, never was, and never will be. Release your struggle, let go of your mind, throw away your concerns, and relax into the world. No need to resist life, just do your best. Open your eyes and see that you are far more than you imagine. You are the world, you are the universe; you are yourself and everyone else, too! It's all the marvelous Play of God. Wake up, regain your humor. Don't worry, just be happy. You are already free!" -- Dan Millman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 12:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arlene add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46179-i-must-say-a-word-about-fear-it-is-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must say a word about fear. It is life's only true opponent. Only fear can defeat life. It is a clever, treacherous adversary, how well I know. It has no decency, respects no law or convention, shows no mercy. It goes for your weakest spot, which it finds with unnerving ease. It begins in your mind, always ... so you must fight hard to express it. You must fight hard to shine the light of words upon it. Because if you don't, if your fear becomes a wordless darkness that you avoid, perhaps even manage to forget, you open yourself to further attacks of fear because you never truly fought the opponent who defeated you." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
