<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/847495-lauren]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/847495-lauren" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 12:08:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110820-and-he-gave-me-a-few-of-the-xeroxed-sheets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 12:08:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Milorad Pavic]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110820-and-he-gave-me-a-few-of-the-xeroxed-sheets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And he gave me a few of the Xeroxed sheets of paper lying on the table in front of him. As he passed them to me, his thumb brushed mine and I trembled from the touch. I had the sensation that our past and our future were in our fingers and that they had touched. And so, when I began to read the proffered pages, I at one moment lost the train of thought in the text and drowned it in my own feelings. In these seconds of absence and self-oblivion, centuries passed with every read but uncomprehended and unabsorbed line, and when, after a few moments, I came to and re-established contact with the text, I knew that the reader who returns from the open seas of his feelings is no longer the same reader who embarked on that sea only a short while ago. I gained and learned more by not reading than by reading those pages..." -- Milorad Pavic]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110821-it-is-not-i-who-mix-the-colors-but-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 12:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Milorad Pavic]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110821-it-is-not-i-who-mix-the-colors-but-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not I who mix the colors but your own vision,' he answered. 'I only place them next to one another on the wall in their natural state; it is the observer who mixes the colors in his own eye, like porridge. Therein lies the secret. The better the porridge, the better the painting, but you cannot make good porridge from bad buckwheat. Therefore, faith in seeing, listening, and reading is more important than faith in painting, singing, or writing.' 

He took blue and red and placed them next to each other, painting the eyes of an angel. And I saw the angel's eyes turn violet. 

 'I work with something like a dictionary of colors,' Nikon added, 'and from it the observer composes sentences and books, in other words, images. You could do the same with writing. Why shouldn't someone create a dictionary of words that make up one book and let the reader himself assemble the words into a whole?" -- Milorad Pavic]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2008 12:10:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4907-unless-someone-like-you-cares-a-whole-awful-lot-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless someone like you cares a whole awful lot,
Nothing is going to get better. It's not." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206800-kurt-vonnegut-to-shakespeare-i-asked-him-if-he-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 06:18:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206800-kurt-vonnegut-to-shakespeare-i-asked-him-if-he-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kurt Vonnegut to Shakespeare:
I asked him if he had love affairs with men as well as women, knowing how eager my WNYC audience was to have this matter settled. His answer, however, celebrated affection between animals of any sort:

&quot;We were as twinn'd lambs that did frisk in the sun, and bleat the one at the other: what we chang'd was innocence for innocence.&quot; By changed he meant exchanged: &quot;What we exchanged was innocence for innocence.&quot; That has to be the softest core pornography I ever heard." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2009 06:21:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13104-there-are-more-things-in-heaven-and-earth-horatio-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are more things in Heaven and Earth, Horatio, than are dreamt of in your philosophy." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571953-the-vieux-carre-is-most-beautiful-in-the-early-evening</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2012 14:47:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Rex Noone]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/571953-the-vieux-carre-is-most-beautiful-in-the-early-evening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Vieux Carre is most beautiful in the early evening, when the subtle colors of a sunset provide a perfect complement to the concrete, creating a harmony of architecture on each street... Thoughts also have a softer tone during these evenings. So, I chose this time to walk and think after a personally oppressive day. A day when my mind needed the relief of a pastel cityscape." -- Rex Noone]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578759-women-were-also-urged-to-work-on-a-mysterious-quality</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 14:52:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Susan Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578759-women-were-also-urged-to-work-on-a-mysterious-quality]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women were also urged to work on a mysterious quality called 'fascination.' Coming of age in the 1920's was a competitive business..." -- Susan Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665007-howard-resented-the-ache-in-his-heart-he-resented-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2012 10:51:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by Paul Harding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/665007-howard-resented-the-ache-in-his-heart-he-resented-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Howard resented the ache in his heart. He resented that it was there every morning when he woke up... He resented equally the ache and resentment itself. He resented his resentment because it was a sign of his limitations of spirit and humility, no matter that he understood that such was each man's burden. He resented the ache because it was uninvited, seemed imposed, a sentence, and, despite the encouragement he gave himself each morning, it baffled him because it was there whether the day was good or bad, whether he witnessed major kindness or minor transgression, suffered sourceless grief or spontaneous joy." -- Paul Harding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 16:30:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480596-i-m-in-love-with-you-he-said-quietly-augustus-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 16:31:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lauren add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/480596-i-m-in-love-with-you-he-said-quietly-augustus-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm in love with you,&quot; he said quietly.

&quot;Augustus,&quot; I said.

&quot;I am,&quot; he said. He was staring at me, and I could see the corners of his eyes crinkling. &quot;I'm in love with you, and I'm not in the business of denying myself the simple pleasure of saying true things. I'm in love with you, and I know that love is just a shout into the void, and that oblivion is inevitable, and that we're all doomed and that there will come a day when all our labor has been returned to dust, and I know the sun will swallow the only earth we'll ever have, and I am in love with you." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
