<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/847700-debra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/847700-debra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:28:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:28:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827-among-those-whom-i-like-or-admire-i-can-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Among those whom I like or admire, I can find no common denominator, but among those whom I love, I can; all of them make me laugh." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3725-some-books-are-undeservedly-forgotten-none-are-undeservedly-remembered</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:28:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by W.H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3725-some-books-are-undeservedly-forgotten-none-are-undeservedly-remembered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some books are undeservedly forgotten; none are undeservedly remembered." -- W.H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3254-behind-the-corpse-in-the-reservoir-behind-the-ghost-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:28:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by W. H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3254-behind-the-corpse-in-the-reservoir-behind-the-ghost-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Behind the corpse in the reservoir, behind the ghost on the links, 
Behind the lady who dances and the man who madly drinks, 
Under the look of fatigue, the attack of migraine and the sigh 
There is always another story, there is more than meets the eye." -- W. H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:34:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The individual has always had to struggle to keep from being overwhelmed by the tribe. If you try it, you will be lonely often, and sometimes frightened. But no price is too high to pay for the privilege of owning yourself." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2043-the-snake-which-cannot-cast-its-skin-has-to-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:34:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2043-the-snake-which-cannot-cast-its-skin-has-to-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The snake which cannot cast its skin has to die. As well the minds which are prevented from changing their opinions; they cease to be mind." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your visions will become clear only when you can look into your own heart. Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakes." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3240-you-are-what-you-do-not-what-you-say-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:45:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3240-you-are-what-you-do-not-what-you-say-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are what you do, not what you say you'll do." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5846-everything-that-irritates-us-about-others-can-lead-us-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:45:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5846-everything-that-irritates-us-about-others-can-lead-us-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything that irritates us about others can lead us to an understanding of ourselves." -- Carl Gustav Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:46:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15303-ah-how-good-it-is-to-be-among-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, how good it is to be among people who are reading!" -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:47:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745-perhaps-all-the-dragons-in-our-lives-are-princesses-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps all the dragons in our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us act, just once, with beauty and courage. Perhaps everything that frightens us is, in its deepest essence, something helpless that wants our love." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9029-i-wish-that-all-nations-may-recover-and-retain-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:49:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9029-i-wish-that-all-nations-may-recover-and-retain-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish that all nations may recover and retain their independence; that those which are overgrown may not advance beyond safe measures of power, that a salutary balance may be ever maintained among nations, and that our peace, commerce, and friendship, may be sought and cultivated by all. It is our business to manufacture for ourselves whatever we can, to keep our markets open for what we can spare or want; and the less we have to do with the amities or enmities of Europe, the better. Not in our day, but at no distant one, we may shake a rod over the heads of all, which may make the stoutest of them tremble. &lt;b&gt;But I hope our wisdom will grow with our power, and teach us, that &lt;i&gt;the less we use our power, the greater it will be&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:49:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["4. Religion. Your reason is now mature enough to examine this object. In the first place, divest yourself of all bias in favor of novelty &amp; singularity of opinion... shake off all the fears &amp; servile prejudices, under which weak minds are servilely crouched. &lt;b&gt;Fix reason firmly in her seat, and call to her tribunal every fact, every opinion. Question with boldness even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blindfolded fear&lt;/b&gt;. You will naturally examine first, the religion of your own country. Read the Bible, then as you would read [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The facts which are within the ordinary course of nature, you will believe on the authority of the writer, as you do those of the same kind in [author:Livy|2840091] and [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The testimony of the writer weighs in their favor, in one scale, and their not being against the laws of nature, does not weigh against them. But those facts in the Bible which contradict the laws of nature, must be examined with more care, and under a variety of faces. Here you must recur to the pretensions of the writer to inspiration from God. Examine upon what evidence his pretensions are founded, and whether that evidence is so strong, as that its falsehood would be more improbable than a change in the laws of nature, in the case he relates. For example in the book of Joshua we are told the sun stood still several hours. Were we to read that fact in [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846] we should class it with their showers of blood, speaking of statues, beasts, &amp;c. But it is said that the writer of that book was inspired. Examine therefore candidly what evidence there is of his having been inspired. The pretension is entitled to your inquiry, because millions believe it. On the other hand you are astronomer enough to know how contrary it is to the law of nature that a body revolving on its axis as the earth does, should have stopped, should not by that sudden stoppage have prostrated animals, trees, buildings, and should after a certain time have resumed its revolution, &amp; that without a second general prostration. Is this arrest of the earth's motion, or the evidence which affirms it, most within the law of probabilities? You will next read the New Testament. It is the history of a personage called Jesus. Keep in your eye the opposite pretensions: 1, of those who say he was begotten by God, born of a virgin, suspended &amp; reversed the laws of nature at will, &amp; ascended bodily into heaven; and 2, of those who say he was a man of illegitimate birth, of a benevolent heart, enthusiastic mind, who set out without pretensions to divinity, ended in believing them, and was punished capitally for sedition, by being gibbeted, according to the Roman law, which punished the first commission of that offence by whipping, &amp; the second by exile, or death &lt;i&gt;in fureâ&lt;/i&gt;.

...Do not be frightened from this inquiry by any fear of its consequences. If it ends in a belief that there is no God, you will find incitements to virtue in the comfort and pleasantness you feel in its exercise, and the love of others which it will procure you... In fine, I repeat, you must lay aside all prejudice on both sides, and neither believe nor reject anything, because any other persons, or description of persons, have rejected or believed it... I forgot to observe, when speaking of the New Testament, that you should read all the histories of Christ, as well of those whom a council of ecclesiastics have decided for us, to be Pseudo-evangelists, as those they named Evangelists. Because these Pseudo-evangelists pretended to inspiration, as much as the others, and you are to judge their pretensions by your own reason, and not by the reason of those ecclesiastics. Most of these are lost...

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to his nephew, Peter Carr, advising him in matters of religion, 1787&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14310-the-most-valuable-of-all-talents-is-that-of-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:49:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14310-the-most-valuable-of-all-talents-is-that-of-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most valuable of all talents is that of never using two words when one will do." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:50:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have observed, indeed, generally, that while in protestant countries the defections from the Platonic Christianity of the priests is to Deism, in catholic countries they are to Atheism. [author:Diderot|11004], [author:D'Alembert|3295333], [author:D’Holbach|1228712], [author:Condorcet|6420223], are known to have been among the most virtuous of men. Their virtue, then, must have had some other foundation than the love of God.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Thomas Law, 13 June 1814&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:50:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2008 10:51:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4056-a-government-big-enough-to-give-you-everything-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A government big enough to give you everything you want is a government big enough to take from you everything you have." -- Gerald R. Ford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:49:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:49:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:49:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:50:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:50:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:51:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Maurice Switzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/363-it-is-better-to-remain-silent-at-the-risk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." -- Maurice Switzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 21:54:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Debra add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
