<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/849620-beverly-rousch]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/849620-beverly-rousch" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 09:10:55 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 09:10:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/638800-tampon-commercial-detergent-commercial-maxi-pad-commercial-windex-commercial--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tampon commercial, detergent commercial, maxi pad commercial, windex commercial - you'd think all women do is clean and bleed." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 09:11:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612195-my-gosh-nick-why-are-you-so-wonderful-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 09:12:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/612195-my-gosh-nick-why-are-you-so-wonderful-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My gosh, Nick, why are you so wonderful to me?' 

He was supposed to say: You deserve it. I love you.

But he said,'Because I feel sorry for you.' 

'Why?' 

'Because every morning you have to wake up and be you." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290707-you-love-me-real-or-not-real-i-tell-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 20:01:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Suzanne Collins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290707-you-love-me-real-or-not-real-i-tell-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You love me. Real or not real?&quot;
I tell him, &quot;Real." -- Suzanne Collins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639599-push-yourself-don-t-settle-wear-those-stripy-legs-with-pride</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 15:09:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Jojo Moyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/639599-push-yourself-don-t-settle-wear-those-stripy-legs-with-pride]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Push yourself. Don’t settle. Wear those stripy legs with pride. And if you insist on settling down with some ridiculous bloke, make sure some of this is squirreled away somewhere. Knowing you still have possibilities is a luxury. Knowing I might have given them to you has alleviated something for me." -- Jojo Moyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807649-i-will-never-ever-regret-the-things-i-ve-done-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 15:09:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Jojo Moyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807649-i-will-never-ever-regret-the-things-i-ve-done-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will never, ever regret the things I've done. Because most days, all you have are places in your memory that you can go to." -- Jojo Moyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630477-i-kissed-him-trying-to-bring-him-back-i-kissed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 15:10:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Jojo Moyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630477-i-kissed-him-trying-to-bring-him-back-i-kissed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I kissed him, trying to bring him back. I kissed him and let my lips rest against his so that our breath mingled and the tears from my eyes became salt on his skin, and I told myself that, somewhere, tiny particles of him would become tiny particles of me, ingested, swallowed, alive, perpetual. I wanted to press every bit of me against him. I wanted to will something into him. I wanted to give him every bit of life I felt and force him to live." -- Jojo Moyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/984891-the-old-cobbler-had-believed-in-something-he-called-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 20:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/984891-the-old-cobbler-had-believed-in-something-he-called-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The old cobbler had believed in something he called &quot;the signature of all things&quot;-namely, that God had hidden clues for humanity's betterment inside the design of every flower, leaf, fruit, and tree on earth. All the natural world was a divine code, Boehme claimed, containing proof of our Creator's love." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/903709-who-will-ever-kiss-this-encyclopedia-of-a-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 20:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/903709-who-will-ever-kiss-this-encyclopedia-of-a-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who will ever kiss this encyclopedia of a head?" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056692-well-child-you-may-do-whatever-you-like-with-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 20:26:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1056692-well-child-you-may-do-whatever-you-like-with-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, child, you may do whatever you like with your suffering,” Hanneke said mildly. “It belongs to you. But I shall tell you what I do with mine. I grasp it by the small hairs, I cast it to the ground, and I grind it under the heel of my boot. I suggest you learn to do the same." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149062-i-will-tell-you-why-we-have-these-extraordinary-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 20:28:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149062-i-will-tell-you-why-we-have-these-extraordinary-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will tell you why we have these extraordinary minds and souls, Miss Whittaker,” he continued, as though he had not heard her. “We have them because there is a supreme intelligence in the universe, which wishes for communion with us. This supreme intelligence longs to be known. It calls out to us. It draws us close to its mystery, and it grants us these remarkable minds, in order that we try to reach for it. It wants us to find it. It wants union with us, more than anything." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856391-take-me-someplace-where-we-can-be-silent-together</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 12:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856391-take-me-someplace-where-we-can-be-silent-together]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take me someplace where we can be silent together." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856393-there-is-a-level-of-grief-so-deep-that-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 12:48:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856393-there-is-a-level-of-grief-so-deep-that-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a level of grief so deep that it stops resembling grief at all. The pain becomes so severe that the body can no longer feel it. The grief cauterizes itself, scars over, prevents inflated feeling. Such numbness is a kind of mercy." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/949371-i-will-tell-you-why-we-have-these-extraordinary-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 12:48:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/949371-i-will-tell-you-why-we-have-these-extraordinary-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will tell you why we have these extraordinary minds and souls, Miss Whittaker,&quot; he continued, as though he had not heard her. &quot;We have them because there is a supreme intelligence in the universe, which wishes for communion with us. This supreme intelligence longs to be known. It calls out to us. It draws us close to its mystery, and grants us these remarkable minds, in order that we try to reach for it. It wants us to find it. It wants union with us, more than anything." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926987-who-loves-you-most-who-loves-you-best-who-thinks</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 12:48:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beverly add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926987-who-loves-you-most-who-loves-you-best-who-thinks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who loves you most? Who loves you best? Who thinks of you when others rest?" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
