<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851132-chisom]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851132-chisom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:50:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:50:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chisom add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He awoke each morning with the desire to do right, to be a good and meaningful person, to be, as simple as it sounded and as impossible as it actually was, happy. And during the course of each day his heart would descend from his chest into his stomach. By early afternoon he was overcome by the feeling that nothing was right, or nothing was right for him, and by the desire to be alone. By evening he was fulfilled: alone in the magnitude of his grief, alone in his aimless guilt, alone even in his loneliness. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad,&lt;/i&gt; he would repeat to himself over and over, &lt;i&gt;I am not sad&lt;/i&gt;. As if he might one day convince himself. Or fool himself. Or convince others--the only thing worse than being sad is for others to know that you are sad. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad. I am not sad. &lt;/i&gt;Because his life had unlimited potential for happiness, insofar as it was an empty white room. He would fall asleep with his heart at the foot of his bed, like some domesticated animal that was no part of him at all. And each morning he would wake with it again in the cupboard of his rib cage, having become a little heavier, a little weaker, but still pumping. And by the midafternoon he was again overcome with the desire to be somewhere else, someone else, someone else somewhere else. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127631-she-was-a-genius-of-sadness-immersing-herself-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:50:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chisom add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127631-she-was-a-genius-of-sadness-immersing-herself-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was a genius of sadness, immersing herself in it, separating its numerous strands, appreciating its subtle nuances. She was a prism through which sadness could be divided into its infinite spectrum." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43013-love-me-because-love-doesn-t-exist-and-i-have-tried</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:50:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chisom add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43013-love-me-because-love-doesn-t-exist-and-i-have-tried]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chisom add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43334-i-love-you-also-means-i-love-you-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you also means I love you more than anyone loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that no one loves you, or has loved you, or will love you, and also, I love you in a way that I love no one else, and never have loved anyone else, and never will love anyone else." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chisom add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
