<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851100-clark]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851100-clark" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:21:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22412-the-question-is-frequently-asked-why-does-a-man-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22412-the-question-is-frequently-asked-why-does-a-man-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question is frequently asked: Why does a man become a drug addict?
The answer is that he usually does not intend to become an addict. You don’t wake up one morning and decide to be a drug addict. It takes at least three months’ shooting twice a day to get any habit at all. And you don’t really know what junk sickness is until you have had several habits. It took me almost six months to get my first habit, and then the withdrawal symptoms were mild. I think it no exaggeration to say it takes about a year and several hundred injections to make an addict.
The questions, of course, could be asked: Why did you ever try narcotics? Why did you continue using it long enough to become an addict? You become a narcotics addict because you do not have strong motivations in the other direction. Junk wins by default. I tried it as a matter of curiosity. I drifted along taking shots when I could score. I ended up hooked. Most addicts I have talked to report a similar experience. They did not start using drugs for any reason they can remember. They just drifted along until they got hooked. If you have never been addicted, you can have no clear idea what it means to need junk with the addict’s special need. You don’t decide to be an addict. One morning you wake up sick and you’re an addict. (Junky, Prologue, p. xxxviii)" -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22406-what-does-he-say-he-asked-he-s-very-sad-rsula</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22406-what-does-he-say-he-asked-he-s-very-sad-rsula]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does he say?' he asked.
'He’s very sad,’ Úrsula answered, ‘because he thinks that you’re going to die.'
'Tell him,' the colonel said, smiling, 'that a person doesn’t die when he should but when he can." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22402-h-l-ne-lagonelle-s-body-is-heavy-innocent-still-her-skin-s-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 08:14:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22402-h-l-ne-lagonelle-s-body-is-heavy-innocent-still-her-skin-s-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hélène Lagonelle’s body is heavy, innocent still, her skin’s as soft as that of certain fruits, you almost can’t grasp her, she’s almost illusory, it’s too much.  She makes you want to kill her, she conjures up a marvelous dream of putting her to death with your own hands.  Those flour-white shapes, she bears them unknowingly, and offers them for hands to knead, for lips to eat, without holding them back, without any knowledge of them and without any knowledge of their fabulous power.  I’d like to eat Hélène Lagonelle’s breasts as he eats mine in the room in the Chinese town where I go every night to increase my knowledge of God.  I’d like to devour and be devoured by those flour-white breasts of hers.
I am worn out with desire for Hélène Lagonelle.
I am worn out with desire.
I want to take Hélène Lagonelle with me to where every evening, my eyes shut, I have imparted to me the pleasure that makes you cry out.  I’d like to give Hélène Lagonelle to the man who does that to me, so he may do it in turn to her.  I want it to happen in my presence, I want her to do it as I wish, I want her to give herself where I give myself.  It’s via Hélène Lagonelle’s body, through it, that the ultimate pleasure would pass from him to me.
A pleasure unto death." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22404-they-laid-me-down-again-while-somebody-fetched-a-stretcher</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:21:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22404-they-laid-me-down-again-while-somebody-fetched-a-stretcher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They laid me down again while somebody fetched a stretcher. As soon as I knew that the bullet had gone clean through my neck I took it for granted that I was done for. I had never heard of a man or an animal getting a bullet through the middle of the neck and surviving it. The blood was dribbling out of the comer of my mouth. ‘The artery's gone,’ I thought. I wondered how long you last when your carotid artery is cut; not many minutes, presumably. Everything was very blurry. There must have been about two minutes during which I assumed that I was killed. And that too was interesting—I mean it is interesting to know what your thoughts would be at such a time. My first thought, conventionally enough, was for my wife. My second was a violent resentment at having to leave this world which, when all is said and done, suits me so well. I had time to feel this very vividly. The stupid mischance infuriated me. The meaninglessness of it! To be bumped off, not even in battle, but in this stale comer of the trenches, thanks to a moment's carelessness! I thought, too, of the man who had shot me—wondered what he was like, whether he was a Spaniard or a foreigner, whether he knew he had got me, and so forth. I could not feel any resentment against him. I reflected that as he was a Fascist I would have killed him if I could, but that if he had been taken prisoner and brought before me at this moment I would merely have congratulated him on his good shooting. It may be, though, that if you were really dying your thoughts would be quite different." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71103-to-tell-the-truth-sir-i-believe-i-had-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 14:21:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71103-to-tell-the-truth-sir-i-believe-i-had-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To tell the truth, sir, I believe I had rather sit in the shelter for a while.  The cabbage seems to have turned my inward parts to water.’
Nonsense,’ said Stephen, ‘it is the most wholesome cabbage I have ever come across in the whole of my career.  I hope, Mr. Herapath, that you are not going to join in the silly weak womanish unphilosophical mewling and puling about the cabbage.  So it is a little yellow in certain lights, so it is a little sharp, so it smells a little strange:  so much the better, say I.  At least that will stop the insensate Phaeacian hogs from abusing it, as they abuse the brute creation, stuffing themselves with flesh until what little brain they have is drowned in fat.  A virtuous esculent!  Even its boldest detractors, ready to make the most hellish declarations and to swear through a nine-inch plank that the cabbage makes them fart and rumble, cannot deny that it cured their purpurae.  Let them rumble till the heavens shake and resound again; let them fart fire and brimstone, the Gomorrhans, I will not have a single case of scurvy on my hands, the sea-surgeon’s shame, while there is a cabbage to be culled." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169239-i-cannot-understand-the-principle-at-all-said-stephen-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 07:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169239-i-cannot-understand-the-principle-at-all-said-stephen-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot understand the principle at all,' said Stephen.  'I should very much like to show it to Captain Aubrey, who is so very well versed in the mathematics and dynamics of sailing.  Landlord, pray ask him whether he is willing to part with the instrument.'
Not on your fucking life,' said the Aboriginal, snatching the boomerang and clasping it to his bosom.
He says he does not choose to dispose of it, your honour,' said the landlord.  'But never fret.  I have a dozen behind the bar that I sell to ingenious travelers for half a guinea.  Choose any one that takes your fancy, sit, and Bennelong will throw it to prove it comes back, a true homing pigeon, as we say.  Won't you?'  This much louder, in the black man's ear.
Won't I what?'
Throw it for the gentleman.'
Give um dram.'
Sir, he says he will be happy to throw it for you; and hopes you will encourage him with a tot of rum.  (pp. 353-354)" -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22403-sometimes-she-said-i-think-i-must-have-invented-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:21:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22403-sometimes-she-said-i-think-i-must-have-invented-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes,’ she said, ‘I think I must have invented him.’
I know all I want to about your child,’ Chauvin said harshly.
Anne Desbaresdes moaned again, louder than before.  Again she put her hand on the table.  His eyes followed her movement and finally, painfully, he understood and lifted his own leaden hand and placed it on hers.  Their hands were so cold they were touching only in intention, an illusion, in order for this to be fulfilled, for the sole reason that it should be fulfilled, none other, it was no longer possible.  And yet, with their hands frozen in this funereal pose, Anne Desbaresdes stopped moaning.
One last time,’ she begged, ‘tell me about it one last time.’
Chauvin hesitated, his eyes somewhere else, still fixed on the back wall.  Then he decided to tell her about it as if it were a memory.
He had never dreamed, before meeting her, that he would one day want anything so badly.’
And she acquiesced completely?’
Wonderfully.’
Anne Desbaresdes looked at Chauvin absently.  Her voice became thin, almost childlike.
I'd like to understand why his desire to have it happen one day was so wonderful?’
Chauvin still avoided looking at her.  Her voice was steady, wooden, the voice of a deaf person.
There's no use trying to understand.  It's beyond understanding.’
You mean there are some things like that that can't be gone into?’
I think so.’
Anne Desbaresdes' expression became dull, almost stupid.  Her lips had turned pale, they were gray and trembled as though she were on the verge of tears.
She does nothing t try and stop him?’ she whispered.
No.  Have a little more wine.’
She sipped her wine.  He also drank, and his lips on the glass were also trembling.
Time,’ he said
Does it take a long time, a very long time?’
Yes, a very long time.  But I don't know anything.’  He lowered his voice.  ‘Like you, I don't know anything.  Nothing at all.’
Anne Desbaresdes forced back her tears.  Her voice was normal, momentarily awake.
She will never speak again,’ she said." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479860-he-knew-that-her-body-was-his-to-engage-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:49:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479860-he-knew-that-her-body-was-his-to-engage-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew that her body was his to engage in all the acrobatics he had learned in the books he kept hidden in a corner of his library, but with Clara even the most abominable contortions were like the thrashings of a newborn; it was impossible to spice them up with the salt of evil or the pepper of submission." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22408-the-men-digging-in-on-both-sides-of-me-cursed</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 08:21:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Eugene B. Sledge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22408-the-men-digging-in-on-both-sides-of-me-cursed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The men digging in on both sides of me cursed the stench and the mud.  I began moving the heavy, sticky clay mud with my entrenching shovel to shape out the extent of the foxhole before digging deeper.  Each shovelful had to be knocked off the spade, because it stuck like glue.  I was thoroughly exhausted and thought my strength wouldn’t last from one sticky shovelful to the next.
Kneeling on the mud, I had dug the hole no more than six or eight inches deep when the odor of rotting flesh got worse.  There was nothing to do but continue to dig, so I closed up my mouth and inhaled with short shallow breaths.  Another spadeful of soil out of the hole released a mass of wriggling maggots that came welling up as though those beneath were pushing them out.  I cursed and told the NCO as he came by what a mess I was digging into.
‘You heard him, he said put the holes five yards apart.’
In disgust, I drove the spade into the soil, scooped out the insects, and threw them down the front of the ridge.  The next stroke of the spade unearthed buttons and scraps of cloth from a Japanese army jacket in the mud—and another mass of maggots.  I kept on doggedly.  With the next thrust, metal hit the breastbone of a rotting Japanese corpse.  I gazed down in horror and disbelief as the metal scraped a clean track through the mud along the dirty whitish bone and cartilage with ribs attached.  The shoved skidded into the rotting abdomen with a squishing sound.  The odor nearly overwhelmed me as I rocked back on my heels.
I began choking and gagging as I yelled in desperation, ‘I can’t dig in here!  There’s a dead Nip here!’
The NCO came over, looked down at my problem and at me, and growled, ‘You heard him; he said put the holes five yards apart." -- Eugene B. Sledge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139073-in-august-1944-the-war-ministry-in-tokyo-had-issued</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:48:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Hampton Sides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139073-in-august-1944-the-war-ministry-in-tokyo-had-issued]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In August 1944, the War Ministry in Tokyo had issued a directive to the commandants of various POW camps, outlining a policy for what it called the ‘final disposition’ of prisoners.  A copy of this document, which came to be known as the ‘August 1 Kill-All Order,’ would surface in the war crimes investigations in Tokyo.  Bearing a chilling resemblance to actual events that occurred at Palawan, the directive stated:
‘When the battle situation becomes urgent the POWs will be concentrated and confined to their location and kept under heavy guard until preparations for the final disposition will be made.  Although the basic aim is to act under superior orders, individual dispositions may be made in [certain] circumstances.  Whether they are destroyed individually or in groups, and whether it is accomplished by means of mass bombing, poisonous smoke, poisons, drowning, or decapitation, dispose of them as the situation dictates.  It is the aim not to allow the escape of a single one, to annihilate them all, and not to leave any traces.’  (pp. 23-24)" -- Hampton Sides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120744-were-you-ever-in-elsinore-mr-jagiello-asked-jack-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:47:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120744-were-you-ever-in-elsinore-mr-jagiello-asked-jack-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were you ever in Elsinore, Mr Jagiello?’ asked Jack.
Oh, many a time, sir,’ said Jagiello.  ‘I know it well.  I believe I could show you Hamlet’s grave from here.’
I was really wondering whether they had ten or thirteen inch mortars on the upper terrace,’ said Jack, ‘but I should be very happy to see Hamlet’s grave as well.’
Both ten and thirteen, sir.  And if you go a little to the right from the farthest turret, there are some trees:  and among those trees there is the grave.  You can just make out the rocks.’
So there he lies,’ said jack, his telescope leveled.  ‘Well, well:  we must all come to it.  But it was a capital piece, capital.  I never laughed so much in my life.’
A capital piece indeed,’ said Stephen, ‘and I doubt I could have done much better myself.  But, do you know, I have never in my own mind classed it among the comedies.  Pray did you read it recently?’
I never read it at all,’ said Jack.  ‘That is to say, not right through.  No:  I did something better than that—I acted in it.  There, the upper terrace fires.  I was a midshipman at the time." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115787-it-is-a-queer-weapon-a-shotgun-every-effort-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:48:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Charles Askins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115787-it-is-a-queer-weapon-a-shotgun-every-effort-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a queer weapon, a shotgun. Every effort to secure additional range is well paid for. A bird may be going away at tremendous speed, &quot;burning the air&quot; as a youngster would put it. Seemingly nothing but chain-lightning, which zig-zagged a bit, could stop him. A crack of the gun and that wild flier is dead in the air, a full forty yards away. Right then the conviction comes to us that man never made another weapon so deadly as the shotgun. However, go back another forty yards, set the bird up on the limb of a tree and you might shoot at him all day and not kill him. The shotgun is a deadly weapon but its range is strictly limited and we are ourselves pretty well convinced that nothing less than a two-inch cannon will regularly kill single game-birds at one-hundred yards, with any kind of shot that can be put in the gun." -- Charles Askins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479861-she-had-been-born-to-cradle-other-people-s-children-wear</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2011 17:51:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479861-she-had-been-born-to-cradle-other-people-s-children-wear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been born to cradle other people's children, wear their hand-me-down clothing, eat their leftovers, live on borrowed happiness and grief, grow old beneath other people's roofs, die one day in her miserable little room in the far courtyard in a bed that did not belong to her, and be buried in a common grave in the public cemetery." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484784-you-know-how-to-check-fer-thin-ice-boy-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 21:17:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Patrick Mcmanus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/484784-you-know-how-to-check-fer-thin-ice-boy-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know how to check fer thin ice, boy?&quot; he would ask me.  &quot;Wall, what you do is stick one foot way out ahead of you and stomp the ice real hard and listen fer it to make a crackin' sound.  Thar now, did you hear how the ice cracked whan Ah stomped it?  Thet means it's too thin to hold a man's weight.  Now pull me up out of hyar and we'll run back to shore and see if we kin built a fahr b'fore Ah freezes to death!" -- Patrick Mcmanus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146164-until-the-millennium-arrives-and-countries-cease-trying-to-enslave</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 08:49:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by E.B. Sledge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146164-until-the-millennium-arrives-and-countries-cease-trying-to-enslave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until the millennium arrives and countries cease trying to enslave others, it will be necessary to accept one's responsibilities and be willing to make sacrifices for one's country - as my comrades did. As the troops used to say, &quot;If the country is good enough to live in, it's good enough to fight for.&quot; With privilege goes responsibility." -- E.B. Sledge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492458-there-is-nothing-better-than-to-be-headed-into-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2012 13:53:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Patrick Mcmanus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/492458-there-is-nothing-better-than-to-be-headed-into-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing better than to be headed into the mountains on a clean fresh day with the sun rising through the trees and good company and good talk and the sense of ease that comes from the knowledge that you are in somebody else's car and it is not your transmission that is going to get torn out on a big rock." -- Patrick Mcmanus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629378-love-is-nothing-but-lust-lust-and-more-lust-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2012 11:04:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Jöns in The Seventh Seal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/629378-love-is-nothing-but-lust-lust-and-more-lust-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is nothing but lust, lust, and more lust, with a lot of cheating, lies, and general tomfoolery thrown in.  Love is the blackest of all plagues, and the only pleasure would be to die of it.  But it almost always passes." -- Jöns in The Seventh Seal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722970-we-leafed-through-a-series-of-the-1941-soviet-front</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 12:10:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Vasily Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/722970-we-leafed-through-a-series-of-the-1941-soviet-front]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We leafed through a series of the [1941 Soviet] Front newspaper.  I came across the following phrase in a leading article:  'The much-battered enemy continued his cowardly advance." -- Vasily Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772130-i-felt-as-though-i-were-plunging-into-something-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2013 12:08:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Herzog Maurice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/772130-i-felt-as-though-i-were-plunging-into-something-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt as though I were plunging into something new and quite abnormal.  I had the strangest and most vivid impressions, such as I had never before known in the mountains.  There was something unnatural in the way I saw Lachenal and everything around us.  I smiled to myself at the paltriness of our efforts, for I could stand apart and watch myself making these efforts.  But all sense of exertion was gone, as though there were no longer any gravity.  This diaphanous landscape, this quintessence of purity--these were not the mountains I knew:  they were the mountains of my dreams (pp.206-207)." -- Herzog Maurice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889134-march-18-1945-brief-morning-reflection-arisen-from-great-love-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2013 19:45:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Victor Klemperer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889134-march-18-1945-brief-morning-reflection-arisen-from-great-love-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["March 18...[1945]
Brief morning reflection arisen from great love.  In fact, the main point after all is that for forty years we have so much loved one another and do love one another; in fact, I am not at all sure at all that all this is going to come to an end.  For certain, nothingness--en tant que individual consciousness, and there is the true nothingness--is altogether probable, and anything else highly improbable.  But have we not continually experienced, since 1914 and even more since 1933 and with ever greater frequency in recent weeks, the most utterly improbable, the most monstrously fantastic things?  Has not what was formerly completely unimaginable to us become commonplace and a matter of course?  If I have lived through the persecutions in Dresden, if I have lived through February 13 and these weeks as a refugee--why should I not just as well live (or rather: die) to find the two of us somewhere, Eva and I, with angel wings or in some other droll form?  It's not only the word &quot;impossible&quot; that has gone out of circulation, &quot;unimaginable&quot; also has no validity anymore." -- Victor Klemperer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905062-academics-love-the-semicolon-their-hankering-after-logic-demands-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 08:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Victor Klemperer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/905062-academics-love-the-semicolon-their-hankering-after-logic-demands-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Academics love the semicolon; their hankering after logic demands a division which is more emphatic than a comma, but not quite as absolute a demarcation as a full stop." -- Victor Klemperer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189610-the-institutions-conventions-customs-and-laws-that-make-up-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 20:54:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Will Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189610-the-institutions-conventions-customs-and-laws-that-make-up-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The institutions, conventions, customs and laws that make up the complex structure of a society are the work of a hundred centuries and a billion minds; and one mind must not expect to comprehend them in one lifetime, much less in twenty years." -- Will Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189615-n-o-language-has-ever-had-a-word-for-a-virgin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 20:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clark add a quote by Will Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1189615-n-o-language-has-ever-had-a-word-for-a-virgin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[N]o language has ever had a word for a virgin man." -- Will Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
