<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851459-lucas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/851459-lucas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 18:22:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41186-a-day-of-dappled-seaborne-clouds-the-phrase-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 18:22:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by James Joyce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41186-a-day-of-dappled-seaborne-clouds-the-phrase-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day of dappled seaborne clouds.

The phrase and the day and the scene harmonised in a chord.  Words.  Was it their colours?  He allowed them to glow and fade, hue after hue: sunrise gold, the russet and green of apple orchards, azure of waves, the greyfringed fleece of clouds.  No, it was not their colours: it was the poise and balance of the period itself.  Did he then love the rhythmic rise and fall of words better than their associations of legend and colour?  Or was it that, being as weak of sight as he was shy of mind, he drew less pleasure from the reflection of the glowing sensible world through the prism of a language manycoloured and richly storied than from the contemplation of an inner world of individual emotions mirrored perfectly in a lucid supple periodic prose?" -- James Joyce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117473-i-sat-in-the-sun-on-a-bench-the-animal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 18:24:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117473-i-sat-in-the-sun-on-a-bench-the-animal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sat in the sun on a bench; the animal within me licking the chops of memory; the spiritual side a little drowsed, promising subsequent penitence, but not yet moved to begin." -- Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193944-the-most-merciful-thing-in-the-world-i-think-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 18:25:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193944-the-most-merciful-thing-in-the-world-i-think-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most merciful thing in the world, I think, is the inability of the human mind to correlate all its contents. We live on a placid island of ignorance in the midst of black seas of infinity, and it was not meant that we should voyage far. The sciences, each straining in its own direction, have hitherto harmed us little; but some day the piecing together of dissociated knowledge will open up such terrifying vistas of reality, and of our frightful position therein, that we shall either go mad from the revelation or flee from the light into the peace and safety of a new dark age." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 18:25:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539504-the-time-of-a-man-s-life-is-as-a-point</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2012 02:34:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539504-the-time-of-a-man-s-life-is-as-a-point]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time of a man's life is as a point; the substance of it ever flowing, the sense obscure; and the whole composition of the body tending to corruption. His soul is restless, fortune uncertain, and fame doubtful; to be brief, as a stream so are all things belonging to the body; as a dream, or as a smoke, so are all that belong unto the soul. Our life is a warfare, and a mere pilgrimage. Fame after life is no better than oblivion. What is it then that will adhere and follow? Only one thing, philosophy. And philosophy doth consist in this, for a man to preserve that spirit which is within him, from all manner of contumelies and injuries, and above all pains or pleasures; never to do anything either rashly, or feignedly, or hypocritically: only to depend from himself, and his own proper actions: all things that happen unto him to embrace contentendly, as coming from Him from whom he himself also came; and above all things, with all meekness and a calm cheerfulness, to expect death, as being nothing else but the resolution of those elements, of which every creature is composed. And if the elements themselves suffer nothing by their perpetual conversion of one into another, that dissolution, and alteration, which is so common unto all, why should it be feared by any? Is not this according to nature? But nothing that is according to nature can be evil." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172547-words-move-music-moves-only-in-time-but-that-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 23:14:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172547-words-move-music-moves-only-in-time-but-that-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words move, music moves
Only in time; but that which is only living
Can only die. Words, after speech, reach
Into the silence. Only by the form, the pattern,
Can words or music reach
The stillness..." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544602-logic-n-the-art-of-thinking-and-reasoning-in-strict</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 23:25:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lucas add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/544602-logic-n-the-art-of-thinking-and-reasoning-in-strict]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Logic, n. The art of thinking and reasoning in strict accordance with the limitations and incapacities of the human misunderstanding. The basic of logic is the syllogism, consisting of a major and a minor premise and a conclusion - thus:

Major Premise: Sixty men can do a piece of work sixty times as quickly as one man.
Minor Premise: One man can dig a post-hole in sixty seconds; Therefore-
Conclusion: Sixty men can dig a post-hole in one second.

This may be called syllogism arithmetical, in which, by combining logic and mathematics, we obtain a double certainty and are twice blessed." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
