<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/852972-carl-eric-tangen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/852972-carl-eric-tangen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:27:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235176-i-am-too-alone-in-the-world-and-yet-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:27:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235176-i-am-too-alone-in-the-world-and-yet-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am too alone in the world, and yet not alone enough
to make every moment holy.
I am too tiny in this world, and not tiny enough
just to lie before you like a thing,
shrewd and secretive.
I want my own will, and I want simply to be with my will,
as it goes toward action;
and in those quiet, sometimes hardly moving times,
when something is coming near,
I want to be with those who know secret things
or else alone.
I want to be a mirror for your whole body,
and I never want to be blind, or to be too old
to hold up your heavy and swaying picture.
I want to unfold.
I don’t want to stay folded anywhere,
because where I am folded, there I am a lie.
and I want my grasp of things to be
true before you. I want to describe myself
like a painting that I looked at
closely for a long time,
like a saying that I finally understood,
like the pitcher I use every day,
like the face of my mother,
like a ship
that carried me
through the wildest storm of all." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21687-this-is-the-miracle-that-happens-every-time-to-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21687-this-is-the-miracle-that-happens-every-time-to-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is the miracle that happens every time to those who really love: the more they give, the more they possess." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234336-but-this-is-what-people-are-so-often-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:27:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234336-but-this-is-what-people-are-so-often-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But this is what ... people are so often and disastrously wrong in doing: they (who by their very nature are impatient) fling themselves at each other when love takes hold of them, they scatter themselves, just as they are, in all their messiness, disorder, bewilderment ...

And what can happen then? What can life do with this heap of half broken things that they would like to call their happiness, and their futures?

And so each of them loses himself to the other for the sake of the other person, and loses the other. And loses the vast possibilities ... in exchange for an unfruitful confusion, out of which nothing more can come, nothing but a bit of disgust, disappointment and poverty." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174357-it-is-good-to-be-solitary-for-solitude-is-difficult</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:30:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174357-it-is-good-to-be-solitary-for-solitude-is-difficult]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is good to be solitary, for solitude is difficult; that something is difficult must be a reason the more for us to do it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257855-as-if-no-one-had-ever-tried-before-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257855-as-if-no-one-had-ever-tried-before-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As if no one had ever tried before, try to say what you see and feel and love and lose." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239044-where-something-becomes-extremely-difficult-and-unbearable-there-we-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:30:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239044-where-something-becomes-extremely-difficult-and-unbearable-there-we-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where something becomes extremely difficult and unbearable, there we also stand already quite near its transformation." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172842-we-have-no-reason-to-mistrust-our-world-for-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:31:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172842-we-have-no-reason-to-mistrust-our-world-for-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have no reason to mistrust our world, for it is not against us.  Has it terrors, they are our terrors; has it abysses, those abysses belong to us; are dangers at hand, we must try to love them… How should we be able to forget those ancient myths about dragons that at the least moment turn into princesses; perhaps all the dragons of our lives are princesses who are only waiting to see us once beautiful and brave." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181099-be-of-good-courage-all-is-before-you-and-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181099-be-of-good-courage-all-is-before-you-and-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be of good courage all is before you, and time passed in the difficult is never lost...What is required of us is that we live the difficult and learn to deal with it. In the difficult are the friendly forces, the hands that work on us." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197535-the-deepest-experience-of-the-creator-is-feminine-for-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:33:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197535-the-deepest-experience-of-the-creator-is-feminine-for-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The deepest experience of the creator is feminine, for it is experience of receiving and bearing." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87968-we-are-continually-overflowing-toward-those-who-preceded-us-toward</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 01:33:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/87968-we-are-continually-overflowing-toward-those-who-preceded-us-toward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we are continually overflowing toward those who preceded us, toward our origin, and toward those who seemingly come after us. ... It is our task to imprint this temporary, perishable earth into ourselves so deeply, so painfully and passionately, that its essence can rise again “invisibly,” inside us. We are the bees of the invisible. We wildly collect the honey of the visible, to store it in the great golden hive of the invisible." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202980-again-and-again-however-we-know-the-landscape-of-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 12:18:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202980-again-and-again-however-we-know-the-landscape-of-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Again and again, however we know the landscape of love
and the little churchyard there, with its sorrowing names,
and the frighteningly silent abyss into which the others
fall: again and again the two of us walk out together
under the ancient trees, lie down again and again
among the flowers, face to face with the sky." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140419-how-i-will-cherish-you-then-you-grief-torn-nights-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 12:29:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140419-how-i-will-cherish-you-then-you-grief-torn-nights-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How I will cherish you then,
      you grief-torn nights!
Had I only received you, 
      inconsolable sisters,
on more abject knees, only 
buried myself with more 
                  abandon           
in your loosened hair. How we waste  
                   our afflictions!
We study them, stare out beyond them
            into bleak continuance, 
hoping to glimpse some end. Whereas 
                    they're really
our wintering foliage, our dark greens
                      of meaning, one
of the seasons of the clandestine
                  year -- ; not only
a season --: they're site, settlement,
               shelter, soil, abode." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214375-i-live-my-life-in-growing-orbits-which-move-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 12:30:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214375-i-live-my-life-in-growing-orbits-which-move-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I live my life in growing orbits which move out over this wondrous world, I am circling around God, around ancient towers and i have been circling for a thousand years. And I still dont know if I am an eagle or a storm or a great song." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320713-it-s-ridiculous-here-i-sit-in-my-little-room-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/320713-it-s-ridiculous-here-i-sit-in-my-little-room-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's ridiculous. Here I sit in my little room, I, Brigge, who have got to be twenty-eight years old and about whom no one knows. I sit here and am nothing. And yet this nothing begins to think and thinks, up five flights of stairs, these thoughts on a gray Paris afternoon:

Is it possible, this nothing thinks, that one has not yet seen, recognized, and said anything real and important? Is it possible that one has had thousands of years of time to look, reflect, and write down, and that one has let the millennia pass away like a school recess in which one eats one's sandwich and an apple?
Yes, it is possible.

...Is it possible that in spite of inventions and progress, in spite of culture, religion, and worldly wisdom, that one has remained on the surface of life? Is it possible that one has even covered this surface, which would at least have been something, with an incredibly dull slipcover, so that it looks like living-room furniture during the summer vacation?
Yes, it is possible.

Is it possible that the whole history of the world has been misunderstood? Is it possible that the past is false because one has always spoken of its masses, as if one was telling about a coming together of many people, instead of telling about the one person they were standing around, because he was alien and died?
Yes, it is possible.

Is it possible that one believed one has to make up for everything that happened before one was born? Is it possible one would have to remind every single person that he arose from all earlier people so that he would know it, and not let himself be talked out of it by the others, who see it differently?
Yes, it is possible.

Is it possible that all these people know very precisely a past that never was? Is it possible that everything real is nothing to them; that their life takes its course, connected to nothing, like a clock in an empty room?
Yes, it is possible.

Is it possible that one knows nothing about girls, who are nevertheless alive? Is it possible that one says &quot;the women&quot;, &quot;the children&quot;, &quot;the boys&quot;, and doesn't suspect (in spite of all one's education doesn't suspect) that for the longest time these words have no longer had a plural, but only innumerable singulars?
Yes, it is possible.

Is it possible that there are people who say &quot;God&quot; and think it is something they have in common? Just look at two schoolboys: one buys himself a knife, and the same day his neighbor buys one just like it. And after a week they show each other their knives and it turns out that they bear only the remotest resemblance to each other-so differently have they developed in different hands (Well, the mother of one of them says, if you boys always have to wear everything out right away). Ah, so: is it possible to believe that one could have a God without using him?
Yes, it is possible.

But, if all this is possible, has even an appearance of possibility-then for heaven's sake something has to happen. The first person who comes along, the one who has had this disquieting thought, must begin to accomplish some of what has been missed; even if he is just anyone, not the most suitable person: there is simply no one else there. This young, irrelevant foreigner, Brigge, will have to sit himself down five flights up and write, day and night, he will just have to write, and that will be that." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19562-the-point-of-marriage-is-not-to-create-a-quick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The point of marriage is not to create a quick commonality by tearing down all boundaries; on the contrary, a good marriage is one in which each partner appoints the other to be the guardian of his solitude, and thus they show each other the greatest possible trust. A merging of two people is an impossibility, and where it seems to exist, it is a hemming-in, a mutual consent that robs one party or both parties of their fullest freedom and development. But once the realization is accepted that even between the closest people infinite distances exist, a marvelous living side-by-side can grow up for them, if they succeed in loving the expanse between them, which gives them the possibility of always seeing each other as a whole and before an immense sky." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278821-do-you-recall-from-your-childhood-on-how-very-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:36:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278821-do-you-recall-from-your-childhood-on-how-very-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you recall, from your childhood on, how very much this life of yours has longed for greatness? I see it now, how from the vantage point of greatness it longs for even greater greatness. That is why it does not let up being difficult, but that is also why it will not cease to grow." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157505-vielleicht-da-ich-durch-schwere-berge-gehe-in-harten-adern</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157505-vielleicht-da-ich-durch-schwere-berge-gehe-in-harten-adern]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vielleicht, daß ich durch schwere Berge gehe
in harten Adern, wie ein Erz allein;
und bin so tief, daß ich kein Ende sehe
und keine Ferne: alles wurde Nähe
und alle Nähe wurde Stein.

Ich bin ja kein Wissender im Wehe,—
so macht mich dieses große Dunkel klein;
bist Du es aber: mach dich schwer, brich ein:
daß deine ganze Hand an mir geschehe
und ich an dir mit meinem ganzen Schrein.



It's possible I'm moving through the hard veins
of heavy mountains, like the ore does, alone;
I'm already so deep inside, I see no end in sight,
and no distance: everything is getting near
and everything getting near is turning to stone.

I still can't see very far yet into suffering,—
so this vast darkness makes me small;
are you the one: make yourself powerful, break in:
so that your whole being may happen to me,
and to you may happen, my whole cry. " -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140197-why-should-you-want-to-give-up-a-child-s-wise</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:38:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140197-why-should-you-want-to-give-up-a-child-s-wise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why should you want to give up a child's wise not-understanding in exchange for defensiveness and scorn, since not-understanding is, after all, a way of being alone, whereas defensiveness and scorn are a participation in precisely what, by these means, you want to separate yourself from." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284372-sometimes-a-man-stands-up-during-supper-and-walks-outdoors</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284372-sometimes-a-man-stands-up-during-supper-and-walks-outdoors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sometimes a man stands up during supper
and walks outdoors, and keeps on walking,
because of a church that stands somewhere in the East.

And his children say blessings on him as if he were dead.

And another man, who remains inside his own house,
stays there, inside the dishes and in the glasses,
so that his children have to go far out into the world
toward that same church, which he forgot." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222965-and-still-it-is-not-enough-to-have-memories-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:40:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222965-and-still-it-is-not-enough-to-have-memories-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And still it is not enough to have memories. One must be able to forget them when they are many, and one must have the great patience to wait until they come again. For it is not yet the memories themselves. Not until they have turned to blood within us, to glance, to gesture, nameless and no longer to be distinguished from ourselves - not until then can it happen that in a most rare hour the first word of a verse arises in their midst and goes forth from them." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353310-perhaps-the-great-renewal-of-the-world-will-consist-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:40:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353310-perhaps-the-great-renewal-of-the-world-will-consist-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the great renewal of the world will consist of this, that man and woman, freed of all confused feelings and desires, shall no longer seek each other as opposites, but simply as members of a family and neighbors, and will unite as human beings, in order to simply, earnestly, patiently, and jointly bear the heavy responsibility of sexuality that has been entrusted to them." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217842-everything-is-gestation-and-then-birthing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217842-everything-is-gestation-and-then-birthing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is gestation and then birthing." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346239-always-the-wish-that-you-may-find-patience-enough-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:42:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346239-always-the-wish-that-you-may-find-patience-enough-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["always the wish that you may find patience enough in yourself to endure, and simplicity enough to believe; that you may acquire more and more confidence in that which is difficult, and in your solitude among others." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296261-outside-much-has-changed-i-don-t-know-how-but-inside</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 13:44:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296261-outside-much-has-changed-i-don-t-know-how-but-inside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside much has changed. I don't know how. But inside and before you, O my God, inside before you, spectator, are we not without action? We discover, indeed, that we do not know our part, we look for a mirror, we want to rub off the make-up and remove the counterfeit and be real. But somewhere a bit of mummery still sticks to us that we forget. A trace of exaggeration remains in our eyebrows, we do not notice that the corners of our lips are twisted. And thus we go about, a laughing-stock, a mere half-thing: neither existing, not actors." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:14:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True love is not so much a matter of romance as it is a matter of anxious concern for the well-being of one's companion." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prejudices, it is well known, are most difficult to eradicate from the heart whose soil has never been loosened or fertilised by education: they grow there, firm as weeds among stones." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48964-the-trouble-is-not-that-i-am-single-and-likely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:14:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48964-the-trouble-is-not-that-i-am-single-and-likely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is not that I am single and likely to stay single, but that I am lonely and likely to stay lonely." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40580-every-atom-of-your-flesh-is-as-dear-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:14:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40580-every-atom-of-your-flesh-is-as-dear-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every atom of your flesh is as dear to me as my own: in pain and sickness it would still be dear." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25851-gentle-reader-may-you-never-feel-what-i-then-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:15:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25851-gentle-reader-may-you-never-feel-what-i-then-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gentle reader, may you never feel what I then felt!  May your eyes never shed such stormy, scalding, heart-wrung tears as poured from mine.  May you never appeal to Heaven in prayers so hopeless and so agised as in that hour left my lips: for never may you, like me, dread to be the instrument of evil to what you wholly love." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 13:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carl-Eric add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
