<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/853050-dan-grierson]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/853050-dan-grierson" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 22:06:24 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 22:06:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19178-the-cowboy-way-being-a-cowboy-is-doing-the-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 22:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dan add a quote by Charly Gullett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19178-the-cowboy-way-being-a-cowboy-is-doing-the-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Cowboy Way

Being a Cowboy is doing the right thing; common
wisdom born of simple virtues and strong ideals.
Above all, it is a strict adherence to honesty
even when it is not in our best interests.
It is having an inherent sense of justice in a
world where the cards are often stacked against us.
We try to hold enough common sense to recognize
the value of a lost cause and the cost of lost values.
Generally speaking, we are quietly reserved in all
things except freedom, fresh air and Saturday night.
We have a keen eye for a
good horse, a good gun,and a good Cowgirl.
Constant to friends, we are more so when
friends need us, less so when they don't.
Familiar with hard work we also know
hard knocks and hard roads.
Often given to tears
when lesser individuals would display indifference;
we are as well given to joy in a few
places others would only find disdain.
We enjoy plain living, not because
we relish doing without, but because we have
discovered the treasures within.
And, finally, we have that elusive emotion called
courage which is, at worst, a badly directed sense of
conceit and, at best, it is the stuff
of which dreams are made. . . ." -- Charly Gullett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
