<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85397-ryan-louis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85397-ryan-louis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 22:51:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 22:51:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21044-we-die-containing-a-richness-of-lovers-and-tribes-tastes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We die containing a richness of lovers and tribes, tastes we have swallowed, bodies we have plunged into and swum up as if rivers of wisdom, characters we have climbed into as if trees, fears we have hidden in as if caves. 

I wish for all this to be marked on by body when I am dead.  I believe in such cartography - to be marked by nature, not just to label ourselves on a map like the names of rich men and women on buildings.  We are communal histories, communal books.  We are not owned or monogamous in our taste or experience." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 22:52:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53414-writing-is-like-driving-at-night-in-the-fog-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is like driving at night in the fog. You can only see as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way." -- E.L. Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12303-if-you-saw-atlas-the-giant-who-holds-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 08:13:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12303-if-you-saw-atlas-the-giant-who-holds-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you saw Atlas, the giant who holds the world on his shoulders, if you saw that he stood, blood running down his chest, his knees buckling, his arms trembling but still trying to hold the world aloft with the last of his strength, and the greater his effort the heavier the world bore down upon his shoulders - What would you tell him?&quot;

I…don't know. What…could he do? What would you tell him?&quot;

To shrug." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2012 00:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when he died, I suddenly realized I wasn’t crying for him at all, but for the things he did. I cried because he would never do them again, he would never carve another piece of wood or help us raise doves and pigeons in the backyard or play the violin the way he did, or tell us jokes the way he did. He was part of us and when he died, all the actions stopped dead and there was no one to do them the way he did. He was individual. He was an important man. I’ve never gotten over his death. Often I think what wonderful carvings never came to birth because he died. How many jokes are missing from the world, and how many homing pigeons untouched by his hands? He shaped the world. He did things to the world. The world was bankrupted of ten million fine actions the night he passed on." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
