<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/854256-kristi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/854256-kristi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 12:40:59 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8736-so-long-as-there-shall-exist-by-reason-of-law</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 12:40:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8736-so-long-as-there-shall-exist-by-reason-of-law]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So long as there shall exist, by reason of law and custom, a social condemnation which, in the midst of civilization, artificially creates a hell on earth, and complicates with human fatality a destiny that is divine; so long as the three problems of the century - the  degradation of man by the exploitation of his labour, the ruin of women by starvation and the atrophy of childhood by physical and spiritual night are not solved; so long as, in certain regions, social asphyxia shall be possible; in other words and from a still broader point of view, so long as ignorance and misery remain on earth, there should be a need for books such as this." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31609-and-if-it-seem-evil-unto-you-to-serve-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 12:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31609-and-if-it-seem-evil-unto-you-to-serve-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And if it seem evil unto you to serve the Lord, choose you this day whom you will serve, wether the Gods of your fathers who were on the other side of the flood, or the Gods of the ammorites in whos land you dwell: but as for me and my house, we will serve the Lord." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12613-it-is-so-easy-to-be-hopeful-in-the-daytime</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 10:33:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12613-it-is-so-easy-to-be-hopeful-in-the-daytime]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is so easy to be hopeful in the daytime when you can see the things you wish on.  But it was night, it stayed night.  Night was striding across nothingness with the whole round world in his hands . . . They sat in company with the others in other shanties, their eyes straining against cruel walls and their souls asking if He meant to measure their puny might against His.  They seemed to be staring at the dark, but their eyes were watching God." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 09:38:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
