<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85461-maia]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85461-maia" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 16:08:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276997-but-oh-the-blessing-it-is-to-have-a-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 16:08:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maia add a quote by Dinah Craik]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276997-but-oh-the-blessing-it-is-to-have-a-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But oh! the blessing it is to have a friend to whom one can speak fearlessly on any subject; with whom one's deepest as well as one's most foolish thoughts come out simply and safely.  Oh, the comfort - the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person - having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words, but pouring them all right out, just as they are, chaff and grain together; certain that a faithful hand will take and sift them, keep what is worth keeping, and then with the breath of kindness blow the rest away." -- Dinah Craik]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237928-anyway-there-is-one-thing-i-have-learned-and-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 16:21:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maia add a quote by George Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237928-anyway-there-is-one-thing-i-have-learned-and-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, there is one thing I have learned and that is not to dress uncomfortably, in styles which hurt: winklepicker shoes that cripple your feet and tight pants that squash your balls.  Indian clothes are better." -- George Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378268-in-this-sad-world-of-ours-sorrow-comes-to-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 16:23:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maia add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378268-in-this-sad-world-of-ours-sorrow-comes-to-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this sad world of ours, sorrow comes to all; and, to the young, it comes with bitterest agony, because it takes them unawares. The older have learned to ever expect it. I am anxious to afford some alleviation of your present distress. Perfect relief is not possible, except with time. You can not now realize that you will ever feel better. Is not this so? And yet it is a mistake. You are sure to be happy again. To know this, which is certainly true, will make you some less miserable now. I have had experience enough to know what I say; and you need only to believe it, to feel better at once." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418957-sometimes-i-m-so-deeply-buried-under-self-reproaches-that-i-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 16:23:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maia add a quote by Anne Frank]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/418957-sometimes-i-m-so-deeply-buried-under-self-reproaches-that-i-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I'm so deeply buried under self-reproaches that I long for a word of comfort to help me dig myself out again." -- Anne Frank]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
