<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85501-megankellie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85501-megankellie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:46:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204535-a-ll-i-want-to-do-is-sit-on-my-ass</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:46:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204535-a-ll-i-want-to-do-is-sit-on-my-ass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[A]ll I want to do is sit on my ass and fart and think of Dante." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:45:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perfectionism is the voice of the oppressor, the enemy of the people. It will keep you cramped and insane your whole life, and it is the main obstacle between you and a shitty first draft. I think perfectionism is based on the obsessive belief that if you run carefully enough, hitting each stepping-stone just right, you won't have to die. The truth is that you will die anyway and that a lot of people who aren't even looking at their feet are going to do a whole lot better than you, and have a lot more fun while they're doing it." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578061-we-approach-the-divine-by-enlarging-our-souls-and-lighting</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:45:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/578061-we-approach-the-divine-by-enlarging-our-souls-and-lighting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We approach the divine by enlarging our souls and lighting up our brains." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562251-the-morning-slathers-its-whatever-across-the-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:45:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Michael Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/562251-the-morning-slathers-its-whatever-across-the-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The morning slathers its whatever
across the thing." -- Michael Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723013-okay-i-know--my-superpower--i-d-be-able-to-shoot-lightening-bolts</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:46:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723013-okay-i-know--my-superpower--i-d-be-able-to-shoot-lightening-bolts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Okay, I know--my superpower--I'd be able to shoot lightening bolts out from my fingertips--great big knowledge network lightening bolts--and when a person was zapped by one of those bolts, they'd fall down on their knees and once on their knees, they'd be under water, in this place I saw once off the east coast of the Bahamas, a place where a billion electric blue fish swam up to me and made me a part of their school--and then they'd be up in the air, up in Manhattan, above the World Trade Center, with a flock of pigeons, flying amid the skyscrapers, and then--then what? And then they'd go blind, and then they'd be taken away--they'd feel homesick--more homesick than they'd felt in their entire life--so homesick they were throwing up--and they'd be abandoned, I don't know...in the middle of a harvested corn field in Missouri. And then they'd be able to see again, and from the edges of the field people would appear--everybody they'd known--and they'd be carrying Black Forest cakes and burning tiki lamps and boom boxes playing the same song, and they sky would turn into a sunset, the way it does in Walt Disney brochure, and the person I zapped would never be alone or isolated again." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212969-i-sometimes-think-the-sexual-organs-were-put-there-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 12:24:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212969-i-sometimes-think-the-sexual-organs-were-put-there-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sometimes think the sexual organs were put there to keep the human race humble,&quot; she said. &quot;They've certainly kept me humble." -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24903-if-you-wait-all-that-happens-is-that-you-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 13:23:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24903-if-you-wait-all-that-happens-is-that-you-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you wait, all that happens is that you get older." -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226354-you-should-be-proud-of-her-she-cracked-the-wall</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 11:26:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226354-you-should-be-proud-of-her-she-cracked-the-wall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should be proud of her. She cracked the wall, and I never thought I'd live to see it cracked.&quot;
What are you talking about?&quot; I said. &quot;What wall?&quot;
The one you built around you,&quot; Jeannie said. &quot;Don't say it wasn't there. It was there. I tried to crack it but I didn't have the confidence, you know? What happened is, it cracked me, but that's okay, I'm working around my crack pretty well. But you were dying behind your wall, and you're lucky to have a daughter who has the guts to crack it. I hope she smashes it to fucking smithereens and you never have another peaceful day in your whole fucking life, Mr. Deck!" -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226356-i-don-t-know-why-you-would-even-want-to-stay</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 11:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Larry McMurtry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226356-i-don-t-know-why-you-would-even-want-to-stay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know why you would even want to stay with me,&quot; I said.
T.R. looked stunned for a second and then whipped her elbow into my side as hard as she could--months later it was determined that the jab cracked a rib.
Oh, get fucked!&quot; she said, jumping up. &quot;No wonder you don't have no girlfriend if you don't have no more feelings than to say a horrible thing like that. All I want to do is love you. Ain't you even gonna let me?" -- Larry McMurtry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 07:53:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147582-every-now-and-then-i-ll-run-into-someone-who-claims</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 09:09:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Steve Almond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147582-every-now-and-then-i-ll-run-into-someone-who-claims]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every now and then, I'll run into someone who claims not to like chocolate, and while we live in a country where everyone has the right to eat what they want, I want to say for the record that I don't trust these people, that I think something is wrong with them, and that they're probably - and this must be said - total duds in bed." -- Steve Almond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294833-when-you-wish-for-something-over-and-over-again-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2010 21:09:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Elna Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294833-when-you-wish-for-something-over-and-over-again-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you wish for something over and over again and it doesn't come true, something else happens; not only do you give up, but you resent your wish and you resent wishing." -- Elna Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 21:42:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2012 22:46:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27799-the-more-one-judges-the-less-one-loves</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 12:45:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27799-the-more-one-judges-the-less-one-loves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more one judges, the less one loves." -- Honoré de Balzac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2384-moral-indignation-is-jealousy-with-a-halo</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 10:07:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by H.G. Wells]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2384-moral-indignation-is-jealousy-with-a-halo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Moral indignation is jealousy with a halo." -- H.G. Wells]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214662-hope-begins-in-the-dark-the-stubborn-hope-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2012 00:28:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214662-hope-begins-in-the-dark-the-stubborn-hope-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope begins in the dark, the stubborn hope that if you just show up and try to do the right thing, the dawn will come. You wait and watch and work: you don't give up." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/771279-it-was-always-himself-that-the-coward-abandoned-first-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 10:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/771279-it-was-always-himself-that-the-coward-abandoned-first-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was always himself that the coward abandoned first. After this all other betrayals came easily." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338907-at-this-point-i-reveal-myself-in-my-true-colours</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2013 19:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Kenneth Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338907-at-this-point-i-reveal-myself-in-my-true-colours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At this point I reveal myself in my true colours, as a stick-in-the-mud. I hold a number of beliefs that have been repudiated by the liveliest intellects of our time. I believe that order is better than chaos, creation better than destruction. I prefer gentleness to violence, forgiveness to vendetta. On the whole I think that knowledge is preferable to ignorance, and I am sure that human sympathy is more valuable than ideology. I believe that in spite of the recent triumphs of science, men haven't changed much in the last two thousand years; and in consequence we must still try to learn from history. History is ourselves. I also hold one or two beliefs that are more difficult to put shortly. For example, I believe in courtesy, the ritual by which we avoid hurting other people's feelings by satisfying our own egos. And I think we should remember that we are part of a great whole. All living things are our brothers and sisters. Above all, I believe in the God-given genius of certain individuals, and I value a society that makes their existence possible." -- Kenneth Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497678-among-a-coward-s-weapons-cynicism-is-the-nastiest-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 10:50:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Tracy Kidder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497678-among-a-coward-s-weapons-cynicism-is-the-nastiest-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["among a coward's weapons, cynicism is the nastiest of all" -- Tracy Kidder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034071-you-almost-believe-that-you-will-never-come-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 12:12:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Nicholson Baker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1034071-you-almost-believe-that-you-will-never-come-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…you almost believe that you will never come to the end of a roll of tape; and when you do, there is a feeling, nearly, though very briefly, of shock and grief." -- Nicholson Baker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84214-chaos-often-breeds-life-when-order-breeds-habit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 09:42:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Henry Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84214-chaos-often-breeds-life-when-order-breeds-habit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chaos often breeds life, when order breeds habit." -- Henry Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70581-people-always-think-that-happiness-is-a-faraway-thing-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 19:29:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70581-people-always-think-that-happiness-is-a-faraway-thing-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People always think that happiness is a faraway thing,&quot; thought Francie, &quot;something complicated and hard to get.  Yet, what little things can make it up; a place of shelter when it rains - a cup of strong hot coffee when you're blue; for a man, a cigarette for contentment; a book to read when you're alone - just to be with someone you love.  Those things make happiness." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33127-who-wants-to-die-everything-struggles-to-live-look-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 19:30:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Betty  Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33127-who-wants-to-die-everything-struggles-to-live-look-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who wants to die?  Everything struggles to live.  Look at that tree growing up there out of that grating.  It gets no sun, and water only when it rains.  It's growing out of sour earth.  And it's strong because its hard struggle to live is making it strong.  My children will be strong that way." -- Betty  Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146692-they-learned-no-compassion-from-their-own-anguish-thus-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 19:30:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Betty Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146692-they-learned-no-compassion-from-their-own-anguish-thus-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They learned no compassion from their own anguish.  thus their suffering was wasted." -- Betty Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285436-in-the-beginner-s-mind-there-are-many-possibilities-but-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 20:58:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Shunryu Suzuki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/285436-in-the-beginner-s-mind-there-are-many-possibilities-but-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the beginner’s mind there are many possibilities, but in the expert’s there are few" -- Shunryu Suzuki]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36686-some-people-have-a-way-with-words-and-other-people-oh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 08:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megankellie add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36686-some-people-have-a-way-with-words-and-other-people-oh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people have a way with words, and other people...oh, uh, not have way." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
