<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85761-mike]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85761-mike" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 12:13:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 12:13:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are careful,' Garp wrote, 'if you use good ingredients, and you don't take any shortcuts, then you can usually cook something very good. Sometimes it is the only worthwhile product you can salvage from a day; what you make to eat. With writing, I find, you can have all the right ingredients, give plenty of time and care, and still get nothing. Also true of love. Cooking, therefore, can keep a person who tries hard sane." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46946-in-a-world-where-you-are-constantly-asked-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 11:14:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46946-in-a-world-where-you-are-constantly-asked-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a world where you are constantly asked to be 'committed,' it is liberating to give yourself the license to be a dilettante. Commit to nothing. Try everything." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46947-guilt-is-also-a-way-for-us-to-express-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 11:16:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46947-guilt-is-also-a-way-for-us-to-express-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Guilt is also a way for us to express to others that we are a person of good conscience. 'I feel really guilty about getting drunk last night,' we say, when in actual fact we feel no guilt whatsoever or, at least, we could &lt;i&gt;choose&lt;/i&gt; to feel no guilt. When people say to me, 'I drank too much last night,' I always reply, 'I drank exactly the right amount." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47282-w-e-should-be-mucking-about-all-the-time-because-mucking</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 13:40:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47282-w-e-should-be-mucking-about-all-the-time-because-mucking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[W]e should be mucking about all the time, because mucking about is enjoying life for its own sake, now, and not in preparation for an imaginary future. It's obvious that the mirth-filled man, the cheerful soul, the childish adult is the one who has least to fear from life." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48509-beauty-feeds-us-anarchy-is-beauty-we-are-against-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 20:12:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48509-beauty-feeds-us-anarchy-is-beauty-we-are-against-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty feeds us. Anarchy is beauty. We are against the grey people. We want to decorate, like those fantastic Indian lorries which are covered with flowers. Beauty must conquer the lust for order; order is ugliness." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2008 20:12:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53465-what-art-seeks-to-disturb-is-monotony-of-type-slavery</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53465-what-art-seeks-to-disturb-is-monotony-of-type-slavery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What art seeks to disturb is monotony of type, slavery of custom, tyranny of habit, and the reduction of man to the level of a machine." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53468-there-is-nothing-so-perfect-as-pinball-and-a-pint</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:43:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53468-there-is-nothing-so-perfect-as-pinball-and-a-pint]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing so perfect as pinball and a pint at 11 a.m." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53476-sensible-people-advise-against-drinking-on-an-empty-stomach-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53476-sensible-people-advise-against-drinking-on-an-empty-stomach-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sensible people advise against drinking on an empty stomach, but to my mind it is the best sort of drinking." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53477-paradoxically-to-be-truly-idle-you-also-have-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53477-paradoxically-to-be-truly-idle-you-also-have-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Paradoxically, to be truly idle, you also have to be efficient." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3046-i-tell-you-we-are-here-on-earth-to-fart</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 20:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3046-i-tell-you-we-are-here-on-earth-to-fart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tell you, we are here on Earth to fart around, and don't let anybody tell you different." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69201-i-m-in-no-position-to-hand-down-any-advice-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69201-i-m-in-no-position-to-hand-down-any-advice-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm in no position to hand down any advice,&quot; he said, &quot;but there's a rule I follow when I don't know what to do.&quot;

&quot;A rule?&quot;

&quot;If you have to choose between something that has form and something that doesn't, go for the one without form. That's my rule. Whenever I run into a wall I follow that rule, and it always works out. Even if it's hard going at the time." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74655-there-is-evidence-that-the-honoree-leonard-cohen-might-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 08:33:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74655-there-is-evidence-that-the-honoree-leonard-cohen-might-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is evidence that the honoree [Leonard Cohen] might be privy to the secret of the universe, which, in case you're wondering, is simply this: Everything is connected. &lt;i&gt;Everything&lt;/i&gt;. Many, if not most, of the links are difficult to determine. The instrument, the apparatus, the focused ray that can uncover and illuminate those connections is language." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74657-our-great-human-adventure-is-the-evolution-of-consciousness-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2008 08:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74657-our-great-human-adventure-is-the-evolution-of-consciousness-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our great human adventure is the evolution of consciousness. We are in this life to enlarge the soul, liberate the spirit, and light up the brain." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79891-as-my-friend-jeremy-gilbert-rolfe-has-argued-persuasively-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 20:09:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79891-as-my-friend-jeremy-gilbert-rolfe-has-argued-persuasively-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As my friend Jeremy Gilbert-Rolfe has argued persuasively, there is an element of positivity in the visible world, and in color particularly, that totally eludes the historicity of language, with its protocols of absence and polarity. The color red, as an attribute of the world, is always there. It is something other than the absence of yellow and blue--and, thus, when that red becomes less red, it becomes &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; one or the other. It never exists in a linguistic condition of degradation or excess that must necessarily derive from our expectations." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 21:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79912-jazz-presumes-that-it-would-be-nice-if-the-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jazz presumes that it would be nice if the four of us--simpatico dudes that we are--while playing this complicated song together, might somehow be free and autonomous as well. Tragically, this never quite works out. At best, we can only be free one or two at a time--while the other dudes hold onto the wire. Which is not to say that no one has tried to dispense with wires. Many have, and sometimes it works--but it doesn't feel like &lt;i&gt;jazz&lt;/i&gt; when it does. The music simply drifts away into the stratosphere of formal dialectic, beyond our social concerns.

Rock-and-roll, on the other hand, presumes that the four of us--as damaged and anti-social as we are--might possibly get it &lt;i&gt;to-fucking-gether&lt;/i&gt;, man, and play this simple song. And play it right, okay? Just this once, in tune and on the beat. But we can't. The song's too simple, and we're too complicated and too excited. We try like hell, but the guitars distort, the intonation bends, and the beat just moves, imperceptibly, against our formal expectations, whetehr we want it to or not. Just because we're &lt;i&gt;breathing&lt;/i&gt;, man. Thus, in the process of trying to play this very simple song together, we create this hurricane of noise, this infinitely complicated, fractal filigree of delicate distinctions.

And you can thank the wanking eighties, if you wish, and digital sequencers, too, for proving to everyone that technologically &quot;perfect&quot; rock--like &quot;free&quot; jazz--sucks rockets. Because order sucks. I mean, look at the Stones. Keith Richards is &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; on top of the beat, and Bill Wyman, until he quit, was always behind it, because Richards is leading the band and Charlie Watts is listening to him and Wyman is listening to Watts. So the beat is sliding on those tiny neural lapses, not so you can tell, of course, but so you can feel it in your stomach. And the intonation is wavering, too, with the pulse in the finger on the amplified string. This is the delicacy of rock-and-roll, the bodily rhetoric of tiny increments, necessary imperfections, and contingent community. And it has its virtues, because jazz only works if we're trying to be free and are, in fact, together. Rock-and-roll works because we're all a bunch of flakes. That's something you can &lt;i&gt;depend&lt;/i&gt; on, and a good thing too, because in the twentieth century, that's all there is: jazz and rock-and-roll. The rest is term papers and advertising." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79916-i-cannot-tell-you-how-many-quiet-mornings-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2008 21:39:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Dave Hickey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79916-i-cannot-tell-you-how-many-quiet-mornings-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot tell you how many quiet mornings I have spent sitting around hotel rooms and furnished apartments in the United States and Mexico, smoking cigarettes, plunking the guitar, and watching &lt;i&gt;Perry Mason&lt;/i&gt;--telling myself, &quot;Well, at least I don't have a day job. And there is nothing wrong with that. I am not guilty of anything. Perry would see that in a minute." -- Dave Hickey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109102-straightening-himself-and-stealthily-fingering-his-pocket-knife-he-started-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 14:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109102-straightening-himself-and-stealthily-fingering-his-pocket-knife-he-started-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Straightening himself and stealthily fingering his pocket-knife he started after her to follow this woman, this excitement, which seemed even with its back turned to shed on him a light which connected them, which singled him out, as if the random uproar of the traffic had whispered through hallowed hands his name, not Peter, but his private name which he called himself in his own thoughts." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109103-such-are-the-visions-which-proffer-great-cornucopias-full-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 14:57:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109103-such-are-the-visions-which-proffer-great-cornucopias-full-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Such are the visions which proffer great cornucopias full of fruit to the solitary traveller, or murmur in his ear like sirens lolloping away on the green sea waves, or are dashed in his face like bunches of roses, or rise to the surface like pale faces which fishermen flounder through floods to embrace." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109104-for-this-is-the-truth-about-our-soul-he-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 14:59:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109104-for-this-is-the-truth-about-our-soul-he-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For this is the truth about our soul, he thought, who fish-like inhabits deep seas and plies among obscurities threading her way between the boles of giant weeds, over sun-flickered spaces and on and on into gloom, cold, deep, inscrutable; suddenly she shoots to the surface and sports on the wind-wrinkled waves; that is, has a positive need to brush, scrape, kindle herself, gossiping." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109105-the-cold-stream-of-visual-impressions-failed-him-now-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2008 15:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109105-the-cold-stream-of-visual-impressions-failed-him-now-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cold stream of visual impressions failed him now as if the eye were a cup that overflowed and let the rest run down its china walls unrecorded." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111756-undressing-her-was-an-act-of-recklessness-a-kind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 10:08:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111756-undressing-her-was-an-act-of-recklessness-a-kind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Undressing her was an act of recklessness, a kind of vandalism, like releasing a zoo full of animals, or blowing up a dam." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111757-it-struck-me-that-the-chief-obstacle-to-marital-contentment</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 10:12:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111757-it-struck-me-that-the-chief-obstacle-to-marital-contentment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It struck me that the chief obstacle to marital contentment was this perpetual gulf between the well-founded, commendable pessimism of women and the sheer dumb animal optimism of men, the latter a force more than any other responsible for the lamentable state of the world." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12411-when-the-immense-drugged-universe-explodes-in-a-cascade-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 10:13:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Robert Graves]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12411-when-the-immense-drugged-universe-explodes-in-a-cascade-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the immense drugged universe explodes
In a cascade of unendurable colour
And leaves us gasping naked,
This is no more than the ectasy of chaos:
Hold fast, with both hands, to that royal love
Which alone, as we know certainly, restores
Fragmentation into true being.

Ecstasy of Chaos" -- Robert Graves]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55023-what-is-perceptible-to-one-s-mistrust-is-the-cut-and-dried-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 10:13:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Robert Musil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55023-what-is-perceptible-to-one-s-mistrust-is-the-cut-and-dried-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is perceptible to one’s mistrust is the cut-and-dried way that life is divided up and the ready-made form it assumes, the ever-recurring sameness of it, the pre-formations passed down by generation after generation, the ready-made language not only of the tongue but also of the sensations and the feelings. " -- Robert Musil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10410-to-love-is-to-suffer-to-avoid-suffering-one-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 10:15:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10410-to-love-is-to-suffer-to-avoid-suffering-one-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love is to suffer. To avoid suffering one must not love. But then one suffers from not loving. Therefore, to love is to suffer; not to love is to suffer; to suffer is to suffer. To be happy is to love. To be happy, then, is to suffer, but suffering makes one unhappy. Therefore, to be happy one must love or love to suffer or suffer from too much happiness." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209536-we-are-accused-of-being-obsessed-by-property-the-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 09:12:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by John Berger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209536-we-are-accused-of-being-obsessed-by-property-the-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are accused of being obsessed by property. The truth is the other way round. It is the society and culture in question which is so obsessed. Yet to an obsessive his obsession always seems to be of the nature of things and so is not recognized for what it is. The relation between property and art in European culture appears natural to that culture, and consequently if somebody demonstrates the extent of the property interest in a given cultural field, it is said to be a demonstration of &lt;i&gt;his&lt;/i&gt; obsession. And this allows the Cultural Establishment to project for a little longer its false rationalized image of itself." -- John Berger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26200-i-count-it-as-an-absolute-certainty-that-in-paradise</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 09:13:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26200-i-count-it-as-an-absolute-certainty-that-in-paradise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I count it as an absolute certainty that in paradise, everyone naps. A nap is a perfect pleasure and it's useful, too. It splits the day into two halves, making each half more manageable and enjoyable. How much easier it is to work in the morning if we know we have a nap to look forward to after lunch; and how much more pleasant the late afternoon and evening become after a little sleep. If you know there is a nap to come later in the day, then you can banish forever that terrible sense of doom one feels at 9 A.M. with eight hours of straight toil ahead. Not only that, but a nap can offer a glimpse into a twilight nether world where gods play and dreams happen." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122543-labour-saving-devices-just-make-us-try-to-cram-more-pointless</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 09:13:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122543-labour-saving-devices-just-make-us-try-to-cram-more-pointless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Labour-saving devices just make us try to cram more pointless activities into each day, rather than doing the important thing, which is to enjoy our life." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122541-idleness-for-me-is-not-a-giving-up-on-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2009 09:13:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122541-idleness-for-me-is-not-a-giving-up-on-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Idleness for me is not a giving up on life but a spirited grabbing hold of it." -- Tom Hodgkinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
