<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85777-joanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/85777-joanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 06:55:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299339-in-most-books-the-i-or-first-person-is-omitted</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2012 06:55:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299339-in-most-books-the-i-or-first-person-is-omitted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In most books, the I, or first person, is omitted; in this it will be retained; that, in respect to egotism, is the main difference. We commonly do not remember that it is, after all, always the first person that is speaking. I should not talk so much about myself if there were anybody else whom I knew as well. Unfortunately, I am confined to this theme by the narrowness of my experience. Moreover, I, on my side, require of every writer, first or last, a simple and sincere account of his own life, and not merely what he has heard of other men's lives; some such account as he would send to his kindred from a distant land; for if he has lived sincerely, it must have been in a distant land to me. Perhaps these pages are more particularly addressed to poor students. As for the rest of my readers, they will accept such portions as apply to them. I trust that none will stretch the seams in putting on the coat, for it may do good service to him whom it fits." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 22:20:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Federico García Lorca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460006-to-burn-with-desire-and-keep-quiet-about-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To burn with desire and keep quiet about it is the greatest punishment we can bring on ourselves." -- Federico García Lorca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200951-i-am-an-instrument-in-the-shape-of-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 13:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Adrienne Rich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200951-i-am-an-instrument-in-the-shape-of-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am an instrument in the shape/ of a woman trying to translate pulsations/ into images for the relief of the body/ and the reconstruction of the mind." -- Adrienne Rich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245726-in-the-night-i-come-to-you-and-it-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 07:24:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Carolyn Forche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245726-in-the-night-i-come-to-you-and-it-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the night I come to you and it seems a shame   
to waste my deepest shudders on a wall of a man." -- Carolyn Forche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 18:12:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Judith Butler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54041-let-s-face-it-we-re-undone-by-each-other-and-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's face it. We're undone by each other. And if we're not, we're missing something. If this seems so clearly the case with grief, it is only because it was already the case with desire. One does not always stay intact. It may be that one wants to, or does, but it may also be that despite one's best efforts, one is undone, in the face of the other, by the touch, by the scent, by the feel, by the prospect of the touch, by the memory of the feel. And so when we speak about my sexuality or my gender, as we do (and as we must), we mean something complicated by it. Neither of these is precisely a possession, but both are to be understood as modes of being dispossessed, ways of being for another, or, indeed, by virtue of another." -- Judith Butler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222904-a-large-part-of-the-popularity-and-persuasiveness-of-psychology</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 20:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222904-a-large-part-of-the-popularity-and-persuasiveness-of-psychology]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A large part of the popularity and persuasiveness of psychology comes from its being a sublimated spiritualism: a secular, ostensibly scientific way of affirming the primacy of spirit over matter." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830-today-everything-exists-to-end-in-a-photograph</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 20:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/830-today-everything-exists-to-end-in-a-photograph]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today everything exists to end in a photograph." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171854-a-good-book-is-an-education-of-the-heart-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 20:29:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171854-a-good-book-is-an-education-of-the-heart-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good book is an education of the heart. It enlarges your sense of human possibility what human nature is of what happens in the world. It's a creator of inwardness." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249188-what-i-really-wanted-was-every-kind-of-life-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2013 21:35:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249188-what-i-really-wanted-was-every-kind-of-life-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I really wanted was every kind of life, and the writer’s life seemed the most inclusive." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2843-i-wanted-her-to-see-that-the-only-life-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 22:37:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Pam Houston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2843-i-wanted-her-to-see-that-the-only-life-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted her to see that the only life worth living is a life full of love; that loss is always part of the equation; that love and loss conjoined are the best opportunity we get to live fully, to be our strongest, our most compassionate, our most graceful selves. " -- Pam Houston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375744-all-men-make-mistakes-but-a-good-man-yields-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:08:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Sophocles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/375744-all-men-make-mistakes-but-a-good-man-yields-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men make mistakes, but a good man yields when he knows his course is wrong, and repairs the evil. The only crime is pride." -- Sophocles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21686-a-man-though-wise-should-never-be-ashamed-of-learning</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 10:08:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Sophocles]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21686-a-man-though-wise-should-never-be-ashamed-of-learning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man, though wise, should never be ashamed of learning more, and must unbend his mind." -- Sophocles]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234703-we-have-to-recognise-that-there-cannot-be-relationships-unless</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:05:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234703-we-have-to-recognise-that-there-cannot-be-relationships-unless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to recognise that there cannot be relationships unless there is commitment, unless there is loyalty, unless there is love, patience, persistence." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279991-never-forget-that-justice-is-what-love-looks-like-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:05:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/279991-never-forget-that-justice-is-what-love-looks-like-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never forget that justice is what love looks like in public" -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49495-you-can-t-lead-the-people-if-you-don-t-love-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:05:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49495-you-can-t-lead-the-people-if-you-don-t-love-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't lead the people if you don't love the people.  You can't save the people if you don't serve the people." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245290-i-cannot-be-an-optimist-but-i-am-a-prisoner</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:05:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245290-i-cannot-be-an-optimist-but-i-am-a-prisoner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot be an optimist but I am a prisoner of hope." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21280-nihilism-is-a-natural-consequence-of-a-culture-or-civilization</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:06:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21280-nihilism-is-a-natural-consequence-of-a-culture-or-civilization]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nihilism is a natural consequence of a culture (or civilization) ruled and regulated by categories that mask manipulation, mastery and domination of peoples and nature." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161702-to-be-a-christian-is-to-live-dangerously-honestly-freely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:06:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161702-to-be-a-christian-is-to-live-dangerously-honestly-freely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a Christian is to live dangerously, honestly, freely - to step in the name of love as if you may land on nothing, yet to keep on stepping because the something that sustains you no empire can give you and no empire can take away." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16013-white-supremacist-ideology-is-based-first-and-foremost-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:07:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16013-white-supremacist-ideology-is-based-first-and-foremost-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["White supremacist ideology is based first and foremost on the degradation of black bodies in order to control them. One of the best ways to instill fear in people is to terrorize them. Yet this fear is best sustained by convincing them that their bodies are ugly, their intellect is inherently underdeveloped, their culture is less civilized, and their future warrants less concern than that of other peoples." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78819-market-moralities-and-mentalities---fueled-by-economic-imperatives-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:07:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78819-market-moralities-and-mentalities---fueled-by-economic-imperatives-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Market moralities and mentalities-- fueled by economic imperatives to make a profit at nearly any cost-- yield unprecedented levels of loneliness, isolation, and sadness. And our public life lies in shambles, shot through with icy cynicism and paralyzing pessimism. To put it bluntly, beneath the record-breaking stock markets on Wall Street and bipartisan budget-balancing deals in the White House lurk ominous clouds of despair across this nation." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625924-we-re-beings-toward-death-we-re-two-legged-linguistically-conscious-creatures-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:08:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Cornel West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625924-we-re-beings-toward-death-we-re-two-legged-linguistically-conscious-creatures-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re beings toward death, we’re … two-legged, linguistically-conscious creatures born between urine and feces whose body will one day be the culinary delight of terrestrial worms." -- Cornel West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395456-organizations-for-writers-palliate-the-writer-s-loneliness-but-i-doubt</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 15:13:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395456-organizations-for-writers-palliate-the-writer-s-loneliness-but-i-doubt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Organizations for writers palliate the writer's loneliness, but I doubt if they improve his writing.... For he does his work alone and if he is a good enough writer he must face eternity, or the lack of it, each day." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308240-often-black-people-especially-non-gay-folk-become-enraged-when-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 07:09:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joanna add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308240-often-black-people-especially-non-gay-folk-become-enraged-when-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often black people, especially non-gay folk, become enraged when they hear a white person who is gay suggest homosexuality is synonymous with the suffering people experience as a consequence of racial exploitation and oppression. The need to make gay experience and black experience of oppression synonymous seems to be one that surfaces much more in the minds of white people. Too often it is a way of minimizing or diminishing the particular problems people of color face in a white supremacist society, especially the problems ones encounter because they do not have white skin. Many of us have been in discussions where a non-white person – a black person – struggles to explain to white folks that while we can acknowledge that gay people of all colors are harassed and suffer exploitation and domination, we also recognize that there is a significant difference that arises because of the visibility of dark skin. Often homophobic attacks on gay people of all occur in situations where knowledge of sexual preference is established – outside of gay bars, for example. While it in no way lessens the severity of such suffering for gay people, or the fear that it causes, it does mean that in a given situation the apparatus of protection and survival may be simply not identifying as gay.

In contrast, most people of color have no choice. No one can hide, change or mask dark skin color. White people, gay and straight, could show greater understanding of the impact of racial oppression on people of color by not attempting to make these oppressions synonymous, but rather by showing the ways they are linked and yet differ. Concurrently, the attempt by white people to make synonymous experience of homophobic aggression with racial oppression deflects attention away from the particular dual dilemma that non-white gay people face, as individuals who confront both racism and homophobia." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
