<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/858056-anna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/858056-anna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:08:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57738-each-contact-with-a-human-being-is-so-rare-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:08:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57738-each-contact-with-a-human-being-is-so-rare-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each contact with a human being is so rare, so precious, one should preserve it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57756-if-i-could-have-any-job-in-the-world-i-d</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:19:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57756-if-i-could-have-any-job-in-the-world-i-d]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I could have any job in the world I'd be a professional Cinderella." -- Susanna Kaysen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57759-the-true-harvest-of-my-life-is-intangible---a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:21:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57759-the-true-harvest-of-my-life-is-intangible---a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true harvest of my life is intangible - a little star dust caught, a portion of the rainbow I have clutched." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2009 05:37:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57763-magic-can-be-found-in-stolen-moments</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2008 19:35:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57763-magic-can-be-found-in-stolen-moments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Magic can be found in stolen moments." -- Francesca Lia Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 20:59:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36496-she-was-lo-plain-lo-in-the-morning-standing-four]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 20:59:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32046-lolita-light-of-my-life-fire-of-my-loins-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lolita, light of my life, fire of my loins. My sin, my soul. Lo-lee-ta: the tip of the tongue taking a trip of three steps down the palate to tap, at three, on the teeth. Lo. Lee. Ta. She was Lo, plain Lo, in the morning, standing four feet ten in one sock. She was Lola in slacks. She was Dolly at school. She was Dolores on the dotted line. But in my arms she was always Lolita. Did she have a precursor? She did, indeed she did. In point of fact, there might have been no Lolita at all had I not loved, one summer, an initial girl-child. In a princedom by the sea. Oh when? About as many years before Lolita was born as my age was that summer. You can always count on a murderer for a fancy prose style. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, exhibit number one is what the seraphs, the misinformed, simple, noble-winged seraphs, envied. Look at this tangle of thorns." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 21:04:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 16:28:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 12:52:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Anna add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127614-he-awoke-each-morning-with-the-desire-to-do-right]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He awoke each morning with the desire to do right, to be a good and meaningful person, to be, as simple as it sounded and as impossible as it actually was, happy. And during the course of each day his heart would descend from his chest into his stomach. By early afternoon he was overcome by the feeling that nothing was right, or nothing was right for him, and by the desire to be alone. By evening he was fulfilled: alone in the magnitude of his grief, alone in his aimless guilt, alone even in his loneliness. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad,&lt;/i&gt; he would repeat to himself over and over, &lt;i&gt;I am not sad&lt;/i&gt;. As if he might one day convince himself. Or fool himself. Or convince others--the only thing worse than being sad is for others to know that you are sad. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad. I am not sad. &lt;/i&gt;Because his life had unlimited potential for happiness, insofar as it was an empty white room. He would fall asleep with his heart at the foot of his bed, like some domesticated animal that was no part of him at all. And each morning he would wake with it again in the cupboard of his rib cage, having become a little heavier, a little weaker, but still pumping. And by the midafternoon he was again overcome with the desire to be somewhere else, someone else, someone else somewhere else. &lt;i&gt;I am not sad.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
