<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859395-kelly-marques]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859395-kelly-marques" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 17:49:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142577-why-why-does-what-was-beautiful-suddenly-shatter-in-hindsight</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 17:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142577-why-why-does-what-was-beautiful-suddenly-shatter-in-hindsight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why? Why does what was beautiful suddenly shatter in hindsight because it concealed dark truths? Why does the memory of years of happy marriage turn to gall when our partner is revealed to have had a lover all those years? Because such a situation makes it impossible to be happy? But we were happy! Sometimes the memory of happiness cannot stay true because it ended unhappily. Because happiness is only real if it lasts forever? Because things always end painfully if they contained pain, conscious or unconscious, all along? But what is unconscious, unrecognized pain?" -- Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180120-i-m-not-frightened-i-m-not-frightened-of-anything-the-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 17:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180120-i-m-not-frightened-i-m-not-frightened-of-anything-the-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm not frightened. I'm not frightened of anything. The more I suffer, the more I love. Danger will only increase my love. It will sharpen it, forgive its vice. I will be the only angel you need. You will leave life even more beautiful than you entered it. Heaven will take you back and look at you and say: Only one thing can make a soul complete and that thing is love." -- Bernhard Schlink]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30515-i-was-in-the-fifth-grade-the-first-time-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 11:00:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30515-i-was-in-the-fifth-grade-the-first-time-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was in the fifth grade the first time I thought about turning thirty. My best friend Darcy and I came across a perpetual calendar in the back of the phone book, where you could look up any date in the future, and by using this little grid, determine what the day of the week would be. So we located our birthdays in the following year, mine in May and hers in September. I got Wednesday, a school night. She got a Friday. A small victory, but typical. Darcy was always the lucky one. Her skin tanned more quickly, her hair feathered more easily, and she didn't need braces. Her moonwalk was superior, as were her cart-wheels and her front handsprings (I couldn't handspring at all). She had a better sticker collection. More Michael Jackson pins. Forenze sweaters in turquoise, red, and peach (my mother allowed me none- said they were too trendy and expensive). And a pair of fifty-dollar Guess jeans with zippers at the ankles (ditto). Darcy had double-pierced ears and a sibling- even if it was just a brother, it was better than being an only child as I was.

But at least I was a few months older and she would never quite catch up. That's when I decided to check out my thirtieth birthday- in a year so far away that it sounded like science fiction. It fell on a Sunday, which meant that my dashing husband and I would secure a responsible baby-sitter for our two (possibly three) children on that Saturday evening, dine at a fancy French restaurant with cloth napkins, and stay out past midnight, so technically we would be celebrating on my actual birthday. I would have just won a big case- somehow proven that an innocent man didn't do it. And my husband would toast me: &quot;To Rachel, my beautiful wife, the mother of my chidren and the finest lawyer in Indy.&quot; I shared my fantasy with Darcy as we discovered that her thirtieth birthday fell on a Monday. Bummer for her. I watched her purse her lips as she processed this information.

&quot;You know, Rachel, who cares what day of the week we turn thirty?&quot; she said, shrugging a smooth, olive shoulder. &quot;We'll be old by then. Birthdays don't matter when you get that old.&quot;

I thought of my parents, who were in their thirties, and their lackluster approach to their own birthdays. My dad had just given my mom a toaster for her birthday because ours broke the week before. The new one toasted four slices at a time instead of just two. It wasn't much of a gift. But my mom had seemed pleased enough with her new appliance; nowhere did I detect the disappointment that I felt when my Christmas stash didn't quite meet expectations. So Darcy was probably right. Fun stuff like birthdays wouldn't matter as much by the time we reached thirty.

The next time I really thought about being thirty was our senior year in high school, when Darcy and I started watching ths show Thirty Something together. It wasn't our favorite- we preferred cheerful sit-coms like Who's the Boss? and Growing Pains- but we watched it anyway. My big problem with Thirty Something was the whiny characters and their depressing issues that they seemed to bring upon themselves. I remember thinking that they should grow up, suck it up. Stop pondering the meaning of life and start making grocery lists. That was back when I thought my teenage years were dragging and my twenties would surealy last forever.

Then I reached my twenties. And the early twenties did seem to last forever. When I heard acquaintances a few years older lament the end of their youth, I felt smug, not yet in the danger zone myself. I had plenty of time.." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28504-be-glad-be-good-be-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 18:35:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Eleanor Hodgman Porter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28504-be-glad-be-good-be-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be glad. Be good. Be brave." -- Eleanor Hodgman Porter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 17:39:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
