<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859446-rochelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859446-rochelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:50:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123439-i-love-libraries-i-love-books-there-is-something-sacred</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:50:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123439-i-love-libraries-i-love-books-there-is-something-sacred]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love libraries. I love books. There is something sacred, I think, about a great library because it represents the preservation of the wisdom, the learning, the pondering, of men and women of all the ages accumulated together under one roof to which we can have access as our needs require." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76862-it-s-not-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:50:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76862-it-s-not-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not as bad as you sometimes think it is. It ALL works out. Don't worry. I say that to myself every morning. It will all work out. If you do your best, it all works out. Put your trust in God and move forward, with faith and confidence in the future. The lord will not forsake us... If we put our trust in him, if we will pray to him, if we will live worthy of his blessings, He will hear our prayers." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230335-believe-in-yourself-believe-in-your-capacity-to-do-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:50:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230335-believe-in-yourself-believe-in-your-capacity-to-do-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Believe in yourself.  Believe in your capacity to do great and good things.  Believe that no mountain is so high that you cannot climb it.  Believe that no storm is so great that you cannot weather it.  You are not destined to be a scrub.  You are a child of God, of infinite capacity.

Believe that you can do it whatever it is that you set your heart on.  Opportunities will unfold and open before you.  The skies will clear when they have been dark with portent...He who is our Eternal Father has blessed you with miraculous powers of mind and body.  He never intended that you should be less than the crowning glory of His creations." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147781-under-the-plan-of-heaven-the-husband-and-the-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147781-under-the-plan-of-heaven-the-husband-and-the-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Under the plan of heaven, the husband and the wife walk side by side as companions, neither one ahead of the other, but a daughter of God and a son of God walking side by side. Let your families be families of love and peace and happiness. Gather your children around you and have your family home evenings, teach your children the ways of the Lord, read to them from the scriptures, and let them come to know the great truths of the eternal gospel as set forth in these words of the Almighty." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209839-my-plea-is-that-we-stop-seeking-out-the-storms</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:51:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209839-my-plea-is-that-we-stop-seeking-out-the-storms]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My plea is that we stop seeking out the storms and enjoy more fully the sunlight...I am asking that we look a little deeper for the good, that we still our voices of insult and sarcasm, that we more generously compliment and endorse virtue and effort." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273466-we-ve-got-to-have-a-little-humor-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:52:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273466-we-ve-got-to-have-a-little-humor-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’ve got to have a little humor in our lives. You had better take seriously that which should be taken seriously but, at the same time, we can bring in a touch of humor now and again. If the time ever comes when we can’t smile at ourselves, it will be a sad time." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/433401-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:54:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/433401-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who imagines that bliss is normal is going to waste a lot of time running around shouting that he’s been robbed.  The fact is that most putts don’t drop, most beef is tough, most children grow up to just be people, most successful marriages require a high degree of mutual toleration, most jobs are more often dull than otherwise.  Life is like an old time rail journey…delays…sidetracks,  smoke, dust, cinders and jolts, interspersed only occasionally by beautiful vistas and thrilling burst of speed.  The trick is to thank the Lord for letting you have the ride." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131915-it-s-true-isn-t-it-then-what-else-really-matters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:55:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131915-it-s-true-isn-t-it-then-what-else-really-matters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s true, isn’t it? Then what else really matters?" -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:58:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:59:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We women have a lot to learn about simplifying our lives.  We have to decide what is important and then move along at a pace that is comfortable for us.  We have to develop the maturity to stop trying to prove something.  We have to learn to be content with what we are." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 21:59:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it is hard for you young mothers to believe that almost before you can turn around the children will be gone and you will be alone with your husband.  You had better be sure you are developing the kind of love and friendship that will be delightful and enduring.  Let the children learn from your attitude that he is important.  Encourage him.  Be kind.  It is a rough world, and he, like everyone else, is fighting to survive.  Be cheerful.  Don't be a whiner." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533533-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 22:11:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533533-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to get through life is to laugh your way through it. You either have to laugh or cry. I prefer to laugh. Crying gives me a headache.”


“I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133018-many-more-people-could-ride-out-the-storm-tossed-waves-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 22:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rochelle add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133018-many-more-people-could-ride-out-the-storm-tossed-waves-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many more people could ride out the storm-tossed waves in their economic lives if they had their year's supply of food…and were debt-free. Today we find that many have followed this counsel in reverse: they have at least a year's supply of debt and are food-free." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
