<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859535-clinton]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/859535-clinton" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 09:14:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337712-from-this-distant-vantage-point-the-earth-might-not-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 09:14:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clinton add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/337712-from-this-distant-vantage-point-the-earth-might-not-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From this distant vantage point, the Earth might not seem of particular interest. But for us, it's different. Consider again that dot. That's here, that's home, that's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there – on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena. Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot. Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.     

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.     

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet. Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.     

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309633-toska---noun-t--sk---russian-word-roughly-translated-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 20:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clinton add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309633-toska---noun-t--sk---russian-word-roughly-translated-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Toska - noun /ˈtō-skə/ - Russian word roughly translated as sadness, melancholia, lugubriousness.

&quot;No single word in English renders all the shades of toska. At its deepest and most painful, it is a sensation of great spiritual anguish, often without any specific cause. At less morbid levels it is a dull ache of the soul, a longing with nothing to long for, a sick pining, a vague restlessness, mental throes, yearning. In particular cases it may be the desire for somebody of something specific, nostalgia, love-sickness. At the lowest level it grades into ennui, boredom." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36729-one-should-always-be-drunk-that-s-all-that-matters-but-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 14:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clinton add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36729-one-should-always-be-drunk-that-s-all-that-matters-but-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One should always be drunk. That's all that matters...But with what? With wine, with poetry, or with virtue, as you chose. But get drunk." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677019-if-you-are-trying-to-decide-among-a-few-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 09:00:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Clinton add a quote by Jason Fried]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677019-if-you-are-trying-to-decide-among-a-few-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are trying to decide among a few people to fill a position hire the best writer. it doesn't matter if the person is marketer, salesperson, designer, programmer, or whatever, their writing skills will pay off. That's because being a good writer is about more than writing clear writing. Clear writing is a sign of clear thinking. great writers know how to communicate. they make things easy to understand. they can put themselves in someone else's shoes. they know what to omit. And those are qualities you want in any candidate. Writing is making a comeback all over our society... Writing is today's currency for good ideas." -- Jason Fried]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
