<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/860192-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/860192-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:56:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20486-there-are-times-when-solitude-is-better-than-society-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:56:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20486-there-are-times-when-solitude-is-better-than-society-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are times when solitude is better than society, and silence is wiser than speech. We should be better Christians if we were more alone, waiting upon God, and gathering through meditation on His Word spiritual strength for labour in his service. We ought to muse upon the things of God, because we thus get the real nutriment out of them. . . . Why is it that some Christians, although they hear many sermons, make but slow advances in the divine life? Because they neglect their closets, and do not thoughtfully meditate on God's Word. They love the wheat, but they do not grind it; they would have the corn, but they will not go forth into the fields to gather it; the fruit hangs upon the tree, but they will not pluck it; the water flows at their feet, but they will not stoop to drink it. From such folly deliver us, O Lord. . . ." -- Charles Spurgeon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16473-i-want-the-presence-of-god-himself-or-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:56:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by A.W. Tozer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16473-i-want-the-presence-of-god-himself-or-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want the presence of God Himself, or I don't want anything at all to do with religion... I want all that God has or I don't want any." -- A.W. Tozer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2919-he-is-no-fool-who-gives-what-he-cannot-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:56:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Jim Elliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2919-he-is-no-fool-who-gives-what-he-cannot-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is no fool who gives what he cannot keep to gain that which he cannot lose." -- Jim Elliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12747-wherever-you-are-be-all-there-live-to-the-hilt</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 09:56:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Jim Elliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12747-wherever-you-are-be-all-there-live-to-the-hilt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wherever you are, be all there! Live to the hilt every situation you believe to be the will of God." -- Jim Elliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 23:37:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 10:09:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30-that-which-does-not-kill-us-makes-us-stronger]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which does not kill us makes us stronger." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
