<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/860128-zak]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/860128-zak" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 10:00:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142714-there-are-many-self-proclaimed-screenwriting-gurus-though-how-you-get-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 10:00:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zak add a quote by Thomas Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1142714-there-are-many-self-proclaimed-screenwriting-gurus-though-how-you-get-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many self-proclaimed “screenwriting gurus”—though how you get to be a “guru” of something you’ve never actually done is beyond us. Screenplays are like blueprints. A guy who’s drawn up a lot of blueprints that have never actually been made into buildings is not an “architecture guru,” he’s an “unemployed douchebag.” A guy who talks about screen-writing but who’s never sold a screenplay is not a “screenwriting guru,” he’s a “lecture circuit bullshit artist.” From now on, that’s what we’ll call them." -- Thomas Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149984-the-burg-of-maker-s-bell-lives-on-that-line-between</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2014 01:07:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zak add a quote by Chuck Wendig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1149984-the-burg-of-maker-s-bell-lives-on-that-line-between]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the burg of Maker’s Bell lives on that line between rural and suburban, between farmland and white picket fences" -- Chuck Wendig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253891-actors-always-want-to-know-how-i-come-up-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 08:47:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Zak add a quote by Harold Guskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253891-actors-always-want-to-know-how-i-come-up-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Actors always want to know how I come up with interesting and creative takes on characters, characters that aren’t like me as I appear in daily life and that aren’t like each other. It’s simple: I let the lines and images connect with my imagination. I don’t worry about consistency; I let myself respond moment by moment, piecemeal, to the character’s dialogue and actions. Then I let my responses take me wherever they go, making mistakes and discarding them until choices start repeating themselves on their own no matter how arbitrary they seem at first. Then I know I’m on to something. But I don’t try to put the character together. I leave it in pieces. The script and story put the character together so my moment by moment performance seems like a creative take on the whole character." -- Harold Guskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
