<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/861650-laura]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/861650-laura" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 16:21:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29376-animals-are-more-than-ever-a-test-of-our-character</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 16:21:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Matthew Scully]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29376-animals-are-more-than-ever-a-test-of-our-character]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Animals are more than ever a test of our character, of mankind's capacity for empathy and for decent, honorable conduct and faithful stewardship.  We are called to treat them with kindness, not because they have rights or power or some claim to equality, but in a sense because they don't; because they all stand unequal and powerless before us." -- Matthew Scully]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45426-the-circus-is-a-jealous-wench-indeed-that-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:20:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Henry Ringling North]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45426-the-circus-is-a-jealous-wench-indeed-that-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The circus is a jealous wench. Indeed that is an understatement. She is a ravening hag who sucks your vitality as a vampire drinks blood – who kills the brightest stars in her crown and will allow no private life for those who serve her; wrecking their homes, ruining their bodies, and destroying the happiness of their loved ones by her insatiable demands. She is all of these things, and yet, I love her as I love nothing else on earth." -- Henry Ringling North]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89286-for-several-thousand-years-man-has-been-in-contact-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Hans Brick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89286-for-several-thousand-years-man-has-been-in-contact-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For several thousand years man has been in contact with animals whose character and habits have been deformed by domestication.  He has ended by believing that he understands them.  All he means by this is that he is able to rely on certain reflex actions which he himself has implanted in them.  He will flatter himself at times on the grasp of animal psychology which has brought him the love of the dog and the purr of the cat; and on the strength of such assumptions he approaches the beasts of the jungle.  The old tag about nature being an open book is just not true.  What nature offers on a first examination may appear to be simple but it is never as simple as it appears." -- Hans Brick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37948-if-language-naturally-evolves-to-serve-the-needs-of-tiny</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:21:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Temple Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37948-if-language-naturally-evolves-to-serve-the-needs-of-tiny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If language naturally evolves to serve the needs of tiny rodents with tiny rodent brains, then what's unique about language isn't the brilliant humans who invented it to communicate high-level abstract thoughts.  What's unique about language is that the creatures who develop it are highly vulnerable to being eaten." -- Temple Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49141-if-you-show-someone-something-you-ve-written-you-give-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49141-if-you-show-someone-something-you-ve-written-you-give-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you show someone something you've written, you give them a sharpened stake, lie down in your coffin, and say, ‘When you’re ready’." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2008 19:44:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Per Petterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117407-people-like-it-when-you-tell-them-things-in-suitable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People like it when you tell them things, in suitable portions, in a modest, intimate tone, and they think they know you, but they do not, they know _about_ you, for what they are let in on are facts, not feelings, not what your opinion is about anything at all, not how what has happened to you and how all the decisions you have made have turned you into who you are. What they do is they fill in with their own feelings and opinions and assumptions, and they compose a new life which has precious little to do with yours, and that lets you off the hook. No-one can touch you unless you yourself want them to." -- Per Petterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118515-home-is-anywhere-that-you-know-all-your-friends-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 16:39:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118515-home-is-anywhere-that-you-know-all-your-friends-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Home is anywhere that you know all your friends and all your enemies." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4061-the-most-exciting-phrase-to-hear-in-science-the-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 13:52:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4061-the-most-exciting-phrase-to-hear-in-science-the-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most exciting phrase to hear in science, the one that heralds the most discoveries, is not &quot;Eureka!&quot; (I found it!) but 'That's funny..." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 21:24:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The family is the cradle of the world’s misinformation. There must be something in family life that generates factual error. Over-closeness, the noise and heat of being. Perhaps even something deeper like the need to survive. Murray says we are fragile creatures surrounded by a world of hostile facts. Facts threaten our happiness and security. The deeper we delve into things, the looser our structure may seem to become. The family process works towards sealing off the world. Small errors grow heads, fictions proliferate. I tell Murray that ignorance and confusion can’t possibly be the driving forces behind family solidarity. What an idea, what a subversion. He asks me why the strongest family units exist in the least developed societies. Not to know is a weapon of survival, he says. Magic and superstition become entrenched as the powerful orthodoxy of the clan. The family is strongest where objective reality is most likely to be misinterpreted. What a heartless theory, I say. But Murray insists it’s true." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191736-the-perfect-society-to-which-we-aspire-in-theory-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 19:29:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Mark Sagoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191736-the-perfect-society-to-which-we-aspire-in-theory-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The perfect society to which we aspire in theory may become a powerful enemy of the good society we can become in fact." -- Mark Sagoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 20:45:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31245-i-have-never-listened-to-anyone-who-criticized-my-taste</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2012 13:10:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laura add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31245-i-have-never-listened-to-anyone-who-criticized-my-taste]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never listened to anyone who criticized my taste in space travel, sideshows or gorillas. When this occurs, I pack up my dinosaurs and leave the room." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
