<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/862143-duncan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/862143-duncan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 08:22:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4648-my-favourite-definition-of-an-intellectual-someone-who-has-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 08:22:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Duncan add a quote by Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4648-my-favourite-definition-of-an-intellectual-someone-who-has-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My favourite definition of  an  intellectual: 'Someone  who  has been  educated beyond his/her intelligence.

[&lt;i&gt;Sources and Acknowledgements&lt;/i&gt;: Chapter 19]" -- Arthur C. Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173942-the-little-black-boy-had-seen-tarzan-bring-down-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Duncan add a quote by Edgar Rice Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173942-the-little-black-boy-had-seen-tarzan-bring-down-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[The little black boy] had seen Tarzan  bring down a buck, just as Numa, the lion, might have done... Tibo had shuddered at the sight, but he had thrilled, too, and for the first time there entered his dull, Negroid mind a vague desire to emulate his savage foster parent.  But Tibo, the little black boy, lacked the divine spark which had permitted Tarzan, the white boy, to benefit by his training in the ways of the fierce jungle.  In imagination he was wanting, and imagination is but another name for super-intelligence.

Imagination it is which builds bridges, and cities, and empires.  The beasts know it not, the blacks only a little, while to one in a hundred thousand of earth's dominant race it is given as a gift from heaven that man may not perish from the earth." -- Edgar Rice Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173945-jill-had-explained-homosexuality-after-mike-had-read-about-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:35:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Duncan add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173945-jill-had-explained-homosexuality-after-mike-had-read-about-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jill... had explained homosexuality, after Mike had read about it and failed to grok--and had given him rules for avoiding passes; she knew that Mike, pretty as he was, would attract such.  He had followed her advice and had made his face more masculine, instead of the androgynous beauty he had had.  But Jill was not sure that Mike would refuse a pass, say, from Duke--fortunately Mike's male water brothers were decidedly masculine, just as his others were very female women.  Jill suspected that Mike would grok a 'wrongness' in the poor in-betweeners anyhow--they would never be offered water." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
