<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/862731-isaac]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/862731-isaac" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 02:10:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 02:10:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57178-the-whole-modern-world-has-divided-itself-into-conservatives-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:36:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57178-the-whole-modern-world-has-divided-itself-into-conservatives-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole modern world has divided itself into Conservatives and Progressives. The business of Progressives is to go on making mistakes. The business of Conservatives is to prevent mistakes from being corrected. Even when the revolutionist might himself repent of his revolution, the traditionalist is already defending it as part of his tradition. Thus we have two great types -- the advanced person who rushes us into ruin, and the retrospective person who admires the ruins. He admires them especially by moonlight, not to say moonshine. Each new blunder of the progressive or prig becomes instantly a legend of immemorial antiquity for the snob. This is called the balance, or mutual check, in our Constitution." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198539-if-the-ordinary-wage-earner-worked-four-hours-a-day-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 23:41:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198539-if-the-ordinary-wage-earner-worked-four-hours-a-day-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the ordinary wage-earner worked four hours a day, there would be enough for everybody and no unemployment -- assuming a certain very moderate amount of sensible organization. This idea shocks the well-to-do, because they are convinced that the poor would not know how to use so much leisure. In America men often work long hours even when they are well off; such men, naturally, are indignant at the idea of leisure for wage-earners, except as the grim punishment of unemployment; in fact, they dislike leisure even for their sons." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277090-one-thing-was-for-sure-i-had-no-interest-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 10:00:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isaac add a quote by Michael Muhammad Knight]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277090-one-thing-was-for-sure-i-had-no-interest-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing was for sure: I had no interest in questioning whether Islam was inherently a religion of peace or one of war, whether the terrorists had misappropriated an innocent faith or the liberal Muslims were only in denial of what Islam actually taught.  I'd never claim to know what &quot;true&quot; Islam stood for; religions were too big to make it that simple, there was too much history and too many verses, and everyone just took the parts that they wanted anyway. For a prophet's message to become what they call a world religion, it'd have to be big enough to accommodate all kinds of personalities. Good ones, mean ones, greedy ones, kind ones, hard ones, soft ones, and they all own Islam as much as it owns them. The water has no shape; it's shaped by the bottle. I could see that as a Muslim, contrasting Qari Saheb's sweetness with that maniac Rushdie, and I even saw it with Catholics in Geneva, between sweet Gramps and that dickhead monsignor or Fat Ed." -- Michael Muhammad Knight]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
