<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/86362-amar-pai]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/86362-amar-pai" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 14:47:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 14:47:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amar add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4339-is-it-so-bad-then-to-be-misunderstood-pythagoras-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it so bad, then, to be misunderstood? Pythagoras was misunderstood, and Socrates, and Jesus, and Luther, and Copernicus, and Galileo, and Newton, and every pure and wise spirit that ever took flesh. To be great is to be misunderstood." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916900-but-the-third-emir-now-seeing-himself-all-alone-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 17:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amar add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916900-but-the-third-emir-now-seeing-himself-all-alone-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the third Emir, now seeing himself all alone on the quarter-deck, seems to feel relieved from some curious restraint; for, tipping all sorts of knowing winks in all sorts of directions, and kicking off his shoes, he strikes into a sharp but noiseless squall of a hornpipe right over the Grand Turk's head; and then, by a dexterous sleight, pitching his cap up into the mizentop for a shelf, he goes down rollicking so far at least as he remains visible from the deck, reversing all other processions, by bringing up the rear with music. But ere stepping into the cabin doorway below, he pauses, ships a new face altogether, and, then, independent, hilarious little Flask enters King Ahab's presence, in the character of Abjectus, or the Slave." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921739-conceits-that-swayed-me-to-my-purpose-two-and-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 20:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amar add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/921739-conceits-that-swayed-me-to-my-purpose-two-and-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["conceits that swayed me to my purpose, two and two there floated into my" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920998-why-did-the-poor-poet-of-tennessee-upon-suddenly-receiving</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2013 20:47:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amar add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920998-why-did-the-poor-poet-of-tennessee-upon-suddenly-receiving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did the poor poet of Tennessee, upon suddenly receiving two handfuls of silver, deliberate whether to buy him a coat, which he sadly needed, or invest his money in a pedestrian trip to Rockaway Beach? Why is almost every robust healthy boy with a robust healthy soul in him, at some time or other crazy to go to sea? Why upon your first voyage as a passenger, did you yourself feel such a mystical vibration, when first told that you and your ship were now out of sight of land? Why did the old Persians hold the sea holy?" -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926359-accommodate-the-quickly-expanding-population-intrigued-warren-contacted-religious-leaders</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 11:03:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amar add a quote by Charles Duhigg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/926359-accommodate-the-quickly-expanding-population-intrigued-warren-contacted-religious-leaders]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["accommodate the quickly expanding population. Intrigued, Warren contacted religious leaders in Southern California who told him that many locals self-identified as Christian but didn’t attend services. “In the dusty, dimly lit basement of that university" -- Charles Duhigg]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
