<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/863801-abailart]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/863801-abailart" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:51:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20370-to-understand-the-limitation-of-things-desire-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:51:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20370-to-understand-the-limitation-of-things-desire-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To understand the limitation of things, desire them." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12583-religious-doctrines-are-all-illusions-they-do-not-admit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:30:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Sigmund Freud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12583-religious-doctrines-are-all-illusions-they-do-not-admit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religious doctrines … are all illusions, they do not admit of proof, and no one can be compelled to consider them as true or to believe in them." -- Sigmund Freud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24638-against-the-disease-of-writing-one-must-take-special-precautions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:33:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Pierre Abélard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24638-against-the-disease-of-writing-one-must-take-special-precautions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Against the disease of writing one must take special precautions, since it is a dangerous and contagious disease." -- Pierre Abélard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2008 08:55:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/845-the-individual-has-always-had-to-struggle-to-keep-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The individual has always had to struggle to keep from being overwhelmed by the tribe. If you try it, you will be lonely often, and sometimes frightened. But no price is too high to pay for the privilege of owning yourself." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24853-whether-life-is-worth-living-depends-on-whether-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 02:10:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by R.D. Laing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24853-whether-life-is-worth-living-depends-on-whether-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether life is worth living depends on whether there is love in life." -- R.D. Laing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20080-what-is-a-poet-an-unhappy-man-who-hides-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 02:14:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20080-what-is-a-poet-an-unhappy-man-who-hides-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a poet? An unhappy man who hides deep anguish in his heart, but whose lips are so formed that when the sigh and cry pass through them, it sounds like lovely music.... And people flock around the poet and say: 'Sing again soon' - that is, 'May new sufferings torment your soul but your lips be fashioned as before, for the cry would only frighten us, but the music, that is blissful." -- Soren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24857-love-is-not-primarily-a-relationship-to-a-specific-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 02:18:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by erich fromm]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24857-love-is-not-primarily-a-relationship-to-a-specific-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is not primarily a relationship to a specific person; it is an attitude, an ordination of character which determines the relatedness of the person to the whole world as a whole, not toward one object of love" -- erich fromm]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24858-the-courage-to-be-is-the-courage-to-accept-oneself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2008 02:20:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by paul tillich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24858-the-courage-to-be-is-the-courage-to-accept-oneself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The courage to be is the courage to accept oneself, in spite of being unacceptable." -- paul tillich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:06:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 09:37:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 12:02:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,
While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.
Tis some visitor,&quot; I muttered, &quot;tapping at my chamber door —
      Only this, and nothing more.&quot;

Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow; — vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow — sorrow for the lost Lenore —
For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore —
      Nameless here for evermore.

And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me — filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating,
Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door —
Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; —
    This it is, and nothing more.&quot;

Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer,
Sir,&quot; said I, &quot;or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you&quot;— here I opened wide the door; —
    Darkness there, and nothing more.

Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken, and the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, &quot;Lenore?&quot;
This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, &quot;Lenore!&quot; —
      Merely this, and nothing more.

Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before.
Surely,&quot; said I, &quot;surely that is something at my window lattice:
Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore —
Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; —
    'Tis the wind and nothing more.&quot;

Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he;
But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door —
Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door —
    Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore.
Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,&quot; I said, &quot;art sure no craven,
Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore —
Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!&quot;
      Quoth the Raven, &quot;Nevermore.&quot;

Much I marveled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning— little relevancy bore;
For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing bird above his chamber door —
Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,
      With such name as &quot;Nevermore." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28552-if-a-way-to-the-better-there-be-it-exacts</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 10:16:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28552-if-a-way-to-the-better-there-be-it-exacts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a way to the Better there be, it exacts a full look at the Worst." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10764-i-dreamed-i-spoke-in-another-s-language-i-dreamed-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2008 11:56:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Clive Barker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10764-i-dreamed-i-spoke-in-another-s-language-i-dreamed-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dreamed I spoke in another's language,
I dreamed I lived in another's skin,
I dreamed I was my own beloved,
I dreamed I was a tiger's kin.

I dreamed that Eden lived inside me,
And when I breathed a garden came,
I dreamed I knew all of Creation,
I dreamed I knew the Creator's name.

I dreamed--and this dream was the finest--
That all I dreamed was real and true,
And we would live in joy forever,
You in me, and me in you." -- Clive Barker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2008 02:31:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23101-pleasure-to-me-is-wonder-the-unexplored-the-unexpected-the-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pleasure to me is wonder—the unexplored, the unexpected, the thing that is hidden and the changeless thing that lurks behind superficial mutability. To trace the remote in the immediate; the eternal in the ephemeral; the past in the present; the infinite in the finite; these are to me the springs of delight and beauty." -- H.P. Lovecraft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7879-either-kill-me-or-take-me-as-i-am-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 10:54:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by marquis de sade]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7879-either-kill-me-or-take-me-as-i-am-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Either kill me or take me as I am, because I'll be damned if I ever change." -- marquis de sade]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 10:54:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Franz Kafka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1791-a-book-must-be-the-axe-for-the-frozen-sea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A book must be the axe for the frozen sea within us." -- Franz Kafka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 10:12:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 15:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Gautama Buddha]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that we are is the result of what we have thought: it is founded on our thoughts and made up of our thoughts. If a man speak or act with an evil thought, suffering follows him as the wheel follows the hoof of the beast that draws the wagon....  If a man speak or act with a good thought, happiness follows him like a shadow that never leaves him." -- Gautama Buddha]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32992-man-s-world-is-manifold-and-his-attitudes-are-manifold-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:56:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32992-man-s-world-is-manifold-and-his-attitudes-are-manifold-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man’s world is manifold, and his attitudes are manifold. What is manifold is often frightening because it is not neat and simple. Men prefer to forget how many possibilities are open to them.
	They like to be told that there are two worlds and two ways. This is comforting because it is so tidy. Almost always one way turns out to be common and the other is celebrated as superior.
Those who tell of two ways and praise one are recognised as prophets or great teachers. They save men from confusion and hard choices. They offer a single choice that is easy to make because those who do not take the path that is commended to them live a wretched life.
To walk on this path may be difficult, but the choice is easy, and to hear the celebration of the path is pleasant. Wisdom offers simple schemes, but truth is not so simple.
" -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32995-mundus-vult-decipi-the-world-wants-to-be-deceived-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:56:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32995-mundus-vult-decipi-the-world-wants-to-be-deceived-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mundus vult decipi: the world wants to be deceived. The truth is too complex and frightening; the taste for the truth is an acquired taste that few acquire….
….The world winks at dishonesty. the world does not call it dishonesty" -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33343-the-good-must-be-clearly-good-but-not-wholly-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33343-the-good-must-be-clearly-good-but-not-wholly-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The good must be clearly good but not wholly clear. If it is wholly clear it is too easy to reject.
What is wanted is an oversimplification, a reduction of a multitude of possibilities to only two. But if the recommended path were utterly devoid of mystery, it would cease to fascinate men….There would be nothing left to discuss and interpret, to lecture and write about, to admire and merely think about.
The world exacts a price for calling teachers wise: it keeps discussing the paths they recommend, but few men follow them. The wise give men endless opportunities to discuss what is good." -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34390-men-love-jargon-it-is-so-palpable-tangible-visible-audible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 12:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34390-men-love-jargon-it-is-so-palpable-tangible-visible-audible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men love jargon. It is so palpable, tangible, visible, audible; it makes so obvious what one has learned; it satisfies the craving for results. It is impressive for the uninitiated. It makes one feel that one belongs. Jargon divides men into Us and Them….
Obscurity is fascinating. One tries to puzzle out details, is stumpred, and becomes increasingly concerned with meaning – unless one feels put off and gives up altogether.
Those who persevere and take the author seriously are led to ask about what he could possibly have meant, but rarely seem to wonder or discuss whether what he says is true." -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39451-not-all-deceptions-are-palatable-untruths-are-too-easy-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 07:10:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39451-not-all-deceptions-are-palatable-untruths-are-too-easy-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not all deceptions are palatable. Untruths are too easy to come by, too quickly exploded, too cheap and ephemeral to give lasting comfort. Mundus vult decipi, but there is a hierarchy of deceptions.
Near the bottom of the ladder is journalism: a steady stream of irresponsible distortions that most people find refreshing although on the morning after, or at least within a week, it will be stale and flat.
On a higher level we find fictions that men eagerly believe, regardless of the evidence, because they gratify some wish.
Near the top of the ladder we encounter curious mixtures of untruth and truth that exert a lasting fascination on the intellectual community." -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39452-success-is-no-proof-of-virtue-in-the-case-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2008 07:11:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39452-success-is-no-proof-of-virtue-in-the-case-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success is no proof of virtue. In the case of a book, quick acclaim is presumptive evidence of a lack of substance and originality." -- Walter Kaufmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55022-by-the-time-they-have-reached-the-middle-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 09:56:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Robert Musil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55022-by-the-time-they-have-reached-the-middle-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…. by the time they have reached the middle of their life’s journey, few people remember how they have managed to arrive at themselves, at their amusements, their point of view, their wife, character, occupation and successes, but they cannot help feeling that not much is likely to change anymore. It might even be asserted that they have been cheated, for one can nowhere discover any sufficient reason for everything’s coming about as it has. It might just have well as turned out differently. The events of people’s lives have, after all, only to the last degree originated in them, having generally depended on all sorts of circumstances such as the moods, the life or death of quite different people, and have, as it were, only at the given point of time come hurrying towards them" -- Robert Musil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55023-what-is-perceptible-to-one-s-mistrust-is-the-cut-and-dried-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2008 09:58:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Robert Musil]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55023-what-is-perceptible-to-one-s-mistrust-is-the-cut-and-dried-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is perceptible to one’s mistrust is the cut-and-dried way that life is divided up and the ready-made form it assumes, the ever-recurring sameness of it, the pre-formations passed down by generation after generation, the ready-made language not only of the tongue but also of the sensations and the feelings. " -- Robert Musil]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56080-i-am-a-violent-man-who-has-learned-not-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 10:49:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56080-i-am-a-violent-man-who-has-learned-not-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a violent man who has learned not to be violent and regrets his violence." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59778-mind-is-the-forerunner-of-all-evil-states-mind-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 09:09:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Buddha (Dhammapada)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59778-mind-is-the-forerunner-of-all-evil-states-mind-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mind is the forerunner of (all evil) states. Mind is chief; mind-made are they. If one speaks or acts with wicked mind, suffering follows one, even as the wheel follows the hoof of the draught-ox.

Mind is the forerunner of (all good) states. Mind is chief; mind-made are they. If one speaks or acts with pure mind, AFFECTION follows one, even as one's shadow that never leaves. " -- Buddha (Dhammapada)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60116-it-took-me-a-long-time-my-lifetime-so-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2008 10:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60116-it-took-me-a-long-time-my-lifetime-so-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It took me a long time, my lifetime so to speak, to realise that the colour of an eye half seen, or the source of some distant sound, are closer to Giudecca in the hell of unknowing than the existence of God, or the origins of protoplasm, or the eistence of self, and even less worthy than these to occupy the wise, It's a bit much, a lifetime, to achieve this consoling conclusion, it doesn't leave you much time to profit by it." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70368-i-consider-the-power-in-the-comic-a-vitally-necessary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 01:14:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abailart add a quote by Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70368-i-consider-the-power-in-the-comic-a-vitally-necessary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I consider the power in the comic a vitally necessary legitimation for anyone who is to be regarded as authorized in the world of spirit in our day&quot; (Concluding Unscientific Postscript to Philosophical Fragments, ed. and trans. Howard V. Hong and Edna H. Hong [Princeton: Princeton University Press, 1992]--hereafter CUPPF--1:281)." -- Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
