<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864164-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864164-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 09:13:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109427-perseverance-is-the-hard-work-you-do-after-you-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2012 09:13:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Newt Gingrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109427-perseverance-is-the-hard-work-you-do-after-you-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perseverance is the hard work you do after you get tired of doing the hard work you already did." -- Newt Gingrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617206-the-true-story-of-every-person-in-this-world-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 22:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by John Eldredge Brent Curtis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/617206-the-true-story-of-every-person-in-this-world-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true story of every person in this world is not the story you see, the external story. The true story of each person is the journey of his or her heart." -- John Eldredge Brent Curtis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308331-the-ragamuffin-who-sees-his-life-as-a-voyage-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 21:53:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308331-the-ragamuffin-who-sees-his-life-as-a-voyage-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ragamuffin who sees his life as a voyage of discovery and runs the risk of failure has a better feel for faithfulness than the timid man who hides behind the law and never finds out who he is at all." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377269-the-noonday-devil-of-the-christian-life-is-the-temptation</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 21:55:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377269-the-noonday-devil-of-the-christian-life-is-the-temptation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The noonday devil of the Christian life is the temptation to lose the inner self while preserving the shell of edifying behavior. Suddenly I discover that I am ministering to AIDS victims to enhance my resume. I find I renounced ice cream for Lent to lose five excess pounds... I have fallen victim to what T.S. Eliot calls the greatest sin: to do the right thing for the wrong reason." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308356-the-word-we-study-has-to-be-the-word-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 21:56:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308356-the-word-we-study-has-to-be-the-word-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Word we study has to be the Word we pray. My personal experience of the relentless tenderness of God came not from exegetes, theologians, and spiritual writers, but from sitting still in the presence of the living Word and beseeching Him to help me understand with my head and heart His written Word. Sheer scholarship alone cannot reveal to us the gospel of grace. We must never allow the authority of books, institutions, or leaders to replace the authority of *knowing* Jesus Christ personally and directly. When the religious views of others interpose between us and the primary experience of Jesus as the Christ, we become unconvicted and unpersuasive travel agents handing out brochures to places we have never visited." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308366-because-salvation-is-by-grace-through-faith-i-believe-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 21:55:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308366-because-salvation-is-by-grace-through-faith-i-believe-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because salvation is by grace through faith, I believe that among the countless number of people standing in front of the throne and in front of the Lamb, dressed in white robes and holding palms in their hands (see Revelation 7:9), I shall see the prostitute from the Kit-Kat Ranch in Carson City, Nevada, who tearfully told me that she could find no other employment to support her two-year-old son. I shall see the woman who had an abortion and is haunted by guilt and remorse but did the best she could faced with grueling alternatives; the businessman besieged with debt who sold his integrity in a series of desperate transactions; the insecure clergyman addicted to being liked, who never challenged his people from the pulpit and longed for unconditional love; the sexually abused teen molested by his father and now selling his body on the street, who, as he falls asleep each night after his last 'trick', whispers the name of the unknown God he learned about in Sunday school.

'But how?' we ask.

Then the voice says, 'They have washed their robes and have made them white in the blood of the Lamb.'

There they are. There *we* are - the multitude who so wanted to be faithful, who at times got defeated, soiled by life, and bested by trials, wearing the bloodied garments of life's tribulations, but through it all clung to faith. 

My friends, if this is not good news to you, you have never understood the gospel of grace." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589574-how-i-treat-a-brother-or-sister-from-day-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2013 21:56:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Brennan Manning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/589574-how-i-treat-a-brother-or-sister-from-day-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How I treat a brother or sister from day to day, how I react to the sin-scarred wino on the street, how I respond to interruptions from people I dislike, how I deal with normal people in their normal confusion on a normal day may be a better indication of my reverence for life than the antiabortion sticker on the bumper of my car." -- Brennan Manning]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
