<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/8646-fabiano-caruso]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/8646-fabiano-caruso" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385998-the-next-step-in-the-process-is-to-measure-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385998-the-next-step-in-the-process-is-to-measure-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The next step in the process is to measure the impact that these increases in reach have on your number of new transacting customers. The secret to a company’s reach strategy lies in the program’s ability not only to acquire fans, followers, subscribers and connections, but to convert them through its use of social media into transacting customers." -- Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385999-myth-number-4-social-media-is-the-shiny-new-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385999-myth-number-4-social-media-is-the-shiny-new-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Myth Number 4: Social Media Is the Shiny New Thing. Two Years from Now, That Bubble Will Burst Yes, it is the shiny new thing. No, two years from now, that bubble will not burst. There is no bubble. What social media represents is an evolution in the field of communications, just as the Internet and mobility before it. The tools will change, the platforms will evolve, but the way in which people communicate with other people through digital networks and electronic devices has been fundamentally transformed through the development of social media. We did not grow tired of the telephone, of the..." -- Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386000-you-see-the-thing-about-working-with-pirates-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386000-you-see-the-thing-about-working-with-pirates-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, the thing about working with pirates is that they know what they are doing. They already know more than you do because they are sailing and raiding. They are the experts in your organization, and you need to get them on your side, not turn them against you. Here is how to deal with a pirate ship model in ten simple steps: 1. Respect the pirates. (They know how to execute.) 2. Invite the pirates to the table. Recognize their wins. 3. Ask the pirates to report on what they see and hear. 4. Ask the pirates to report on their wins and losses. 5. Ask the pirates how you can help them win more...." -- Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386001-ultimately-the-purpose-of-a-certification-is-to-establish-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386001-ultimately-the-purpose-of-a-certification-is-to-establish-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately, the purpose of a certification is to establish a particular level of proficiency in a discipline. Unfortunately, “social media” in and of itself, is not a discipline. Digital crisis management, on the other hand, is. So are digital customer service and online community management. This means that a certification program that focuses on social media without addressing each specific business function adapted to social media won’t end up certifying anyone in much of anything." -- Olivier Blanchard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386002-principle-1-by-setting-limitations-we-must-choose-the-essential</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Leo Babauta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386002-principle-1-by-setting-limitations-we-must-choose-the-essential]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Principle 1: By setting limitations, we must choose the essential. So in everything you do, learn to set limitations.   Principle 2: By choosing the essential, we create great impact with minimal resources. Always choose the essential to maximize your time and energy." -- Leo Babauta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386003-the-power-of-less-is-perfect-for-achieving-goals-limit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Leo Babauta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386003-the-power-of-less-is-perfect-for-achieving-goals-limit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Power of Less is perfect for achieving goals: Limit yourself to fewer goals, and you’ll achieve more. At the same time, we’ll look at ways to narrow your focus on your projects, so that you can complete them more effectively and move forward on your goals. We’ll apply limitations to our projects to increase our effectiveness." -- Leo Babauta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386004-the-challenge-it-turns-out-isn-t-in-perfecting-your-ability</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Seth Godin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386004-the-challenge-it-turns-out-isn-t-in-perfecting-your-ability]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The challenge, it turns out, isn’t in perfecting your ability to know when to start and when to stand by. The challenge is getting into the habit of" -- Seth Godin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386005-it-s-okay-let-your-ego-push-you-to-be-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 03:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Seth Godin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386005-it-s-okay-let-your-ego-push-you-to-be-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s okay. Let your ego push you to be the initiator. But tell your ego that the best way to get something shipped is to let other people take the credit. The real win for you (and your ego) is seeing something get shipped, not in getting the credit when it does." -- Seth Godin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390400-as-a-business-owner-you-should-share-everything-you-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390400-as-a-business-owner-you-should-share-everything-you-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a business owner, you should share everything you know too. This is anathema to most in the business world. Businesses are usually paranoid and secretive. They think they have proprietary this and competitive advantage that. Maybe a rare few do, but most don’t. And those that don’t should stop acting like those that do. Don’t be afraid of sharing." -- Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390401-it-s-a-beautiful-way-to-put-it-leave-the-poetry</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jason Fried]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390401-it-s-a-beautiful-way-to-put-it-leave-the-poetry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a beautiful way to put it: Leave the poetry in what you make. When something becomes too polished, it loses its soul. It seems robotic." -- Jason Fried]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390402-the-real-world-just-doesn-t-offer-up-as-easily-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jane McGonigal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390402-the-real-world-just-doesn-t-offer-up-as-easily-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real world just doesn’t offer up as easily the carefully designed pleasures, the thrilling challenges, and the powerful social bonding afforded by virtual environments. Reality doesn’t motivate us as effectively. Reality isn’t engineered to maximize our potential. Reality wasn’t designed from the bottom up to make us happy." -- Jane McGonigal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390403-today-i-look-forward-and-i-see-a-future-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jane McGonigal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390403-today-i-look-forward-and-i-see-a-future-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today, I look forward and I see a future in which games once again are explicitly designed to improve quality of life, to prevent suffering, and to create real, widespread happiness." -- Jane McGonigal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390404-no-object-no-event-no-outcome-or-life-circumstance-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jane McGonigal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390404-no-object-no-event-no-outcome-or-life-circumstance-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No object, no event, no outcome or life circumstance can deliver real happiness to us. We have to make our own happiness—by working hard at activities that provide their own reward.15" -- Jane McGonigal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390405-nesse-s-research-focuses-on-the-evolutionary-origins-of-depression-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 20:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fabiano add a quote by Jane McGonigal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390405-nesse-s-research-focuses-on-the-evolutionary-origins-of-depression-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nesse’s research focuses on the evolutionary origins of depression. Why does depression exist at all? If it’s stayed in our gene pool for so long, he argues, there must be some evolutionary benefit. Nesse believes that depression may be an adaptive mechanism meant to prevent us from falling victim to blind optimism—and squandering resources on the wrong goals.11 It’s to our evolutionary advantage not to waste time and energy on goals we can’t realistically achieve. And so when we have no clear way to make productive progress, our neurological systems default to a state of low energy..." -- Jane McGonigal]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
