<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864983-amanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864983-amanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 21:55:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140397-time-is-more-precious-than-gold-more-precious-than-diamonds</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2013 21:55:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140397-time-is-more-precious-than-gold-more-precious-than-diamonds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is more precious than gold, more precious than diamonds, more precious than oil or any valuable treasures. It is time that we do not have enough of; it is time that causes the war within our hearts, and so we must spend it wisely." -- Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149738-it-s-easy-to-believe-in-something-when-you-win-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2013 18:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149738-it-s-easy-to-believe-in-something-when-you-win-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's easy to believe in something when you win all the time...The losses are what define a man's faith." -- Brandon Sanderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377103-baby-she-says-in-a-harsh-whisper-in-this-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Holly Black]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377103-baby-she-says-in-a-harsh-whisper-in-this-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Baby,&quot; she says in a harsh whisper, &quot;in this world, lots of people will try to grind you down. They need you to be small so they can be big. You let them think whatever they want, but you make sure you get yours. You get yours." -- Holly Black]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414507-i-d-never-been-a-good-damsel-in-distress-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:25:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jennifer Armintrout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414507-i-d-never-been-a-good-damsel-in-distress-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd never been a good damsel in distress. I was a &quot;hands-on&quot; damsel." -- Jennifer Armintrout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464009-i-write-about-adversity-i-praise-adversity-not-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:27:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Criss Jami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464009-i-write-about-adversity-i-praise-adversity-not-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write about adversity, I praise adversity, not to be pessimistic, but rather to strengthen myself. The more familiar that you are with it, the less likely you are to have a breakdown when it occurs. You become more reflective of its purpose, you understand God's reason for it, and are then able to make the best of everything that you are handed. The darkness is only frightening after constant sunshine." -- Criss Jami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882219-the-crazy-creatives-are-the-creatives-who-never-go-completely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:30:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Criss Jami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882219-the-crazy-creatives-are-the-creatives-who-never-go-completely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The crazy creatives are the creatives who never go completely mad. They aren't so easily disheartened by the seemingly endless amounts of scrutiny that creative individuals tend to receive because they, like insanity, are the ones who feed off of opposition and negative feedback and manage to continue along with a healthy ambition. It is the crazy that teaches us to use our gifts wisely and own all the attackers." -- Criss Jami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857575-she-regretted-nothing-she-had-shared-with-her-lover-nor</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:34:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Isabel Allende]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/857575-she-regretted-nothing-she-had-shared-with-her-lover-nor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She regretted nothing she had shared with her lover, nor was she ashamed of the fires that had changed her life; just the opposite, she felt that they had tempered her, made her strong, given her pride in making decisions and paying the consequences for them." -- Isabel Allende]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880764-i-have-faith-in-us-as-a-family-and-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 23:35:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jessica Fortunato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/880764-i-have-faith-in-us-as-a-family-and-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have faith in us as a family, and our friends. I think we will survive because we don’t wish to harm anyone. If you ever need something to believe in, believe that to stand and fight for the people you love is the most honorable thing you can do with your life." -- Jessica Fortunato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175873-and-now-i-m-looking-at-you-he-said-and-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Cassandra Clare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175873-and-now-i-m-looking-at-you-he-said-and-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now I’m looking at you,” he said, “and you’re asking me if I still want you, as if I could stop loving you. As if I would want to give up the thing that makes me stronger than anything else ever has. I never dared give much of myself to anyone before – bits of myself to the Lightwoods, to Isabelle and Alec, but it took years to do it – but, Clary, since the first time I saw you, I have belonged to you completely. I still do. If you want me." -- Cassandra Clare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:10:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Shana Abe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116153-i-heard-what-you-said-i-m-not-the-silly-romantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I heard what you said. I’m not the silly romantic you think. I don’t want the heavens or the shooting stars. I don’t want gemstones or gold. I have those things already. I want…a steady hand. A kind soul. I want to fall asleep, and wake, knowing my heart is safe. I want to love, and be loved." -- Shana Abe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 20:10:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
