<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864961-kimberly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/864961-kimberly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 13:24:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 13:24:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 13:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 13:25:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who believes that the secrets of the world are forever hidden lives in mystery and fear. Superstitiion will drag him down. The rain will erode the deeds of his life. But that man who sets himself the task of singling out the thread of order from the tapestry will by the decision alone have taken charge of the world and it is only by such taking charge that he will effect a way to dictate the terms of his own fate. 

I dont see what that has to do with catchin birds. 

The freedom of birds is an insult to me. I'd have them all in zoos. 

That would be a hell of a zoo. 

The judge smiled. Yes, he said. Even so." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15383-after-the-leaves-have-fallen-we-return-to-a-plain</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 13:38:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Wallace Stevens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15383-after-the-leaves-have-fallen-we-return-to-a-plain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After the leaves have fallen, we return
To a plain sense of things.  It is as if
We had come to an end of the imagination,
Inanimate in an inert savoir." -- Wallace Stevens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19718-our-ignorance-can-be-divided-into-problems-and-mysteries-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 14:31:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Noam Chomsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19718-our-ignorance-can-be-divided-into-problems-and-mysteries-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our ignorance can be divided into problems and mysteries. When we face a problem, we may not know its solution, but we have insight, increasing knowledge, and an inkling of what we are looking for. When we face a mystery, however, we can only stare in wonder and bewilderment, not knowing what an explanation would even look like." -- Noam Chomsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54212-absolute-power-does-not-corrupt-absolutely-absolute-power-attracts-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 14:44:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54212-absolute-power-does-not-corrupt-absolutely-absolute-power-attracts-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Absolute power does not corrupt absolutely, absolute power attracts the corruptible." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:25:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13719-we-are-what-we-pretend-to-be-so-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful about what we pretend to be." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:25:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1291-and-on-the-subject-of-burning-books-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.

So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152609-truth-is-not-spoken-in-anger-truth-is-spoken-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:52:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152609-truth-is-not-spoken-in-anger-truth-is-spoken-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Truth is not spoken in anger. Truth is spoken, if it ever comes to be spoken, in love. The gaze of love is not deluded. It sees what is best in the beloved even when what is best in the beloved finds it hard to emerge into the light." -- J.M. Coetzee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:03:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:03:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:21:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32306-better-to-sleep-with-a-sober-cannibal-than-a-drunk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to sleep with a sober cannibal than a drunk Christian." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13765-i-would-prefer-not-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13765-i-would-prefer-not-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would prefer not to." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 04:57:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by C.G. Jung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39433-your-visions-will-become-clear-only-when-you-can-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your visions will become clear only when you can look into your own heart. Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakes." -- C.G. Jung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 11:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27349-if-you-are-bored-and-disgusted-by-politics-and-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are bored and disgusted by politics and don't bother to vote, you are in effect voting for the entrenched Establishments of the two major parties, who please rest assured are not dumb, and who are keenly aware that it is in their interests to keep you disgusted and bored and cynical and to give you every possible reason to stay at home doing one-hitters and watching MTV on primary day.  By all means stay home if you want, but don't bullshit yourself that you're not voting.  In reality, there is &lt;i&gt;no such thing as not voting:&lt;/i&gt; you either vote by voting, or you vote by staying home and tacitly doubling the value of some Diehard's vote." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 11:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36729-one-should-always-be-drunk-that-s-all-that-matters-but-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 09:32:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36729-one-should-always-be-drunk-that-s-all-that-matters-but-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One should always be drunk. That's all that matters...But with what? With wine, with poetry, or with virtue, as you chose. But get drunk." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2011 12:09:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the mustn'ts, child. Listen to the don'ts. Listen to the shouldn'ts, the impossibles, the won'ts. Listen to the never haves, then listen close to me... Anything can happen, child. Anything can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48979-when-the-starry-sky-a-vista-of-open-seas-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 14:12:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Julia Kristeva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48979-when-the-starry-sky-a-vista-of-open-seas-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the starry sky, a vista of open seas, or a stained-glass window  shedding purple beams fascinate me, there is a cluster of meaning, of colors, of words, of caresses,  there are light touches, scents, sighs, cadences that arise, shroud me, carry me away, and sweep me beyond the things I see, hear, or think, The &quot;sublime&quot; object dissolves in the raptures of a bottomless memory.  It is such a memory, which, from stopping point to stopping point, remembrance to remembrance, love to love, transfers that object to the refulgent point of the dazzlement in which I stray in order to be." -- Julia Kristeva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310525-it-is-not-the-slumber-of-reason-that-engenders-monsters</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310525-it-is-not-the-slumber-of-reason-that-engenders-monsters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the slumber of reason that engenders monsters, but vigilant and insomniac rationality." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310517-christianity-taught-us-to-see-the-eye-of-the-lord</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:03:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310517-christianity-taught-us-to-see-the-eye-of-the-lord]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Christianity taught us to see the eye of the lord looking down upon us. Such forms of knowledge project an image of reality, at the expense of reality itself. They talk figures and icons and signs, but fail to perceive forces and flows. They bind us to other realities, and especially the reality of power as it subjugates us. Their function is to tame, and the result is the fabrication of docile and obedient subjects." -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310518-d-h-lawrence-had-the-impression-that-psychoanalysis-was-shutting</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:03:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310518-d-h-lawrence-had-the-impression-that-psychoanalysis-was-shutting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["D.H. Lawrence had the impression – that psychoanalysis was shutting sexuality up in a bizarre sort of box painted with bourgeois motifs, in a kind of rather repugnant artificial triangle, thereby stifling the whole of sexuality as a production of desire so as to recast it along entirely different lines, making of it a ‘dirty little secret’, a dirty little family secret, a private theater rather than the fantastic factory of nature and production" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310520-what-does-belief-applied-to-the-unconscious-signify-what-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:07:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310520-what-does-belief-applied-to-the-unconscious-signify-what-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does belief applied to the unconscious signify? What is an unconscious that no longer does anything but believe, rather than produce? What are the operations, the artifices that inject the unconscious with ‘beliefs’ that are not even rational, but on the contrary only too reasonable and consistent with the established order?" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310523-psychoanalysts-are-bent-on-producing-man-abstractly-that-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:13:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/310523-psychoanalysts-are-bent-on-producing-man-abstractly-that-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Psychoanalysts are bent on producing man abstractly, that is to say ideologically, for culture. It is Oedipus who produces man in this fashion and who gives a structure to the false movement of infinite progression and regression" -- Gilles Deleuze]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people never go crazy. What truly horrible lives they must lead." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:09:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:10:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14996-my-ambition-is-handicapped-by-laziness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My ambition is handicapped by laziness" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:10:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139472-some-lose-all-mind-and-become-soul-insane-some-lose-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2012 19:18:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139472-some-lose-all-mind-and-become-soul-insane-some-lose-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some lose all mind and become soul,insane.
some lose all soul and become mind, intellectual.
some lose both and become accepted" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64707-forget-trying-to-pass-for-normal-follow-your-geekdom-embrace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 07:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Bruce Sterling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64707-forget-trying-to-pass-for-normal-follow-your-geekdom-embrace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forget trying to pass for normal.  Follow your geekdom.  Embrace nerditude.  In the immortal words of Lafcadio Hearn, a geek of incredible obscurity whose work is still in print after a hundred years, “Woo the muse of the odd.”  You may be a geek.  You may have geek written all over you.  You should aim to be one geek they'll never forget.  Don't aim to be civilized.  Don’t hope that straight people will keep you on as some sort of pet.  To hell with them.  You should fully realize what society has made of you and take a terrible revenge.  Get weird.  Get way weird.  Get dangerously weird.  Get sophisticatedly, thoroughly weird, and don't do it halfway.  Put every ounce of horsepower you have behind it.  Don't become a well-rounded person.  Well-rounded people are smooth and dull.  Become a thoroughly spiky person.  Grow spikes from every angle.  Stick in their throats like a pufferfish." -- Bruce Sterling]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
