<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867099-liza]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867099-liza" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 09:42:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25562-what-she-had-long-believed-was-not-true-and-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 09:42:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25562-what-she-had-long-believed-was-not-true-and-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What she had long believed was not true, and now the world was wide open to discover what was.
It is like all my life I thought the sky was green." -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67756-your-real-new-self-which-is-christ-s-and-also-yours</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 20:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Liza add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67756-your-real-new-self-which-is-christ-s-and-also-yours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your real, new self (which is Christ's and also yours, and yours just because it is His) will not come as long as you are looking for it. It will come when you are looking for Him. Does that sound strange? The same principle holds, you know, for more everyday matters. Even in social life, you will never make a good impression on other people until you stop thinking about what sort of impression you are making. Even in literature and art, no man who bothers about originality will ever be original whereas if you simply try to tell the truth (without caring twopence how often it has been told before) you will, nine times out of ten, become original without ever having noticed it. The principle runs through all life from top to bottom, Give up yourself, and you will find your real self. Lose your life and you will save it. Submit to death, death of your ambitions and favourite wishes every day and death of your whole body in the end submit with every fibre of your being, and you will find eternal life. Keep back nothing. Nothing that you have not given away will be really yours. Nothing in you that has not died will ever be raised from the dead. Look for yourself, and you will find in the long run only hatred, loneliness, despair, rage, ruin, and decay. But look for Christ and you will find Him, and with Him everything else thrown in." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
