<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867693-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867693-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:07:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:07:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beet is the most intense of vegetables. The radish, admittedly, is more feverish, but the fire of the radish is a cold fire, the fire of discontent not of passion. Tomatoes are lusty enough, yet there runs through tomatoes an undercurrent of frivolity. Beets are deadly serious.

Slavic peoples get their physical characteristics from potatoes, their smoldering inquietude from radishes, their seriousness from beets.

The beet is the melancholy vegetable, the one most willing to suffer. You can't squeeze blood out of a turnip...

The beet is the murderer returned to the scene of the crime. The beet is what happens when the cherry finishes with the carrot. The beet is the ancient ancestor of the autumn moon, bearded, buried, all but fossilized; the dark green sails of the grounded moon-boat stitched with veins of primordial plasma; the kite string that once connected the moon to the Earth now a muddy whisker drilling desperately for rubies.

The beet was Rasputin's favorite vegetable. You could see it in his eyes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149010-it-s-no-fun-to-be-yellow-maybe-i-m-not-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:07:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149010-it-s-no-fun-to-be-yellow-maybe-i-m-not-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's no fun to be yellow. Maybe I'm not all yellow. I don't know. I think maybe I'm just partly yellow and partly the type that doesn't give much of a damn if they lose their gloves. One of my troubles is, I never care too much when I lose something - it used to drive mother crazy when I was a kid. Some guys spend days looking for something they've lost. I never seem to have anything that if I lost it I'd care too much. Maybe that's why I'm partly yellow. It's no excuse, though. It really isn't. What you should be is not yellow at all." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149014-in-one-day-i-had-altered-my-life-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:05:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Carol Shields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149014-in-one-day-i-had-altered-my-life-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In one day I had altered my life; my life, therefore, was alterable. This simple axiom did not call out for exegesis; no, it entered my bloodstream directly, as powerful as heroin. I could feel it pump and surge, the way it brightened my veins to a kind of glass. I had wakened that morning to narrowness and predestination and now I was falling asleep in the storm of my own free will." -- Carol Shields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149016-but-think-of-the-glory-of-the-choice-that-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:05:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149016-but-think-of-the-glory-of-the-choice-that-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But think of the glory of the choice! That makes a man a man. A cat has no choice, a bee must make honey. There's no godliness there." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36570-we-have-only-one-story-all-novels-all-poetry-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36570-we-have-only-one-story-all-novels-all-poetry-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have only one story. All novels, all poetry, are built on the neverending contest in ourselves of good and evil. And it occurs to me that evil must constantly respawn, while good, while virtue, is immortal. Vice has always a new fresh young face, while virtue is venerable as nothing else in the world is." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149015-i-felt-like-praying-or-something-when-i-was-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149015-i-felt-like-praying-or-something-when-i-was-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I felt like praying or something, when I was in bed, but I couldn't do it. I can't always pray when I feel like it. In the first place, I'm sort of an atheist. I like Jesus and all, but I don't care too much for most of the other stuff in the Bible. Take the Disciples, for instance. They annoy the hell out of me, if you want to know the truth. They were all right after Jesus was dead and all, but while He was alive, they were about as much use to Him as a hole in the head. All they did was keep letting Him down." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131245-that-s-what-fiction-is-about-isn-t-it-the-selective-transforming</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:05:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131245-that-s-what-fiction-is-about-isn-t-it-the-selective-transforming]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what fiction is about, isn't it, the selective transforming of reality? The twisting of it to bring out its essence?" -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75587-it-s-a-misery-peculiar-to-would-be-writers-your-theme-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:05:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75587-it-s-a-misery-peculiar-to-would-be-writers-your-theme-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a misery peculiar to would-be writers. Your theme is good, as are your sentences. Your characters are so ruddy with life they practically need birth certificates. The plot you've mapped out for them is grand, simple and gripping. You've done your research, gathering the facts; historical, social, climatic culinary, that will give your story its feel of authenticity. The dialogue zips along, crackling with tension. The descriptions burst with color, contrast and telling detail.
Really, your story can only be great. But it all adds up to nothing.
In spite the obvious, shining promise of it, there comes a moment when you realize that the whisper that has been pestering you all along from the back of your mind is speaking the flat, awful truth: IT WON'T WORK.
An element is missing, that spark that brings to life in a real story, regardless of whether the history or the food is right.
Your story is emotionally dead, that's the crux of it.
The discovery is something soul-destroying, I tell you. It leaves you with an aching hunger." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149022-i-couldn-t-get-him-out-of-my-head-still-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149022-i-couldn-t-get-him-out-of-my-head-still-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't get Him out of my head. Still can't. I spent three solid days thinking about Him. The more He bothered me, the less I coul forget Him. And the more I learned about Him, the less I wanted to leave Him." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78445-to-me-religion-is-about-our-dignity-not-our-depravity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78445-to-me-religion-is-about-our-dignity-not-our-depravity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me, religion is about our dignity, not our depravity." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149027-it-s-not-atheists-who-get-stuck-in-my-caw-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149027-it-s-not-atheists-who-get-stuck-in-my-caw-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not atheists who get stuck in my caw, but agnostics. Doubt is useful for awhile. We all must pass through the garden of Gethsemane. If Christ played with doubt, so must we... But we must move on. To choose doubt as a philosophy of life is akin to choosing immobility as means of transportation." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122713-the-reason-death-sticks-so-closely-to-life-isn-t-biological</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:04:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122713-the-reason-death-sticks-so-closely-to-life-isn-t-biological]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The reason death sticks so closely to life isn't biological necessity; it's envy. Life is so beautiful that death has fallen in love with it, a jealous, possessive love that grabs at what it can." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149029-later-when-she-sees-the-photographs-for-the-first-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149029-later-when-she-sees-the-photographs-for-the-first-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Later, when she sees the photographs for the first time, she will be surprised at how calm her face looks - how steady her gaze, how erect her posture. In the picture her eyes will be slightly closed, and there will be a shadow on her neck. The shawl will be draped around her shoulders, and her hands will rest in her lap. In this deceptive photograph, she will look a young woman who is not at all disturbed or embarrassed, but instead appears to be rather serious. And she wonders if, in its ability to deceive, photography is not unlike the sea, which may offer a benign surface to the observe even as it conceals depths and current below." -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149031-and-this-all-causes-her-to-wonder-at-the-disparity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149031-and-this-all-causes-her-to-wonder-at-the-disparity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this all causes her to wonder at the disparity between the silk dresses and the natural postures of the body, and to think: How far, HOW FAR, we are willing to go to pretend we are not of the body at all." -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149034-she-suddenly-looks-different-to-olympia-physically-different-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149034-she-suddenly-looks-different-to-olympia-physically-different-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... she suddenly looks different to Olympia, physically different, as though a portrait has been alterred. And Olympia thinks that possibly such adjustments might have to be made for everyone she knows. Upon meeting a person, a sketch is formed, and for the life of the relationship, however intimate or not, a portrait is painted, with oils or pastels or with black ink or with watercolor, and only at a persons's death can the portraits be considered finished. Perhaps not even at the person's death." -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64506-the-heaviest-of-burdens-crushes-us-we-sink-beneath-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heaviest of burdens crushes us, we sink beneath it, it pins us to the ground. But in love poetry of every age, the woman longs to be weighed down by the man's body.The heaviest of burdens is therefore simultaneously an image of life's most intense fulfillment. The heavier the burden, the closer our lives come to the earth, the more real and truthful they become. Conversely, the absolute absence of burden causes man to be lighter than air, to soar into heights, take leave of the earth and his earthly being, and become only half real, his movements as free as they are insignificant. What then shall we choose? Weight or lightness?" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24991-do-not-pity-the-dead-harry-pity-the-living-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not pity the dead, Harry. Pity the living, and, above all those who live without love." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18284-it-was-he-thought-the-difference-between-being-dragged-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18284-it-was-he-thought-the-difference-between-being-dragged-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was, he thought, the difference between being dragged into the arena to face a battle to the death and walking into the arena with your head held high. Some people, perhaps, would say that there was little to choose between the two ways, but Dumbledore knew - and so do I, thought Harry, with a rush of fierce pride, and so did my parents - that there was all the difference in the world." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30727-it-is-the-unknown-we-fear-when-we-look-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30727-it-is-the-unknown-we-fear-when-we-look-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the unknown we fear when we look upon death and darkness, nothing more." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19798-if-you-want-to-understand-any-woman-you-must-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Anita Diamant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19798-if-you-want-to-understand-any-woman-you-must-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to understand any woman you must first ask about her mother and then listen carefully. Stories about food show a strong connection. Wistful silences demonstrate unfinished business. The more a daughter knows about the details of her mother's life - without flinching or whining - the stronger the daughter." -- Anita Diamant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1197-harry-was-left-to-ponder-in-silence-the-depths-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 16:03:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1197-harry-was-left-to-ponder-in-silence-the-depths-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Harry was left to ponder in silence the depths to which girls would sink to get revenge." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232431-olympia-thinks-often-about-desire---desire-that-stops-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 05:57:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Anita Shreve]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232431-olympia-thinks-often-about-desire---desire-that-stops-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Olympia thinks often about desire - desire that stops the breath, that causes a preoccupied pause in the midst of uttering a sentence - and how it may upend a life and threaten to dissolve the soul." -- Anita Shreve]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352867-the-battle-over-flesh-and-blood-cannot-compare-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 13:55:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Ted Dekker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352867-the-battle-over-flesh-and-blood-cannot-compare-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The battle over flesh and blood cannot compare to the battle for the heart." -- Ted Dekker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169202-i-m-up-to-here-with-cool-okay-i-am-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 14:00:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169202-i-m-up-to-here-with-cool-okay-i-am-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm up to here with cool, okay? I am so amazingly cool you could keep a side of meat in me for a month. I am so hip I have difficulty seeing over my pelvis." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71510-the-history-of-every-major-galactic-civilization-tends-to-pass</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2011 14:22:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71510-the-history-of-every-major-galactic-civilization-tends-to-pass]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The History of every major Galactic Civilization tends to pass through three distinct and recognizable phases, those of Survival, Inquiry and Sophistication, otherwise known as the How, Why, and Where phases.  For instance, the first phase is characterized by the question 'How can we eat?' the second by the question 'Why do we eat?' and the third by the question 'Where shall we have lunch?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31698-he-tried-to-name-which-of-the-deadly-seven-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 06:21:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31698-he-tried-to-name-which-of-the-deadly-seven-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He tried to name which of the deadly seven might apply, and when he failed he decided to append an eighth, regret." -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387480-she-had-been-struck-by-the-figure-of-a-woman-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 06:26:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charles Frazier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/387480-she-had-been-struck-by-the-figure-of-a-woman-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been struck by the figure of a woman's back in a mirror. She stopped and looked. The dress the figure wore was the color called ashes of roses, and Ada stood, held in place by a sharp stitch of envy or th woman's dress and the fine shape of her back and her thick dark hair and the sense of assurance she seemed to evidence in her very posture.

Then Ada took a step forward, and the other woman did too, and Ada realized that it was herself she was admiring, the mirror having caught the reflection of an opposite mirror on the wall behind her. The light of the lamps and the tint of the mirrors had conspired to shift colors, bleaching mauve to rose. She climbed the steps to her room and prepared for bed, but she slept poorly that night, for the music went on until dawn. As she lay awake she thought how odd it had felt to win her own endorsement." -- Charles Frazier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2397-there-is-a-theory-which-states-that-if-ever-anyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 06:46:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2397-there-is-a-theory-which-states-that-if-ever-anyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a theory which states that if ever anyone discovers exactly what the Universe is for and why it is here, it will instantly disappear and be replaced by something even more bizarre and inexplicable. 
There is another theory which states that this has already happened." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3156-the-guide-says-there-is-an-art-to-flying-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 06:55:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3156-the-guide-says-there-is-an-art-to-flying-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Guide says there is an art to flying&quot;, said Ford, &quot;or rather a knack. The knack lies in learning how to throw yourself at the ground and miss." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175854-but-thou-mayest-why-that-makes-a-man-great-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 19:28:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175854-but-thou-mayest-why-that-makes-a-man-great-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But 'Thou mayest!'! Why, that makes a man great, that gives him stature with the gods, for in his weakness and his filth and his murder of his brother he has still the great choice. He can choose his course and fight it through and win" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
