<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867955-joe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/867955-joe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 14:00:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538794-harry-potter-is-about-confronting-fears-finding-inner-strength-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 14:00:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/538794-harry-potter-is-about-confronting-fears-finding-inner-strength-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Harry Potter is about confronting fears, finding inner strength and doing
what is right in the face of adversity. Twilight is about how important it
is to have a boyfriend." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834249-a-hot-city-slaked-out-on-the-banks-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:06:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Richard Jessup]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834249-a-hot-city-slaked-out-on-the-banks-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A hot city, slaked out on the banks of the Mississippi, with too much of its muscle showing to be a dignified city." -- Richard Jessup]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834251-a-breath-of-air-caught-the-bottom-of-the-shade</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:07:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Richard Jessup]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834251-a-breath-of-air-caught-the-bottom-of-the-shade]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A breath of air caught the bottom of the shade, brushed it, and a streak of golden sunlight flashed instantly into the room.  Then, as quickly, the air sucked the shade back into position and it was dark again." -- Richard Jessup]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834252-i-knowed-lancey-from-back-yonder-i-see-him-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:11:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Richard Jessup]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834252-i-knowed-lancey-from-back-yonder-i-see-him-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I knowed Lancey from back yonder.  I see him to Nig's in Memphis and down to Yeller's in Noorlins, back yonder when they was shunting booze into the country.  Him.  Sheet!  Nothing but a comer like you, Kid, only he liked wimmen too.  Always got to feel a leg, that's the kind he is.  Oooeeeh!  That sonsabitch is cold.  I seen him gut a feller with a furth card and rattle him s'bad, the feller quit and got up and pissed red in the john and went square.  They ain't but one way to ferk with the kind of man Lancey Hodges is..." -- Richard Jessup]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834253-good-crowd-lancey-said-yeah-the-kid-said-nice-groceries</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:15:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Richard Jessup]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834253-good-crowd-lancey-said-yeah-the-kid-said-nice-groceries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good crowd,&quot; Lancey said.
&quot;Yeah,&quot; the Kid said.
&quot;Nice groceries, too.&quot;
&quot;And good booze.  My brandy must be Napoleon.&quot;
&quot;Uh-huh.&quot;
&quot;Yeah.&quot;
&quot;Nice looking broads.&quot;
&quot;That's a fact,&quot; The Kid said.
&quot;Ain't that Shooter something?  Love to see him skin a deck.&quot;
&quot;It's downright sexy,&quot; The Kid said.
&quot;He loves 'em.&quot;
&quot;Like stroking a beautiful tit,&quot; The Kid said.
&quot;That's it - that's it,&quot; Lancey said, nodding." -- Richard Jessup]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834254-i-remember-being-unusually-pensive-that-may-evening-perhaps-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Neal Cassady]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834254-i-remember-being-unusually-pensive-that-may-evening-perhaps-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember being unusually pensive that May evening, perhaps it was the heat of Spring's first warm day which, encountering my thick winter blood, forced a dilution upward into a brain weary of straining the last six months to overcome freezing and the long absent thinning of blood stirred a weakening desire for the softer things, a nostalgia, yet a death, a precognition, if you will..." -- Neal Cassady]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834262-like-here-it-was-that-i-entered-that-stage-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 20:45:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Neal Cassady]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834262-like-here-it-was-that-i-entered-that-stage-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like here it was that I entered that stage when a child overcomes naivite enough to realize an adult's emotional reaction as somethimes freakish for its inconsistencies, so can, on his own reasoning canvas, paint those early pale colors of judgement, resulting from initial moments of ability to critically examine life's perplexities, in tentative little brain-engine stirrings, before they faded to quickly join that train of remembered experience carrying signals indicating existence which itself far outweighs traction effort by thinking's soon slipping drivers to effectively resist any slack-action advantage, for starting so necessitates continual cuts on the hauler - performed as if governed lifelong by the tagwork of a student-green foreman who, crushed under on rushing time always building against his excessive load of emotional contents, is forever a lost ball in the high weeds of personal developments - until, with ever changing emphasis through a whole series of grades of consciousness (leading up from root-beginnings of obscure childish inconscious soul within a world), early lack - for what child sustains logic? - reaches a point of late fossilization, resultant of repeated wrong moves in endless switching of dark significances crammed inside the cranium, where, through such hindering habits, there no longer is the flexibility for thought transfer and unloading of dead freight that a standard gauge would afford and thus, as Faustian Destiny dictates, is an inept mink, limited, being in existence firmly tracked just above the constant &quot;T&quot; biased ballast supporting wherever space yearnings lead the worn rails of civilized comprehension, so henceforth is restricted to mere pickups and setouts of drab distortion, while traveling wearily along its familiar Western Thinking right-of-way.  But choo-choo nonsense aside, ..." -- Neal Cassady]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834899-i-was-going-to-grow-up-to-walk-in-sleet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 19:55:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834899-i-was-going-to-grow-up-to-walk-in-sleet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was going to grow up to walk in sleet in fields..." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834901-somewhere-in-the-vast-jewelry-of-the-long-island-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 19:56:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834901-somewhere-in-the-vast-jewelry-of-the-long-island-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Somewhere in the vast jewelry of the Long Island night we walked, in wind and rain..." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834905-can-i-make-you-happier-with-powder-on-my-chest</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 19:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/834905-can-i-make-you-happier-with-powder-on-my-chest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can I make you happier with powder on my chest?  Do you need a thousand movie shows?  Sixteen million people to ride the bus with, hit the stop—I shoulda never let you go away from home—“  Rich lips brooded in my deaf ear.  “The fog’ll fall all over you, Jacky, you’ll wait in fields—You’ll let me die—you wont come save me—I wont even know where your grave is—remember what you were like, where your house, what your life—you’ll die without knowing what happened to my face—my love—my youth—You’ll burn yourself out like a moth jumping in a locomotive boiler looking for light—Jacky—and you’ll be dead—and lose yourself from yourself—and forget—and sink—and me too—and what is all this then?”
“I dont know—“
“Then come back to our porch of the river the night time the trees and you love stars—I hear the bus on the corner—where you’re getting off—no more, boy, no more—I saw, had visions and idees of you handsome my husband walking across the top of the America with your lantern...
Out of her eyes I saw smoldering I’d like to rip this damn dress off and never see it again!" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188789-from-the-first-day-i-met-his-daughter-all-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 12:18:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188789-from-the-first-day-i-met-his-daughter-all-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the first day I met his daughter, all I could think about was snuffling up under that sweet dimity like some bad old bear, just crawling up into that honeycomb, nose twitching, and never come out of there till early spring. Think that’s disgusting? Dammit, I do, too, but that’s the way male animals are made. Those peculiar delights were created to entrap us, and anybody who disapproves can take it up with God.

In their wondrous capacity of knowing the Lord’s mind, churchly folks will tell you that He would purely hate to hear such dirty talk. My idea is, He wouldn’t mind it half so much as they would have us think, because even according to their own queer creed, we are God’s handiwork, created in His image, lust, piss, shit, and all. Without that magnificent Almighty lust that we mere mortals dare to call a sin, there wouldn’t be any more mortals, and God’s grand design for the human race, if He exists and if He ever had one, would turn to dust, and dust unto dust, forever and amen. Other creatures would step up and take over, realizing that man was too weak and foolish to properly reproduce himself. I nominate hogs to inherit the Earth, because hogs love to eat any old damned thing God sets in front of them, and they’re ever so grateful for God’s green earth even when it’s all rain and mud, and they just plain adore to feed and fuck and frolic and fulfill God’s holy plan. For all we know, it’s hogs which are created in God’s image, who’s to say?" -- Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840904-in-the-jungle-during-one-night-in-each-month-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 12:39:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840904-in-the-jungle-during-one-night-in-each-month-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the jungle, during one night in each month, the moths did not come to the lanterns; through the black reaches of the outer night, so it was said, they flew toward the full moon." -- Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840908-holding-his-breath-swaying-drunkenly-beneath-a-bulb-which-illumined</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 12:41:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840908-holding-his-breath-swaying-drunkenly-beneath-a-bulb-which-illumined]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holding his breath, swaying drunkenly beneath a bulb which illumined little more than grime and moisture, Moon stared awhile at the cement wall; it took just such a hopeless international latrine in the early hours of a morning, when a man was weak in the knees, short in the breath, numb in the forehead and rotten in the gut, to make him wonder where he was, how he got there, where he was going; he realized that he did not know and never would. He had confronted this same latrine on every continent and not once had it come up with an answer; or rather, it always came up with the same answer, a suck and gurgle of unspeakable vileness, a sort of self-satisfied low chuckling: Go to it, man, you’re pissing your life away." -- Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840909-you-mean-billy-exclaimed-at-last-you-mean-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 12:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840909-you-mean-billy-exclaimed-at-last-you-mean-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You mean...” Billy exclaimed at last, “you mean...” – his voice rose high and clear – “you mean...” – and he jumped to his feet, and standing there under the giant trees, pointed at himself, a small outraged boy named William Martin Quarrier, aged eight: “You mean I just came crashing down into Ma’s under-pants?" -- Peter Matthiessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840915-i-unknot-his-tie-and-offer-him-a-cold-sandwich</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 12:53:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Grace Paley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/840915-i-unknot-his-tie-and-offer-him-a-cold-sandwich]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I unknot his tie and offer him a cold sandwich.  He raps my backside, paying attention to the bounce.  I walk around him as though he were a Maypole, kissing as I go.
“I lost my cuff link, goddamnit” he says, and drops to the floor to look for it.  I go down too on my knees, but I know he never had a cuff link in his life.  Still I would do a lot for him.
“Got you off you feet that time,” he says, laughing.  “Oh yes, I did.”  And before I can even make myself half comfortable on that polka-dotted linoleum, he got onto me right where we were, and the truth is, we were so happy, we forgot the precautions." -- Grace Paley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/841035-doc-bought-a-package-of-yellow-pads-and-two-dozen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 16:49:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/841035-doc-bought-a-package-of-yellow-pads-and-two-dozen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Doc bought a package of yellow pads and two dozen pencils.  He laid them out on his desk, the pencils sharpened to needle points and lined up like yellow soldiers.  At the top of a page he printed: OBSERVATIONS AND SPECULATIONS.  His pencil point broke.  He took up another and drew lace around the O and the B, made a block letter of the S and put fish hooks on each end.  His ankle itched.  He rolled down his sock and scratched, and that made his ear itch.  “Someone’s talking about me,” he said and looked at the yellow pad.  He wondered whether he had fed the cotton rats.  It is easy to forget when you’re thinking." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/841036-the-pictures-were-designed-to-soothe-without-arousing-interest</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2013 16:50:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/841036-the-pictures-were-designed-to-soothe-without-arousing-interest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... the pictures were designed to soothe without arousing interest – engravings of cows in ponds, deer in streams, dogs in lakes.  Wet animals seem to serve some human need." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958995-it-s-true-that-when-you-read-ya-you-rarely-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2013 11:42:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Erin Bow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/958995-it-s-true-that-when-you-read-ya-you-rarely-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's true that when you read YA you rarely have to read about middle-aged men having affairs.  Personally I consider that a plus." -- Erin Bow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2338-if-i-can-t-dance-to-it-it-s-not-my-revolution</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 10:15:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2338-if-i-can-t-dance-to-it-it-s-not-my-revolution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I can't dance to it, it's not my revolution." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1092205-craftsmanship-names-an-enduring-basic-human-impulse-the-desire-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 07:59:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Richard Sennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1092205-craftsmanship-names-an-enduring-basic-human-impulse-the-desire-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Craftsmanship names an enduring, basic human impulse, the desire to do a job well for its own sake." -- Richard Sennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120195-factory-windows-are-always-broken-other-windows-are-let-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 12:06:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by Vachel Lindsay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1120195-factory-windows-are-always-broken-other-windows-are-let-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Factory windows are always broken
Other windows are let alone.
No one throws through the chapel-window
The bitter, snarling, derisive stone." -- Vachel Lindsay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591983-yes-i-have-actually-mined-coal-and-distilled-liquor-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 11:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joe add a quote by James M. Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591983-yes-i-have-actually-mined-coal-and-distilled-liquor-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, I have actually mined coal, and distilled liquor, as well as seen a girl in a pink dress, and seen her take it off.  I am 54 years old, weigh 220 pounds, and look like the chief dispatcher of a long-distance driving concern.  I am a registered Democrat.  I drink." -- James M. Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
