<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/868069-noah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/868069-noah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 16:14:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 16:14:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 08:46:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1342-goodbye-said-the-fox-and-now-here-is-my-secret]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Goodbye,&quot; said the fox. &quot;And now here is my secret, a very simple secret: It is only with the heart that one can see rightly; what is essential is invisible to the eye." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6044-quand-tu-veux-construire-un-bateau-ne-commence-pas-par</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 08:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6044-quand-tu-veux-construire-un-bateau-ne-commence-pas-par]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quand tu veux construire un bateau, ne commence pas par rassembler du bois, couper des planches et distribuer du travail, mais reveille au sein des hommes le desir de la mer grande et large.

If you want to build a ship, don't drum up people together to collect wood and don't assign them tasks and work, but rather teach them to long for the endless immensity of the sea." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16480-we-have-come-from-god-and-inevitably-the-myths-woven</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 19:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16480-we-have-come-from-god-and-inevitably-the-myths-woven]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have come from God, and inevitably the myths woven by us, though they contain error, will also reflect a splintered fragment of the true light, the eternal truth that is with God.  Indeed only by myth-making, only by becoming 'sub-creator' and inventing stories, can Man aspire to the state of perfection that he knew before the Fall.  Our myths may be misguided, but they steer however shakily towards the true harbour, while materialistic 'progress' leads only to a yawning abyss and the Iron Crown of the power of evil." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40267-a-man-inherited-a-field-in-which-was-an-accumulation</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 19:17:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40267-a-man-inherited-a-field-in-which-was-an-accumulation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man inherited a field in which was an accumulation of old stone, part of an older hall.  Of the old stone some had already been used in building the house in which he actually lived, not far from the old house of his fathers.  Of the rest he took some and built a tower.  But his friends coming perceived at once (without troubling to climb the steps) that these stones had formerly belonged to a more ancient building.  So they pushed the tower over, with no little labour, and in order to look for hidden carvings and inscriptions, or to discover whence the man's distant forefathers had obtained their building material.  Some suspecting a deposit of coal under the soil began to dig for it, and forgot even the stones.  They all said: 'This tower is most interesting.' But they also said (after pushing it over): 'What a muddle it is in!' And even the man's own descendants, who might have been expected to consider what he had been about, were heard to murmur: 'He is such an odd fellow!  Imagine using these old stones just to build a nonsensical tower!  Why did not he restore the old house?  he had no sense of proportion.'  But from the top of that tower the man had been able to look out upon the sea." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 08:34:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have claimed that Escape is one of the main functions of fairy-stories, and since I do not disapprove of them, it is plain that I do not accept the tone of scorn or pity with which 'Escape' is now so often used. Why should a man be scorned if, finding himself in prison, he tries to get out and go home? Or if he cannot do so, he thinks and talks about other topics than jailers and prison-walls?" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6156-in-old-days-books-were-written-by-men-of-letters</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 08:34:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6156-in-old-days-books-were-written-by-men-of-letters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In old days books were written by men of letters and read by the public. Nowadays books are written by the public and read by nobody." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38702-myths-are-public-dreams-dreams-are-private-myths</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 23:11:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38702-myths-are-public-dreams-dreams-are-private-myths]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Myths are public dreams, dreams are private myths." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125802-in-reading-great-literature-i-become-a-thousand-men-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 13:56:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Noah add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125802-in-reading-great-literature-i-become-a-thousand-men-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In reading great literature I become a thousand men and yet remain myself...I see with a myriad of eyes,but it is still I who see." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
