<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/868307-jane]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/868307-jane" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:19:11 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16309-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-people-in-the-end</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:19:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16309-there-are-only-two-kinds-of-people-in-the-end]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two kinds of people in the end: those who say to God, &quot;Thy will be done,&quot; and those to whom God says, in the end, &quot;Thy will be done.&quot; All that are in Hell, choose it. Without that self-choice there could be no Hell. No soul that seriously and constantly desires joy will ever miss it. Those who seek find. Those who knock it is opened." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33128-and-out-of-that-hopeless-attempt-has-come-nearly-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:20:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33128-and-out-of-that-hopeless-attempt-has-come-nearly-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And out of that hopeless attempt has come nearly all that we call human history—money, poverty, ambition, war, prostitution, classes, empires, slavery—the long terrible story of man trying to find something other than God which will make him happy." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35094-miss-barry-was-a-kindred-spirit-after-all-anne-confided</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:20:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35094-miss-barry-was-a-kindred-spirit-after-all-anne-confided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miss Barry was a kindred spirit after all,&quot; Anne confided to Marilla, &quot;You wouldn't think so to look at her, but she is. . . Kindred spirits are not so scarce as I used to think. It's splendid to find out there are so many of them in the world." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79805-our-opportunities-to-give-of-ourselves-are-indeed-limitless-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:21:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79805-our-opportunities-to-give-of-ourselves-are-indeed-limitless-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our opportunities to give of ourselves are indeed limitless, but they are also perishable. There are hearts to gladden. There are kind words to say. There are gifts to be given. There are deeds to be done. There are souls to be saved.

As we remember that “when ye are in the service of your fellow beings ye are only in the service of your God,” (Mosiah 2:17) we will not find ourselves in the unenviable position of Jacob Marley’s ghost, who spoke to Ebenezer Scrooge in Charles Dickens’s immortal &quot;Christmas Carol.&quot; Marley spoke sadly of opportunities lost. Said he: 'Not to know that any Christian spirit working kindly in its little sphere, whatever it may be, will find its mortal life too short for its vast means of usefulness. Not to know that no space of regret can make amends for one life’s opportunity misused! Yet such was I! Oh! such was I!'

Marley added: 'Why did I walk through crowds of fellow-beings with my eyes turned down, and never raise them to that blessed Star which led the Wise Men to a poor abode? Were there no poor homes to which its light would have conducted me!'

Fortunately, as we know, Ebenezer Scrooge changed his life for the better. I love his line, 'I am not the man I was.'

Why is Dickens’ &quot;Christmas Carol&quot; so popular? Why is it ever new? I personally feel it is inspired of God. It brings out the best within human nature. It gives hope. It motivates change. We can turn from the paths which would lead us down and, with a song in our hearts, follow a star and walk toward the light. We can quicken our step, bolster our courage, and bask in the sunlight of truth. We can hear more clearly the laughter of little children. We can dry the tear of the weeping. We can comfort the dying by sharing the promise of eternal life. If we lift one weary hand which hangs down, if we bring peace to one struggling soul, if we give as did the Master, we can—by showing the way—become a guiding star for some lost mariner." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61675-never-did-she-find-anything-so-difficult-as-to-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2011 13:23:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jane add a quote by Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61675-never-did-she-find-anything-so-difficult-as-to-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never did she find anything so difficult as to keep herself from losing her temper when she was suddenly disturbed while absorbed in a book. People who are fond of books know the feeling of irritation which sweeps over them at such a moment. The temptation to be unreasonable and snappish is one not easy to manage.

&quot;It makes me feel as if something had hit me,&quot; Sara had told Ermengarde once in confidence. &quot;And as if I want to hit back. I have to remember things quickly to keep from saying something ill-tempered." -- Frances Hodgson Burnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
