<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/86904-darice]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/86904-darice" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:15:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47679-how-many-people-ask-you-to-come-share-their-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47679-how-many-people-ask-you-to-come-share-their-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How many people ask you to come share their life?" -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24441-that-was-the-thing-about-words-they-were-clear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24441-that-was-the-thing-about-words-they-were-clear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was the thing about words, they were clear and specific-chair, eye, stone- but when you talked about feelings, words were too stiff, they were this and not that, they couldn't include all the meanings. In defining, they always left something out." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27661-in-a-perverse-way-i-was-glad-for-the-stitches</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:14:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27661-in-a-perverse-way-i-was-glad-for-the-stitches]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a perverse way, I was glad for the stitches, glad it would show, that there would be scars. What was the point in just being hurt on the inside? It should bloody well show." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35086-people-go-on-marrying-because-they-can-t-resist-natural-forces</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:13:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35086-people-go-on-marrying-because-they-can-t-resist-natural-forces]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People go on marrying because they can't resist natural forces, although many of them may know perfectly well that they are possibly buying a month's pleasure with a life's discomfort." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78134-a-man-s-silence-is-wonderful-to-listen-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by thomas hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78134-a-man-s-silence-is-wonderful-to-listen-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man's silence is wonderful to listen to." -- thomas hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35083-some-women-s-love-of-being-loved-is-insatiable-and-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 15:08:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35083-some-women-s-love-of-being-loved-is-insatiable-and-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some women's love of being loved is insatiable; and so, often, is their love of loving; and in the last case they may find that they can't give it continuously to the chamber-officer appointed by the bishop's license to receive it." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95138-let-me-enjoy-the-earth-no-less-because-the-all-enacting</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 15:11:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95138-let-me-enjoy-the-earth-no-less-because-the-all-enacting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me enjoy the earth no less because the all-enacting light that fashioned forth its loveliness had other aims than my delight." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1327-always-learn-poems-by-heart-they-have-to-become-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:14:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1327-always-learn-poems-by-heart-they-have-to-become-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always learn poems by heart. They have to become the marrow in your bones. Like fluoride in the water, they'll make your soul impervious to the world's soft decay." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77077-i-don-t-let-anyone-touch-me-i-finally-said-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 15:14:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77077-i-don-t-let-anyone-touch-me-i-finally-said-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't let anyone touch me,&quot; I finally said.
Why not?&quot;
Why not? Because I was tired of men. Hanging in doorways, standing too close, their smell of beer or fifteen-year-old whiskey. Men who didn't come to the emergency room with you, men who left on Christmas Eve. Men who slammed the security gates, who made you love them then changed their minds. Forests of boys, their ragged shrubs full of eyes following you, grabbing your breasts, waving their money, eyes already knocking you down, taking what they felt was theirs. (...) It was a play and I knew how it ended, I didn't want to audition for any of the roles. It was no game, no casual thrill. It was three-bullet Russian roulette." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110973-let-me-tell-you-a-few-things-about-regret-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 15:17:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110973-let-me-tell-you-a-few-things-about-regret-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me tell you a few things about regret...There is no end to it.  You cannot find the beginning of the chain that brought us from there to here.  Should you regret the whole chain, and the air in between, or each link separately as if you could uncouple them?  Do you regret the beginning which ended so badly, or just the ending itself?" -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35085-it-is-foreign-to-a-man-s-nature-to-go-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 13:13:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Thomas Hardy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35085-it-is-foreign-to-a-man-s-nature-to-go-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it is foreign to a man's nature to go on loving a person when he is told that he must and shall be that person's lover. There would be a much likelier chance of his doing it if he were told not to love. If the marriage ceremony consisted in an oath and signed contract between the parties to cease loving from that day forward, in consideration of personal possession being given, and to avoid each other's society as much as possible in public, there would be more loving couples than there are now. Fancy the secret meetings between the perjuring husband and wife, the denials of having seen each other, the clambering in at bedroom windows, and the hiding in closets! There'd be little cooling then." -- Thomas Hardy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974988-i-don-t-remember-a-time-in-my-life-that-jules</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2013 08:19:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Kristen Proby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974988-i-don-t-remember-a-time-in-my-life-that-jules]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don’t remember a time in my life that Jules and her family weren’t in it. You have shared everything that has ever mattered with me, even the birth of my baby. When Jules and Nate got together,” Natalie turns to the audience and smiles. Will takes my hand in his and kisses my knuckles. “I was astonished to watch the change in her. Jules is a kick-ass girl. She’s not big on public displays of affection, which she reminds me of almost daily.” “Seriously, you guys are gross,” Jules rolls her eyes, but I can see the tears threatening to spill over. “But Nate brought out that soft side of her. He makes her better. And I think she does the same for him. I just couldn’t have found anyone more suited to you, my friend, if I tried.” Nat raises her glass and we all follow suit. “So, to my new brother-in-law Nate, and my sister of the heart, his Julianne. May your love continue to grow every day." -- Kristen Proby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378521-it-s-all-very-well-to-read-about-sorrows-and-imagine</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:47:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/378521-it-s-all-very-well-to-read-about-sorrows-and-imagine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's all very well to read about sorrows and imagine yourself living through them heroically, but it's not so nice when you really come to have them, is it?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396231-well-now-i-d-rather-have-you-than-a-dozen-boys</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:48:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396231-well-now-i-d-rather-have-you-than-a-dozen-boys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well now, I'd rather have you than a dozen boys, Anne,' said Matthew patting her hand.  'Just mind you that — rather than a dozen boys.  Well now, I guess it wasn't a boy that took the Avery scholarship, was it?  It was a girl — my girl — my girl that I'm proud of." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358882-do-you-think-amethysts-can-be-the-souls-of-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:49:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/358882-do-you-think-amethysts-can-be-the-souls-of-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think amethysts can be the souls of good violets?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396211-listen-to-the-trees-talking-in-their-sleep-she-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:49:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396211-listen-to-the-trees-talking-in-their-sleep-she-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the trees talking in their sleep,' she whispered, as he lifted her to the ground.  'What nice dreams they must have!" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299042-when-i-left-queen-s-my-future-seemed-to-stretch-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:51:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299042-when-i-left-queen-s-my-future-seemed-to-stretch-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I left Queen's my future seemed to stretch out before me like a straight road. I thought I could see along it for many a milestone. Now there is a bend in it. I don't know what lies around the bend, but I am going to believe that the best does. It has a fascination of its own, that bend, Marilla. I wonder how the road beyond it goes - what there is of green glory and soft, checkered light and shadows - what new landscapes - what new beauties - what curves and hills and valleys farther on." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528272-mrs-spencer-said-it-was-wicked-of-me-to-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 17:54:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/528272-mrs-spencer-said-it-was-wicked-of-me-to-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mrs. Spencer said it was wicked of me to talk like that, but I didn’t mean to be wicked. It’s so easy to be wicked without knowing it, isn’t it?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970125-i-used-to-think-that-when-people-fell-in-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 23:00:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Veronica Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/970125-i-used-to-think-that-when-people-fell-in-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to think that when people fell in love, they just landed where they landed, and they had no choice in the matter afterward. And maybe that’s true of beginnings, but it’s not true of this, now. I fell in love with him. But I don’t just stay with him by default as if there’s no one else available to me. I stay with him because I choose to, every day that I wake up, every day that we fight or lie to each other or disappoint each other. I choose him over and over again, and he chooses me." -- Veronica Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1042389-bloody-men-bloody-men-are-like-bloody-buses-you-wait</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 19:34:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Daisy Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1042389-bloody-men-bloody-men-are-like-bloody-buses-you-wait]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bloody Men Bloody men are like bloody buses— You wait for about a year— And as soon as one approaches your stop Two or three others appear. You look at them flashing their indicators, Offering you a ride. You’re trying to read the destinations, You haven’t much time to decide. If you make a mistake, there is no turning back. Jump off, and you’ll stand there and gaze While the cars and taxis and lorries go by And the minutes, the hours, the days. Wendy Cope" -- Daisy Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1042454-love-poem-sharing-one-umbrella-we-have-to-hold-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 19:52:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Daisy Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1042454-love-poem-sharing-one-umbrella-we-have-to-hold-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love Poem Sharing one umbrella We have to hold each other Round the waist to keep together. You ask me why I’m smiling — It’s because I’m thinking I want it to rain for ever. Vicki Feaver" -- Daisy Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2014 11:06:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465988-sometimes-you-read-a-book-and-it-fills-you-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, you read a book and it fills you with this weird evangelical zeal, and you become convinced that the shattered world will never be put back together unless and until all living humans read the book." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1086275-were-she-better-or-you-sicker-then-the-stars-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 23:35:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1086275-were-she-better-or-you-sicker-then-the-stars-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were she better or you sicker, then the stars would not be so terribly crossed, but it is the nature of stars to cross, and never was Shakespeare more wrong than when he had Cassius note, “The fault, dear Brutus, is not in our stars / But in ourselves.” Easy enough to say when you’re a Roman nobleman (or Shakespeare!), but there is no shortage of fault to be found amid our stars." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1185856-i-know-i-know-she-seems-a-little-crossing-his-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 06:28:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Marissa Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1185856-i-know-i-know-she-seems-a-little-crossing-his-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know, I know. She seems a little”—crossing his eyes, he swirled both fingers around his ears—“but it’s really part of her charm, once you get to know her." -- Marissa Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/953170-i-have-always-felt-nathan-said-that-the-truth-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 23:25:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/953170-i-have-always-felt-nathan-said-that-the-truth-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always felt,” Nathan said, “that the truth is simply the truth. And perhaps does not exist for us to bend and revise. Or even filter to suit the feelings of those we love and want to protect." -- Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1207888-world-is-full-of-people-so-troubled-they-don-t-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 06:19:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1207888-world-is-full-of-people-so-troubled-they-don-t-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["World is full of people so troubled they don’t even understand themselves. You could offer them a thousand dollars to explain their motivations, but they can’t tell you what they don’t know. And most of those miserable creatures find their way through here soon enough. So, I’m sorry, Mr. McCann. If there was a reason, it died with her. But if you ask me, it’s a question that never had an answer. Because there’s just no explanation that makes a lick of sense." -- Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216101-in-the-beginnings-of-that-silence-he-knew-something-clearly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 23:03:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1216101-in-the-beginnings-of-that-silence-he-knew-something-clearly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the beginnings of that silence, he knew something. Clearly. Once you throw down that gauntlet of ultimatum, the “one more thing” will happen. Nat figured it probably wouldn’t even matter much what it was. It would be the straw that broke her. And it had been defined. Prepared for. So it would happen. It was only a matter of time." -- Catherine Ryan Hyde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231240-i-want-to-pull-finny-out-of-my-mind-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 23:58:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Laura Nowlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231240-i-want-to-pull-finny-out-of-my-mind-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to pull Finny out of my mind like a splinter so that I can adore Jamie the way he deserves to be adored. And even more than that, because I am a selfish, bad creature, I want to feel that adoration. I want to be free of this guilt." -- Laura Nowlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231243-i-lay-on-my-bed-in-late-afternoon-watching-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2014 00:01:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Laura Nowlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231243-i-lay-on-my-bed-in-late-afternoon-watching-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I lay on my bed in late afternoon, watching a patch of light move across the floor, my throat tight, my body still. This is the saddest part of any day, when too much time has passed to create happiness while it is still light out. It’s too late. The daylight has been squandered on my immobility. The patch of light falls still; it begins to fade. It will be better when it is gone. This is only one day, I remind myself, and it is very nearly over." -- Laura Nowlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1251747-when-one-is-confronted-with-a-random-act-of-kindness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 16:48:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Darice add a quote by Heather Burch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1251747-when-one-is-confronted-with-a-random-act-of-kindness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When one is confronted with a random act of kindness that is neither expected nor ordinary, one is obligated to meet that kindness and exceed it if possible." -- Heather Burch]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
