<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/869238-kathy-wright]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/869238-kathy-wright" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 01:54:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388651-glanced-up-and-caught-ammu-s-gaze-centuries-telescoped-into-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 01:54:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388651-glanced-up-and-caught-ammu-s-gaze-centuries-telescoped-into-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...glanced up and caught Ammu's gaze. Centuries telescoped into one evanescent moment. History was wrong-footed, caught off guard. Sloughed off like an old snakeskin. Its marks , its scars its wouns from old wars and the walking backwards days all fell away. In its abscence it left an aura, a palpable shimmering that was as plain as water in a river or the sun in the sky. As plain to feel the heat on a hot day, or the tug of a fish on a taut line. So obvious that no-one noticed.
  In that brief moment, Velutha looked up and saw things that he hadn't seen before. Things that had been out of bounds so far, obscured by histor's blinkers.
...This knowing slid into him cleanly, like the sharp edge of a knife. Cold and hot at once. It only took a moment.
  Ammu saw that he saw. She looked away. He did too. History's fiends returned to claim them. To rewrap them in its old scarred pelt and drag them back to where they really lived. Where the Love Laws lay down who should be loved. And how. And how much." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388657-it-wasn-t-what-lay-at-the-end-of-her-road</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 02:05:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388657-it-wasn-t-what-lay-at-the-end-of-her-road]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It wasn't what lay at the end of her road that frightened Ammu as much as the nature of the road itself. No milestones marked its progress. No trees grew along it. No dappled shadows shaded it. No mists rolled over it. No birds circled it. No twists, no turns or hairpin bends obscured even momentarily, her clear view of the end. This filled Ammu with an awful dread, because she was not the kind of woman who wanted her future told. She dreaded it too much. So if she were granted one small wish perhaps it would have been Not to Know, Not to know what each day hed in store for her. Not to know where she might be, next month, next year. Ten years on. Not to know which way her road might turn and what lay beyond the bend." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388659-she-discovered-that-underneath-the-aspect-of-the-rumpled-porcupine</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2011 02:12:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/388659-she-discovered-that-underneath-the-aspect-of-the-rumpled-porcupine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She discovered that underneath the aspect of the Rumpled Porcupine, a tortured Marxist was at war with an impossible, incurable Romantic - who forgot the candles, who broke the wine glasses, who forgot the ring. Who made love to her with a passion that took her breath away. She had always thought of herself as a somewhat uninteresting, thick-waisted, thick ankled girl. Not bad-looking. Not special. But when she was with Chacko, old limits were pushed back. Horizons expanded.
She had never before met a man who spoke of the workd - of what it was, and how it came to be, or what he thought would become of it - in the way in which other men she knew discussed their jobs, their friends or their weekends at the beach.
Being with Chacko made Margaret Kochamma feel as though her soul had escaped from the narrow confines of her island country, into the vast extravagant spaces of his. He made her feel as though the world belonged to them - as though it lay before thm like an opened frog on a dissecting table, begging to be examined." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4735-fate-is-like-a-strange-unpopular-restaurant-filled-with-odd</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 23:00:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathy add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4735-fate-is-like-a-strange-unpopular-restaurant-filled-with-odd]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fate is like a strange, unpopular restaurant filled with odd little waiters who bring you things you never asked for and don't always like." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
