<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/869364-savo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/869364-savo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:51:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22336-we-learn-from-history-that-we-don-t-learn-from-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:51:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Savo add a quote by Desmond Tutu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22336-we-learn-from-history-that-we-don-t-learn-from-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We learn from history that we don't learn from history!" -- Desmond Tutu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23198-despite-the-variety-and-the-differences-and-however-much-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 05:29:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Savo add a quote by Edward Said]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23198-despite-the-variety-and-the-differences-and-however-much-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despite the variety and the differences, and however much we proclaim the contrary, what the media produce is neither spontaneous nor completely “free:” “news” does not just happen, pictures and ideas do not merely spring from reality into our eyes and minds, truth is not directly available, we do not have unrestrained variety at our disposal. 

For like all modes of communication, television, radio, and newspapers observe certain rules and conventions to get things across intelligibly, and it is these, often more than the reality being conveyed, that shape the material delivered by the media. " -- Edward Said]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23199-those-who-make-us-believe-that-anything-s-possible-and-fire</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 05:30:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Savo add a quote by Paul Rogat Loeb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23199-those-who-make-us-believe-that-anything-s-possible-and-fire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who make us believe that anything’s possible and fire our imagination over the long haul, are often the ones who have survived the bleakest of circumstances. The men and women who have every reason to despair, but don’t, may have the most to teach us, not only about how to hold true to our beliefs, but about how such a life can bring about seemingly impossible social change. " -- Paul Rogat Loeb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25225-all-knowledge-that-is-about-human-society-and-not-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 06:15:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Savo add a quote by Edward Said]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25225-all-knowledge-that-is-about-human-society-and-not-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All knowledge that is about human society, and not about the natural world, is historical knowledge, and therefore rests upon judgment and interpretation. This is not to say that facts or data are nonexistent, but that facts get their importance from what is made of them in interpretation… for interpretations depend very much on who the interpreter is, who he or she is addressing, what his or her purpose is, at what historical moment the interpretation takes place." -- Edward Said]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
