<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/870333-laurel-wicke]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/870333-laurel-wicke" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 14:31:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66209-any-nation-that-expects-to-be-ignorant-and-free-jefferson</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 14:31:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66209-any-nation-that-expects-to-be-ignorant-and-free-jefferson]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any nation that expects to be ignorant and free,&quot; Jefferson said, &quot;expects what never was and never will be.&quot; And if the gap between the educated and the uneducated in America continues to grow as it is in our time, as fast as or faster than the gap between the rich and the poor, the gap between the educated and the uneducated is going to be of greater consequence and the more serious threat to our way of life. We must not, by any means, misunderstand that." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43584-the-submission-of-one-s-will-is-really-the-only-uniquely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2010 11:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43584-the-submission-of-one-s-will-is-really-the-only-uniquely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The submission of one's will is really the only uniquely personal thing we have to place on God's altar.  The many other things we 'give' are actually the things He has already given or loaned to us." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386554-i-viewed-with-regret-the-many-hours-i-have-spent</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:37:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Merriweather Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386554-i-viewed-with-regret-the-many-hours-i-have-spent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I viewed with regret the many hours I have spent in indolence, and now sorely felt the want of that information which those hours would have given me had they been judidiously expended.  But since they are past and cannot be recalled, I dash from me the gloomy thought, and resolved in future, to redouble my exertions and at least endeavor to promote those two primary objects of human existence, by giving them the aid of that portion of talents which nature and fortune have bestowed upon me; or in future, to live for MANKIND, as I have hertofore lived FOR MYSELF." -- Merriweather Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386555-but-then-he-remembered-what-george-had-told-him-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:39:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by James Alexander Thom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386555-but-then-he-remembered-what-george-had-told-him-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But then he remembered what George had told him about pain. You know what you can do, even if your body says quit. It's only pain.

&quot;It's only pain, he thought, hearing George's voice and seeing his eagle-face. If anyone would know, George would, he thought. And truly, he thought, it's the most useful one thing a body can know." -- James Alexander Thom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386559-he-remembered-another-one-of-his-mother-s-saying-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:45:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by James Alexander Thom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386559-he-remembered-another-one-of-his-mother-s-saying-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He remembered another one of his mother's saying.  It was back when she'd birthed Fanny, her tenth. Someone had siad it was about time she gave up mothering and rested.  &quot;Nay,&quot; she had said.  &quot;I've started something, and now I wouldn't stop if I could, and I couldn't stop if I would." -- James Alexander Thom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386561-great-advantages-are-often-attended-with-great-inconveniences-and-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:48:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Mercy Otis Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386561-great-advantages-are-often-attended-with-great-inconveniences-and-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Great advantages are often attended with great inconveniences, and great minds called to severe trials." -- Mercy Otis Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315859-it-is-not-in-the-still-calm-of-life-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315859-it-is-not-in-the-still-calm-of-life-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not in the still calm of life, or the repose of a pacific station, that great characters are formed. The habits of a vigorous mind are formed in contending with difficulties. Great necessities call out great virtues. When a mind is raised, and animated by scenes that engage the heart, then those qualities which would otherwise lay dormant, wake into life and form the character of the hero and the statesman." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386565-it-is-to-me-a-most-affecting-thing-to-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 09:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Abigail Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386565-it-is-to-me-a-most-affecting-thing-to-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is to me a most affecting thing to hear myself prayed for, in particular as I do every day in the week, and disposes me to bear with more composure, some disagreeable circumstances that attend my situation." -- Abigail Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123754-when-gods-die-they-die-hard-it-s-not-like-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 22:33:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Gary Schmidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123754-when-gods-die-they-die-hard-it-s-not-like-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When gods die, they die hard. It's not like they fade away, or grow old, or fall asleep. They die in fire and pain, and when they come out of you, they leave your guts burned. It hurts more than anything you can talk about. And maybe worst of all is, you're not sure if there will ever be another god to fill their place. Or if you'd ever want another god to fill their place. You don't want the fire to go out inside you twice." -- Gary Schmidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386566-if-the-way-to-do-good-to-my-country-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2013 22:33:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386566-if-the-way-to-do-good-to-my-country-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the way to do good to my country were to render myself popular, I could easily do it.  But extravagant popularity is not the road to public advantage." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330020-a-comedy-isn-t-about-being-funny-said-mrs-baker-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 18:52:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Gary D. Schmidt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330020-a-comedy-isn-t-about-being-funny-said-mrs-baker-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A comedy isn't about being funny,&quot; said Mrs. Baker. 

&quot;We talked about this before.&quot;

&quot;A comedy is about character who dare to know that they may choose a happy ending after all. That's how I know.&quot;

&quot;Suppose you can't see it?&quot;

&quot;That's the daring part,&quot; said Mrs. Baker." -- Gary D. Schmidt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449045-mama-yes-emmy-she-traced-a-rivulet-of-rain-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 16:27:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Karen White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449045-mama-yes-emmy-she-traced-a-rivulet-of-rain-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mama?&quot;

&quot;Yes, Emmy.&quot;

She traced a rivulet of rain with her finger as it made its journey down the glass. &quot;How do you know when it's been long enough?&quot;

Emmy could sense her mother smiling into the phone.  &quot;When you relaize that love doesn't have a time span.  Only pain does.  I think sometimes it's hard to distinguish between the two, so we just hold on to both of them like they're inseparable." -- Karen White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464880-god-helps-me--that-s-what-i-think--and-then-i-am-calm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 08:00:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Carl Bloch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/464880-god-helps-me--that-s-what-i-think--and-then-i-am-calm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God helps me--that's what I think--and then I am calm." -- Carl Bloch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116775-when-i-was-very-young-and-the-urge-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 08:01:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116775-when-i-was-very-young-and-the-urge-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was very young and the urge to be someplace else was on me, I was assured by mature people that maturity would this itch. When years described me as mature, the remedy prescribed was middle age.In middle age I was assured greater age would calm my fever and now that I am fifty-eight perhaps senility will do the job. Nothing has worked. Four hoarse blasts of a ships's whistle still raise the hair on my neck and set my feet to tapping. The sound of a jet, an engine warming up, even the clopping of shod hooves on pavement brings on the ancient shudder, the dry mouth and vacant eye, the hot palms and the churn of stomach high up under the rib cage. In other words, once a bum always a bum. I fear this disease incurable. I set this matter down not to instruct others but to inform myself....A journey is a person in itself; no two are alike. And all plans, safeguards, policing, and coercion are fruitless. We find after years of struggle that we not take a trip; a trip takes us." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67301-a-sad-soul-can-kill-you-quicker-far-quicker-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 08:02:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67301-a-sad-soul-can-kill-you-quicker-far-quicker-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A sad soul can kill you quicker, far quicker, than a germ." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69391-love-is-the-only-way-to-grasp-another-human-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:39:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69391-love-is-the-only-way-to-grasp-another-human-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the only way to grasp another human being in the innermost core of his personality. No one can become fully aware of the very essence of another human being unless he loves him. By his love he is enabled to see the essential traits and features in the beloved person; and even more, he sees that which is potential in him, which is not yet actualized but yet ought to be actualized. Furthermore, by his love, the loving person enables the beloved person to actualize these potentialities. By making him aware of what he can be and of what he should become, he makes these potentialities come true." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60409-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-saw-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:39:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60409-for-the-first-time-in-my-life-i-saw-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the first time in my life I saw the truth as it is set into song by so many poets, proclaimed as the final wisdom by so many thinkers. The truth - that Love is the ultimate and highest goal to which man can aspire. Then I grasped the meaning of the greatest secret that human poetry and human thought and belief have to impart: The salvation of man is through love and in love." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40139-we-who-lived-in-concentration-camps-can-remember-the-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:40:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40139-we-who-lived-in-concentration-camps-can-remember-the-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We who lived in concentration camps can remember the men who walked through the huts comforting others, giving away their last piece of bread. They may have been few in number, but they offer sufficient proof that everything can be taken from a man but one thing: the last of the human freedoms -- to choose one's attitude in any given set of circumstances, to choose one's own way." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18980-ultimately-man-should-not-ask-what-the-meaning-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:42:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18980-ultimately-man-should-not-ask-what-the-meaning-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ultimately, man should not ask what the meaning of his life is, but rather must recognize that it is he who is asked. In a word, each man is questioned by life; and he can only answer to life by answering for his own life; to life he can only respond by being responsible." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69398-a-human-being-is-not-one-thing-among-others-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 09:44:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69398-a-human-being-is-not-one-thing-among-others-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being is not one thing among others; things determine each other, but man is ultimately self-determining. What he becomes - within the limits of endowment and environment- he has made out of himself. In the concentration camps, for example, in this living laboratory and on this testing ground, we watched and witnessed some of our comrades behave like swine while others behaved like saints. Man has both potentialities within himself; which one is actualized depends on decisions but not on conditions." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21406-so-live-as-if-you-were-living-already-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:38:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21406-so-live-as-if-you-were-living-already-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So live as if you were living already for the second time and as if you had acted the first time as wrongly as you are about to act now!" -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55188-in-some-ways-suffering-ceases-to-be-suffering-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:39:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55188-in-some-ways-suffering-ceases-to-be-suffering-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In some ways suffering ceases to be suffering at the moment it finds a meaning, such as the meaning of a sacrifice." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:39:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132157-the-pessimist-resembles-a-man-who-observes-with-fear-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pessimist resembles a man who observes with fear and sadness that his wall calendar, from which he daily tears a sheet, grows thinner with each passing day.  On the other hand, the person who attacks the problems of life actively is like a man who removes each successive leaf from his calendar and files it neatly and carefully away with its predecessors, after first having jotted down a few diary notes on the back.  He can reflect with pride and joy on all the richness set down in these notes, on all the life he has already lived to the fullest.  What will it matter to him if he notices that he is growing old?  Has he any reason to envy the young people whom he sees, or wax nostalgic over his own lost youth?  What reasons has he to envy a young person?  For the possibilities that a young person has, the future which is in store for him?

No, thank you,' he will think.  'Instead of possibilities, I have realities in my past, not only the reality of work done and of love loved, but of sufferings bravely suffered.  These sufferings are even the things of which I am most proud, although these are things which cannot inspire envy.' &quot;

From &quot;Logotherapy in a Nutshell&quot;, an essay" -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42132-the-attempt-to-develop-a-sense-of-humor-and-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:41:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor Emil Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42132-the-attempt-to-develop-a-sense-of-humor-and-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The attempt to develop a sense of humor and to see things in a humorous light is some kind of a trick learned while mastering the art of living." -- Viktor Emil Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164171-by-declaring-that-man-is-responsible-and-must-actualize-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:41:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164171-by-declaring-that-man-is-responsible-and-must-actualize-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By declaring that man is responsible and must actualize the potential meaning of his life, I wish to stress that the true meaning of life is to be discovered in the world rather than within man or his own psyche, as though it were a closed system. I have termed this constitutive characteristic &quot;the self-transcendence of human existence.&quot; It denotes the fact that being human always points, and is directed, to something or someone, other than oneself--be it a meaning to fulfill or another human being to encounter. The more one forgets himself--by giving himself to a cause to serve or another person to love--the more human he is and the more he actualizes himself. What is called self-actualization is not an attainable aim at all, for the simple reason that the more one would strive for it, the more he would miss it. In other words, self-actualization is possible only as a side-effect of self-transcendence." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82089-for-the-world-is-in-a-bad-state-but-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82089-for-the-world-is-in-a-bad-state-but-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the world is in a bad state, but everything will become still worse unless each of us does his best." -- Viktor E. Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317614-if-there-is-meaning-in-life-at-all-then-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2011 10:48:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Viktor Frankl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317614-if-there-is-meaning-in-life-at-all-then-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is meaning in life at all, then there must be meaning in suffering." -- Viktor Frankl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524296-some-stories-don-t-get-told-some-stories-you-hold-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 15:29:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Sarah Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524296-some-stories-don-t-get-told-some-stories-you-hold-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some stories don't get told. Some stories you hold on to. To stand and watch and hold it in your arms was not cowardice. To look straight at the beast and feel its breath on your flanks and not to turn--one could carry the world that way.  

They sat together, the four of them, a little longer, before Harry rose slowly to his feet.  It was Thursday.  It was the end of the afternoon.  It was time to pick up and carry on to the other side of the day." -- Sarah Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524298-and-one-day-i-got-it-i-lifted-my-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 15:31:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Sarah Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524298-and-one-day-i-got-it-i-lifted-my-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And one day I got it. I lifted my head from the child's chest I was listening to and realized, with a shock of relief: whatever is coming, comes. That's what holds it all together. We are all of us here in the mess. There's no way around it. And all that I am in the face of it is a single voice and a pair of hands...Anonymous but necessary. Vital." -- Sarah Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560669-and-you-ve-gone-on-all-these-years-hating-each-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 May 2012 23:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurel add a quote by Mildred Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/560669-and-you-ve-gone-on-all-these-years-hating-each-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And you've gone on all these years hating each other.  Gil felt that hate.  He could tell just being here.  That's one of the things that drove him away from here, from me...'

Mom was still so long I looked up at her...She shook her head.

...'No, Yelena, I never hate Ben an' Ben don't hate me.  Gospode Boge!  I love him here so all these years!' Mom touched her breast and her face broke into life.  Her eyes were softer.  'Me hate Ben!' she laughed...

I couldn't look at her, but I had to say what was in my mind.  'But all these years, even when I was a child, I've felt that you hated each other.  When I heard you that night you both sounded cold and hard.'

Mom made a sound of disgust in her throat. 'That don't mean nothing.  We get mad, sure!  Like ice an' snow an' thunder an' lightning storm, but they don't hurt the wheat down in the ground any.'  Mom picked up her whitewash brush and slapped it against the rough boards.  'Yolochka, you don't know how love is yet.'

...She finished her wall and poured the whitewash that was left back in the bigger pail.  'You can write that young Gil of yours that he don't know what he think he does.  Sure, we fight sometime, but we got no hate here." -- Mildred Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
