<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/871326-nicole-mandell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/871326-nicole-mandell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 07:14:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 07:14:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For some of us, books are as important as almost anything else on earth.  What a miracle it is that out of these small, flat, rigid squares of paper unfolds world after world after world, worlds that sing to you, comfort and quiet or excite you.  Books help us understand who we are and how we are to behave.  They show us what community and friendship mean; they show us how to live and die." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 07:14:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40088-perfectionism-is-the-voice-of-the-oppressor-the-enemy-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perfectionism is the voice of the oppressor, the enemy of the people. It will keep you cramped and insane your whole life, and it is the main obstacle between you and a shitty first draft. I think perfectionism is based on the obsessive belief that if you run carefully enough, hitting each stepping-stone just right, you won't have to die. The truth is that you will die anyway and that a lot of people who aren't even looking at their feet are going to do a whole lot better than you, and have a lot more fun while they're doing it." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2010 07:14:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nicole add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["E.L. Doctorow said once said that 'Writing a novel is like driving a car at night. You can see only as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way.' You don't have to see where you're going, you don't have to see your destination or everything you will pass along the way. You just have to see two or three feet ahead of you. This is right up there with the best advice on writing, or life, I have ever heard." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
