<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/872456-lovely-beasts]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/872456-lovely-beasts" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:35:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:35:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1288-i-don-t-know-about-you-but-i-m-kind-of-fed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't know about you, but I'm kind of fed up with realism. After all, there's enough reality already; why make more of it? Why not leave realism for the memoirs of drug addicts, the histories of salt, the biographies of porn stars? Why must we continue to read about the travails of divorced people or mildly depressed Canadians when we could be contemplating the shopping habits of zombies, or the difficulties that ensue when living and dead people marry each other? We should be demanding more stories about faery handbags and pyjamas inscribed with the diaries of strange women. We should not rest until someone writes about a television show that features the Free People's World-Tree Library, with its elaborate waterfalls and Forbidden Books and Pirate-Magicians. We should be pining for a house haunted by rabbits." -- Audrey Niffenger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12904-she-would-smile-and-show-no-surprise-convinced-as-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:36:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Julio Cortazar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12904-she-would-smile-and-show-no-surprise-convinced-as-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She would smile and show no surprise, convinced as she was, the same as I, that casual meetings are apt to be just the opposite, and that people who make dates are the same kind who need lines on their writing paper, or who always squeeze up from the bottom on a tube of toothpaste." -- Julio Cortazar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12390-there-is-nothing-more-alone-than-being-in-a-car</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:36:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12390-there-is-nothing-more-alone-than-being-in-a-car]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing more alone than being in a car at night in the rain. I was in the car. And I was glad of it. Between one point on the map and another point on the map, there was the being alone in the car in the rain. They say you are not you except in terms of relation to other people. If there weren't any other people there wouldn't be any you because what you do which is what you are, only has meaning in relation to other people. That is a very comforting thought when you are in the car in the rain at night alone, for then you aren't you, and not being you or anything, you can really lie back and get some rest. It is a vacation from being you. There is only the flow of the motor under you foot spinning that frail thread of sound out of its metal guy like a spider, that filament, that nexus, which isn't really there, between the you which you have just left in one place and the you which you will be where you get to the other place." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260-process-as-process-is-neither-morally-good-nor-morally-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:37:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260-process-as-process-is-neither-morally-good-nor-morally-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Process as process is neither morally good nor morally bad.  We may judge results but not process.  The morally bad agent may perform the deed which is good.  The morally good agent may perform the deed which is bad.  Maybe a man has to sell his soul to get the power to do good." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259-i-heard-somebody-open-and-shut-the-gate-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:37:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259-i-heard-somebody-open-and-shut-the-gate-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I heard somebody open and shut the gate to the barn lot, but I didn't look around.  If I didn't look around it would not be true that somebody had opened the gate with the creaky hinges, and that is a wonderful principle for a man to get hold of... What you don't know know don't hurt you, for it ain't real.  They called that Idealism in my book I had when I was in college, and after I got hold of that principle I became an Idealist... If you are an Idealist it does not matter what you do or what goes on around you because it isn't real anyway." -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1394-all-serious-daring-starts-from-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:37:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1394-all-serious-daring-starts-from-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All serious daring starts from within." -- Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:38:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7558-art-never-responds-to-the-wish-to-make-it-democratic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Art never responds to the wish to make it democratic; it is not for everybody; it is only for those who are willing to undergo the effort needed to understand it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16977-i-have-tried-imagining-that-the-single-peacock-i-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:38:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16977-i-have-tried-imagining-that-the-single-peacock-i-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have tried imagining that the single peacock I see before me is the only one I have, but then one comes to join him, another flies off the roof, four or five crash out of the crepe-myrtle hedge; from the pond one screams and from the barn I hear the dairyman denouncing another that has got into the cow-feed. My kin are given to such phrases as, 'Let's face it." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 06:39:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1939-i-can-with-one-eye-squinted-take-it-all-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can, with one eye squinted, take it all as a blessing." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 07:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/919-the-man-who-does-not-read-has-no-advantage-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not read has no advantage over the man who cannot read." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1427-i-have-never-let-my-schooling-interfere-with-my-education</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 07:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1427-i-have-never-let-my-schooling-interfere-with-my-education]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have never let my schooling interfere with my education." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7903-draw-your-chair-up-close-to-the-edge-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 08:00:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7903-draw-your-chair-up-close-to-the-edge-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Draw your chair up close to the edge of the precipice and I’ll tell you a story." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 08:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lovely Beasts  add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2314-so-we-beat-on-boats-against-the-current-borne-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So we beat on, boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
