<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/872977-russell-guldin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/872977-russell-guldin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 17:39:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257918-when-you-are-growing-up-there-are-two-institutional-places</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 17:39:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Keith Richards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257918-when-you-are-growing-up-there-are-two-institutional-places]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you are growing up there are two institutional places that affect you most powerfully: the church, which belongs to God, and the public library, which belongs to you." -- Keith Richards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420907-a-library-outranks-any-other-one-thing-a-community-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2013 17:44:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Andrew Carnegie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420907-a-library-outranks-any-other-one-thing-a-community-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A library outranks any other one thing a community can do to benefit its people. It is a never failing spring in the desert." -- Andrew Carnegie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190585-imagine-the-earth-s-population-of-six-billion-people-reduced-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by grant morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190585-imagine-the-earth-s-population-of-six-billion-people-reduced-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine the earth’s population of six billion people reduced to just one hundred representatives. Statistically, that makes 30 white, 70 non-white. It means 6 people own 59% of the wealth and they all live in North America. 80 are in substandard housing. One has an education. One owns a computer. Don’t blame me if it all sounds crazy." -- grant morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493980-we-tell-our-children-they-re-trapped-like-rats-on-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:38:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493980-we-tell-our-children-they-re-trapped-like-rats-on-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We tell our children they're trapped like rats on a doomed, bankrupt, gangster-haunted planet with dwindling resources, with nothing to look forward to but rising sea levels and imminent mass extinctions, then raise a disapproving eyebrow when, in response, they dress in black, cut themselves with razors, starve themselves, gorge themselves, or kill one another." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494122-writers-and-artists-build-by-hand-little-worlds-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:38:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494122-writers-and-artists-build-by-hand-little-worlds-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writers and artists build by hand little worlds that they hope might effect change in real minds, in the real world where stories are read. A story can make us cry and laugh, break our hearts, or make us angry enough to change the world." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219193-the-perfect-fascist-state-needs-to-operate-in-conditions-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:39:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219193-the-perfect-fascist-state-needs-to-operate-in-conditions-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The perfect fascist state needs to operate in conditions of perpetual warfare. Have you ever noticed how the world has been in constant crisis since World War II?" -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568367-the-medium-is-unaware-of-its-attractiveness-that-s-all-everyone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:40:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568367-the-medium-is-unaware-of-its-attractiveness-that-s-all-everyone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The 'medium' is unaware of its attractiveness, that's all. Everyone loves comics. I've proven this to my own satisfaction by handing them out to acountants, insurance brokers, hairdressers, mothers of children, black belts, pop stars, taxi drivers, painters, lesbians, doctors etc. etc. The X-Files, Buffy, the Matrix, X-Men - mainstream culture is not what it once was when science fiction and comics fans huddled in cellars like Gnostic Christians dodging the Romans. We should come up into the light soon before we suffocate." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493987-superhero-science-has-taught-me-this-entire-universes-fit-comfortably</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:41:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/493987-superhero-science-has-taught-me-this-entire-universes-fit-comfortably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Superhero science has taught me this: Entire universes fit comfortably inside our skulls. Not just one or two but endless universes can be packed into that dark, wet, and bony hollow without breaking it open from the inside. The space in our heads will stretch to accommodate them all. The real doorway to the fifth dimension was always right here. &lt;i&gt;Inside.&lt;/i&gt; That infinite interior space contains all the divine, the alien, and the unworldly we’ll ever need." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640335-these-characters-were-like-twelve-bar-blues-or-other-chord-progressions</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:41:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640335-these-characters-were-like-twelve-bar-blues-or-other-chord-progressions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These characters were like twelve-bar blues or other chord progressions. Given the basic parameters of Batman, different creators could play very different music." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353448-animal-man-listen-just-tell-me-one-thing-am-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/353448-animal-man-listen-just-tell-me-one-thing-am-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Animal Man: 'Listen, just tell me one thing: am I REAL or what?'

Grant Morrison: 'Of COURSE you're real! We wouldn't be here talking if you weren't real.

'You existed long before I wrote about you and, if you're lucky, you'll still be young when I'm old or dead.

'You're more real than I am." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723472-if-our-shallow-self-critical-culture-sometimes-seems-to-lack-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 08:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Grant Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723472-if-our-shallow-self-critical-culture-sometimes-seems-to-lack-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If our shallow, self-critical culture sometimes seems to lack a sense of the numinous or spiritual it’s only in the same way a fish lacks a sense of the ocean. Because the numinous is everywhere, we need to be reminded of it. We live among wonders. Superhuman cyborgs, we plug into cell phones connecting us to one another and to a constantly updated planetary database, an exo-memory that allows us to fit our complete cultural archive into a jacket pocket. We have camera eyes that speed up, slow down, and even reverse the flow of time, allowing us to see what no one prior to the twentieth century had ever seen — the thermodynamic miracle of broken shards and a puddle gathering themselves up from the floor to assemble a half-full wineglass. We are the hands and eyes and ears, the sensitive probing feelers through which the emergent, intelligent universe comes to know its own form and purpose. We bring the thunderbolt of meaning and significance to unconscious matter, blank paper, the night sky. We are already divine magicians, already supergods. Why shouldn’t we use all our brilliance to leap in as many single bounds as it takes to a world beyond ours, threatened by overpopulation, mass species extinction, environmental degradation, hunger, and exploitation? Superman and his pals would figure a way out of any stupid cul-de-sac we could find ourselves in — and we made Superman, after all." -- Grant Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118525-now-there-is-a-final-reason-i-think-that-jesus</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 13:23:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118525-now-there-is-a-final-reason-i-think-that-jesus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now there is a final reason I think that Jesus says, &quot;Love your enemies.&quot; It is this: that love has within it a redemptive power. And there is a power there that eventually transforms individuals.  Just keep being friendly to that person.  Just keep loving them, and they can’t stand it too long. Oh, they react in many ways in the beginning. They react with guilt feelings, and sometimes they’ll hate you a little more at that transition period, but just keep loving them. And by the power of your love they will break down under the load. That’s love, you see. It is redemptive, and this is why Jesus says love. There’s something about love that builds up and is creative. There is something about hate that tears down and is destructive. So love your enemies.  (from &quot;Loving Your Enemies&quot;)" -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/669506-many-suburban-legislators-representing-affluent-school-districts-use-terms-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 06:14:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/669506-many-suburban-legislators-representing-affluent-school-districts-use-terms-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many suburban legislators representing affluent school districts use terms such as &quot;sinkhole&quot; when opposing funding for Chicago's children. &quot;We can't keep throwing money,&quot; said Governor Thompson in 1988, &quot;into a black hole.&quot; The Chicago Tribune notes that, when this phrase is used, people hasten to explain that it is not intended as a slur against the race of many of Chicago's children. &quot;But race,&quot; says the Tribune, &quot;never is far from the surface..." -- Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650072-research-experts-want-to-know-what-can-be-done-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 06:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/650072-research-experts-want-to-know-what-can-be-done-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Research experts want to know what can be done about the values of poor segregated children; and this is a question that needs asking. But they do not ask what can be done about the values of the people who have segregated these communities. There is no academic study of the pathological detachment of the very rich..." -- Jonathan Kozol]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2013 06:18:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don’t want to go among mad people,&quot; Alice remarked.
&quot;Oh, you can’t help that,&quot; said the Cat: &quot;we’re all mad here. I’m mad. You’re mad.&quot;
&quot;How do you know I’m mad?&quot; said Alice.
&quot;You must be,&quot; said the Cat, or you wouldn’t have come here." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706825-it-s-now-very-common-to-hear-people-say-i-m-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 08:51:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Stephen Fry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706825-it-s-now-very-common-to-hear-people-say-i-m-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's now very common to hear people say, 'I'm rather offended by that.' As if that gives them certain rights. It's actually nothing more... than a whine. 'I find that offensive.' It has no meaning; it has no purpose; it has no reason to be respected as a phrase. 'I am offended by that.' Well, so fucking what.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;I saw hate in a graveyard -- Stephen Fry&lt;/i&gt;, The Guardian, 5 June 2005]" -- Stephen Fry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38364-you-can-t-talk-about-fucking-in-america-people-say-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 08:51:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Richard Pryor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38364-you-can-t-talk-about-fucking-in-america-people-say-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't talk about fucking in America, people say you're dirty. But if you talk about killing somebody, that's cool." -- Richard Pryor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17797-everyone-is-in-favor-of-free-speech-hardly-a-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 08:51:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Russell add a quote by Winston Churchill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17797-everyone-is-in-favor-of-free-speech-hardly-a-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone is in favor of free speech. Hardly a day passes without its being extolled, but some people's idea of it is that they are free to say what they like, but if anyone else says anything back, that is an outrage." -- Winston Churchill]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
