<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/873099-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/873099-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:18:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31464-i-can-live-alone-if-self-respect-and-circumstances-require-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:18:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31464-i-can-live-alone-if-self-respect-and-circumstances-require-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can live alone, if self-respect, and circumstances require me so to do. I need not sell my soul to buy bliss. I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all extraneous delights should be withheld, or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94823-i-do-not-think-sir-you-have-any-right-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:19:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94823-i-do-not-think-sir-you-have-any-right-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not think, sir, you have any right to command me, merely because you are older than I, or because you have seen more of the world than I have; your claim to superiority depends on the use you have made of your time and experience." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93471-we-know-that-god-is-everywhere-but-certainly-we-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:19:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93471-we-know-that-god-is-everywhere-but-certainly-we-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We know that God is everywhere; but certainly we feel His presence most when His works are on the grandest scale spread before us; and it is in the unclouded night-sky, where His worlds wheel their silent course, that we read clearest His infinitude, His omnipotence, His omnipresence." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9927-i-ask-you-to-pass-through-life-at-my-side-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:19:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9927-i-ask-you-to-pass-through-life-at-my-side-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I ask you to pass through life at my side—to be my second self, and best earthly companion." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2011 10:20:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They spoke almost as loud as Feeling: and that clamoured wildly. &quot;Oh, comply!&quot; it said. &quot;Think of his misery; think of his danger — look at his state when left alone; remember his headlong nature; consider the recklessness following on despair — soothe him; save him; love him; tell him you love him and will be his. Who in the world cares for you? or who will be injured by what you do?&quot;

Still indomitable was the reply — &quot;I care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself. I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. I will hold to the principles received by me when I was sane, and not mad — as I am now. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth? They have a worth — so I have always believed; and if I cannot believe it now, it is because I am quite insane — quite insane: with my veins running fire, and my heart beating faster than I can count its throbs. Preconceived opinions, foregone determinations, are all I have this hour to stand by: there I plant my foot." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
