<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874331-autumn-linford]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874331-autumn-linford" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 08:35:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 08:35:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 08:35:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it is hard for you young mothers to believe that almost before you can turn around the children will be gone and you will be alone with your husband.  You had better be sure you are developing the kind of love and friendship that will be delightful and enduring.  Let the children learn from your attitude that he is important.  Encourage him.  Be kind.  It is a rough world, and he, like everyone else, is fighting to survive.  Be cheerful.  Don't be a whiner." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141191-think-about-your-particular-assignment-at-this-time-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 18:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141191-think-about-your-particular-assignment-at-this-time-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think about your particular assignment at this time in your life.  It may be to get an education, it may be to rear children, it may be to be a grandparent, it may be to care for an relieve the suffering of someone you love, it may be to do a job in the most excellent way possible, it may be to support someone who has a difficult assignment of their own.  Our assignments are varied and they change from time to time.  Don't take them lightly.  Give them your full heart and energy.  Do them with enthusiasm.  Do whatever you have to do this week with your whole heart and soul.  To do less than this will leave you with an empty feeling." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159326-there-are-some-years-in-our-lives-that-we-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 18:18:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159326-there-are-some-years-in-our-lives-that-we-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some years in our lives that we would not want to live again.  But even these years will pass away, and the lessons learned will be a future blessing." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197766-life-is-not-a-journey-to-the-grave-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 18:20:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Autumn add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197766-life-is-not-a-journey-to-the-grave-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is not a journey to the grave with the intention of arriving safely in a well preserved body, but rather to skid in broadside, thoroughly used up, totally worn out, and loudly proclaiming, “Wow what a ride!" -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
