<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874335-courtney]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874335-courtney" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 10:32:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8524-you-get-a-strange-feeling-when-you-re-about-to-leave</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 10:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Azar Nafisi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8524-you-get-a-strange-feeling-when-you-re-about-to-leave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get a strange feeling when you're about to leave a place, I told him, like you'll not only miss the people you love but you'll miss the person you are now at this time and this place, because you'll never be this way ever again." -- Azar Nafisi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110908-have-you-ever-noticed-that-when-your-mind-is-awakened</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 09:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110908-have-you-ever-noticed-that-when-your-mind-is-awakened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever noticed that when your mind is awakened or drawn to someone new, that person's name suddenly pops up everywhere you go? My friend Sophie calls it coincidence, and Mr. Simpless, my parson friend, calls it Grace. He thinks that if one cares deeply about someone or something new one throws a kind of energy out into the world, and &quot;fruitfulness&quot; is drawn in. " -- Mary Ann Shaffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453293-what-an-unsubstantial-happy-foolish-time-of-all-the-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 10:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/453293-what-an-unsubstantial-happy-foolish-time-of-all-the-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What an unsubstantial, happy, foolish time! Of all the times of mine that Time has in his grip, there is none that in one retrospection I can smile at half so much, and think of half so tenderly." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115087-it-was-drizzling-as-people-rushed-along-they-began-opening</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 10:32:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115087-it-was-drizzling-as-people-rushed-along-they-began-opening]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was drizzling. As people rushed along, they began opening umbrellas over their heads, and all at once the streets were crowded too. Arched umbrella roofs collided with one another. The men were courteous, and when passing Tereza they held their umbrellas high over their heads and gave her room to go by. But the women would not yield; each looked straight ahead, waiting for the other women to acknowledge her inferiority and step aside.  The meeting of the umbrellas was a test of strength. At first Tereza gave way, but when she realized her courtesy was not being reciprocated, she started clutching her umbrella like the other women and ramming it forcefully against the oncoming umbrellas. No one ever said &quot;Sorry.&quot; For the most part no one said anything, though once or twice she did hear a &quot;Fat cow!&quot; or &quot;Fuck you!&quot; The women thus armed with umbrellas were both young and old, but the younger among them proved the more steeled warriors...  [editors note: I love this paragraph, it reminds me of walking down the crowded streets of Philly when I'm late for the train... so frustrating.]  " -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
