<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874506-nutter]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874506-nutter" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:54:29 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21335-then-it-was-you-who-wounded-aravis-it-was-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:54:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nutter add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21335-then-it-was-you-who-wounded-aravis-it-was-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then it was you who wounded Aravis?&quot;
  &quot;It was I.&quot;
  &quot;But what for?&quot;
  &quot;Child,&quot; said the Voice, &quot;I am telling you your story, not hers.  I tell no one any story but his own." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21337-in-the-castle-of-benwick-the-french-boy-was-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:57:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nutter add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21337-in-the-castle-of-benwick-the-french-boy-was-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the castle of Benwick, the French boy was looking at his face in the polished surface of a kettle-hat.  It flashed in the sunlight with the stubborn gleam of metal.  It was practically the same as the steel helmet which soldiers still wear, and it did not make a good mirror, but it was the best he could get.  He turned the hat in various directions, hoping to get an average idea of his face from the different distoritons which the bulges made.  He was trying to find out what he was, and he was afraid of what he would find.

The boy thought that there was something wrong with him.  All through his life--even when he was a great man with the world at his feet--he was to feel this gap:  something at the bototm of his heart of which he was aware, and ashamed, but which he did not understand. There is no need for us to try to understand it.  &lt;i&gt;We&lt;/i&gt; do not have to dabble in a place which he preferred to keep secret." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21339-jenny-all-my-life-i-have-wanted-to-do-miracles</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:58:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nutter add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21339-jenny-all-my-life-i-have-wanted-to-do-miracles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jenny, all my life I have wanted to do miracles.  I have wanted to be holy.  I suppose it was ambition or pride or some other unworthy thing. It was not enough for me to conquer the world--I wanted to conquer heaven too." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21341-he-unfortunately-for-himself-had-been-beautifully-brought-up-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 15:59:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nutter add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21341-he-unfortunately-for-himself-had-been-beautifully-brought-up-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He, unfortunately for himself, had been beautifully brought up.  His teacher had educated him as the child is educated in the womb, where it lives the history of man from fish to mammal--and, like the child in the womb, he had been protected with love meanwhile.  The effect of such an education was that he had grown up without any of the useful accomplishments for living--without malice, vanity, suspicion, cruelty, and the commoner forms of selfishness.  Jealousy seemed to him the most ignoble of vices.  He was sadly unfitted for hating his best friend or torturing his wife.  He had been given too much love and trust to be good at these things." -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21342-if-god-is-supposed-to-be-merciful-arthur-retorted-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2008 16:00:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nutter add a quote by T.H. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21342-if-god-is-supposed-to-be-merciful-arthur-retorted-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If God is supposed to be merciful,' [Arthur] retorted, 'I don't see why He shouldn't allow people to stumble into heaven, just as well as climb there" -- T.H. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
