<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874721-nathan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/874721-nathan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 14:16:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2942-happiness-is-beneficial-for-the-body-but-it-is-grief</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 14:16:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2942-happiness-is-beneficial-for-the-body-but-it-is-grief]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is beneficial for the body, but it is grief that develops the powers of the mind." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58372-hard-people-are-weak-people-whom-nobody-wants-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 17:21:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58372-hard-people-are-weak-people-whom-nobody-wants-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Hard people are weak people whom nobody wants, and the strong, caring little whether they are wanted or not, have alone that meekness which the common herd mistake for weakness." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58449-now-the-same-mystery-which-often-veils-from-our-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 19:59:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58449-now-the-same-mystery-which-often-veils-from-our-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now the same mystery which often veils from our eyes the reason for a catastrophe envelops just as frequently, when love is in question, the suddenness of certain happy solutions, such as had been brought to me by Gilberte's letter. Happy, or at least seemingly happy, for there are few that can really be happy when we are dealing with a sentiment of such a kind that any satisfaction we can give it does no more, as a rule, than dislodge some pain. And yet sometimes a respite is granted us, and we have for a little while the illusion of being healed." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51213-the-postmodernists-tyranny-wears-people-down-by-boredom-and-semi-literate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2010 11:10:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51213-the-postmodernists-tyranny-wears-people-down-by-boredom-and-semi-literate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Postmodernists' tyranny wears people down by boredom and semi-literate prose." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48435-loves-are-like-empires-when-the-idea-they-are-founded</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 08:09:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48435-loves-are-like-empires-when-the-idea-they-are-founded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["loves are like empires: when the idea they are founded on crumbles, they, too, fade away." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:11:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/315932-once-a-little-boy-sent-me-a-charming-card-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once a little boy sent me a charming card with a little drawing on it. I loved it. I answer all my children’s letters — sometimes very hastily — but this one I lingered over. I sent him a card and I drew a picture of a Wild Thing on it. I wrote, “Dear Jim: I loved your card.” Then I got a letter back from his mother and she said, “Jim loved your card so much he ate it.” That to me was one of the highest compliments I’ve ever received. He didn’t care that it was an original Maurice Sendak drawing or anything. He saw it, he loved it, he ate it." -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819946-her-mother-an-unshapely-chubby-cheeked-creature-from-the-rural-gentry</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2013 23:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/819946-her-mother-an-unshapely-chubby-cheeked-creature-from-the-rural-gentry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her mother, an unshapely, chubby-cheeked creature from the rural gentry of Styria, permanently lost her hair at the age of forty after being treated for influenza by her husband, and prematurely withdrew from society. She and her husband were able to live in the Gentzgasse thanks to her mother's fortune, which derived from the family estates in Styria and then devolved upon &lt;I&gt;her.&lt;/I&gt; She provided for everything, since her husband earned nothing as a doctor. He was a socialite, what is known as a beau, who went to all the big Viennese balls during the carnival season and throughout his life was able to conceal his stupidity behind a pleasingly slim exterior. Throughout her life Auersberger's mother-in-law had a raw deal from her husband, but was content to accept her modest social station, not that of a member of the nobility, but one that was thoroughly petit bourgeois. Her son-in-law, as I suddenly recalled, sitting in the wing chair, made a point of hiding her wig from time to time--whenever the mood took him--both in the Gentzgasse and at the Maria Zaal in Styria, so that the poor woman was unable to leave the house. It used to amuse him, after he had hidden her wig, to drive his mother-in-law up the wall, as they say. Even when he was going on forty he used to hide her wigs--by that time she has provided herself with several--which was a symptom of his sickness and infantility. I often witnessed this game of hide-and-seek at Maria Zaal and in the Gentzgasse, and I honestly have to say that I was amused by it and did not feel in the least bit ashamed of myself. His mother-in-law would be forced to stay at home because her son-in-law had hidden her wigs, and this was especially likely to happen on public holidays. In the end he would throw the wig in her face. He needed his mother-in-law's humiliation, I reflected, sitting in the wing chair and observing him in the background of the music room, just as he needed the triumph that this diabolical behavior brought him." -- Thomas Bernhard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937409-he-owned</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2013 19:58:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nathan add a quote by William Strunk Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/937409-he-owned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He owned" -- William Strunk Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
