<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875491-gregory]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875491-gregory" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:02:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373049-the-fiction-of-ayn-rand-is-as-low-as-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/373049-the-fiction-of-ayn-rand-is-as-low-as-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fiction of Ayn Rand is as low as you can get re fiction. I hope you picked it up off the floor of the subway and threw it in the nearest garbage pail. She makes Mickey Spillane look like Dostoevsky." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211146-the-only-thing-that-makes-the-church-endurable-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:04:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211146-the-only-thing-that-makes-the-church-endurable-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...the only thing that makes the Church endurable is that it is somehow the body of Christ and that on this we are fed. It seems to be a fact that you have to suffer as much from the Church as for it but if you believe in the divinity of Christ, you have to cherish the world at the same time that you struggle to endure it.  " -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317725-i-have-got-over-the-years-a-sense-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317725-i-have-got-over-the-years-a-sense-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have got, over the years, a sense of the immense sweep of creation, of the evolutionary process in everything, of how incomprehensible God must necessarily be to be the God of heaven and earth. You can’t fit the Almighty into your intellectual categories…. What kept me a skeptic [of secularism] in college was precisely my Christian faith. It always said: wait, don’t bite on this, get a wider picture, continue to read. If you want your faith, you have to work for it…. Even in the life of a Christian, faith rises and falls like the tides of an invisible sea. It’s there, even when he can’t see it or feel it, if he wants it to be there. You realize, I think, that it is more valuable, more mysterious, altogether more immense than anything you can learn or decide in college. Learn what you can, but cultivate Christian skepticism." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321028-later-he-saw-jesus-move-from-tree-to-tree-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 19:18:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321028-later-he-saw-jesus-move-from-tree-to-tree-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Later he saw Jesus move from tree to tree in the back of his mind, a wild ragged figure motioning him to turn around and come off into the dark where he might be walking on the water and not know it and then suddenly know it and drown." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99358-i-therefore-hate-the-corrupt-slaveholding-women-whipping-cradle-plundering-partial-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 19:52:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99358-i-therefore-hate-the-corrupt-slaveholding-women-whipping-cradle-plundering-partial-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...I therefore hate the corrupt, slaveholding, women-whipping, cradle-plundering, partial and hypocritical Christianity of the land... I look upon it as the climax of all misnomers, the boldest of all frauds, and the grossest of all libels. Never was there a clearer case of 'stealing the livery of the court of heaven to serve the devil in.' I am filled with unutterable loathing when I contemplate the religious pomp and show, together with the horrible inconsistencies, which every where surround me. We have men-stealers for ministers, women-whippers for missionaries, and cradle-plunderers for church members. The man who wields the blood-clotted cowskin during the week fills the pulpit on Sunday, and claims to be a minister of the meek and lowly Jesus. . . . The slave auctioneer’s bell and the church-going bell chime in with each other, and the bitter cries of the heart-broken slave are drowned in the religious shouts of his pious master. Revivals of religion and revivals in the slave-trade go hand in hand together. The slave prison and the church stand near each other. The clanking of fetters and the rattling of chains in the prison, and the pious psalm and solemn prayer in the church, may be heard at the same time. The dealers in the bodies of men erect their stand in the presence of the pulpit, and they mutually help each other. The dealer gives his blood-stained gold to support the pulpit, and the pulpit, in return, covers his infernal business with the garb of Christianity. Here we have religion and robbery the allies of each other—devils dressed in angels’ robes, and hell presenting the semblance of paradise." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84585-the-american-people-have-this-to-learn-that-where-justice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 19:55:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gregory add a quote by Frederick Douglass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84585-the-american-people-have-this-to-learn-that-where-justice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The American people have this to learn: that where justice is denied, where poverty is enforced, where ignorance prevails, and where any one class is made to feel that society is an organized conspiracy to oppress, rob, and degrade them, neither person nor property is safe." -- Frederick Douglass]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
