<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875654-joseph]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875654-joseph" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:23:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218368-this-is-why-the-liberian-waiter-laughed-at-me-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:23:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Rose George]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218368-this-is-why-the-liberian-waiter-laughed-at-me-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is why the Liberian waiter laughed at me. He thought that I thought a toilet was my right, when he knew it was a privilege.
&quot;It must be, when 2.6 billion people don't have sanitation. I don't mean that they have no toilet in their house and must use a public one with queues and fees. Or that they have an outhouse, or a ricety shack that empties into a filthy drain or pigsty. All that counts as sanitation, though not a safe variety. The people who have those are the fortunate ones. Four in ten people have no access to any latrine, toilet, bucket, or box. Nothing. Instead, they defecate by train tracks and in forests. They do it in plastic bags and fling them through the air in narrow slum alleyways. If they are women, they get up at 4 A.M. to be able to do their business under cover of darkness for reasons of modesty, risking rape and snakebites. Four in ten people live in situations where they are surrounded by human excrement because it is in the bushes outside the village or in their city yards, left by children outside the backdoor. It is tramped back in on their feet, carried on fingers onto clothes, food and drinking water.
&quot;The disease toll of this is stunning. A gram of feces can contain 10 million viruses, 1 million bacteria, 1,000 parasite cysts, and 100 worm eggs..." -- Rose George]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155757-i-ve-always-envied-people-who-sleep-easily-their-brains-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 22:22:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155757-i-ve-always-envied-people-who-sleep-easily-their-brains-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always envied people who sleep easily. Their brains must be cleaner, the floorboards of the skull well swept, all the little monsters closed up in a steamer trunk at the foot of the bed." -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158016-talent-must-be-a-fanatical-mistress-she-s-beautiful-when-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 22:23:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by David Benioff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158016-talent-must-be-a-fanatical-mistress-she-s-beautiful-when-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talent must be a fanatical mistress. She's beautiful; when you're with her, people watch you, they notice. But she bangs on your door at odd hours, and she disappears for long stretches, and she has no patience for the rest of your existence; your wife, your children, your friends. She is the most thrilling evening of your week, but some day she will leave you for good. One night, after she's been gone for years, you will see her on the arm of a younger man, and she will pretend not to recognize you." -- David Benioff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2012 23:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Joseph add a quote by Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48648-once-upon-a-midnight-dreary-while-i-pondered-weak-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore,
While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door.
Tis some visitor,&quot; I muttered, &quot;tapping at my chamber door —
      Only this, and nothing more.&quot;

Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow; — vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow — sorrow for the lost Lenore —
For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore —
      Nameless here for evermore.

And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me — filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating,
Tis some visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door —
Some late visitor entreating entrance at my chamber door; —
    This it is, and nothing more.&quot;

Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer,
Sir,&quot; said I, &quot;or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you&quot;— here I opened wide the door; —
    Darkness there, and nothing more.

Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken, and the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, &quot;Lenore?&quot;
This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, &quot;Lenore!&quot; —
      Merely this, and nothing more.

Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping somewhat louder than before.
Surely,&quot; said I, &quot;surely that is something at my window lattice:
Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore —
Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore; —
    'Tis the wind and nothing more.&quot;

Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he; not a minute stopped or stayed he;
But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door —
Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door —
    Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore.
Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou,&quot; I said, &quot;art sure no craven,
Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore —
Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!&quot;
      Quoth the Raven, &quot;Nevermore.&quot;

Much I marveled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning— little relevancy bore;
For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing bird above his chamber door —
Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,
      With such name as &quot;Nevermore." -- Edgar Allan Poe]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
