<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/87583-ashlee-draper-galyean]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/87583-ashlee-draper-galyean" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 19:40:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 19:40:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24210-i-believe-that-there-is-one-story-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 11:46:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24210-i-believe-that-there-is-one-story-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that there is one story in the world, and only one. . . . Humans are caught—in their lives, in their thoughts, in their hungers and ambitions, in their avarice and cruelty, and in their kindness and generosity too—in a net of good and evil. . . . There is no other story. A man, after he has brushed off the dust and chips of his life, will have left only the hard, clean questions: Was it good or was it evil? Have I done well—or ill?" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68226-and-this-i-believe-that-the-free-exploring-mind-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 11:46:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68226-and-this-i-believe-that-the-free-exploring-mind-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And this I believe: that the free, exploring mind of the individual human is the most valuable thing in the world. And this I would fight for: the freedom of the mind to take any direction it wishes, undirected. And this I must fight against: any idea, religion, or government which limits or destroys the individual. This is what I am and what I am about." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 06:40:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 13:27:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52202-true-love-is-not-so-much-a-matter-of-romance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True love is not so much a matter of romance as it is a matter of anxious concern for the well-being of one's companion." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12779-we-all-know-that-something-is-eternal-and-it-ain-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 12:53:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12779-we-all-know-that-something-is-eternal-and-it-ain-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all know that something is eternal. And it ain’t houses and it ain’t names, and it ain’t earth, and it ain’t even the stars . . . everybody knows in their bones that something is eternal, and that something has to do with human beings. All the greatest people ever lived have been telling us that for five thousand years and yet you’d be surprised how people are always losing hold of it. There’s something way down deep that’s eternal about every human being.

-stage manager, in the play OUR TOWN" -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105613-oh-earth-you-re-too-wonderful-for-anybody-to-realize-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 12:53:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ashlee add a quote by Thornton Wilder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105613-oh-earth-you-re-too-wonderful-for-anybody-to-realize-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, earth, you're too wonderful for anybody to realize you. Do any human beings ever realize life while they live it -- every, every minute?" -- Thornton Wilder]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
