<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875986-ray-norsworthy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/875986-ray-norsworthy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 22:51:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60302-every-secret-of-a-writer-s-soul-every-experience-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 22:51:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ray add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60302-every-secret-of-a-writer-s-soul-every-experience-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every secret of a writer's soul, every experience of his life, every quality of his mind is written large in his works." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448784-life-s-single-lesson-that-there-is-more-accident-to-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 23:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ray add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/448784-life-s-single-lesson-that-there-is-more-accident-to-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's single lesson: that there is more accident to it than a man can ever admit to in a lifetime and stay sane." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132640-my-god-a-moment-of-bliss-why-isn-t-that-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 21:31:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ray add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132640-my-god-a-moment-of-bliss-why-isn-t-that-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My God, a moment of bliss.  Why, isn't that enough for a whole lifetime?" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223933-because-it-begins-to-seem-to-me-at-such-times</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 21:32:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ray add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223933-because-it-begins-to-seem-to-me-at-such-times]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because it begins to seem to me at such times that I am incapable of beginning a life in real life, because it has seemed to me that I have lost all touch, all instinct for the actual, the real; because at last I have cursed myself; because after my fantastic nights I have moments of returning sobriety, which are awful! Meanwhile, you hear the whirl and roar of the crowd in the vortex of life around you; you hear, you see, men living in reality; you see that life for them is not forbidden, that their life does not float away like a dream, like a vision; that their life is being eternally renewed, eternally youthful, and not one hour of it is the same as another; while fancy is so spiritless, monotonous to vulgarity and easily scared, the slave of shadows, of the idea, the slave of the first cloud that shrouds the sun... One feels that this inexhaustible fancy is weary at last and worn out with continual exercise, because one is growing into manhood, outgrowing one's old ideals: they are being shattered into fragments, into dust; if there is no other life one must build one up from the fragments. And meanwhile the soul longs and craves for something else! And in vain the dreamer rakes over his old dreams, as though seeking a spark among the embers, to fan them into flame, to warm his chilled heart by the rekindled fire, and to rouse up in it again all that was so sweet, that touched his heart, that set his blood boiling, drew tears from his eyes, and so luxuriously deceived him!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
