<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/876342-weston]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/876342-weston" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 13:15:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21750-examine-then-and-see-if-he-be-not-the-dispenser</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 13:15:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Weston add a quote by Tertullian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21750-examine-then-and-see-if-he-be-not-the-dispenser]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Examine then, and see if He be not the dispenser of kingdoms, who is Lord at once of the world which is ruled, and of man himself who rules; if He have not ordained the changes of dynasties, with their appointed seasons, who was before all time, and made the world a body of times; if the rise and the fall of states are not the work of Him, under whose sovereignty the human race once existed without states at all." -- Tertullian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21753-to-put-radically-asunder-what-nature-and-nature-s-god-joined</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 13:20:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Weston add a quote by Paul Ramsey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21753-to-put-radically-asunder-what-nature-and-nature-s-god-joined]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To put radically asunder what nature and nature’s God joined together in parenthood when he made love procreative, and to disregard the foundation of the covenant of marriage and the covenant of parenthood in the reality that makes for a loving procreation, and to attempt to soar so high above an eminently human parenthood, is inevitably to fall far below - into a vast technological alienation of man." -- Paul Ramsey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21754-although-it-is-very-easy-to-marry-a-wife-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 13:22:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Weston add a quote by Martin Luther]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21754-although-it-is-very-easy-to-marry-a-wife-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although it is very easy to marry a wife, it is very difficult to support her along with the children and the household. Accordingly, no one notices this faith of Jacob. Indeed, many hate fertility in a wife for the sole reason that the offspring must be supported and brought up. For this is what they commonly say: ‘Why should I marry a wife when I am a pauper and a beggar? I would rather bear the burden of poverty alone and not load myself with misery and want.’ But this blame is unjustly fastened on marriage and fruitfulness. Indeed, you are indicting your unbelief by distrusting God’s goodness, and you are bringing greater misery upon yourself by disparaging God’s blessing. For if you had trust in God’s grace and promises, you would undoubtedly be supported. But because you do not hope in the Lord, you will never prosper." -- Martin Luther]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21759-returning-to-the-moral-majority-we-must-realize-that-regardless</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 13:32:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Weston add a quote by Francis Schaeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21759-returning-to-the-moral-majority-we-must-realize-that-regardless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Returning to the Moral Majority, we must realize that regardless of whether we think the Moral Majority has always said the right things or whether we do not, or whether we think they have made some mistakes or whether we do not, they have certainly done one thing right: they have used the freedom we still have in the political arena to stand against the other total entity [secular humanism]. They have carried the fact that law is king, law is above the lawmakers, and God is above the law in to this area of life where it always should have been. And this is a part of true spirituality.

The Moral Majority has drawn a line between the one total view of reality and the other total view of reality and the results this brings forth in government and law. And if you personally do not like some of the details of what they have done, do it better. But you must understand that all Christians have got to do the same kind of thing or you are simply not showing the Lordship of Christ in the totality of life." -- Francis Schaeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
