<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/876716-catherine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/876716-catherine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 09:26:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83230-we-must-use-time-creatively-and-forever-realize-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 09:26:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Nelson Mandela]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83230-we-must-use-time-creatively-and-forever-realize-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must use time creatively, and forever realize that the time is always ripe to do right." -- Nelson Mandela]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80637-it-s-so-easy-to-laugh-it-s-so-easy-to-hate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 09:19:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80637-it-s-so-easy-to-laugh-it-s-so-easy-to-hate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so easy to laugh
It's so easy to hate
It takes guts to be gentle and kind" -- Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14642-lord-what-fools-these-mortals-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 08:11:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14642-lord-what-fools-these-mortals-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lord, what fools these mortals be!" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100787-all-of-our-waste-which-we-dumped-on-her-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2012 18:57:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100787-all-of-our-waste-which-we-dumped-on-her-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of our waste which we dumped on her and which she absorbed. And all of our beauty, which was hers first and which she gave to us. All of us--all who knew her--felt so wholesome after we cleaned ourselves on her. We were so beautiful when we stood astride her ugliness. her simplicity decorated us, her guilt sanctified us, her pain made us glow with health, her awkwardness made us think we has a sense of humor. Her inarticulateness made us believe we were eloquent. Her poverty kept us generous. Even her waking dreams we used--to silence our own nightmares. And she let us, and thereby deserved our contempt. We honed our egos on her, padded our characters with her frailty, and yawned in the fantasy of our strength.

And fantasy it was, for we were not strong, only aggressive; we were not free, merely licensed; we were not compassionate, we were polite; not good, but well behaved. We courted death in order to call ourselves brave, and hid like thieves from life. We substituted good grammar for intellect; we switched habits to simulate maturity; we rearranged lies and called it truth, seeing in the new pattern of an old idea the Revelation and the Word." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2757-it-is-not-inertia-alone-that-is-responsible-for-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 11:22:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2757-it-is-not-inertia-alone-that-is-responsible-for-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not inertia alone that is responsible for human relationships repeating themselves from case to case, indescribably monotonous and unrenewed: it is shyness before any sort of new, unforeseeable experience with which one does not think oneself able to cope. But only someone who is ready for everything, who excludes nothing, not even the most enigmatical will live the relation to another as something alive." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 11:31:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17266-never-never-be-afraid-to-do-what-s-right-especially-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never, never be afraid to do what's right, especially if the well-being of a person or animal is at stake. Society's punishments are small compared to the wounds we inflict on our soul when we look the other way." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
