<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/877177-sasha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/877177-sasha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 19:11:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42770-i-stood-right-in-this-house-in-that-room-aunt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2008 19:11:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Betsy Byars]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42770-i-stood-right-in-this-house-in-that-room-aunt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I stood right in this house, in that room,&quot; Aunt Willie interrupted.  She pointed toward the front bedroom. &quot;And I promised your mother, Sara, that I would look after Charlie all my life.  I promised your mother nothing would ever happen to Charlie as long as there was breath in my body, and now look.  Look! Where is this boy I'm taking such good care of?&quot; She threw her hands into the air. &quot;Vanished without a trace, that's where.&quot;

Aunt Willie, you can't watch him every minute.&quot;

Why not?  Why can't I?  What have I got more important in my life than looking after that boy?  Only one thing more important than Charlie.  Only one thing--that devil television there.&quot;

Aunt Willie--&quot;

Oh, yes, that devil television. I was sitting right in that chair last night and he wanted me to sew on one button for him but I was too busy with the television. I'll tell you what I should have told your mother six years ago.  I should have told her, &quot;Sure, I'll be glad to look after Charlie except when there's something good on television. I'll be glad to watch him in my spare time.' My tongue should fall out on the floor for promising to look after your brother and not doing it." -- Betsy Byars]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71411-distinctively-gentle-he-was-and-trustworthy-and-of-special-courtesy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 13:19:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71411-distinctively-gentle-he-was-and-trustworthy-and-of-special-courtesy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Distinctively gentle he was, and trustworthy, and of special courtesy.  His great physical strength was never used in combat, men remembered, except when needed for the defence of the weak.  In the last hours, when his mind went roving over the past, he said to someone who stoody by:  'I thank god that in all my life I never struck a man in anger...Ishould have killed my antagonist and then his blood, at this awful moment, would have lain heavily on my soul....Idie at peace with all mankind.'  (Referring to Augustine Washington, husband of Mary Ball and father of George Washington.)" -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71484-it-is-perhaps-too-much-to-ask-of-hero-worshippers</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 19:35:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71484-it-is-perhaps-too-much-to-ask-of-hero-worshippers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is perhaps too much to ask of hero worshippers that they peer back of the hero and consider the principal factor that shaped him for glory--that is, whoever it was that had charge of his grubby little boyhood." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71486-it-is-safe-to-say-that-not-all-the-cooking</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 19:37:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71486-it-is-safe-to-say-that-not-all-the-cooking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is safe to say that not all the cooking and sewing and farm management of an entire year signified as much hard work as the job of keeping those five children alive for a month.  Their mother did it, though,...with never a murmur.  It was not merely a part of her life's routine; it was her life itself." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71487-common-sense-was-one-of-the-strongest-ingredients-of-her-character</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 19:39:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71487-common-sense-was-one-of-the-strongest-ingredients-of-her-character]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Common sense...was one of the strongest ingredients of her character.  She knew well enough that her fate was not to be an iota different from the fate of all mothers since the world began.  her five would all go, somehow and somewhere, one by one.  She would do what she coult to manage the goings, no doubt about that, but meanwhile their food must be prepared and their buttons sewed on to the best of her marked ability.  And so they were." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71490-by-nature-and-by-training-this-woman-was-all-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 19:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71490-by-nature-and-by-training-this-woman-was-all-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By nature and by training this woman was all for conservation of life.  She had been brought up in rather a strict and narrow school.  In her day although no one, certainly no woman, was expected to save humanity, every female was confidently expected to produce it.  More than that, she was earnestly enjoined to guard and protect it.  So Mary Ball and her successor Mary Washington, early imbibed not only a sense of the woman's responsibility for the family but a sense of her authority over it....At any rate, in this particular crisi she was merely obeying a law of nature as old as womanhood--to protect the creature she had brought into the world.  There was no subtlety in her.  She could not see the finer shadings of ths situation, the fact that in holding him back from the frontier she might be putting him into even greater peril.  Her course was prompted by instinct and impulse, and she never thought of questioning the right or wrong of it.  So, armed with the most primitive of all weapons, she faced her son for a hard fight.

But she was pitted here against a temendous paradox.  With her whole might she was resisting the demands of war, and yet it had been that very strength that had produced the warrior.  Her opponent was remarkably like her--in strength of mind and body, in resolution, in force of will.  Now, it is one of the ironies of life that sameness creates opposition.  In the conflict that day at Mount Vernon, therefore, the contestants were fighting with identical weapons, even though from different spheres...

George Washington must have been a very patient man.  And if he had patience, that, too, came from her by that same theory of heredity that makes a firstborn son peculiarly like his mother.  So this must be written in to her credity when for the third time she has to be recorded as trying to interrupt his destiny.

As a last resort he used a weapon that she herself had put into his hand.

Madam,&quot; he is said to have remarked with respectful finality, &quot;the God to whom you commended me when first I went to war will be my protector stil." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71491-she-saw-at-last-that-her-strange-son-was-fired</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 19:57:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71491-she-saw-at-last-that-her-strange-son-was-fired]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She saw at last that her strange son was fired by some purpose which he would carry out or die.  Seeing that, she finally currendered--the first casualty of the Revolution in Virginia.  In so far as she herself realized, the sacrifice was made for George Wahington, but subconsciously she made it for his cause--just as unaware and obeying by blind instinct the laws of her nature, she had made him to begin with out of stuff that had been in the wearving a thousand years." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71502-the-trouble-is-we-are-incurable-sentimentalists-we-insist-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 20:41:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71502-the-trouble-is-we-are-incurable-sentimentalists-we-insist-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is, we are incurable sentimentalists.  We insist on makin over historical characters to suit our preconceived notions of what they should be, chipping, sandpapering, and polishing each personality until it assumes what we consider the proper contour and color." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71503-but-this-woman-was-all-mother-a-stern-one-perhaps</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2008 20:45:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71503-but-this-woman-was-all-mother-a-stern-one-perhaps]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But this woman was all mother.  A stern one, perhaps, and autocratic at times, and somewhat hard--but after all and in spite of all, intensely maternal.  She did not look to large, far issues, nor did she know how to deal with subtleties and potentialityies; her business, from first to last, was the old elemental business of bearing and rearing.  The sod, the hearth, the young that she had brought into the world, those were the trusts committed to her, and according to her best lights she was faithful to them." -- Nancy Byrd Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72732-liberty-without-learning-is-always-in-peril-and-learning-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 09:27:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sasha add a quote by John F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72732-liberty-without-learning-is-always-in-peril-and-learning-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Liberty without Learning is always in peril and Learning without Liberty is always in vain." -- John F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
