<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/877452-fanny]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/877452-fanny" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:31:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12434-las-religiones-tambi-n-son-como-el-vino-hay-gente-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:31:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Fernando Savater]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12434-las-religiones-tambi-n-son-como-el-vino-hay-gente-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Las religiones también son como el vino: hay gente a la que le sienta mal y gente a la que le sienta bien." -- Fernando Savater]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9305-if-one-wanted-to-depict-the-whole-thing-graphically-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:33:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9305-if-one-wanted-to-depict-the-whole-thing-graphically-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one wanted to depict the whole thing graphically, every episode, with its climax, would require a three-dimensional, or, rather, no model: every experience is unrepeatable. What makes lovemaking and reading resemble each other most is that within both of them times and spaces open, different from measurable time and space." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37-anyone-whose-goal-is-something-higher-must-expect-someday-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone whose goal is 'something higher' must expect someday to suffer vertigo. What is vertigo? Fear of falling? No, Vertigo is something other than fear of falling. It is the voice of the emptiness below us which tempts and lures us, it is the desire to fall, against which, terrified, we defend ourselves." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 09:37:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1975-listen-up---there-s-no-war-that-will-end-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen up - there's no war that will end all wars." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30700-he-had-learned-the-worst-lesson-that-life-can-teach</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 09:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30700-he-had-learned-the-worst-lesson-that-life-can-teach]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had learned the worst lesson that life can teach - that it makes no sense." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 09:36:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Fanny add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13208-you-fight-your-superficiality-your-shallowness-so-as-to-try]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fight your superficiality, your shallowness, so as to try to come at people without unreal expectations, without an overload of bias or hope or arrogance, as untanklike as you can be, sans cannon and machine guns and steel plating half a foot thick; you come at them unmenacingly on your own ten toes instead of tearing up the turf with your caterpillar treads, take them on with an open mind, as equals, man to man, as we used to say, and yet you never fail to get them wrong.  You might as well have the brain of a tank.  You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again.  Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ...  The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway.  It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again.  That's how we know we're alive:  we're wrong.  Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride.  But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
