<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/878044-jan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/878044-jan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 12:46:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38926-my-friend-dick-bass-now-in-his-70s-has-travelled</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 12:46:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Roger Horchow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38926-my-friend-dick-bass-now-in-his-70s-has-travelled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My friend Dick Bass (now in his 70s) has travelled far and wide and had many adventures. His achievements include being the first person to climb the highest peak on each of the seven continents, as well as being the oldest person (by five years) to climb Mount Everest (at the age of 55.) He once told me a story of a plane ride, on which he sat next to a nice man who listened to him go on about the treacherous peaks of Everest and McKinley, the time he almost died in the Himalayas, and his upcoming plan to reclimb Everest. Just before the plane landed, Bass turned to the man sitting next to him and said, ‘After all this, I don’t think I’ve introduced myself. My name is Dick Bass.’ The man shook his hand, and responded, ‘Hi, I’m Neil Armstrong." -- Roger Horchow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62307-here-is-edward-bear-coming-downstairs-now-bump-bump-bump</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 09:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62307-here-is-edward-bear-coming-downstairs-now-bump-bump-bump]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is Edward Bear, coming downstairs now, bump, bump, bump, on the back of his head, behind Christopher Robin. It is, as far as he knows, the only way of coming downstairs, but sometimes he feels that there really is another way, if only he could stop bumping for a moment and think of it. And then he feels that perhaps there isn't." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2008 08:54:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64509-mr-camphor-could-see-that-he-freddie-was-thinking-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 09:36:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Walter Brooks        ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64509-mr-camphor-could-see-that-he-freddie-was-thinking-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Camphor could see that he (Freddie) was thinking, because he shut his eyes and put on a fiercely determined look. But when presently he opened his eyes, he shook his head. &quot;No good,&quot; he said. &quot;Thinking's like fishing. You bait your hook and throw it in the water, but if there aren't any fish around, you naturally can't catch anything. There isn't an idea around anywhere right now. I'll try again later." -- Walter Brooks        ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23157-life-is-compost</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 09:39:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Diane Setterfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23157-life-is-compost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is compost." -- Diane Setterfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1183366-i-believe-it-is-in-fear-that-we-commit-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 19:55:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jan add a quote by Phyllis Kirk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1183366-i-believe-it-is-in-fear-that-we-commit-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe it is in fear that we commit the crimes of intolerance and prejudice and what seems to me to be perhaps the saddest, most grave crime of all, our resistance to change. Afraid, we fail to see that the change is the natural and good fruit of knowledge and growth. We cling to the familiar because it is familiar and seems, therefore, to be secure. We butcher the unfamiliar and slaughter justice with the same stroke.

... 

I believe tomorrow is hopeful and that if I am to recognize tomorrow as promising, I must not fear its being different from today." -- Phyllis Kirk]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
