<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/878562-mary-rodeback]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/878562-mary-rodeback" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 17:32:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31469-happiness-is-only-real-when-shared</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2008 17:32:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31469-happiness-is-only-real-when-shared]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HAPPINESS [is] ONLY REAL WHEN SHARED" -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290141-gulls-wheel-through-spokes-of-sunlight-over-gracious-roofs-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 15:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290141-gulls-wheel-through-spokes-of-sunlight-over-gracious-roofs-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gulls wheel through spokes of sunlight over gracious roofs and dowdy thatch, snatching entrails at the marketplace and escaping over cloistered gardens, spike topped walls and treble-bolted doors. Gulls alight on whitewashed gables, creaking pagodas and dung-ripe stables; circle over towers and cavernous bells and over hidden squares where urns of urine sit by covered wells, watched by mule-drivers, mules and wolf-snouted dogs, ignored by hunch-backed makers of clogs; gather speed up the stoned-in Nakashima River and fly beneath the arches of its bridges, glimpsed form kitchen doors, watched by farmers walking high, stony ridges. Gulls fly through clouds of steam from laundries' vats; over kites unthreading corpses of cats; over scholars glimpsing truth in fragile patterns; over bath-house adulterers, heartbroken slatterns; fishwives dismembering lobsters and crabs; their husbands gutting mackerel on slabs; woodcutters' sons sharpening axes; candle-makers, rolling waxes; flint-eyed officials milking taxes; etiolated lacquerers; mottle-skinned dyers; imprecise soothsayers; unblinking liars; weavers of mats; cutters of rushes; ink-lipped calligraphers dipping brushes; booksellers ruined by unsold books; ladies-in-waiting; tasters; dressers; filching page-boys; runny-nosed cooks; sunless attic nooks where seamstresses prick calloused fingers; limping malingerers; swineherds; swindlers; lip-chewed debtors rich in excuses; heard-it-all creditors tightening nooses; prisoners haunted by happier lives and ageing rakes by other men's wives; skeletal tutors goaded to fits; firemen-turned-looters when occasion permits; tongue-tied witnesses; purchased judges; mothers-in-law nurturing briars and grudges; apothecaries grinding powders with mortars; palanquins carrying not-yet-wed daughters; silent nuns; nine-year-old whores; the once-were-beautiful gnawed by sores; statues of Jizo anointed with posies; syphilitics sneezing through rotted-off noses; potters; barbers; hawkers of oil; tanners; cutlers; carters of night-soil; gate-keepers; bee-keepers; blacksmiths and drapers; torturers; wet-nurses; perjurers; cut-purses; the newborn; the growing; the strong-willed and pliant; the ailing; the dying; the weak and defiant; over the roof of a painter withdrawn first from the world, then his family, and down into a masterpiece that has, in the end, withdrawn from its creator; and around again, where their flight began, over the balcony of the Room of Last Chrysanthemum, where a puddle from last night's rain is evaporating; a puddle in which Magistrate Shiroyama observes the blurred reflections of gulls wheeling through spokes of sunlight. This world, he thinks, contains just one masterpiece, and that is itself." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58435-we-must-strive-to-be-like-the-moon-an-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2011 20:02:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Ishmael Beah]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58435-we-must-strive-to-be-like-the-moon-an-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must strive to be like the moon.' An old man in Kabati repeated this sentence often... the adage served to remind people to always be on their best behavior and to be good to others. [S]he said that people complain when there is too much sun and it gets unbearably hot, and also when it rains too much or when it is cold. But, no one grumbles when the moon shines. Everyone becomes happy and appreciates the moon in their own special way. Children watch their shadows and play in its light, people gather at the square to tell stories and dance through the night. A lot of happy things happen when the moon shines. These are some of the reasons why we should want to be like the moon." -- Ishmael Beah]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405759-the-problem-is-that-children-believe-what-adults-say-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 09:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405759-the-problem-is-that-children-believe-what-adults-say-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem is that children believe what adults say and once they're adults themselves they exact their revenge by deceiving their own children. &quot;Life has meaning and we grown-ups know what it is&quot; is the universal lie that everyone is supposed to believe. Once you become an adult and you realize that's not true it's too late. The mystery remains intact but all your available energy has long ago been wasted on stupid things. All that's left is to anesthetize yourself by trying to hide the fact that you can't find any meaning in your life and then the better to convince yourself you deceive your own children. ... People aim for the stars and they end up like goldfish in a bowl. I wonder if it wouldn't be simpler just to teach children right from the start that life is absurd. That might deprive you of a few good moments in your childhood but it would save you a considerable amount of time as an adultnot to mention the fact that you'd be spared at least one traumatic experience i.e. the goldfish bowl." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405766-live-or-die-mere-consequences-of-what-you-have-built</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 09:22:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405766-live-or-die-mere-consequences-of-what-you-have-built]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live or die: mere consequences of what you have built. What matters is building well. So here we are I've assigned myself a new obligation. I'm going to stop undoing deconstructing I'm going to start building... ... What matters is what you are doing when you die... ...  I want to be building." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405769-if-you-dread-tomorrow-it-s-because-you-don-t-know-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 09:27:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405769-if-you-dread-tomorrow-it-s-because-you-don-t-know-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you dread tomorrow it's because you don't know how to build the present, and when you don't know how to build the present, you tell yourself you can deal with it tomorrow, and it's a lost cause anyway because tomorrow always ends up being today don't you see  ...  We have to live with the certainty that we'll get old and that it won't look nice or be good or feel happy. And tell ourselves that it's now that matters: to build something now at any price using all our strength. Always remember that there's a retirement home waiting somewhere and so we have to surpass ourselves every day, make every day undying. Climb our own personal Everest and do it in such a way that every step is a little bit of eternity. That's what the future is for: to build the present with real plans made by living people." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405770-if-you-want-to-heal-heal-others-and-smile-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 09:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/405770-if-you-want-to-heal-heal-others-and-smile-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to heal
Heal others
And smile or weep
At this very happy reversal of fate" -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287205-thinking-back-on-it-this-evening-with-my-heart-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 09:35:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287205-thinking-back-on-it-this-evening-with-my-heart-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thinking back on it, this evening, with my heart and my stomach all jelly, I have finally concluded, maybe that's what life is about: there's a lot of despair, but also the odd moment of beauty, where time is no longer the same. It's as if those strains of music created a sort of interlude in time, something suspended, an elsewhere that had come to us, an always within a never." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247142-when-someone-that-you-love-dies-it-s-like-fireworks-suddenly-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 10:17:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247142-when-someone-that-you-love-dies-it-s-like-fireworks-suddenly-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone that you love dies..it's like fireworks suddenly burning out in the sky and everything going black." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55778-c-est-peut--tre-a-la-vie-beaucoup-de-d-sespoir</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 10:17:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55778-c-est-peut--tre-a-la-vie-beaucoup-de-d-sespoir]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["... c'est peut-être ça la vie : beaucoup de désespoir mais aussi quelques moments de beauté où le temps n'est plus le même. C'est comme si les notes de musique faisaient un genre de parenthèses dans le temps, de supension, un ailleurs ici même, un toujours dans le jamais. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oui, c'est ça, un &lt;i&gt;toujours&lt;/i&gt; dans le &lt;i&gt;jamais&lt;/i&gt;." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247130-what-i-dread-more-than-anything-else-in-this-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 10:18:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247130-what-i-dread-more-than-anything-else-in-this-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...what I dread more than anything else in this life is noise...silence helps you to go inward..anyone who is interested in something more than just life outside actually needs silence." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247129-it-would-be-so-much-better-if-we-could-share</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 10:18:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247129-it-would-be-so-much-better-if-we-could-share]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It would be so much better if we could share our insecurity, if we could all venture inside ourselves and realize that green beans and vitamin C, however much they nurture us, cannot save lives, or sustain our souls." -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186371-do-you-know-that-it-is-in-your-company-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2011 10:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Muriel Barbery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186371-do-you-know-that-it-is-in-your-company-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know that it is in your company that I have had my finest thoughts?" -- Muriel Barbery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61807-reading-because-we-control-it-is-adaptable-to-our-needs</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 14:35:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Sven Birkerts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61807-reading-because-we-control-it-is-adaptable-to-our-needs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading, because we control it, is adaptable to our needs and rhythms. We are free to indulge our subjective associative impulse; the term I coin for this is &lt;i&gt;deep reading&lt;/i&gt;: the slow and meditative possession of a book. We don't just read the words, we dream our lives in their vicinity. The printed page becomes a kind of wrought-iron fence we crawl through, returning, once we have wandered, to the very place we started." -- Sven Birkerts]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611577-love-is-an-abstract-noun-something-nebulous-and-yet-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 14:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/611577-love-is-an-abstract-noun-something-nebulous-and-yet-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is an abstract noun, something nebulous. And yet love turns out to be the only part of us that is solid, as the world turns upside down and the screen goes black." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383192-we-do-literature-a-real-disservice-if-we-reduce-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 20:30:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Marjorie Garber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383192-we-do-literature-a-real-disservice-if-we-reduce-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do literature a real disservice if we reduce it to knowledge or to use, to a problem to be solved.  If literature solves problems, it does so by its own inexhaustibility, and by its ultimate refusal to be applied or used, even for moral good.  This refusal, indeed, is literature's most moral act.  At a time when meanings are manifold, disparate, and always changing, the rich possibility of interpretation--the happy resistance of the text to ever be fully known and mastered--is one of the most exhilarating products of human culture." -- Marjorie Garber]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
