<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/879911-despond]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/879911-despond" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:00:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994868-why-man-christ-is-so-hid-in-god-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:00:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by John Bunyan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994868-why-man-christ-is-so-hid-in-god-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why, man! Christ is so hid in God from the natural apprehensions of the flesh, that he cannot by any man be savingly known, unless God the Father reveals him to them." -- John Bunyan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994880-369-hope-i-do-believe-as-you-say-that-fear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:09:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by John Bunyan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994880-369-hope-i-do-believe-as-you-say-that-fear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["{369} HOPE. I do believe, as you say, that fear tends much to men's good, and to make them right, at their beginning to go on pilgrimage." -- John Bunyan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994883-chr-true-or-right-fear-is-discovered-by-three-things---</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 11:12:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by John Bunyan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/994883-chr-true-or-right-fear-is-discovered-by-three-things---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["CHR. True or right fear is discovered by three things:-- 1. By its rise; it is caused by saving convictions for sin. 2. It driveth the soul to lay fast hold of Christ for salvation. 3. It begetteth and continueth in the soul a great reverence of God, his Word, and ways, keeping it tender, and making it afraid to turn from them, to the right hand or to the left, to anything that may dishonour God, break its peace, grieve the Spirit, or cause the enemy to speak reproachfully." -- John Bunyan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995495-there-said-they-is-the-mount-zion-the-heavenly-jerusalem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 20:22:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by John Bunyan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/995495-there-said-they-is-the-mount-zion-the-heavenly-jerusalem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There, said they, is the Mount Zion, the heavenly Jerusalem, the innumerable company of angels, and the spirits of just men made perfect. [Heb. 12:22-24] You are going now, said they, to the paradise of God, wherein you shall see the tree of life, and eat of the never-fading fruits thereof; and when you come there, you shall have white robes given you, and your walk and talk shall be every day with the King, even all the days of eternity. [Rev. 2:7, 3:4, 21:4,5] There you shall not see again such things as you saw when you were in the lower region upon the earth, to wit, sorrow, sickness, affliction, and death, for the former things are passed away. You are now going to Abraham, to Isaac, and Jacob, and to the prophets--men that God hath taken away from the evil to come, and that are now resting upon their beds, each one walking in his righteousness. [Isa. 57:1,2, 65:17]" -- John Bunyan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050766-i-call-upon-you-to-renounce-your-diabolical-blasphemy-if-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:25:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050766-i-call-upon-you-to-renounce-your-diabolical-blasphemy-if-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I call upon you to renounce your diabolical blasphemy...if you will not, we shall all hold your seat as possessed and oppressed by Satan, the damned seat of Antichrist, in the name of Jesus Christ, whom you persecute.&quot;
&quot;And as they excommunicated me for the sacrilege of heresy, so I excommunicate them in the name of the sacred truth of God. Christ will judge whose excommunication will stand. Amen" -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050768-we-recognize-the-authority-but-we-must-rebuke-our-pilates</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:27:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050768-we-recognize-the-authority-but-we-must-rebuke-our-pilates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We recognize the authority, but we must rebuke our Pilates in their crime and self-confidence. Then they say to us, &quot;You are reviling the majesty of God, to which we answer, &quot;We will suffer what you do to us, but to keep still and let it appear that you do right when you do wrong, that we cannot and will not do.&quot; We must confess the truth rebuke the evil. There is a big difference between suffering injustice and keeping still. We should suffer. We should not keep still. The Christian must bear testimony for the truth and die for the truth. But how can he die for the truth if he has not first confessed to truth? Thus Christ showed that Pilate did exercise of authority from God and at the same time rebuked him for doing wrong." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050770-as-god-christ-the-virgin-the-prince-of-the-apostles-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:28:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050770-as-god-christ-the-virgin-the-prince-of-the-apostles-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As God, Christ, the virgin, the prince of the apostles and the shepherds labored even so must we labor in our callings. God had no hands and feet of his own. He must continue his labors through human instruments. The lonelier the task the better. The milkmaid and the carter of manure are doing a work more pleasing to God to psalm singing of the Carthusian. Luther never tired of defending those callings which for one reason or another were disparaged. The mother was considered lower than the virgin. Luther replied that the mother exhibits the pattern of the love of God, which overcomes sins just as her love overcomes dirty diapers" -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050773-we-are-sinners-and-at-the-same-time-righteous</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:28:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050773-we-are-sinners-and-at-the-same-time-righteous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are sinners and at the same time righteous" -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050774-i-must-even-take-to-myself-the-sins-of-others</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:30:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050774-i-must-even-take-to-myself-the-sins-of-others]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" I must even take to myself the sins of others as Christ took mine to himself. Thus we see that the Christian man lives not to himself but to Christ and his neighbor through love. By faith he rises above himself to God and from God goes below himself in love and remains always in God and in love." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050777-when-god-in-his-sheer-mercy-and-without-any-merit</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050777-when-god-in-his-sheer-mercy-and-without-any-merit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["when God in his sheer mercy and without any merit of mine has given me such unspeakable riches, shall I not freely, joyously, wholeheartedly, unprompted do everything that I know will please him? I will give myself as a sort of Christ to my neighbor as Christ gave himself for me." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050779-unless-a-man-is-already-a-believer-and-a-christian</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:31:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050779-unless-a-man-is-already-a-believer-and-a-christian]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless a man is already a believer and a Christian, his works have no value at all. They are foolish, idle, damnable sins, because when good works are brought forward as grounds for justification, they are no longer good. Understand that we do not reject good works, but praise them highly." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050780-good-works-do-not-make-a-man-good-but-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050780-good-works-do-not-make-a-man-good-but-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good works do not make a man good, but a good man does good works" -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050782-temptations-of-course-cannot-be-avoided-but-because-we-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:32:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050782-temptations-of-course-cannot-be-avoided-but-because-we-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Temptations of course cannot be avoided, but because we cannot prevent the birds from flying over our heads, there is no need that we should let them nest in our hair." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050784-when-i-am-told-god-became-man-i-can-follow</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:33:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050784-when-i-am-told-god-became-man-i-can-follow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I am told God became man, I can follow the idea, but I just do not understand what it means. For what man, if left to his natural promptings, if he were God, would humble himself to lie in the feedbox of a donkey or to hang upon a cross? God laid upon Christ the iniquities of us all. 
    This is that ineffable and infinite mercy of God which the slender capacity of a man's heart cannot comprehend and much less utter-that unfathomable depth and burning zeal of God's love toward us. And truly the magnitude of God's mercy engenders in us not only a hardness to believe but also incredulity itself." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050785-not-through-thoughts-wisdom-and-will-does-the-faith-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:34:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050785-not-through-thoughts-wisdom-and-will-does-the-faith-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not through thoughts, wisdom, and will does the faith of Christ arise in us, but through an uncommon incomprehensible and hidden operation of the Spirit, which is given by faith in Christ only at the hearing of the Word and without any other work ours." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050787-divine-majesty-does-not-speak-directly-to-men-god-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 12:34:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1050787-divine-majesty-does-not-speak-directly-to-men-god-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Divine majesty does not speak directly to men. God is a consuming fire, and the dreams and visions of the Saints are terrible… .Prove the spirits; and if you are not able to do so, then take the advice of Gamaliel and wait." -- Roland H. Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118448-spalatin-asked-luther-what-he-thought-of-long-engagements-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 20:26:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118448-spalatin-asked-luther-what-he-thought-of-long-engagements-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spalatin asked Luther what he thought of long engagements. He replied, &quot;Don't put off till tomorrow! By delay Hannibal lost Rome. By delay Esau forfeited his birth right. Christ said, 'Ye shall seek me, and ye shall not find.' Thus Scripture, experience, and all creation testify that the gifts of God must be taking on the wing." -- Roland Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118453-good-god-what-a-lot-of-trouble-there-is-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 20:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by roland bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118453-good-god-what-a-lot-of-trouble-there-is-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good God, what a lot of trouble there is in marriage! Adam has made a mess of our nature. Think of all the squabbles Adam and Eve must of had in the course of their 900 years. Eve would say,  'You ate the apple,' and Adam would retort, 'You gave it to me.' " -- roland bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118456-the-first-love-is-drunken-when-the-intoxication-wears-off</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 20:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118456-the-first-love-is-drunken-when-the-intoxication-wears-off]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first love is drunken. When the intoxication wears off, then comes the real marriage love." -- Roland Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118463-union-of-the-flesh-does-nothing-there-must-also-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 20:31:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by Roland Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1118463-union-of-the-flesh-does-nothing-there-must-also-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Union of the flesh does nothing. There must also be union of manners and mind.&quot; 
Christ said we must become as little children to enter the kingdom of heaven. Dear God, this is too much. How we got to become such idiots?" -- Roland Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190554-so-many-people-come-to-church-with-the-genuine-desire</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 15:46:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Despond add a quote by the cost of discipleship dietrich bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1190554-so-many-people-come-to-church-with-the-genuine-desire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many people come to church with the genuine desire to hear what we have to say, yet they are always going back home with the uncomfortable feeling that we're making it too difficult for them to come to Jesus. Are we determined to have nothing to do with all these people? They are convinced that it is not the Word Jesus himself that puts them off, but the superstructure of human, institutional, and doctrinal elements in our preaching." -- the cost of discipleship dietrich bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
