<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/882696-courtney]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/882696-courtney" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 13:06:47 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 13:06:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2755-the-man-in-black-fled-across-the-desert-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2009 13:09:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2755-the-man-in-black-fled-across-the-desert-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man in black fled across the desert, and the gunslinger followed." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401106-it-s-been-my-experience-that-people-who-make-proclamations-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:08:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Chelsea Handler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/401106-it-s-been-my-experience-that-people-who-make-proclamations-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's been my experience that people who make proclamations about themselves are usually the opposite of what they claim to be." -- Chelsea Handler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106468-at-some-point-during-almost-every-romantic-comedy-the-female</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:10:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Chelsea Handler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106468-at-some-point-during-almost-every-romantic-comedy-the-female]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At some point during almost every romantic comedy, the female lead suddenly trips and falls, stumbling helplessly over something ridiculous like a leaf, and then some Matthew McConaughey type either whips around the corner just in the nick of time to save her or is clumsily pulled down along with her. That event predictably leads to the magical moment of their first kiss. Please. I fall ALL the time. You know who comes and gets me? The bouncer." -- Chelsea Handler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20440-there-are-two-kinds-of-people-i-don-t-trust-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2011 01:10:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Chelsea Handler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20440-there-are-two-kinds-of-people-i-don-t-trust-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of people I don't trust: people who don't drink and people who collect stickers." -- Chelsea Handler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/792472-it-s-not-the-concept-of-marriage-i-have-a-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 13:03:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Courtney add a quote by Chelsea Handler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/792472-it-s-not-the-concept-of-marriage-i-have-a-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the concept of marriage I have a problem with. I'd like to get married too. A couple times. It's the actual wedding that pisses me off.
The problem is that everyone who gets married seems to think that they are the first person in the entire universe to do it, and that the year leading up to the event revolves entirely around them. You have to throw them showers, bachelorette weekends, buy a bridesmaid dress, and then buy a ticket to some godforsaken town wherever they decide to drag you. If you're really unlucky, they'll ask you to recite a poem at their wedding. That's just what I want to do- monitor my drinking until I'm done with my public service announcement. And what do we get out of it, you ask? A dry piece of chicken and a roll in the hay with their hillbilly cousin. I could get that at home, thanks.
Then they have the audacity to go shopping and pick out their own gifts. I want to know who the first person was who said this was okay. After spending all that money on a bachelorette weekend, a shower, and often a flight across the country, they expect you to go to Williams Sonoma or Pottery Barn and do research? Then they send you a thank-you note applauding you for such a thoughtful gift. They're the one who picked it out! I always want to remind the person that absolutely no thought went into typing in a name and having a salad bowl come up." -- Chelsea Handler]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
