<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/883407-brik]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/883407-brik" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 20:57:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2121-it-is-hard-enough-to-remember-my-opinions-without-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 20:57:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2121-it-is-hard-enough-to-remember-my-opinions-without-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard enough to remember my opinions, without also remembering my reasons for them!" -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4406-a-paranoid-is-someone-who-knows-a-little-of-what-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 20:58:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4406-a-paranoid-is-someone-who-knows-a-little-of-what-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A paranoid is someone who knows a little of what's going on. " -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4408-without-deviation-from-the-norm-progress-is-not-possible</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 20:58:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4408-without-deviation-from-the-norm-progress-is-not-possible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without deviation from the norm, progress is not possible." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6776-anyway-because-we-are-readers-we-don-t-have-to-wait-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 20:59:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6776-anyway-because-we-are-readers-we-don-t-have-to-wait-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway—because we are readers, we don't have to wait for some communications executive to decide what we should think about next—and how we should think about it. We can fill our heads with anything from aardvarks to zucchinis—at any time of night or day." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9939-the-price-good-men-pay-for-indifference-to-public-affairs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 21:00:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9939-the-price-good-men-pay-for-indifference-to-public-affairs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The price good men pay for indifference to public affairs is to be ruled by evil men." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7578-a-serious-and-good-philosophical-work-could-be-written-consisting</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 21:02:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7578-a-serious-and-good-philosophical-work-could-be-written-consisting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A serious and good philosophical work could be written consisting entirely of jokes." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 21:06:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing was ever in tune. People just blindly grabbed at whatever there was: communism, health foods, zen, surfing, ballet, hypnotism, group encounters, orgies, biking, herbs, Catholicism, weight-lifting, travel, withdrawal, vegetarianism, India, painting, writing, sculpting, composing, conducting, backpacking, yoga, copulating, gambling, drinking, hanging around, frozen yogurt, Beethoven, Back, Buddha, Christ, TM, H, carrot juice, suicide, handmade suits, jet travel, New York City, and then it all evaporated and fell apart. People had to find things to do while waiting to die. I guess it was nice to have a choice." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16445-today-the-only-class-which-in-its-subjective-self-perception</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 21:12:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16445-today-the-only-class-which-in-its-subjective-self-perception]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...today, the only class which, in its 'subjective' self perception, explicitly conceives of an presents itself as a class is the notorious 'middle class' which is precisely the 'non-class': the allegedly hard-working middle strata of society which define themselves not only by their allegiance to firm moral and religious standards, but by a double opposition to both 'extremes' of the social space - non-patriotic 'deracinated' rich corporations on the one side; poor excluded immigrants and ghetto-members on the other. The 'middle class' grounds its identity in the exclusion of both extremes which, when they are directly counterpoised, give us 'class antagonism' at its purest. The constitutive lie of the very notion of the 'middle class' is thus the same as that of the true Party line between the two extremes of 'right-wing deviation' and left-wing deviation' in Stalinism: the 'middle class' is, in its very 'real' existence, the embodied lie, the denial of antagonism - in psychoanalytic terms, the 'middle class' is a fetish, the impossible intersection of left and right which, by expelling both poles of the antagonism into the position of antisocial 'extremes' which corrode the healthy social body (multinational corporations and intruding immigrants), presents itself as the neutral common ground of Society. In other words, the 'middle class' is the very form of the disavowal of the fact that 'Society doesn't exist' (Laclau) - in it, Society does exist." -- Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16444-young-people-everywhere-have-been-allowed-to-choose-between-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2008 21:13:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by Guy Debord]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16444-young-people-everywhere-have-been-allowed-to-choose-between-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Young people everywhere have been allowed to choose between love and a garbage disposal unit. Everywhere they have chosen the garbage disposal unit." -- Guy Debord]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212336-i-hate-slick-and-pretty-things-i-prefer-mistakes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 04:09:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brik add a quote by David Lynch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212336-i-hate-slick-and-pretty-things-i-prefer-mistakes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hate slick and pretty things. I prefer mistakes and accidents. Which is why I like things like cuts and bruises - they're like little flowers. I've always said that if you have a name for something, like 'cut' or 'bruise,' people will automatically be disturbed by it. But when you see the same thing in nature, and you don't know what it is, it can be very beautiful." -- David Lynch]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
