<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/884058-megan-pruitt]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/884058-megan-pruitt" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:27:17 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:27:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:27:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17062-i-do-not-want-people-to-be-very-agreeable-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:27:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17062-i-do-not-want-people-to-be-very-agreeable-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not want people to be very agreeable, as it saves me the trouble of liking them a great deal." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:28:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:29:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:29:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in that moment, I swear we were infinite." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:30:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:32:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/406-all-god-does-is-watch-us-and-kill-us-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12724-if-you-re-going-to-read-this-don-t-bother</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:32:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12724-if-you-re-going-to-read-this-don-t-bother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're going to read this, don't bother." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16192-my-mom-says-do-you-know-what-the-aids-memorial</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:33:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16192-my-mom-says-do-you-know-what-the-aids-memorial]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mom says, &quot;Do you know what the AIDS memorial quilt is all about?&quot;
Jump to how much I hate my brother at this moment.
I bought this fabric because I thought it would make a nice panel for Shane,&quot; Mom says. &quot;We just ran into some problems with what to sew on it.&quot;
Give me amnesia.
Flash.
Give me new parents.
Flash.
Your mother didn't want to step on any toes,&quot; Dad says. He twists a drumstick off and starts scraping the meat onto a plate. &quot;With gay stuff you have to be so careful since everything means something in secret code. I mean, we didn't want to give people the wrong idea.&quot;
My Mom leans over to scoop yams onto my plate, and says, &quot;Your father wanted a black border, but black on a field of blue would mean Shane was excited by leather sex, you know, bondage and discipline, sado and masochism.&quot; She says, &quot;Really, those panels are to help the people left behind.&quot;
Strangers are going to see us and see Shane's name,&quot; my dad says. &quot;We didn't want them thinking things.&quot;
The dishes all start their slow clockwise march around the table. The stuffing. The olives. The cranberry sauce. &quot;I wanted pink triangles but all the panels have pink triangles,&quot; my mom says. &quot;It's the Nazi symbol for homosexuals.&quot; She says,&quot;Your father suggested black triangles, but that would mean Shane was a lesbian. It looks like female pubic hair. The black triangle does.&quot;
My father says, &quot;Then I wanted a green border, but it turns out that would mean Shane was a male prostitute.&quot;
My mom says, &quot;We almost chose a red border, but that would mean fisting.  Brown would mean either scat or rimming, we couldn't figure which.&quot;
Yellow,&quot; my father says, &quot;means watersports.&quot;
A lighter shade of blue,&quot; Mom says, &quot;would mean just regular oral sex.&quot;
Regular white,&quot; my father says, &quot;would mean anal. White could also mean Shane was excited by men wearing underwear.&quot;  He says, &quot;I can't remember which.&quot;
My mother passes me the quilted chicken with the rolls still warm inside.
We're supposed to sit and eat with Shane dead all over the table in front of us.
Finally we just gave up,&quot; my mom says, &quot;and I made a nice tablecloth out of the material.&quot;
Between the yams and the stuffing, Dad looks down at his plate and says, &quot;Do you know about rimming?&quot;
I know it isn't table talk.
And fisting?&quot; my mom asks.
I say, I know. I don't mention Manus and his vocational porno magazines.
We sit there, all of us around a blue shroud with the turkey more like a big dead baked animal than ever, the stuffing chock full of organs you can still recognize, the heart and gizzard and liver, the gravy thick with cooked fat and blood. The flower centerpiece could be a casket spray.
Would you pass the butter, please?&quot; my mother says. To my father she says, &quot;Do you know what felching is?" -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 00:33:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by J. D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5722-anyway-i-keep-picturing-all-these-little-kids-playing-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, I keep picturing all these little kids playing some game in this big field of rye and all.  Thousands of little kids, and nobody's around - nobody big, I mean - except me.  And I'm standing on the edge of some crazy cliff.  What I have to do, I have to catch everybody if they start to go over the cliff - I mean if they're running and they don't look where they're going I have to come out from somewhere and catch them.  That's all I do all day.  I'd just be the catcher in the rye and all.  I know it's crazy, but that's the only thing I'd really like to be." -- J. D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
