<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/884776-brenda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/884776-brenda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 11:35:25 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22525-from-freedom-is-true-forgiveness-is-one-of-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2008 11:35:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Brandon Bays]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22525-from-freedom-is-true-forgiveness-is-one-of-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From Freedom is:
&quot;True forgiveness is one of the most healing relasing, and freeing gifts we give to ourselves.&quot;

&quot;You can't fake it (forgivenss). It has to come from an open heart. It has to be real. Otherwise it is pointless. In order to fruly  forgive, you must be willing to open your heart and face and release the pain there.&quot; 
&quot;It requires humility. It requites us to give up our rightenous indignation, get off our soapbox, let go of blame, and le go of th pride of being right. It means we have to be willing to drop our victim story, soften our stance, and if necessary, let our heart be broken wide open.&quot;   Brandon Bays Chapter 8 on forgiveness.    " -- Brandon Bays]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34283-book-of-mormon-4-neiphi-1-4-15-20-4-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 07:12:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34283-book-of-mormon-4-neiphi-1-4-15-20-4-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Book of Mormon
4 Neiphi. 1: 4, 15-20

4  And it came to pass that the thirty and seventh year passed away also, and there still continued to be peace in the land. 
      •  •  •
  15   And it came to pass that there was no contention in the land, because of the love of God which did dwell in the hearts of the people. 
  16   And there were no envyings, nor strifes, nor tumults, nor horedoms, nor lyings, nor murders, nor any manner of lasciviousness; and surely there could not be a happier people among all the people who had been created by the hand of God. 
  17   There were no robbers, nor murderers, neither were there Lamanites, nor any manner of -ites; but they were in one, the children of Christ, and heirs to the kingdom of God. 
  18   And how blessed were they! For the Lord did bless them in all their doings; yea, even they were blessed and prospered until an *hundred and ten years had passed away; and the first generation from Christ had passed away, and there was no contention in all the land. " -- The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15888-the-first-peace-which-is-the-most-important-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 07:23:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Black Elk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15888-the-first-peace-which-is-the-most-important-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first peace, which is the most important, is that which comes within the souls of people when they realize their relationship, their oneness with the universe and all its powers, and when they realize at the center of the universe dwells the Great Spirit, and that its center is really everywhere, it is within each of us." -- Black Elk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34295-bruises-heal-more-quickly-than-emotional-scars-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 07:41:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Arbinger Institute]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34295-bruises-heal-more-quickly-than-emotional-scars-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bruises heal more quickly than emotional scars do." -- Arbinger Institute]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34296-seeing-an-equal-person-as-an-inferior-object-is-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 07:42:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Arbinger Institute]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34296-seeing-an-equal-person-as-an-inferior-object-is-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seeing an equal person as an inferior object is an act of violence" -- Arbinger Institute]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34298-life-is-a-gift-from-god-we-hold-from-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 07:51:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34298-life-is-a-gift-from-god-we-hold-from-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life Is a Gift from God.
We hold from God the gift which includes all others. This gift is life -- physical, intellectual, and moral life. 

But life cannot maintain itself alone. The Creator of life has entrusted us with the responsibility of preserving, developing, and perfecting it. In order that we may accomplish this, He has provided us with a collection of marvelous faculties. And He has put us in the midst of a variety of natural resources. By the application of our faculties to these natural resources we convert them into products, and use them. This process is necessary in order that life may run its appointed course. 

Life, faculties, production--in other words, individuality, liberty, property -- this is man. And in spite of the cunning of artful political leaders, these three gifts from God precede all human legislation, and are superior to it. 

Life, liberty, and property do not exist because men have made laws. On the contrary, it was the fact that life, liberty, and property existed beforehand that caused men to make laws in the first place." -- Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3922-cogito-ergo-sum-i-think-therefore-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 12:32:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by René Descartes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3922-cogito-ergo-sum-i-think-therefore-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cogito ergo sum.    &lt;i&gt;(I think, therefore I am.)&lt;/i&gt;" -- René Descartes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34312-by-first-knowing-that-this-power-does-exist-then-using</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2008 08:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Baird T. Spalding]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34312-by-first-knowing-that-this-power-does-exist-then-using]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By first KNOWING that this power does exist, then using it with absolute confidence, you soon become wholly conscious of it.  You soon know that it is all-inclusive in and through you.  If you will but let it flow, it will rush to you in every instance.  It flows to you as you let it flow from you.  Stand forth as God and give it out.  This is God your Father in you and you and your Father are one.  Not servants but SONS, Sons of First Primal Cause.  All that I AM has, is yours; for you are I AM." -- Baird T. Spalding]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36142-love-alone-is-capable-of-uniting-living-beings-in-such</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 19:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Teihand de Chardin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36142-love-alone-is-capable-of-uniting-living-beings-in-such]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love alone is capable of uniting living beings in such a way as to complete and fulfil them for it alone takes them and joins them by what is deepest within themselves. 
" -- Teihand de Chardin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36143-to-be-able-to-be-oneself-and-not-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 19:40:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Milton Avery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36143-to-be-able-to-be-oneself-and-not-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be able to be oneself and not have to disown one's values to please another - That is what intimate love is all about." -- Milton Avery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36144-love-is-making-friends-with-fear-because-fear-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 19:47:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Allen L. Roland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36144-love-is-making-friends-with-fear-because-fear-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is making friends with fear because fear is the constant companion of intimacy ~ and when you bring fear out of the darkness and into the light, you realize it was an illusion based on our own insecurities." -- Allen L. Roland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54573-men-imagine-that-thought-can-be-kept-secret-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 08:28:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by James Allen, ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54573-men-imagine-that-thought-can-be-kept-secret-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["men imagine that thought can be kept secret, but it cannot. It rapidly crystallizes into habit, and habit solidifies into habits of drunkenness and sensuality, which solidify into circumstances of destitution and disease. Impure thoughts of every kind crystallize into enervating and confusing habits, which solidify into distracting and adverse circumstances. Thoughts of fear, doubt, and indecision crystallize into weak, unmanly, and irresolute habits, which solidify into circumstances of failure, indigence, and slavish dependence. 

Lazy thoughts crystallize into habits of uncleanliness and dishonesty, which solidify into circumstances of foulness and beggary. Hateful and condemnatory thoughts crystallize into habits of accusation and violence, which solidify into circumstances of injury and persecution. Selfish thoughts of all kinds crystallize into habits of self-seeking, which solidify into circumstances more of less distressing. 

On the other hand, beautiful thoughts of all crystallize into habits of grace and kindliness, which solidify into genial and sunny circumstances. Pure thoughts crystallize into habits of temperance and self-control, which solidify into circumstances of repose and peace. Thoughts of courage, self-reliance, and decision crystallize into manly habits, which solidify into circumstances of success, plenty, and freedom. 
" -- James Allen, ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290392-it-is-so-easy-to-think-that-the-world-revolves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2012 12:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/290392-it-is-so-easy-to-think-that-the-world-revolves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is so easy to think that the world revolves around you, but all you have to do is stare up at the sky to realize it isn't that way at all." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2012 19:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72160-if-you-only-read-the-books-that-everyone-else-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you only read the books that everyone else is reading, you can only think what everyone else is thinking." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916846-asperger-s-syndrome-is-a-neurological-condition-not-a-mental-illness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 11:02:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Carol Shay Hornung]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916846-asperger-s-syndrome-is-a-neurological-condition-not-a-mental-illness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Asperger's Syndrome is a neurological condition, not a mental illness. Some parts of your brain are over-wired, and work more than other people's, and other parts are under-wired. They don't function the same way as in a typical person. In your case, you have to learn social conventions; you don't pick up on them instinctively. Logic and reason dictate your actions more than emotion or instinct." -- Carol Shay Hornung]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207926-for-my-dad-i-miss-you-every-day-lost</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 11:03:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207926-for-my-dad-i-miss-you-every-day-lost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For My Dad ~ &quot;I miss you every day.&quot; 

Lost love is still love, Eddie. It just takes a different form, that's all. You can't hold their hand... You can't tousle their hair... But when those senses weaken another one comes to life... Memory... Memory becomes your partner. You hold it... you dance with it... Life has to end, Eddie... Love doesn't." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325981-in-school-we-learn-that-mistakes-are-bad-and-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2014 12:10:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Robert T. Kiyosaki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325981-in-school-we-learn-that-mistakes-are-bad-and-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In school we learn that mistakes are bad, and we are punished for making them. Yet, if you look at the way humans are designed to learn, we learn by making mistakes. We learn to walk by falling down. If we never fell down, we would never walk." -- Robert T. Kiyosaki]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32702-in-fact-were-it-given-to-our-human-eye-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 06:54:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32702-in-fact-were-it-given-to-our-human-eye-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In fact, were it given to our human eye to see into the consciences of others, we would judge a man much more surely from what he dreams than from what he thinks. There is will in the thought, there is none in the dream. Even in the gigantic and the ideal, the dream, which is completely spontaneous, takes and keeps the form of our mind. Nothing springs more directly and more sincerely from our innermost souls than our unreflected and indefinite aspirations, much more than in ideas, which are structured, studied, and compared, can we find the true character of each man. Our chimeras are most like us. Each of us dreams the unknown and the impossible according to his own nature." -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460966-if-any-man-despises-me-that-is-his-problem-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2014 06:55:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brenda add a quote by Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460966-if-any-man-despises-me-that-is-his-problem-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If any man despises me, that is his problem. My only concern is not doing or saying anything deserving of contempt." -- Marcus Aurelius]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
