<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/885076-matt]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/885076-matt" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 23:33:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5814-i-do-not-seek-i-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2009 23:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5814-i-do-not-seek-i-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not seek. I find." -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46156-perhaps-it-is-easier-to-understand-that-even-though-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 10:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by virginia axline]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46156-perhaps-it-is-easier-to-understand-that-even-though-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps it is easier to understand that even though we do not have the wisdom to enumerate the reasons for the behavior of another person, we can grant that each individual does have their private world of meaning, conceived out of the integrity and dignity of their personality." -- virginia axline]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114357-the-word-itself-has-another-color-it-s-not-a-word</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 23:46:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by William Gass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/114357-the-word-itself-has-another-color-it-s-not-a-word]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The word itself has another color. It’s not a word with any resonance, although the e was once pronounced. There is only the bump now between b and l, the relief at the end, the whew. It hasn’t the sly turn which crimson takes halfway through, yellow’s deceptive jelly, or the rolled-down sound in brown. It hasn’t violet’s rapid sexual shudder or like a rough road the irregularity of ultramarine, the low puddle in mauve like a pancake covered in cream, the disapproving purse to pink, the assertive brevity of red, the whine of green." -- William Gass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2011 23:51:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2229-to-be-hopeful-in-bad-times-is-not-just-foolishly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["TO BE HOPEFUL in bad times is not just foolishly romantic. It is based on the fact that human history is a history not only of cruelty, but also of compassion, sacrifice, courage, kindness.
What we choose to emphasize in this complex history will determine our lives. If we see only the worst, it destroys our capacity to do something. If we remember those times and places—and there are so many—where people have behaved magnificently, this gives us the energy to act, and at least the possibility of sending this spinning top of a world in a different direction.
And if we do act, in however small a way, we don’t have to wait for some grand utopian future. The future is an infinite succession of presents, and to live now as we think human beings should live, in defiance of all that is bad around us, is itself a marvelous victory." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73904-i-dreamed-i-was-a-single-moment-in-a-single</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2011 15:13:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73904-i-dreamed-i-was-a-single-moment-in-a-single]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I dreamed I was a single moment in a single day. 

A note struck and vanished. A sounding. A reckoning. Gone." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72921-you-should-always-be-trying-to-write-a-poem-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 20:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by John Berryman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72921-you-should-always-be-trying-to-write-a-poem-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should always be trying to write a poem you are unable to write, a poem you lack the technique, the language, the courage to achieve.  Otherwise you're merely imitating yourself, going nowhere, because that's always easiest." -- John Berryman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 19:45:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43122-because-some-days-the-world-holds-true-at-the-drop</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 23:09:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Gary Lutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43122-because-some-days-the-world-holds-true-at-the-drop]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because some days the world holds true at the drop of a hat, don't you find? Things favor themselves: whatever you reach for - a shimmered arm, or parts unknown - is ready, finally, to have itself be handled." -- Gary Lutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25086-always-bear-in-mind-that-your-own-resolution-to-succeed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 11:43:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25086-always-bear-in-mind-that-your-own-resolution-to-succeed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any one thing." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282517-when-i-was-5-years-old-my-mother-always-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2012 21:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by John Lennon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282517-when-i-was-5-years-old-my-mother-always-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was 5 years old, my mother always told me that happiness was the key to life. When I went to school, they asked me what I wanted to be when I grew up. I wrote down ‘happy’. They told me I didn’t understand the assignment, and I told them they didn’t understand life." -- John Lennon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34531-one-day-i-will-find-the-right-words-and-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 19:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34531-one-day-i-will-find-the-right-words-and-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day I will find the right words, and they will be simple." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 19:06:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14013-the-fact-that-we-live-at-the-bottom-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that we live at the bottom of a deep gravity well, on the surface of a gas covered planet going around a nuclear fireball 90 million miles away and think this to be normal is obviously some indication of how skewed our perspective tends to be." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524597-in-the-land-of-gibberish-the-man-who-makes-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 12:09:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524597-in-the-land-of-gibberish-the-man-who-makes-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the land of Gibberish, the man who makes sense, the man who speaks clearly, clearly speaks nonsense. " -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28292-heterosexuality-is-not-normal-it-s-just-common</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 10:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28292-heterosexuality-is-not-normal-it-s-just-common]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heterosexuality is not normal, it's just common." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907175-it-is-your-duty-in-life-to-save-your-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 14:47:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Amedeo Modigliani]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907175-it-is-your-duty-in-life-to-save-your-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is your duty in life to save your dream." -- Amedeo Modigliani]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74813-noble-deeds-and-hot-baths-are-the-best-cures-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 20:48:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Dodie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74813-noble-deeds-and-hot-baths-are-the-best-cures-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Noble deeds and hot baths are the best cures for depression." -- Dodie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
