<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/88513-josiah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/88513-josiah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 15:41:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145325-now-we-have-fathomed-what-our-space-ship-is---a-tiny</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2009 15:41:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josiah add a quote by Harry Martinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145325-now-we-have-fathomed-what-our-space-ship-is---a-tiny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["now we have fathomed what our space-ship is
--a tiny bubble in a glass of God." -- Harry Martinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307032-a-symbolic-unity-formed-by-the-languor-of-the-fluids</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 18:17:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josiah add a quote by Michel Foucault]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307032-a-symbolic-unity-formed-by-the-languor-of-the-fluids]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A symbolic unity formed by the languor of the fluids, by the darkening of the animal spirits and the shadowy twi­light they spread over the images of things, by the viscosity of the blood that laboriously trickles through the vessels, by the thickening of vapors that have become blackish, deleterious, and acrid, by visceral functions that have be­come slow and somehow slimy-this unity, more a product of sensibility than of thought or theory, gives melancholia its characteristic stamp." -- Michel Foucault]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146496-what-does-reading-do-you-can-learn-almost-everything-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 16:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josiah add a quote by Jose Saramago]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146496-what-does-reading-do-you-can-learn-almost-everything-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does reading do, You can learn almost everything from reading, But I read too, So you must know something, Now I'm not so sure, You'll have to read differently then, How, The same method doesn't work for everyone, each person has to invent his or her own, whichever suits them best, some people spend their entire lives reading but never get beyond reading the words on the page, they don't understand that the words are merely stepping stones placed across a fast-flowing river, and the reason they're there is so that we can reach the farther shore, it's the other side that matters, Unless, Unless what, Unless those rivers don't have just two shores but many, unless each reader is his or her own shore, and that shore is the only shore worth reaching." -- Jose Saramago]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
