<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/886221-hyacinth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/886221-hyacinth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:40:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:40:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9752-i-have-lived-lies-i-have-done-it-again-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:40:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Anne Rice]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9752-i-have-lived-lies-i-have-done-it-again-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have lived lies. I have done it again and again. I live lies because I cannot endure the weakness of anger, and I cannot admit the irrationality of love.-Marius" -- Anne Rice]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5087-the-reality-of-the-other-person-lies-not-in-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:42:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5087-the-reality-of-the-other-person-lies-not-in-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Reality of The Other Person Lies Not In What He Reveals To You, But What He Cannot Reveal To You.
Therefore, If You Would Understand Him, Listen Not To What He Says, But Rather To What He Does Not Say." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:43:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The foundation of irreligious criticism is: Man makes religion, religion does not make man. Religion is, indeed, the self-consciousness and self-esteem of man who has either not yet won through to himself, or has already lost himself again. But man is no abstract being squatting outside the world. Man is the world of man – state, society. This state and this society produce religion, which is an inverted consciousness of the world, because they are an inverted world...

Religious suffering is, at one and the same time, the expression of real suffering and a protest against real suffering. Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people.

The abolition of religion as the illusory happiness of the people is the demand for their real happiness. To call on them to give up their illusions about their condition is to call on them to give up a condition that requires illusions. The criticism of religion is, therefore, in embryo, the criticism of that vale of tears of which religion is the halo.

Criticism has plucked the imaginary flowers on the chain not in order that man shall continue to bear that chain without fantasy or consolation, but so that he shall throw off the chain and pluck the living flower. The criticism of religion disillusions man, so that he will think, act, and fashion his reality like a man who has discarded his illusions and regained his senses, so that he will move around himself as his own true Sun. Religion is only the illusory Sun which revolves around man as long as he does not revolve around himself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17256-man-is-a-mystery-it-needs-to-be-unravelled-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:47:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17256-man-is-a-mystery-it-needs-to-be-unravelled-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is a mystery.  It needs to be unravelled, and if you spend your whole life unravelling it, don't say that you've wasted time.  I am studying that mystery because I want to be a human being." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32583-wisest-is-she-who-knows-she-does-not-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:50:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32583-wisest-is-she-who-knows-she-does-not-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wisest is she who knows she does not know." -- Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32586-you-can-never-know-if-a-person-forgives-you-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 17:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32586-you-can-never-know-if-a-person-forgives-you-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never know if a person forgives you when you wrong them. Therefore it is existentially important to you. It is a question you are intensely concerned with. Neither can you know whether a person loves you. It’s something you just have to believe or hope. But these things are more important to you than the fact that the sum of the angles in a triangle is 180 degrees. You don't think about the law of cause and effect or about modes of perception when you are in the middle of your first kiss." -- Jostein Gaarder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 17:31:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5647-and-when-you-want-something-all-the-universe-conspires-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And, when you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you to achieve it." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19219-one-is-loved-because-one-is-loved-no-reason-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 17:33:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Hyacinth add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19219-one-is-loved-because-one-is-loved-no-reason-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One is loved because one is loved. No reason is needed for loving." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
