<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/886847-jenna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/886847-jenna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 08:21:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301740-you-must-not-forget-that-a-monster-is-only-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 08:21:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301740-you-must-not-forget-that-a-monster-is-only-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must not forget that a monster is only a variation, and that to a monster the norm is monstrous." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301741-courage-and-fear-were-one-thing-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 08:22:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/301741-courage-and-fear-were-one-thing-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage and fear were one thing too." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160537-a-kind-of-light-spread-out-from-her-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 08:26:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160537-a-kind-of-light-spread-out-from-her-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A kind of light spread out from her. And everything changed color. And the world opened out. And a day was good to awaken to. And there were no limits to anything. And the people of the world were good and handsome. And I was not afraid any more." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 08:50:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155562-and-when-at-last-you-find-someone-to-whom-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155562-and-when-at-last-you-find-someone-to-whom-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when at last you find someone to whom you feel you can pour out your soul, you stop in shock at the words you utter— they are so rusty, so ugly, so meaningless and feeble from being kept in the small cramped dark inside you so long." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112807-if-the-moon-smiled-she-would-resemble-you-you-leave</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112807-if-the-moon-smiled-she-would-resemble-you-you-leave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the moon smiled, she would resemble you.
You leave the same impression 
Of something beautiful, but annihilating." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104319-we-were-together-i-forget-the-rest</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104319-we-were-together-i-forget-the-rest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We were together.  I forget the rest." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6430-failing-to-fetch-me-at-first-keep-encouraged-missing-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:52:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6430-failing-to-fetch-me-at-first-keep-encouraged-missing-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Failing to fetch me at first, keep encouraged. Missing me one place, search another. I stop somewhere waiting for you." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:06:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Saul Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74917-have-you-ever-lost-yourself-in-a-kiss-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever lost yourself in a kiss? I mean pure psychedelic inebriation. Not just lustful petting but transcendental metamorphosis when you became aware that the greatness of this being was breathing into you. Licking the sides and corners of your mouth, like sealing a thousand fleshy envelopes filled with the essence of your passionate being and then opened by the same mouth and delivered back to you, over and over again - the first kiss of the rest of your life. A kiss that confirms that the universe is aligned, that the world's greatest resource is love, and maybe even that God is a woman. With or without a belief in God, all kisses are metaphors decipherable by allocations of time, circumstance, and understanding" -- Saul Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35461-let-the-beauty-we-love-be-what-we-do-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:08:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35461-let-the-beauty-we-love-be-what-we-do-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let the beauty we love be what we do. There are hundreds of ways to kneel and kiss the ground." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138700-forget-safety-live-where-you-fear-to-live-destroy-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:08:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138700-forget-safety-live-where-you-fear-to-live-destroy-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forget safety.
Live where you fear to live.
Destroy your reputation.
Be notorious." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211289-i-want-to-see-you-know-your-voice-recognize-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:09:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211289-i-want-to-see-you-know-your-voice-recognize-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to see you.

Know your voice.

Recognize you when you
first come 'round the corner.

Sense your scent when I come 
into a room you've just left.

Know the lift of your heel,
the glide of your foot.

Become familiar with the way 
you purse your lips
then let them part, 
just the slightest bit,
when I lean in to your space
and kiss you.

I want to know the joy 
of how you whisper 
&quot;more" -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110122-be-empty-of-worrying-think-of-who-created-thought-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:12:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110122-be-empty-of-worrying-think-of-who-created-thought-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be empty of worrying.
Think of who created thought!

Why do you stay in prison
When the door is so wide open?" -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7587-to-love-life-to-love-it-even-when-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:24:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Ellen Bass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7587-to-love-life-to-love-it-even-when-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["to love life, to love it even
when you have no stomach for it
and everything you've held dear
crumbles like burnt paper in your hands,
your throat filled with the silt of it.
When grief sits with you, its tropical heat
thickening the air, heavy as water
more fit for gills than lungs;
when grief weights you like your own flesh
only more of it, an obesity of grief,
you think, How can a body withstand this?
Then you hold life like a face
between your palms, a plain face,
no charming smile, no violet eyes,
and you say, yes, I will take you
I will love you, again." -- Ellen Bass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34654-do-stuff-be-clenched-curious-not-waiting-for-inspiration-s-shove</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 12:58:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34654-do-stuff-be-clenched-curious-not-waiting-for-inspiration-s-shove]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do stuff. be clenched, curious. Not waiting for inspiration's shove or society's kiss on your forehead. Pay attention. It's all about paying attention. attention is vitality. It connects you with others. It makes you eager. stay eager." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:50:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 14:54:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15849-make-a-radical-change-in-your-lifestyle-and-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt. So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservation, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future. The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure. The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun. If you want to get more out of life, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy. But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252934-cherish-your-solitude-take-trains-by-yourself-to-places-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:09:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Eve Ensler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252934-cherish-your-solitude-take-trains-by-yourself-to-places-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cherish your solitude. Take trains by yourself to places you have never been. Sleep out alone under the stars. Learn how to drive a stick shift. Go so far away that you stop being afraid of not coming back. Say no when you don’t want to do something. Say yes if your instincts are strong, even if everyone around you disagrees. Decide whether you want to be liked or admired. Decide if fitting in is more important than finding out what you’re doing here. Believe in kissing." -- Eve Ensler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140781-and-you-should-not-let-yourself-be-confused-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 15:11:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140781-and-you-should-not-let-yourself-be-confused-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And you should not let yourself be confused in your solitude by the fact that there is something in you that wants to move out of it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304372-my-invitation-to-you-is-to-begin-living-every-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2011 10:04:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Robert White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/304372-my-invitation-to-you-is-to-begin-living-every-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My invitation to you is to begin living every moment as though you are miraculous and deserve to live an extraordinary life. Fake it if you must and keep faking it until it's real to you. The gift you will be giving yourself is a lifelong journey of discovery, one that is infinite and infinitely rewarding. Begin the journey. Today. This moment. Now." -- Robert White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58682-we-can-only-learn-to-love-by-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 11:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Iris Murdock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58682-we-can-only-learn-to-love-by-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can only learn to love by loving.

" -- Iris Murdock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318941-the-truth-is-unless-you-let-go-unless-you-forgive</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 11:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318941-the-truth-is-unless-you-let-go-unless-you-forgive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, unless you let go, unless you forgive yourself, unless you forgive the situation, unless you realize that the situation is over, you cannot move forward." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319248-incredible-change-happens-in-your-life-when-you-decide-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 11:06:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/319248-incredible-change-happens-in-your-life-when-you-decide-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Incredible change happens in your life when you decide to take control of what you do have power over instead of craving control over what you don't." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:44:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59631-i-want-to-do-with-you-what-spring-does-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59631-i-want-to-do-with-you-what-spring-does-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want
To do with you what spring does with the cherry trees." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16898-i-can-write-the-saddest-poem-of-all-tonight-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:50:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16898-i-can-write-the-saddest-poem-of-all-tonight-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can write the saddest poem of all tonight. I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78787-but-i-love-your-feet-only-because-they-walked-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:50:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78787-but-i-love-your-feet-only-because-they-walked-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I love your feet 
only because they walked 
upon the earth and upon 
the wind and upon the waters, 
until they found me." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126301-so-i-wait-for-you-like-a-lonely-house-till</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:52:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126301-so-i-wait-for-you-like-a-lonely-house-till]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["so I wait for you like a lonely house
till you will see me again and live in me.
Till then my windows ache." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8747-and-one-by-one-the-nights-between-our-separated-cities</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8747-and-one-by-one-the-nights-between-our-separated-cities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And one by one the nights between our separated cities are joined to the night that unites us." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205552-so-many-days-oh-so-many-days-seeing-you-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 11:05:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jenna add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205552-so-many-days-oh-so-many-days-seeing-you-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many days, oh so many days
seeing you so tangible and so close,
how do I pay, with what do I pay?

The bloodthirsty spring
has awakened in the woods.
The foxes start from their earths,
the serpents drink the dew,
and I go with you in the leaves
between the pines and the silence,
asking myself how and when
I will have to pay for my luck.

Of everything I have seen,
it's you I want to go on seeing:
of everything I've touched,
it's your flesh I want to go on touching.
I love your orange laughter.
I am moved by the sight of you sleeping.

What am I to do, love, loved one?
I don't know how others love
or how people loved in the past.
I live, watching you, loving you.
Being in love is my nature.

You please me more each afternoon.

Where is she? I keep on asking
if your eyes disappear.
How long she's taking! I think, and I'm hurt.
I feel poor, foolish and sad,
and you arrive and you are lightning
glancing off the peach trees.

That's why I love you and yet not why.
There are so many reasons, and yet so few,
for love has to be so,
involving and general,
particular and terrifying,
joyful and grieving,
flowering like the stars,
and measureless as a kiss.

That's why I love you and yet not why.
There are so many reasons, and yet so few,
for love has to be so,
involving and general,
particular and terrifying,
joyful and grieving,
flowering like the stars,
and measureless as a kiss." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
