<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/887012-dianna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/887012-dianna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 21:58:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18265-knowledge-is-of-two-kinds-we-know-a-subject-ourselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 21:58:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18265-knowledge-is-of-two-kinds-we-know-a-subject-ourselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowledge is of two kinds. We know a subject ourselves, or we know where we can find information on it." -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25455-tonight-no-one-will-rage-and-cry-my-kingdom-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 21:59:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Michel Tremblay]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25455-tonight-no-one-will-rage-and-cry-my-kingdom-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tonight, no one will rage and cry: &quot;My Kingdom for a horse!&quot; No ghost will come to haunt the battlements of a castle in the kingdom of Denmark where, apparently something is rotten. Nor will anyone wring her hands and murmur: &quot;Leave, I do not despise you.&quot; Three still young women will not retreat to a dacha whispering the name of Moscow, their beloved, their lost hope. No sister will await the return of her brother to avenge the death of their father, no son will be forced to avenge an affront to his father, no mother will kill her three children to take revenge on their father. And no husband will see his doll-like wife leave him out of contempt. No one will turn into a rhinoceros. Maids will not plot to assassinate their mistress, after denouncing her lover and having him jailed. No one will fret about &quot;the rain in Spain!&quot; No one will emerge from a garbage pail to tell an absurd story. Italian families will not leave for the seashore. No soldier will return from World War II and bang on his father's bedroom dor protesting the presence of a new wife in his mother's bed. No evanescent blode will drown. No Spanish nobleman will seduce a thousand and three women, nor will an entire family of Spanish women writhe beneath the heel of the fierce Bernarda Alba. You won't see a brute of a man rip his sweat-drenched T-shirt, shouting: &quot;Stella! Stella!&quot; and his sister-in-law will not be doomed the minute she steps off the streetcar named Desire. Nor will you see a stepmother pine away for her new husband's youngest son. The plague will not descend upon the city of Thebes, and the Trojan War will not take place. No king will be betrayed by his ungrateful daughters. There will be no duels, no poisonings, no wracking coughs. No one will die, or, if someone must die, it will become a comic scene. No, there will be none of the usual theatrics. What you will see tonight is a very simple woman, a woman who will simply talk..." -- Michel Tremblay]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25456-one-does-not-argue-about-the-wind-in-the-willows</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25456-one-does-not-argue-about-the-wind-in-the-willows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One does not argue about The Wind in the Willows. The young man gives it to the girl with whom he is in love, and, if she does not like it, asks her to return his letters. The older man tries it on his nephew, and alters his will accordingly. The book is a test of character. We can't criticize it, because it is criticizing us. But I must give you one word of warning. When you sit down to it, don't be so ridiculous as to suppose that you are sitting in judgment on my taste, or on the art of Kenneth Grahame. You are merely sitting in judgment on yourself. You may be worthy: I don't know, But it is you who are on trial." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25457-nothing-is-random-nor-will-anything-ever-be-whether-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:02:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25457-nothing-is-random-nor-will-anything-ever-be-whether-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is random, nor will anything ever be, whether a long string of perfectly blue days that begin and end in golden dimness, the most seemingly chaotic political acts, the rise of a great city, the crystalline structure of a gem that has never seen the light, the distributions of fortune, what time the milkman gets up, the position of the electron, or the occurrence of one astonishing frigid winter after another. Even electrons, supposedly the paragons of unpredictability, are tame and obsequious little creatures that rush around at the speed of light, going precisely where they are supposed to go. They make faint whistling sounds that when apprehended in varying combinations are as pleasant as the wind flying through a forest, and they do exactly as they are told. Of this, one is certain.

And yet, there is a wonderful anarchy, in that the milkman chooses when to arise, the rat picks the tunnel into which he will dive when the subway comes rushing down the track from Borough Hall, and the snowflake will fall as it will. How can this be? If nothing is random, and everything is predetermined, how can there be free will? The answer to that is simple. Nothing is predetermined, it is determined, or was determined, or will be determined. No matter, it all happened at once, in less than an instant, and time was invented because we cannot comprehend in one glance the enormous and detailed canvas that we have been given - so we track it, in linear fashion piece by piece. Time however can be easily overcome; not by chasing the light, but by standing back far enough to see it all at once. The universe is still and complete. Everything that ever was is; everything that ever will be is - and so on, in all possible combinations. Though in perceiving it we image that it is in motion, and unfinished, it is quite finished and quite astonishingly beautiful. In the end, or rather, as things really are, any event, no matter how small, is intimately and sensibly tied to all others. All rivers run full to the sea; those who are apart are brought together; the lost ones are redeemed; the dead come back to life; the perfectly blue days that have begun and ended in golden dimness continue, immobile and accessible; and, when all is perceived in such a way as to obviate time, justice becomes apparent not as something that will be, but something that is." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25460-when-the-two-people-who-thus-discover-that-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:08:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25460-when-the-two-people-who-thus-discover-that-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the two people who thus discover that they are on the same secret road are of different sexes, the friendship which arises between them will very easily pass – may pass in the first half hour – into erotic love. Indeed, unless they are physically repulsive to each other or unless one or both already loves elsewhere, it is almost certain to do so sooner or later. And conversely, erotic love may lead to Friendship between the lovers. But this, so far from obliterating the distinction between the two loves, puts it in a clearer light. If one who was first, in the deep and full sense, your Friend, is then gradually or suddenly revealed as also your lover you will certainly not want to share the Beloved’s erotic love with any third. But you will have no jealousy at all about sharing the Friendship. Nothing so enriches an erotic love as the discovery that the Beloved can deeply, truly and spontaneously enter into Friendship with the Friends you already had; to feel that not only are we two united by erotic love but we three or four or five are all travelers on the same quest, have all a common vision." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770-the-love-of-learning-the-sequestered-nooks-and-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:09:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770-the-love-of-learning-the-sequestered-nooks-and-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The love of learning, the sequestered nooks,
And all the sweet serenity of books" -- Henry Wadsworth Longfellow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25462-that-perfect-tranquility-of-life-which-is-nowhere-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:11:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Aphra Behn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25462-that-perfect-tranquility-of-life-which-is-nowhere-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That perfect tranquility of life, which is nowhere to be found but in retreat, a faithful friend and a good library." -- Aphra Behn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25465-sea-fever-i-must-down-to-the-seas-again-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:15:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by John Masefield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25465-sea-fever-i-must-down-to-the-seas-again-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Sea-fever&lt;/b&gt;

I must down to the seas again, to the lonely sea and the sky,
And all I ask is a tall ship and a star to steer her by,
And the wheel's kick and the wind's song and the white sail's shaking,
And a grey mist on the sea's face, and a grey dawn breaking.

I must down to the seas again, for the call of the running tide
Is a wild call and a clear call that may not be denied;
And all I ask is a windy day with the white clouds flying,
And the flung spray and the blown spume, and the sea-gulls crying.

I must down to the seas again, to the vagrant gypsy life,
To the gull's way and the whale's way where the wind's like a whetted knife;
And all I ask is a merry yarn from a laughing fellow-rover
And quiet sleep and a sweet dream when the long trick's over" -- John Masefield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:19:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25469-stephen-had-been-put-to-sleep-in-his-usual-room]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stephen had been put to sleep in his usual room, far from children and noise, away in that corner of the house which looked down to the orchard and the bowling-green, and in spite of his long absence it was so familiar to him that when he woke at about three he made his way to the window almost as quickly as if dawn had already broken, opened it and walked out onto the balcony. The moon had set: there was barely a star to be seen. The still air was delightfully fresh with falling dew, and a late nightingale, in an indifferent voice, was uttering a routine jug-jug far down in Jack's plantations; closer at hand and more agreeable by far, nightjars churred in the orchard, two of them, or perhaps three, the sound rising and falling, intertwining so that the source could not be made out for sure. There were few birds that he preferred to nightjars, but it was not they that had brought him out of bed: he stood leaning on the balcony rail and presently Jack Aubrey, in a summer-house by the bowling-green, began again, playing very gently in the darkness, improvising wholly for himself, dreaming away on his violin with a mastery that Stephen had never heard equalled, though they had played together for years and years.

Like many other sailors Jack Aubrey had long dreamed of lying in his warm bed all night long; yet although he could now do so with a clear conscience he often rose at unChristian hours, particularly if he were moved by strong emotion, and crept from his bedroom in a watch-coat, to walk about the house or into the stables or to pace the bowling-green. Sometimes he took his fiddle with him. He was in fact a better player than Stephen, and now that he was using his precious Guarnieri rather than a robust sea-going fiddle the difference was still more evident: but the Guarnieri did not account for the whole of it, nor anything like. Jack certainly concealed his excellence when they were playing together, keeping to Stephen's mediocre level: this had become perfectly clear when Stephen's hands were at last recovered from the thumb-screws and other implements applied by French counter-intelligence officers in Minorca; but on reflexion Stephen thought it had been the case much earlier, since quite apart from his delicacy at that period, Jack hated showing away.

Now, in the warm night, there was no one to be comforted, kept in countenance, no one could scorn him for virtuosity, and he could let himself go entirely; and as the grave and subtle music wound on and on, Stephen once more contemplated on the apparent contradiction between the big, cheerful, florid sea-officer whom most people liked on sight but who would have never been described as subtle or capable of subtlety by any one of them (except perhaps his surviving opponents in battle) and the intricate, reflective music he was now creating. So utterly unlike his limited vocabulary in words, at times verging upon the inarticulate.

'My hands have now regained the moderate ability they possessed before I was captured,' observed Maturin, 'but his have gone on to a point I never thought he could reach: his hands and his mind. I am amazed. In his own way he is the secret man of the world." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25471-but-the-tale-or-narrative-set-in-the-past-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:20:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25471-but-the-tale-or-narrative-set-in-the-past-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the tale or narrative set in the past may have its particular time-free value; and the candid reader will not misunderstand me, will not suppose that I intend any preposterous comparison, when I observe that Homer was farther removed in time from Troy than I am from the Napoleonic wars; yet he spoke to the Greeks for 2,000 years and more." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32332-we-only-confess-our-little-faults-to-persuade-people-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:20:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Francois Duc de La Rochefoucauld ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32332-we-only-confess-our-little-faults-to-persuade-people-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We only confess our little faults to persuade people that we have no big ones." -- Francois Duc de La Rochefoucauld ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10979-we-can-experience-nothing-but-the-present-moment-live-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 22:34:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10979-we-can-experience-nothing-but-the-present-moment-live-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can experience nothing but the present moment, live in no other second of time, and to understand this is as close as we can get to eternal life." -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 19:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never get a cup of tea large enough or a book long enough to suit me." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27528-alan-cried-i-what-makes-ye-so-good-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 16:20:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27528-alan-cried-i-what-makes-ye-so-good-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alan,&quot; cried I, &quot;what makes ye so good to me? What makes ye care for such a thankless fellow?&quot;

Deed, and I don't, know&quot; said Alan. &quot;For just precisely what I thought I liked about ye, was that ye never quarrelled:—and now I like ye better!" -- Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29354-books-are-like-lobster-shells-we-surround-ourselves-with-em</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 17:10:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29354-books-are-like-lobster-shells-we-surround-ourselves-with-em]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books... are like lobster shells, we surround ourselves with 'em, then we grow out of 'em and leave 'em behind, as evidence of our earlier stages of development." -- Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21928-books-are-good-enough-in-their-own-way-but-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 17:12:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21928-books-are-good-enough-in-their-own-way-but-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are good enough in their own way but they are a mighty bloodless substitute for life." -- Robert Louis Stevenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25122-you-come-of-the-lord-adam-and-the-lady-eve</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 07:36:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25122-you-come-of-the-lord-adam-and-the-lady-eve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You come of the Lord Adam and the Lady Eve,&quot; said Aslan. &quot;And that is both honour enough to erect the head of the poorest beggar, and shame enough to bow the shoulders of the greatest emperor on earth.  Be content." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43659-man-is-diminished-if-he-lives-without-knowledge-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 08:40:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43659-man-is-diminished-if-he-lives-without-knowledge-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is diminished if he lives without knowledge of his past; without hope of a future he becomes a beast." -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 10:19:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dianna add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The weather had freshened almost to coldness, for the wind was coming more easterly, from the chilly currents between Tristan and the Cape; the sloth was amazed by the change; it shunned the deck and spent its time below. Jack was in his cabin, pricking the chart with less satisfaction than he could have wished: progress, slow, serious trouble with the mainmast-- unaccountable headwinds by night-- and sipping a glass of grog; Stephen was in the mizentop, teaching Bonden to write and scanning the sea for his first albatross. The sloth sneezed, and looking up, Jack caught its gaze fixed upon him; its inverted face had an expression of anxiety and concern. 'Try a piece of this, old cock,' he said, dipping his cake in the grog and proffering the sop. 'It might put a little heart into you.' The sloth sighed, closed its eyes, but gently absorbed the piece, and sighed again.

    Some minutes later he felt a touch upon his knee: the sloth had silently climbed down and it was standing there, its beady eyes looking up into his face, bright with expectation. More cake, more grog: growing confidence and esteem. After this, as soon as the drum had beat the retreat, the sloth would meet him, hurrying toward the door on its uneven legs: it was given its own bowl, and it would grip it with its claws, lowering its round face into it and pursing its lips to drink (its tongue was too short to lap). Sometimes it went to sleep in this position, bowed over the emptiness.

    'In this bucket,' said Stephen, walking into the cabin, 'in this small half-bucket, now, I have the population of Dublin, London, and Paris combined: these animalculae-- what is the matter with the sloth?' It was curled on Jack's knee, breathing heavily: its bowl and Jack's glass stood empty on the table. Stephen picked it up, peered into its affable bleary face, shook it, and hung it upon its rope. It seized hold with one fore and one hind foot, letting the others dangle limp, and went to sleep.

    Stephen looked sharply round, saw the decanter, smelt to the sloth, and cried, 'Jack, you have debauched my sloth." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
