<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/887926-brittany-kubes]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/887926-brittany-kubes" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 13:53:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37020-yet-once-you-ve-come-to-be-part-of-this-particular</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 13:53:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Nelson Algren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37020-yet-once-you-ve-come-to-be-part-of-this-particular]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet once you've come to be part of this particular patch, you'll never love another. Like loving a woman with a broken nose, you may well find lovelier lovelies. But never a lovely so real." -- Nelson Algren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465905-some-junk-novels-were-all-about-airports-some-junk-novels</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2011 14:52:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/465905-some-junk-novels-were-all-about-airports-some-junk-novels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some junk novels were all about airports.  Some junk novels were even called things like Airport.  Why, then you might ask, was there no airport called Junk Novel? …Junk novels have been around for at least as long as non-junk novels, and airports haven’t been around for very long at all.  But they both really took off at the same time.  Readers of junk novels and people in airports wanted the same thing: escape, and quick transfer from one junk novel to another junk novel and from one airport to another airport." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553537-insensibly-he-formed-the-most-delightful-habit-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2012 21:16:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/553537-insensibly-he-formed-the-most-delightful-habit-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Insensibly he formed the most delightful habit in the world, the habit of reading: he did not know that thus he was providing himself with a refuge from all the distress of life; he did not know either that he was creating for himself an unreal world which would make the real world of every day a source of bitter disappointment….He began to read at haphazard.  He entered upon each system with a little thrill of excitement, expecting to find in each some guide by which he could rule his conduct; he felt himself like a traveler in unknown countries and as he pushed forward the enterprise fascinated him; he read emotionally, as other men read pure literature, and his heart leaped as he discovered in noble words what himself had obscurely felt." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674727-so-i-am-nineteen-years-old-and-don-t-usually-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 18:37:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674727-so-i-am-nineteen-years-old-and-don-t-usually-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So I am nineteen years old and don’t usually know what I’m doing, snap my thoughts out of the printed page, get my looks from other eyes, do not overtake dotards and cripples in the street for fear I will depress them with my agility, love watching children and animals at play but wouldn’t mind seeing a beggar kicked or a little girl run over because it’s all experience, dislike myself and sneer at a world less nice and less intelligent than me. I take it this is fairly routine?" -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878055-i-have-ate-out-of-your-garbage-cans-to-stay</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2013 19:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Charles Manson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/878055-i-have-ate-out-of-your-garbage-cans-to-stay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have ate out of your garbage cans to stay out of jail. I have wore your second-hand clothes…I have done my best to get along in your world and now you want to kill me, and I look at you, and then I say to myself, You want to kill me? Ha! I’m already dead, have been all my life. I’ve spent twenty-three years in tombs that you built." -- Charles Manson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
