<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888043-sami-carroll]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888043-sami-carroll" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:12:58 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31737-i-ve-always-been-a-quitter-i-quit-the-boy-scouts</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:12:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sami add a quote by T.C. Boyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31737-i-ve-always-been-a-quitter-i-quit-the-boy-scouts]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always been a quitter. I quit the Boy Scouts, the glee club, the marching band. Gave up my paper route, turned my back on the church, stuffed the basketball team. I dropped out of college, sidestepped the army with a 4-F on the grounds of mental instability, went back to school, made a go of it, entered a Ph.D. program in nineteenth-century British literature, sat in the front row, took notes assiduously, bought a pair of horn-rims, and quit on the eve of my comprehensive exams. I got married, separated, divorced. Quit smoking, quit jogging, quit eating red meat. I quit jobs: digging graves, pumping gas, selling insurance, showing pornographic films in an art theater in Boston. When I was nineteen I made frantic love to a pinch-faced, sack-bosomed girl I'd known from high school. She got pregnant. I quit town." -- T.C. Boyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31736-writing-is-a-habit-an-addiction-as-powerful-and-overmastering</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:13:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sami add a quote by T.C. Boyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31736-writing-is-a-habit-an-addiction-as-powerful-and-overmastering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing is a habit, an addiction, as powerful and overmastering an urge as putting a bottle to your lips or a spike in your arm. Call it the impulse to make something out of nothing, call it an obsessive-compulsive disorder, call it logorrhea. Have you been in a bookstore lately? Have you seen what these authors are doing, the mountainous piles of the flakes of themselves they're leaving behind, like the neatly labeled jars of shit, piss, and toenail clippings one of John Barth's characters bequeathed to his wife, the ultimate expression of his deepest self?" -- T.C. Boyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90165-but-then-that-s-the-beauty-of-writing-stories-each-one-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2012 21:13:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sami add a quote by T.C. Boyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90165-but-then-that-s-the-beauty-of-writing-stories-each-one-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But then, that’s the beauty of writing stories—each one is an exploratory journey in search of a reason and a shape.  And when you find that reason and that shape, there’s no feeling like it.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Peter Wild Interviews TC Boyle&lt;/i&gt;, 3:AM Magazine, June 2003]" -- T.C. Boyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
