<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888230-christine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888230-christine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 11:56:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3506-there-are-few-people-whom-i-really-love-and-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 11:56:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3506-there-are-few-people-whom-i-really-love-and-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are few people whom I really love, and still fewer of whom I think well. The more I see of the world, the more am I dissatisfied with it; and every day confirms my belief of the inconsistency of all human characters, and of the little dependence that can be placed on the appearance of merit or sense." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11566-you-must-learn-some-of-my-philosophy-think-only-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 11:56:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11566-you-must-learn-some-of-my-philosophy-think-only-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must learn some of my philosophy. Think only of the past as its remembrance gives you pleasure." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305160-there-is-always-something-ridiculous-about-the-emotions-of-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 06:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305160-there-is-always-something-ridiculous-about-the-emotions-of-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always something ridiculous about the emotions of people whom one has ceased to love." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147732-there-are-few-of-us-who-have-not-sometimes-wakened</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 09:25:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147732-there-are-few-of-us-who-have-not-sometimes-wakened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are few of us who have not sometimes wakened before dawn, either after one of those dreamless nights that make us almost enamoured of death, or one of those nights of horror and misshapen joy, when through the chambers of the brain sweep phantoms more terrible than reality itself, and instinct with that vivid life that lurks in all grotesques, and that lends to Gothic art its enduring vitality, this art being, one might fancy, especially the art of those whose minds have been troubled with the malady of reverie. Gradually white fingers creep through the curtains, and they appear to tremble. In black fantastic shapes, dumb shadows crawl into the corners of the room and crouch there. Outside, there is the stirring of birds among the leaves, or the sound of men going forth to their work, or the sigh and sob of the wind coming down from the hills and wandering round the silent house, as though it feared to wake the sleepers and yet must needs call forth sleep from her purple cave. Veil after veil of thin dusky gauze is lifted, and by degrees the forms and colours of things are restored to them, and we watch the dawn remaking the world in its antique pattern. The wan mirrors get back their mimic life. The flameless tapers stand where we had left them, and beside them lies the half-cut book that we had been studying, or the wired flower that we had worn at the ball, or the letter that we had been afraid to read, or that we had read too often. Nothing seems to us changed. Out of the unreal shadows of the night comes back the real life that we had known. We have to resume it where we had left off, and there steals over us a terrible sense of the necessity for the continuance of energy in the same wearisome round of stereotyped habits, or a wild longing, it may be, that our eyelids might open some morning upon a world that had been refashioned anew in the darkness for our pleasure, a world in which things would have fresh shapes and colours, and be changed, or have other secrets, a world in which the past would have little or no place, or survive, at any rate, in no conscious form of obligation or regret, the remembrance even of joy having its bitterness and the memories of pleasure their pain." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156704-she-was-becoming-herself-and-daily-casting-aside-that-fictitious</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 07:35:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kate Chopin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156704-she-was-becoming-herself-and-daily-casting-aside-that-fictitious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was becoming herself and daily casting aside that fictitious self which we assume like a garment with which to appear before the world." -- Kate Chopin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/483785-even-as-a-child-she-had-lived-her-own-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2013 07:36:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kate Chopin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/483785-even-as-a-child-she-had-lived-her-own-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even as a child she had lived her own small life within herself. At a very early period she had apprehended instinctively the dual life - that outward existence which conforms, the inward life which questions." -- Kate Chopin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276690-i-m-trying-to-feel-sorry-for-you-really-i-am-north</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 16:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276690-i-m-trying-to-feel-sorry-for-you-really-i-am-north]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm trying to feel sorry for you, really I am,&quot;North said.&quot;If you wait just a moment I'm sure the tears will come." -- Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692440-let-s-carpe-the-hell-out-of-this-diem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 16:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/692440-let-s-carpe-the-hell-out-of-this-diem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's carpe the hell out of this diem." -- Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/727172-he-s-so-busy-looking-inside-people-to-find-the-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 16:20:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/727172-he-s-so-busy-looking-inside-people-to-find-the-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's so busy looking inside people to find the good that he misses the knife they're holding in their hand." -- Alexandra Bracken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499239-will-nodded-toward-hadrian-look-at-the-swords-he-s-carrying</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 15:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Michael J.  Sullivan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/499239-will-nodded-toward-hadrian-look-at-the-swords-he-s-carrying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Will nodded toward Hadrian. “Look at the swords he’s carrying. A man wearing one—maybe he knows how to use it, maybe not. A man carries two—he probably don’t know nothing about swords, but he wants you to think he does. But a man carrying three swords—that’s a lot of weight. No one’s gonna haul that much steel around unless he makes a living using them." -- Michael J.  Sullivan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530605-royce-turned-to-hadrian-it-s-supposed-to-make-them-look</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 15:53:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Michael J.  Sullivan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/530605-royce-turned-to-hadrian-it-s-supposed-to-make-them-look]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Royce turned to Hadrian. “It’s supposed to make them look tough, but all it really does is make it easy to identify them as thieves for the rest of their lives. Painting a red hand on everyone is pretty stupid when you think about it.”
“That tattoo is supposed to be a hand?” Hadrian asked. “I thought it was a little red chicken. But now that you mention it, a hand does make more sense.”
Royce looked back at Will and tilted his head to one side. “Does kinda look like a chicken." -- Michael J.  Sullivan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216060-do-you-think-me-horselike-my-lord-realizing-the-threat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 11:13:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Sarah MacLean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216060-do-you-think-me-horselike-my-lord-realizing-the-threat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think me horselike, my lord?&quot;
Realizing the threat to his personage, Blackmoor wiped the smile from his face and replied, &quot;Not at all.  I said I think you charming.&quot;
&quot;A fine start.&quot;
&quot;And I appreciate your exuberance.&quot;  His eyes glitered with barely contained laughter.
&quot;Like that of a child.&quot;  Hers sparkled with irritation.
&quot;And, of course, you are entertaining.&quot;
&quot;Excellent.  Like the aforementioned child's toy.&quot;
He couldn't hide a chuckle.  &quot;Not at all.  You are a far better companion than any of the toys I had as a child.&quot;
&quot;Oh, I am most flattered.&quot;
&quot;You should be.  I had some tremendous toys." -- Sarah MacLean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/596641-she-looked-up-at-him-and-said-what-did-you-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 11:14:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Sarah MacLean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/596641-she-looked-up-at-him-and-said-what-did-you-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She looked up at him and said,&quot;What did you say?&quot;
&quot;You have beautiful eyes.&quot;
&quot;You told my father that he has beautiful eyes?&quot;
He smiled. &quot;No. You distracted me. I told your father that, while I was very grateful for the lesson, I doubt I would ever need of it again- because I was planning to court only one woman in my lifetime." -- Sarah MacLean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705102-enlighten-me-lord-blackmoor-how-should-i-be-wooed-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 11:16:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Sarah MacLean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705102-enlighten-me-lord-blackmoor-how-should-i-be-wooed-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Enlighten me, Lord Blackmoor, how should I be wooed, as you put it? I am intrigued by your obvious expertise.&quot;
He was quick to respond, &quot;You're too vibrant for them. Too strong. You have a sharp mind and an exciting personality and an unexpected sense of humor. If these men were half the man you deserve, they would have already recognized all those things and they would be romancing you accordingly.  They would be working to intrigue and amuse and inspire you -- just as you do them. And they would know that only when they have won your mind will they even have a chance at winning your heart.&quot;
The room felt much warmer all of a sudden, and Alex resisted the urge to fan herself, trying to ignore the rapid increase in her pulse as color flooded her cheeks. In the silence that followed his impassioned speech, Gavin stood and walked over to her. A cocky grin spread across his face. &quot;That's how I write to the women I hope to interest, Alex." -- Sarah MacLean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533157-momentarily-forgetting-how-wind-works-lex-tried-spitting-at-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 12:10:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Gina Damico]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533157-momentarily-forgetting-how-wind-works-lex-tried-spitting-at-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Momentarily forgetting how wind works, Lex tried spitting at him. This failed" -- Gina Damico]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470210-thanks-i-muttered-and-added-under-my-breath-douchebag-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 13:45:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jennifer L. Armentrout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/470210-thanks-i-muttered-and-added-under-my-breath-douchebag-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks,” I muttered and added under my breath, “Douchebag.”

He laughed, deep and throaty. “Now that’s not very ladylike, Kittycat.”

I whipped around. “Don’t ever call me that,” I snapped.

“It’s better than calling someone a douchebag, isn’t it?” He pushed out the door. “This has been a stimulating visit. I’ll cherish it for a long time to come.”

Okay. That was it. “You know, you’re right. How wrong of me to call you a douchebag. Because a douchebag is too nice of a word for you,” I said, smiling sweetly. “You’re a dickhead.”

“A dickhead?” he repeated. “How charming.”

I flipped him off." -- Jennifer L. Armentrout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524326-oh-no-i-know-that-look-what-are-you-thinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 13:53:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Jennifer L. Armentrout]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524326-oh-no-i-know-that-look-what-are-you-thinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh no I know that look. What are you thinking?
That this is the most ridiculous declaration of attraction I've ever heard" -- Jennifer L. Armentrout]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625615-i-ll-go-talk-to-them-annwyl-said-but-she-cracked</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 14:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by G.A. Aiken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625615-i-ll-go-talk-to-them-annwyl-said-but-she-cracked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ll go talk to them,” Annwyl said. But she cracked her knuckles. “Right now.”
Izzy cut in front of Annwyl, forced a smile. “Why don’t I talk to them? Daddy listens to me.”
“You want my sword?”
Izzy blinked. Hard. “No. I don’t think that’s necessary. To talk to my father and uncles that I adore.”
“You want me warhammer then?" -- G.A. Aiken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268921-i-already-explained-this-i-don-t-like-you-true-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 14:05:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by G.A. Aiken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268921-i-already-explained-this-i-don-t-like-you-true-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I already explained this. I don’t like you. True, I don’t like most people, but I especially dislike you. I could start my own religion based on how much I dislike you." -- G.A. Aiken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715091-but-there-simply-was-no-grey-area-for-him-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 14:10:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by G.A. Aiken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/715091-but-there-simply-was-no-grey-area-for-him-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there simply was no grey area for him. There was only black, white, and annoying." -- G.A. Aiken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253237-rules-exist-for-a-reason-rules-exist-because-when-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 14:23:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Ally Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253237-rules-exist-for-a-reason-rules-exist-because-when-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["rules exist for a reason. Rules exist because when people don't follow them, people get hurt." -- Ally Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520542-zach-i-said-as-i-lay-there-where-did-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 14:32:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Ally Carter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520542-zach-i-said-as-i-lay-there-where-did-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Zach,” I said as I lay there “Where did you go? When you were looking for me?”
I shifted in his arms, looked into his eyes.
“Crazy.” His voice was a whisper against my skin. “I went crazy." -- Ally Carter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734850-you-always-wear-that-necklace-he-said-is-it-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2014 09:41:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Sarah J. Maas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/734850-you-always-wear-that-necklace-he-said-is-it-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You always wear that necklace,&quot; he said. &quot;Is it another gift?&quot; Though she wore gloves, he glanced at her hand - where the amethyst ring always sat - and the spark died from his eyes.
&quot;No.&quot; She covered the amulet with her hand. &quot;I found it in my jewellery box and liked the look of it, you insufferably territorial man." -- Sarah J. Maas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402583-she-found-him-standing-before-the-water-staring-unseeing-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 07:56:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kristine Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/402583-she-found-him-standing-before-the-water-staring-unseeing-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She found him standing before the water staring unseeing at its frozen surface. He was shivering. She watched him doubtfully for a moment.
“Po,” she said to his back, “where’s your coat?”
“Where’s yours?”
She moved to stand beside him. “I’m warm.”
He tilted his head to her. “If you’re warm and I’m coatless, there’s only one friendly thing for you to do.”
“Go back and get your coat for you?”
He smiled. Reaching out to her, he pulled her close against him. Katsa wrapped her arms around him, surprised, and tried to rub some warmth into his shivering shoulders and back.
“That’s it exactly,” Po said. “You must keep me warm.”
She laughed and held him tighter." -- Kristine Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297113-she-looked-at-him-then-but-his-image-blurred-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 07:58:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297113-she-looked-at-him-then-but-his-image-blurred-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She looked at him then, but his image blurred behind tears that swelled into her eyes. She must leave. She must leave this room, because she wanted to hit him, as she had sworn she never would do. She wanted to cause him pain for taking a place in her heart that she wouldn't have given him if she'd known the truth. 
&quot;You lied to me,&quot; she said.
She turned and ran from the room." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442468-i-truly-thought-i-might-hurt-that-man-he-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:00:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442468-i-truly-thought-i-might-hurt-that-man-he-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I truly thought I might hurt that man,&quot; he said, &quot;very badly.&quot;
&quot;I didn't know you were capable of such bad temper.&quot;
&quot;Apparently I am." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240678-sit-your-high-majestic-lord-princes-she-said-she-yanked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240678-sit-your-high-majestic-lord-princes-she-said-she-yanked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sit, Your High Majestic Lord Princes,&quot; she said. She yanked a chair from the table and sat herself down.
&quot;You're in fine temper,&quot; Raffin said.
&quot;Your hair is blue,&quot; Katsa snapped back." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297273-i-know-you-don-t-want-this-katsa-but-i-can-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:01:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Kristin Cashore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297273-i-know-you-don-t-want-this-katsa-but-i-can-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know you don't want this, Katsa. But I can't help myself. The moment you came barreling into my life I was lost. I'm afraid to tell you what I wish for, for fear you'll... oh, I don't know, throw me into the fire. Or more likely, refuse me. Or worst of all, despise me,&quot; he said, his voice breaking and his eyes dropping from her face. His face dropping into his hands. &quot;I love you,&quot; he said. &quot;You're more dear to my heart than I ever knew anyone could be. And I've made you cry; and there I'll stop." -- Kristin Cashore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579081-i-forget-my-own-name-when-he-smiles-like-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 08:58:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Julie Reece]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579081-i-forget-my-own-name-when-he-smiles-like-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I forget my own name when he smiles like that." -- Julie Reece]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449135-how-much-does-your-life-have-to-suck-to-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2014 13:47:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christine add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449135-how-much-does-your-life-have-to-suck-to-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How much does your life have to suck to want the Apocalypse?" -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
