<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888599-jason]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888599-jason" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:32:03 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485145-the-termites-of-reduction-have-always-gnawed-away-at-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:32:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485145-the-termites-of-reduction-have-always-gnawed-away-at-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The termites of reduction have always gnawed away at life: even the greatest love ends up as a skeleton of feeble memories." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98537-memory-is-the-sense-of-loss-and-loss-pulls-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 08:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98537-memory-is-the-sense-of-loss-and-loss-pulls-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory is the sense of loss, and loss pulls us after it." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44630-when-the-heart-speaks-the-mind-finds-it-indecent-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 23:47:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44630-when-the-heart-speaks-the-mind-finds-it-indecent-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the heart speaks, the mind finds it indecent to object." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74432-no-real-social-change-has-ever-been-brought-about-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 23:50:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74432-no-real-social-change-has-ever-been-brought-about-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No real social change has ever been 
brought about without a revolution - 
Revolution is but thought carried into action.
Every effort for progress, for enlightenment, 
for science, for religious, political, and 
economic liberty, emanates from the minority, 
and not from the mass." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 19:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9402-if-you-want-a-picture-of-the-future-imagine-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want a picture of the future, imagine a boot stamping on a human face—for ever." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478479-nothing-has-a-more-sinister-effect-on-art-than-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 10:41:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478479-nothing-has-a-more-sinister-effect-on-art-than-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing has a more sinister effect on art than the artist's desire to prove that he's good. The terrible temptation of idealism! You must achieve mastery over your idealism, over your virtue as well as over your vice, aesthetic mastery over everything that drives you to write in the first place - your outrage, your politics, your grief, your love!" -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379048-words-the-acid-bath-of-words</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 13:32:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379048-words-the-acid-bath-of-words]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words, the acid-bath of words." -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488636-freedom-without-socialism-is-privilege-and-injustice-socialism-without-freedom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 21:04:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Bakunin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488636-freedom-without-socialism-is-privilege-and-injustice-socialism-without-freedom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom without socialism is privilege and injustice; socialism without freedom is slavery and brutality" -- Bakunin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257687-for-me-the-last-few-years-of-the-postmodern-era</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 11:34:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257687-for-me-the-last-few-years-of-the-postmodern-era]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, the last few years of the postmodern era have seemed a bit like the way you feel when you're in high school and your parents go on a trip, and you throw a party. You get all your friends over and throw this wild disgusting fabulous party. For a while it's great, free and freeing, parental authority gone and overthrown, a cat's-away-let's-play Dionysian revel. But then time passes and the party gets louder and louder, and you run out of drugs, and nobody's got any money for more drugs, and things get broken and spilled, and there's cigarette burn on the couch, and you're the host and it's your house too, and you gradually start wishing your parents would come back and restore some fucking order in your house. It's not a perfect analogy, but the sense I get of my generation of writers and intellectuals or whatever is that it's 3:00 A.M. and the couch has several burn-holes and somebody's thrown up in the umbrella stand and we're wishing the revel would end. The postmodern founders' patricidal work was great, but patricide produces orphans, and no amount of revelry can make up for the fact that writers my age have been literary orphans throughout our formative years. We're kind of wishing some parents would come back. And of course we're uneasy about the fact that we wish they'd come back--I mean, what's wrong with us? Are we total pussies? Is there something about authority and limits we actually need? And then the uneasiest feeling of all, as we start gradually to realize that parents in fact aren't ever coming back--which means we're going to have to be the parents." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79715-in-writing-you-must-kill-all-your-darlings</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2013 19:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79715-in-writing-you-must-kill-all-your-darlings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In writing, you must kill all your darlings." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9218-you-get-born-and-you-try-this-and-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 16:33:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by William C. Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9218-you-get-born-and-you-try-this-and-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get born and you try this and you don't know why only you keep on trying it and you are born at the same time with a lot of other people, all mixed up with them, like trying to, having to, move your arms and legs with strings only the same strings are hitched to all the other arms and legs and the others all trying and they don't know why either except that the strings are all in one another's way like five or six people all trying to make a rug on the same loom only each one wants to weave his own pattern into the rug; and it can't matter, you know that, or the Ones that set up the loom would have arranged things a little better, and yet it must matter because you keep on trying or having to keep on trying and then all of a sudden it's all over." -- William C. Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
