<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888837-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/888837-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 08:20:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370558-and-sitting-there-sea-drifting-in-around-them-wolf-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 08:20:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/370558-and-sitting-there-sea-drifting-in-around-them-wolf-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And sitting there, sea drifting in around them, Wolf had understood for the first time what kind of life he wanted to live with Faith. Maybe they wouldn't rise up into the sky the way he'd thought, maybe the real thing was doing what his parents had done, pay the rent, read the paper, hell, maybe that was the dare. To live--day in, day out. Just live." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386612-i-m-always-happy-sasha-said-sometimes-i-just-forget</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 16:34:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/386612-i-m-always-happy-sasha-said-sometimes-i-just-forget]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm always happy,&quot; Sasha said. &quot;Sometimes I just forget." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150191-you-think-because-he-doesn-t-love-you-that-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 18:16:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150191-you-think-because-he-doesn-t-love-you-that-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think because he doesn't love you that you are worthless. You think that because he doesn't want you anymore that he is right -- that his judgement and opinion of you are correct. If he throws you out, then you are garbage. You think he belongs to you because you want to belong to him. Don't. It's a bad word, 'belong.' Especially when you put it with somebody you love. Love shouldn't be like that. Did you ever see the way the clouds love a mountain? They circle all around it; sometimes you can't even see the mountain for the clouds. But you know what? You go up top and what do you see? His head. The clouds never cover the head. His head pokes through, beacuse the clouds let him; they don't wrap him up. They let him keep his head up high, free, with nothing to hide him or bind him. You can't own a human being. You can't lose what you don't own. Suppose you did own him. Could you really love somebody who was absolutely nobody without you? You really want somebody like that? Somebody who falls apart when you walk out the door? You don't, do you? And neither does he. You're turning over your whole life to him. Your whole life, girl. And if it means so little to you that you can just give it away, hand it to him, then why should it mean any more to him? He can't value you more than you value yourself." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 03:45:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385277-sure-everything-is-ending-jules-said-but-not-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2012 03:48:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Jennifer Egan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385277-sure-everything-is-ending-jules-said-but-not-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure, everything is ending,&quot; Jules said, &quot;but not yet." -- Jennifer Egan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554466-our-friendship-was-like-our-writing-in-some-ways-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 16:58:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/554466-our-friendship-was-like-our-writing-in-some-ways-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our friendship was like our writing in some ways. It was the only thing that was interesting about our otherwise dull lives. We were better off when we were together. Together we were a small society of ambition and high ideals. We were tender and patient and kind. We were not like the world at all." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1865-everybody-s-journey-is-individual-if-you-fall-in-love-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 13:58:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1865-everybody-s-journey-is-individual-if-you-fall-in-love-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everybody's journey is individual. If you fall in love with a boy, you fall in love with a boy. The fact that many Americans consider it a disease says more about them than it does about homosexuality. " -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14373-know-from-whence-you-came-if-you-know-whence-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 13:58:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14373-know-from-whence-you-came-if-you-know-whence-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Know from whence you came. If you know whence you came, there are absolutely no limitations to where you can go." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155018-the-writer-s-only-real-task-to-recreate-out-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 13:59:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/155018-the-writer-s-only-real-task-to-recreate-out-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The writer's only real task: to recreate out of the disorder of life that order which is art" -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
