<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889092-benjamin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889092-benjamin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 14:25:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328587-interchangeable-ever-were-the-terms-of-abuse-with-which-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 14:25:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328587-interchangeable-ever-were-the-terms-of-abuse-with-which-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Interchangeable ever were the terms of abuse with which the aggressor discredits those about to be ravaged!" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516268-to-say-nothing-of-what-you-lose-lose-lose-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 15:14:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/516268-to-say-nothing-of-what-you-lose-lose-lose-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say nothing of what you lose, lose, lose, are losing, man. You fool, you stupid fool ... You've even been insulated from the responsibility of genuine suffering ... Even the suffering you do endure is largely unnecessary. Actually spurious. It lacks the very basis you require of it for its tragic nature. You deceive yourself." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328586-the-consul-felt-a-pang-ah-to-have-a-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 15:15:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328586-the-consul-felt-a-pang-ah-to-have-a-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Consul felt a pang.  Ah, to have a horse, and gallop away, singing, to someone you loved perhaps, into the heart of all the simplicity and peace in the world; was that not like the opportunity afforded man by life itself?  Of course not.  Still, just for a moment, it had seemed that it was." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2013 17:56:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Roberto Bolano]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278701-books-are-finite-sexual-encounters-are-finite-but-the-desire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are finite, sexual encounters are finite, but the desire to read and to fuck is infinite; it surpasses our own deaths, our fears, our hopes for peace." -- Roberto Bolano]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221645-this-is-not-an-exit</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 09:14:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221645-this-is-not-an-exit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is not an exit." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42394-disintegration---i-m-taking-it-in-stride</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 09:14:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42394-disintegration---i-m-taking-it-in-stride]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Disintegration---I'm taking it in stride." -- Bret Easton Ellis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972479-indeed-on-the-face-of-it-this-man-of-abnormal</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 20:21:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972479-indeed-on-the-face-of-it-this-man-of-abnormal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Indeed, on the face of it, this man of abnormal strength and constitution and obscure ambition, whom Hugh would never know, could never deliver nor make agreement to God for, but in his way loved and desired to help, had triumphantly succeeded in pulling himself together." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972489-we-dash-the-black-river-its-flats-smooth-as-stone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 20:28:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/972489-we-dash-the-black-river-its-flats-smooth-as-stone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["WE DASH THE BLACK RIVER, ITS flats smooth as stone. Not a ship, not a dinghy, not one cry of white. The water lies broken, cracked from the wind. This great estuary is wide, endless. The river is brackish, blue with the cold. It passes beneath us blurring. The sea birds hang above it, they wheel, disappear. We flash the wide river, a dream of the past. The deeps fall behind, the bottom is paling the surface, we rush by the shallows, boats beached for winter, desolate piers. And on wings like the gulls, soar up, turn, look back." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981969-haven-t-you-got-any-tenderness-or-love-left-for-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 22:19:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981969-haven-t-you-got-any-tenderness-or-love-left-for-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Haven’t you got any tenderness or love left for me at all?” Yvonne asked suddenly, almost piteously, turning round on him, and he thought: Yes, I do love you, I have all the love in the world left for you, only that love seems so far away from me and so strange too, for it is as though I could almost hear it, a droning or a weeping, but far, far away, and a sad lost sound, it might be either approaching or receding, I can’t tell which. “Don’t you think of anything except of how many drinks you’re going to have?" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981972-and-yet-he-was-thinking-all-over-again-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 22:22:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981972-and-yet-he-was-thinking-all-over-again-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["—And yet, he was thinking all over again, and all over again as for the first time, how he had suffered, suffered, suffered without her; indeed such desolation, such a desperate sense of abandonment bereavement, as during this last year without Yvonne, he had never known in his life, unless it was when his mother died. But this present emotion he had never experienced with his mother: this urgent desire to hurt, to provoke, at a time when forgiveness alone could save the day, this, rather, had commenced with his stepmother, so that she would have to cry:—“I can’t eat, Geoffrey, the food sticks in my throat!” It was hard to forgive, hard, hard to forgive. Harder still, not to say how hard it was, I hate you. Even now, of all times. Even though here was God’s moment, the chance to agree, to produce the card, to change everything; or there was but a moment left … Too late. The Consul had controlled his tongue. But he felt his mind divide and rise, like the two halves of a counterpoised drawbridge, ticking, to permit" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981974-far-too-soon-it-had-begun-to-seem-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 22:28:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/981974-far-too-soon-it-had-begun-to-seem-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Far too soon it had begun to seem too much of a triumph, it had been too good, too horribly unimaginable to lose, impossible finally to bear: it was as if it had become itself its own foreboding that it could not last, a foreboding that was like a presence too, turning his steps towards the taverns again. And how could one begin all over again, as though the Café Chagrin, the Farolito, had never been?" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/986599-the-slow-darkening-of-the-murals-as-you-look-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 18:04:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/986599-the-slow-darkening-of-the-murals-as-you-look-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The slow darkening of the murals as you look from right to left. It seems somehow to symbolise the gradual imposition of the Spaniards’ conquering will upon the Indians. Do you see what I mean?" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/989300-i-have-no-house-only-a-shadow-but-whenever-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 20:47:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/989300-i-have-no-house-only-a-shadow-but-whenever-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no house only a shadow. But whenever you are in need of a shadow, my shadow is yours." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/992958-hugh-concentrated-upon-different-objects-in-the-cami-n-the-driver-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 20:31:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/992958-hugh-concentrated-upon-different-objects-in-the-cami-n-the-driver-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hugh concentrated upon different objects in the camión; the driver’s small mirror with the legend running round it—Cooperación de la Cruz Roja, the three picture postcards of the Virgin Mary pinned beside it, the two slim vases of marguerites over the dashboard, the gangrened fire extinguisher, the dungaree jacket and whiskbroom under the seat where the pelado was sitting—he watched him as they hit another bad stretch of road. Swaying from side to side with his eyes shut, the man was trying to tuck in his shirt. Now he was methodically buttoning his coat on the wrong buttons. But it struck Hugh all this was merely preparatory, a sort of grotesque toilet." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1003314-nothing-is-altered-and-in-spite-of-god-s-mercy-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 22:06:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1003314-nothing-is-altered-and-in-spite-of-god-s-mercy-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is altered and in spite of God’s mercy I am still alone. Though my suffering seems senseless I am still in agony. There is no explanation of my life.” Indeed there was not, nor was this what he’d meant to convey." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1003315-please-let-me-make-her-happy-deliver-me-from-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 22:06:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1003315-please-let-me-make-her-happy-deliver-me-from-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…“Please let me make her happy, deliver me from this dreadful tyranny of self. I have sunk low. Let me sink lower still, that I may know the truth. Teach me to love again, to love life.” That wouldn’t do either … “Where is love? Let me truly suffer. Give me back my purity, the knowledge of the Mysteries, that I have betrayed and lost.—Let me be truly lonely, that I may honestly pray. Let us be happy again somewhere, if it’s only together, if it’s only out of this terrible world. Destroy the world!” he cried in his heart." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004021-all-of-them-you-see-misfits-all-good-for-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 13:03:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004021-all-of-them-you-see-misfits-all-good-for-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of them, you see, misfits, all good for nothing, cowards, baboons, meek wolves, parasites, every man jack of them, people afraid to face their own responsibilities, fight their own fight, ready to go anywhere, as Tolstoy well perceived—" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004038-hell-he-finished-absurdly-because-he-produced-a-twenty-peso-note</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 13:10:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004038-hell-he-finished-absurdly-because-he-produced-a-twenty-peso-note]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hell,” he finished absurdly. “Because—” He produced a twenty-peso note and laid it on the table. “I like it,” he called to them, through the open window, from outside. Cervantes stood behind the bar, with scared eyes, holding the cockerel. “I love hell. I can’t wait to get back there. In fact I’m running, I’m almost back there already." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004633-to-night-as-ages-hence-people-would-say-this-or-shut</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 22:27:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004633-to-night-as-ages-hence-people-would-say-this-or-shut]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-night, as ages hence, people would say this, or shut their doors on them, turn in bereaved agony from them, or toward them with love saying: “That is our star up there, yours and mine”; steer by them above the clouds or lost at sea, or standing in the spray on the forecastle head, watch them, suddenly, careen; put their faith or lack of it in them; train, in a thousand observatories, feeble telescopes upon them, across whose lenses swam mysterious swarms of stars and clouds of dead dark stars, catastrophes of exploding suns, or giant Antares raging to its end—a smouldering ember yet five hundred times greater than the earth’s sun." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004634-and-the-earth-itself-still-turning-on-its-axis-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 22:27:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004634-and-the-earth-itself-still-turning-on-its-axis-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the earth itself still turning on its axis and revolving around that sun, the sun revolving around the luminous wheel of this galaxy, the countless unmeasured jewelled wheels of countless unmeasured galaxies, turning, turning, majestically, into infinity, into eternity, through all of which all life ran on—all this, long after she herself was dead, men would still be reading in the night sky, and as the earth turned through those distant seasons, and they watched the constellations still rising, culminating, setting, to rise again—Aries, Taurus, Gemini, the Crab, Leo, Virgo, the Scales and the Scorpion, Capricorn the Sea-goat and Aquarius the Water Bearer, Pisces, and once more, triumphantly, Aries!—would they not, too, still be asking the hopeless eternal question: to what end? What force drives this sublime celestial machinery?" -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004641-they-were-the-cars-at-the-fair-that-were-whirling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 22:55:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1004641-they-were-the-cars-at-the-fair-that-were-whirling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were the cars at the fair that were whirling around her; no, they were the planets, while the sun stood, burning and spinning and guttering in the centre; here they came again, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune, Pluto; but they were not planets, for it was not the merry-go-round at all, but the Ferris wheel, they were constellations, in the hub of which, like a great cold eye, burned Polaris, and round and round it here they went: Cassiopeia, Cepheus, the Lynx, Ursa Major, Ursa Minor, and the Dragon; yet they were not constellations, but, somehow, myriads of beautiful butterflies, she was sailing into Acapulco harbour through a hurricane of beautiful butterflies, zigzagging overhead and endlessly vanishing astern over the sea, the sea, rough and pure, the long dawn rollers advancing, rising, and crashing down to glide in colourless ellipses over the sand, sinking, sinking, someone was calling her name far away and she remembered, they were in a dark wood, she heard the wind and the rain rushing through the forest and saw the tremours of lightning shuddering through the heavens and the horse—great God, the horse—and would this scene repeat itself endlessly and forever?—the horse, rearing, poised over her, petrified in midair, a statue, somebody was sitting on the statue, it was Yvonne Griffaton, no, it was the statue of Huerta, the drunkard, the murderer, it was the Consul, or it was a mechanical horse on the merry-go-round, the carrousel, but the carrousel had stopped and she was in a ravine down which a million horses were thundering towards her, and she must escape, through the friendly forest to their house, their little home by the sea." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005025-closing-his-eyes-again-standing-there-glass-in-hand-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 08:36:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005025-closing-his-eyes-again-standing-there-glass-in-hand-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Closing his eyes again, standing there, glass in hand, he thought for a minute with a freezing detached almost amused calm of the dreadful night inevitably awaiting him whether he drank much more or not, his room shaking with daemonic orchestras, the snatches of fearful tumultuous sleep, interrupted by voices which were really dogs barking, or by his own name being continually repeated by imaginary parties arriving, the vicious shouting, the strumming, the slamming, the pounding, the battling with insolent archfiends, the avalanche breaking down the door, the proddings from under the bed, and always, outside, the cries, the wailing, the terrible music, the dark’s spinets: he returned to the bar." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005824-never-think-that-by-releasing-me-you-will-be-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 20:26:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1005824-never-think-that-by-releasing-me-you-will-be-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never think that by releasing me you will be free. You would only condemn us to an ultimate hell on earth. You would only free something else to destroy us both." -- Malcolm Lowry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009959-but-knowledge-does-not-protect-one-life-is-contemptuous-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 08:08:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1009959-but-knowledge-does-not-protect-one-life-is-contemptuous-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But knowledge does not protect one. Life is contemptuous of knowledge; it forces it to sit in the anterooms, to wait outside. Passion, energy, lies: these are what life admires. Still, anything can be endured if all humanity is watching. The martyrs prove it. We live in the attention of others. We turn to it as flowers to the sun." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013249-children-are-our-crop-our-fields-our-earth-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 16:01:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013249-children-are-our-crop-our-fields-our-earth-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Children are our crop, our fields, our earth. They are birds let loose into darkness. They are errors renewed. Still, they are the only source from which may be drawn a life more successful, more knowing than our own. Somehow they will do one thing, take one step further, they will see the summit. We believe in it, the radiance that streams from the future, from days we will not see. Children must live, must triumph. Children must die; that is an idea we cannot accept." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013263-there-are-things-i-love-about-marriage-i-love-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 16:11:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1013263-there-are-things-i-love-about-marriage-i-love-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["THERE ARE THINGS I LOVE ABOUT marriage. I love the familiarity of it,” Nedra said. “It’s like a tattoo. You wanted it at the time, you have it, it’s implanted in your skin, you can’t get rid of it. You’re hardly even aware of it any more. I suppose I’m very conventional,” she decided." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1014526-england-the-worst-of-all-you-know-i-do-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 18:44:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1014526-england-the-worst-of-all-you-know-i-do-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["England? The worst of all. You know, I do some business there, I have friends in England. Their flats are broken into constantly. The police come, they look around, they dust for fingerprints. Well, we know who it is, they say. Wonderful, who? The same ones who did it last time, they say." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1014544-greatness-is-something-which-can-be-regarded-in-a-number</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 19:01:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1014544-greatness-is-something-which-can-be-regarded-in-a-number]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Greatness is something which can be regarded in a number of ways,” he said. “It is, of course, the apotheosis, man raised to his highest powers, but it also can be, in a way, like insanity, a certain kind of imbalance, a flaw, in most cases a beneficial flaw, an anomaly, an accident.” “Well, many great men are eccentric,” Viri said, “even narrow.” “Not necessarily narrow so much as impatient, intense." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017065-strauss-s-for-instance-which-begins-in-the-heavens-the-artist</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 17:35:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017065-strauss-s-for-instance-which-begins-in-the-heavens-the-artist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strauss’s, for instance, which begins in the heavens. The artist doesn’t ascend to glory, he appears in it, he already has it and the world is prepared to recognize him. Meteoric, like a comet—those are the phrases we apply, and it’s true, it is a kind of burning. It makes them highly visible, and at the same time it consumes them, and it’s only afterwards, when the brilliance is gone, when their bones are lying alongside those of lesser men, that one can really judge. I mean, there are famous works, renowned in antiquity, and today absolutely forgotten: books, buildings, works of art." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017081-the-heart-is-in-darkness-unknowing-like-those-animals-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 17:52:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Benjamin add a quote by James Salter]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1017081-the-heart-is-in-darkness-unknowing-like-those-animals-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The heart is in darkness, unknowing, like those animals in mines that have never seen the day. It has no loyalties, no hopes; it has its task." -- James Salter]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
