<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889742-alyssa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889742-alyssa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:44:46 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469831-telling-an-introvert-to-go-to-a-party-is-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:44:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Criss Jami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/469831-telling-an-introvert-to-go-to-a-party-is-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Telling an introvert to go to a party is like telling a saint to go to Hell." -- Criss Jami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277129-leave-an-extrovert-alone-for-two-minutes-and-he-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Jonathan Rauch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/277129-leave-an-extrovert-alone-for-two-minutes-and-he-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave an extrovert alone for two minutes and he will reach for his cell phone. In contrast, after an hour or two of being socially “on,” we introverts need to turn off and recharge. My own formula is roughly two hours alone for every hour of socializing. This isn’t antisocial. It isn’t a sign of depression. It does not call for medication. For introverts, to be alone with our thoughts is as restorative as sleeping, as nourishing as eating. Our motto: “I’m okay, you’re okay—in small doses." -- Jonathan Rauch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524835-i-talked-to-a-calzone-for-fifteen-minutes-last-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:46:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/524835-i-talked-to-a-calzone-for-fifteen-minutes-last-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I talked to a calzone for fifteen minutes last night before I realized it was just an introverted pizza. I wish all my acquaintances were so tasty. " -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537052-let-s-clear-one-thing-up-introverts-do-not-hate-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:46:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/537052-let-s-clear-one-thing-up-introverts-do-not-hate-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's clear one thing up: Introverts do not hate small talk because we dislike people.  We hate small talk because we hate the barrier it creates between people." -- Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316168-when-psychologists-catherine-caldwell-harris-and-ayse-ay-i-egi-compared-u-s-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316168-when-psychologists-catherine-caldwell-harris-and-ayse-ay-i-egi-compared-u-s-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When psychologists Catherine Caldwell-Harris and Ayse Ayçiçegi compared U.S. and Turkish samples, they found that having &quot;an orientation inconsistent with societal values&quot; is a risk factor for poor mental health. The findings support what the researchers call the personality-culture clash hypothesis: &quot;Psychological adjustment depends on the degree of match between personality and the values of surrounding society.&quot; To the extent that introverts feel the need to explain, apologize, or feel guilty about what works best for them, they feel alienated not only from society but from themselves." -- Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/829482-spend-your-free-time-the-way-you-like-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:51:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Susan Cain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/829482-spend-your-free-time-the-way-you-like-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spend your free time the way you like, not the way you think you're supposed to. Stay home on New Year's Eve if that's what makes you happy. Skip the committee meeting. Cross the street to avoid making aimless chitchat with random acquaintances. Read. Cook. Run. Write a story. Make a deal with yourself that you'll attend a set number of social events in exchange for not feeling guilty when you beg off." -- Susan Cain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573566-a-good-rule-of-thumb-is-that-any-environment-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2013 11:53:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/573566-a-good-rule-of-thumb-is-that-any-environment-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good rule of thumb is that any environment that consistently leaves you feeling bad about who you are is the wrong environment." -- Laurie Helgoe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:22:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33460-let-there-be-spaces-in-your-togetherness-and-let-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let there be spaces in your togetherness, And let the winds of the heavens dance between you. Love one another but make not a bond of love: Let it rather be a moving sea between the shores of your souls. Fill each other's cup but drink not from one cup. Give one another of your bread but eat not from the same loaf. Sing and dance together and be joyous, but let each one of you be alone, Even as the strings of a lute are alone though they quiver with the same music. Give your hearts, but not into each other's keeping. For only the hand of Life can contain your hearts. And stand together, yet not too near together: For the pillars of the temple stand apart, And the oak tree and the cypress grow not in each other's shadow." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197442-if-you-love-somebody-let-them-go-for-if-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:22:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/197442-if-you-love-somebody-let-them-go-for-if-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you love somebody, let them go, for if they return, they were always yours. If they don't, they never were." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38726-it-is-wrong-to-think-that-love-comes-from-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:24:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38726-it-is-wrong-to-think-that-love-comes-from-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is wrong to think that love comes from long companionship and persevering courtship. Love is the offspring of spiritual affinity and unless that affinity is created in a moment, it will not be created for years or even generations." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82821-they-deem-me-mad-because-i-will-not-sell-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:26:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82821-they-deem-me-mad-because-i-will-not-sell-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They deem me mad because I will not sell my days for gold; and I deem them mad because they think my days have a price. " -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156170-my-loneliness-was-born-when-men-praised-my-talkative-faults</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156170-my-loneliness-was-born-when-men-praised-my-talkative-faults]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My loneliness was born when men praised my talkative faults and blamed my silent virtues." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83397-i-wash-my-hands-of-those-who-imagine-chattering-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:29:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83397-i-wash-my-hands-of-those-who-imagine-chattering-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wash my hands of those who imagine chattering to be knowledge, silence to be ignorance, and affection to be art." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95950-only-yesterday-i-was-no-different-than-them-yet-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:30:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95950-only-yesterday-i-was-no-different-than-them-yet-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only yesterday I was no different than them, yet I was saved. I am explaining to you the way of life of a people who say every sort of wicked thing about me because I sacrificed their friendship to gain my own soul. I left the dark paths of their duplicity and turned my eyes toward the light where there is salvation, truth, and justice. They have exiled me now from their society, yet I am content. Mankind only exiles the one whose large spirit rebels against injustice and tyranny. He who does not prefer exile to servility is not free in the true and necessary sense of freedom." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45273-many-of-us-spend-our-whole-lives-running-from-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:36:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45273-many-of-us-spend-our-whole-lives-running-from-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many of us spend our whole lives running from feeling with the mistaken belief that you can not bear the pain. But you have already borne the pain. What you have not done is feel all you are beyond that pain." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203550-love-descends-upon-our-souls-by-the-will-of-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:37:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203550-love-descends-upon-our-souls-by-the-will-of-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love descends upon our souls by the will of God and not by the demand or the plea of the individual." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20843-a-voice-cannot-carry-the-tongue-and-the-lips-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20843-a-voice-cannot-carry-the-tongue-and-the-lips-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A voice cannot carry the tongue and the lips that gave it wings. Alone must it seek the ether. 

And alone and without his nest shall the eagle fly across the sun." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376080-all-our-words-are-but-crumbs-that-fall-down-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376080-all-our-words-are-but-crumbs-that-fall-down-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All our words are but crumbs that fall down from the feast of the mind." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419114-you-talk-when-you-cease-to-be-at-peace-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:45:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419114-you-talk-when-you-cease-to-be-at-peace-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You talk when you cease to be at peace with your thoughts;
And when you can no longer dwell in the solitude of your heart you live in your lips, and sound is a diversion and a pastime.
And in much of your talking, thinking is half murdered." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540764-men-who-do-not-forgive-women-their-little-faults-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:45:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/540764-men-who-do-not-forgive-women-their-little-faults-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men who do not forgive women their little faults will never enjoy their great virtues." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224491-happiness-is-a-vine-that-takes-root-and-grows-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:47:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224491-happiness-is-a-vine-that-takes-root-and-grows-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is a vine that takes root and grows within the heart, never outside it." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712061-solitude-and-seclusion-life-is-an-island-in-an-ocean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:49:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/712061-solitude-and-seclusion-life-is-an-island-in-an-ocean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["SOLITUDE AND SECLUSION
Life is an island in an ocean of solitude and seclusion.
Life is an island, rocks are its desires, trees its dreams, and flowers its loneliness, and it is in the middle of an ocean of solitude and seclusion.
Your life, my friend, is an island separated from all other islands and continents. Regardless of how many boats you send to other shores, you yourself are an island separated by its own pains,secluded its happiness and far away in its compassion and hidden in its secrets and mysteries.
I saw you, my friend, sitting upon a mound of gold, happy in your wealth and great in your riches and believing that a handful of gold is the secret chain that links the thoughts of the people with your own thoughts and links their feeling with your own.
I saw you as a great conqueror leading a conquering army toward the fortress, then destroying and capturing it.
On second glance I found beyond the wall of your treasures a heart trembling in its solitude and seclusion like the trembling of a thirsty man within a cage of gold and jewels, but without water.
I saw you, my friend, sitting on a throne of glory surrounded by people extolling your charity, enumerating your gifts, gazing upon you as if they were in the presence of a prophet lifting their souls up into the planets and stars. I saw you looking at them, contentment and strength upon your face, as if you were to them as the soul is to the body.
On the second look I saw your secluded self standing beside your throne, suffering in its seclusion and quaking in its loneliness. I saw that self stretching its hands as if begging from unseen ghosts. I saw it looking above the shoulders of the people to a far horizon, empty of everything except its solitude and seclusion.
I saw you, my friend, passionately in love with a beautiful woman, filling her palms with your kisses as she looked at you with sympathy and affection in her eyes and sweetness of motherhood on her lips; I said, secretly, that love has erased his solitude and removed his seclusion and he is now within the eternal soul which draws toward itself, with love, those who were separated by solitude and seclusion.
On the second look I saw behind your soul another lonely soul, like a fog, trying in vain to become a drop of tears in the palm of that woman.
Your life, my friend, is a residence far away from any other residence and neighbors.
Your inner soul is a home far away from other homes named after you. If this residence is dark, you cannot light it with your neighbor's lamp; if it is empty you cannot fill it with the riches of your neighbor; were it in the middle of a desert, you could not move it to a garden planted by someone else.
Your inner soul, my friend, is surrounded with solitude and seclusion. Were it not for this solitude and this seclusion you would not be you and I would not be I. If it were not for that solitude and seclusion, I would, if I heard your voice, think myself to be speaking; yet, if I saw your face, i would imagine that I were looking into a mirror." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79524-listen-to-the-women-when-she-looks-at-you-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:51:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79524-listen-to-the-women-when-she-looks-at-you-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the women when she looks at you, not when she talks to you." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579284-a-traveller-i-am-and-a-navigator-and-everyday-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:56:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/579284-a-traveller-i-am-and-a-navigator-and-everyday-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A traveller I am, and a navigator, and everyday I discover a new region within my soul." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625751-man-struggles-to-find-life-outside-himself-unaware-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 14:59:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyssa add a quote by Khalil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/625751-man-struggles-to-find-life-outside-himself-unaware-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man struggles to find life outside himself, unaware that the life he is seeking is within him." -- Khalil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
