<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889899-laurence]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/889899-laurence" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 10:26:13 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350007-whenever-we-doubt-our-own-ability-to-achieve-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 10:26:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurence add a quote by Andrew Matthews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350007-whenever-we-doubt-our-own-ability-to-achieve-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever we doubt our own ability to achieve, it is worthwile pondering the obstacles that others have overcome.  To name a few...
*Napoleon overcame his considerable handicap, his tiny stature, to lead his conquering armies across Europe.
*Abraham Lincon failed in business aged 31, lost a legislative race and 32, again failed in business at 34, had his sweetheart die when he was 35, had a nervous breakdown at 36, lost congressional races aged 43, 46 and 48, lost a senatorial race at 55, failed in his efforts to become vice president of the U.S.A aged 56 and lost a further senatorial contest at 58.  At 60 years of age he was elected president of the U.S.A and is now remembered as one of the great leaders in world history. 
*Winston Churchill was a poor student with a speech impediment. Not only did he win a Nobel Prize at 24, but he became one of the most inspiring speakers of recent times.  
It is not where you start that counts, but where you choose to finish." -- Andrew Matthews]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419771-it-s-not-what-happens-to-you-that-determines-your-happiness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 10:27:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Laurence add a quote by Andrew Matthews]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/419771-it-s-not-what-happens-to-you-that-determines-your-happiness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not what happens to you that determines your happiness. It's how you think about what happens to you." -- Andrew Matthews]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
