<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/88991-mark-desrosiers]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/88991-mark-desrosiers" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 00:53:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6980-if-one-starts-with-the-anatomical-difference-which-even-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 00:53:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6980-if-one-starts-with-the-anatomical-difference-which-even-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one starts with the anatomical difference, which even a patriarchal Viennese novelist was able to see was destiny, then one begins to understand why men and women don't get on very well within marriage, or indeed in any exclusive sort of long-range sexual relationship. &lt;i&gt;He&lt;/i&gt; is designed to make as many babies as possible with as many different women as he can get his hands on, while &lt;i&gt;she&lt;/i&gt; is designed to take time off from her busy schedule as astronaut or role model to lay an egg and bring up the result. Male and female are on different sexual tracks, and that cannot be changed by the Book or any book. Since all our natural instincts are carefully perverted from birth, it is no wonder that we tend to be, if not all of us serial killers, killers of our own true nature. " -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6981-as-with-our-earlier-worship-of-saints-and-facts-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 01:32:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by John Ralston Saul]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6981-as-with-our-earlier-worship-of-saints-and-facts-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As with our earlier worship of saints and facts, there is something silly about grown men and women striving to reduce their vision of themselves and of civilization to bean counting. The message of the competition/efficiency/marketplace Trinity seems to be that we should drop the idea of ourselves developed over two and a half millennia. We are no longer beings distinguished by our ability to think and to act consciously in order to affect our circumstances. Instead we should passively submit ourselves and our whole civilization -- our public structures, social forms and cultural creativity -- to the abstract forces of unregulated commerce. It may be that most citizens have difficulty with the argument and would prefer to continue working on the idea of dignified human intelligence. If they must drop something, they would probably prefer to drop the economists. " -- John Ralston Saul]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6985-hardly-had-juana-had-time-to-get-settled-when-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 01:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Townsend Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6985-hardly-had-juana-had-time-to-get-settled-when-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hardly had Juana had time to get settled when there was a clatter in the courtyard. The night sprang into excitement; instructions were shouted, torches brought. And suddenly the doors burst open; suddenly Philip -- hot, handsome, disheveled -- strode in.

Philip was blond and sturdy; the gunpowder-train of Juana's emotions, long and dark and twisting, exploded at last. Philip's eyes must have seen, if nothing else, a girl in virginal flush, a young body of sixteen. He could hardly endure the formal presentations of the nobles. As soon as they were ended, he did what is generally referred to as commanding the nearest cleric to marry them on the spot. This person, however -- the Spaniard don Diego Villaescusa, Dean of Jaen -- it was not in Philip's power to order about. But the fact that it must have been Juana who gave the command only serves to underline the mutuality of their haste and hunger. The Dean did as he was bidden; the ignited youngsters kneeled; Philip hurried Juana out. In a room on the &lt;i&gt;rez de chaussee&lt;/i&gt; overlooking the turbulent river they tore off their clothes. Someone had managed to get a gilded crucifix nailed on the ceiling above the bed -- surely one of the unnoticed ornaments (and, as things turned out, one of the most inappropriate) ever put up." -- Townsend Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7430-gadzooks-we-ve-jumped-out-of-the-frying-pan-and-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2007 01:16:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Tony Millionaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7430-gadzooks-we-ve-jumped-out-of-the-frying-pan-and-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gadzooks! We've jumped out of the frying pan and into another frying pan!" -- Tony Millionaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12912-i-agree-to-this-constitution-with-all-its-faults-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2008 01:47:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12912-i-agree-to-this-constitution-with-all-its-faults-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I agree to this Constitution with all its faults, if they are such: because I think a General Government necessary for us, and there is no &lt;i&gt;Form&lt;/i&gt; of Government but what may be a Blessing to the People if well-administred; and I believe farther that this is likely to be well administred for a Course of Years and can only end in Despotism as other Forms have done before it, when the People shall become so corrupted as to need Despotic Government, being incapable of any other." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13520-drenched-in-british-purples-i-have-offered-up-my-tones</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2008 21:22:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by James Ensor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13520-drenched-in-british-purples-i-have-offered-up-my-tones]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Drenched in British purples, I have offered up my tones: pigeon breast, hind belly, balky mule lung, monkey bottom pink, lapis lazuli and malachite, excited nymph thigh, panther pee-pee, high-smelling hen hair, hedgehog in aspic, barrel-maker's brothel, revered rose, monkeybush, turkey-like white, sly violet, page's slipper, immaculate nun spring, unspeakable red, Ensor azure, affected yellow, mummy skull, rock-hard gray, brunt celadon, shop soiled smoke ring." -- James Ensor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17565-richard-bedford-bennett-was-the-richest-prime-minister-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 00:26:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gordon Donaldson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17565-richard-bedford-bennett-was-the-richest-prime-minister-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Richard Bedford Bennett] was the richest Prime Minister and the only millionaire to hold office before Pierre Trudeau. His money obviously colored his thinking -- colored it true blue -- but he did not consider it a political drawback. No leader, he said, could serve the public properly if he was constantly looking over his shoulder at the shadow of debts. This theory is now widely accepted in the United States where it has become practically impossible for a non-millionaire to run for high office without selling pieces of himself like a prize-fighter. Yet the public still suspects a self-made millionaire like Lyndon Johnson while revering the much-richer John F. Kennedy, who got it all from his father. " -- Gordon Donaldson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17566-americans-though-apparently-impressed-by-ghastly-sentimentality-and-outrageous-hypocrisy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 00:29:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gordon Donaldson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17566-americans-though-apparently-impressed-by-ghastly-sentimentality-and-outrageous-hypocrisy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Americans, though apparently impressed by ghastly sentimentality and outrageous hypocrisy, are by nature much more politically cynical than Canadians. In their longer history they have had much more to be cynical about. They demand a vulgar show, enjoy it, guffaw, and forget it the next morning. When a new U.S. President takes office all bets are off and his campaign platform is dismantled and stored away. " -- Gordon Donaldson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27905-i-can-t-help-it-either-the-laughing-solemn-gatherings-slow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 22:30:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by A.L. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27905-i-can-t-help-it-either-the-laughing-solemn-gatherings-slow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't help it either, the laughing: solemn gatherings, slow
ballads, pompous orations, any person or occasion that assumes I'll
offer my unreserved respect: I tend to find them all hysterical in the
end. Especially if someone similar is there to set me off. They don't
have to do much: I recognize what it looks like when somebody's
composure starts to strip itself away. They'll maybe cross their arms
with that twitchy, shaky, tension, or they'll grab down little wheezes
of embarrassed air, or they'll simply hood their faces under their
palm, trying to hide how fast they're slipping, how fast *we're*
slipping, because I'll be weakening with them by then, I'll be just as
lost, pulled equally tight against the moment when we both stop caring
and let it disgrace us -- when we laugh." -- A.L. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5880-the-key-is-never-never-work-nothing-is-more-aging</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2008 22:34:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Quentin Crisp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5880-the-key-is-never-never-work-nothing-is-more-aging]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The key is never, never work. Nothing is more aging than work. It's not only the strain of getting up in the morning for work, but it's the resentment that settles on your face" -- Quentin Crisp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58032-the-problem-with-defending-the-purity-of-the-english-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 17:28:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by James Nicoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58032-the-problem-with-defending-the-purity-of-the-english-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with defending the purity of the English language is that English is about as pure as a cribhouse whore. We don't just borrow words; on occasion, English has pursued other languages down alleyways to beat them unconscious and rifle their pockets for new vocabulary." -- James Nicoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 23:33:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1146-it-was-about-eleven-o-clock-in-the-morning-mid-october]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was about eleven o'clock in the morning, mid October, with the sun not shining and a look of hard wet rain in the clearness of the foothills. I was wearing my powder-blue suit, with dark blue shirt, tie and display handkerchief, black brogues, black wool socks with dark little clocks on them. I was neat, clean, shaved and sober, and I didn't care who knew it. I was everything the well-dressed private detective ought to be. I was calling on four million dollars." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48006-for-years-i-felt-that-being-respectable-meant-maintaining-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:25:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Paul Theroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48006-for-years-i-felt-that-being-respectable-meant-maintaining-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For years I felt that being respectable meant maintaining a sinister complacency, and the disreputable freedom I sought helped make me a writer." -- Paul Theroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11603-and-meanwhile-time-goes-about-its-immemorial-work-of-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:26:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11603-and-meanwhile-time-goes-about-its-immemorial-work-of-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And meanwhile time goes about its immemorial work of making everyone look and feel like shit." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53092-money-doesn-t-mind-if-we-say-it-s-evil-it-goes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:29:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53092-money-doesn-t-mind-if-we-say-it-s-evil-it-goes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Money doesn't mind if we say it's evil, it goes from strength to strength. It's a fiction, an addiction, and a tacit conspiracy." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:30:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Martin Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5015-what-did-nabokov-and-joyce-have-in-common-apart-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What did Nabokov and Joyce have in common, apart from the poor teeth and the great prose? Exile, and decades of near pauperism. A compulsive tendency to overtip. An uxoriousness that their wives deservedly inspired. More than that, they both lived their lives 'beautifully'--not in any Jamesian sense (where, besides, ferocious solvency would have been a prerequisite), but in the droll fortitude of their perseverance. They got the work done, with style." -- Martin Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8467-the-smell-of-good-bread-baking-like-the-sound-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:30:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8467-the-smell-of-good-bread-baking-like-the-sound-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The smell of good bread baking, like the sound of lightly flowing water, is indescribable in its evocation of innocence and delight...

[Breadmaking is] one of those almost hypnotic businesses, like a dance from some ancient ceremony. It leaves you filled with one of the world's sweetest smells... there is no chiropractic treatment, no Yoga exercise, no hour of
meditation in a music-throbbing chapel. that will leave you emptier of bad thoughts than this homely ceremony of making bread." -- M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8448-it-seems-to-me-that-our-three-basic-needs-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:31:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8448-it-seems-to-me-that-our-three-basic-needs-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that our three basic needs, for food and security and love, are so mixed and mingled and entwined that we cannot straightly think of one without the others. So it happens that when I write of hunger, I am really writing about love and the hunger for it, and warmth and the love of it and the hunger for it… and then the warmth and richness and fine reality of hunger satisfied… and it is all one." -- M.F.K. Fisher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47067-dixon-was-alive-again-consciousness-was-upon-him-before-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:35:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Kingsley Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47067-dixon-was-alive-again-consciousness-was-upon-him-before-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dixon was alive again. Consciousness was upon him before he could get out of the way; not for him the slow, gracious wandering from the halls of sleep, but a summary, forcible ejection. He lay sprawled, too wicked to move, spewed up like a broken spider-crab on the tarry shingle of morning. The light did him harm, but not as much as looking at things did; he resolved, having done it once, never to move his eyeballs again. A dusty thudding in his head made the scene before him beat like a pulse. His mouth had been used as a latrine by some small creature of the night, and then as its mausoleum. During the night, too, he'd somehow been on a cross-country run and then been expertly beaten up by secret police. He felt bad." -- Kingsley Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33215-you-ll-find-that-marriage-is-a-good-short-cut-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 23:36:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Kingsley Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33215-you-ll-find-that-marriage-is-a-good-short-cut-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll find that marriage is a good short cut to the truth. No, not quite that. A way of doubling back to the truth. Another thing you'll find is that the years of illusion aren't those of adolescence, as the grown-ups try to tell us; they're the ones immediately after it, say the middle twenties, the false maturity if you like, when you first get thoroughly embroiled in things and lose your head. Your age, by the way, Jim. That's when you first realize that sex is important to other people besides yourself. A discovery like that can't help knocking you off balance for a time." -- Kingsley Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70366-i-love-that-name-a-country-named-chad-sounds-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 01:01:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Gary Brecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70366-i-love-that-name-a-country-named-chad-sounds-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love that name. A country named Chad. Sounds like somebody who lived next door to the Brady Bunch. But if Chad actually lived next door to the Bradys, Greg would be roasting over a slow fire and Marcia would be standing naked on an auction block, because Chad is one of the hungriest, craziest, most desperate places on the planet." -- Gary Brecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90952-there-was-a-lot-of-pretense-floating-around-not-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2008 18:23:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Mark E. Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90952-there-was-a-lot-of-pretense-floating-around-not-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was a lot of pretense floating around; not just with aunties and all that but with emotions and how people saw you. They had a point. There's a lot to learn from that generation -- the stoic approach. I think it's disgusting how they've been forgotten about in this way. It's the American hippies' fault, they saw an in there, a way of making money out of bad moods. That's all it is most of the time. You can't expect to feel cock-a-hoop every minute of every day. My mam and dad's generation understood this. They were just thankful the bombs had stopped threatening their lives. They just wanted to get on with living." -- Mark E. Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109895-if-any-man-tells-you-he-loves-america-yet-hates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2011 16:23:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109895-if-any-man-tells-you-he-loves-america-yet-hates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If any man tells you he loves America, yet hates labor, he is a liar.  If any man tells you he trusts America, yet fears labor, he is a fool." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
