<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/890022-janipanda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/890022-janipanda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 19:49:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135030-if-you-would-take-one-step-forward-darling-you-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 19:49:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janipanda add a quote by Judith McNaught]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135030-if-you-would-take-one-step-forward-darling-you-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you would take one step forward, darling, you could cry in my arms. And while you do, I'll tell you how sorry I am for everything I've done -&quot; Unable to wait, Ian caught her, pulling her tightly against him. &quot;And when I'm finished,&quot; he whispered hoarsely as she wrapped her arms around him and wept brokenly, &quot;you can help me find a way to forgive myself.&quot;
Tortured by her tears, he clasped her tighter and rubbed his jaw against her temple, his voice a ravaged whisper: &quot;I'm sorry,&quot; he told her. He cupped her face between his palms, tipping it up and gazing into her eyes, his thumbs moving over her wet cheeks. &quot;I'm sorry.&quot; Slowly, he bent his head, covering her mouth with his. &quot;I'm so damned sorry." -- Judith McNaught]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2011 20:05:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janipanda add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer believed in the idea of soul mates, or love at first sight.  But I was beginning to believe that a very few times in your life, if you were lucky, you might meet someone who was exactly right for you.  Not because he was perfect, or because you were, but because your combined flaws were arranged in a way that allowed two separate beings to hinge together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
