<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/890167-jackie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/890167-jackie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 12:33:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23287-a-mismatched-outfit-a-slightly-defective-denture-an-exquisite-mediocrity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 12:33:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23287-a-mismatched-outfit-a-slightly-defective-denture-an-exquisite-mediocrity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mismatched outfit, a slightly defective denture, an exquisite mediocrity of the soul-those are the details that make a woman real, alive. The women you see on posters or in fashion magazines-the ones all the women try to imitate nowadays-how can they be attractive? They have no reality of their own; they're just the sum of a set of abstract rules. They aren't born of human bodies; they hatch ready-made from the computers.&quot; ~The Book of Laughter and Forgetting" -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23288-he-was-well-aware-that-of-the-two-of-three</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 12:36:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23288-he-was-well-aware-that-of-the-two-of-three]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was well aware that of the two of three thousand times he had made love (how many times had he made love in his life?) only two or three were really essential and unforgettable.  The rest were mere echoes, imitations, repetitions, or reminiscences." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23290-by-giving-the-love-act-a-name-if-only-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 12:38:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23290-by-giving-the-love-act-a-name-if-only-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By giving the love act a name, if only an innocent little word like, &quot;it,&quot; he paved the way for other words, words that would reflect physical love as in a set of mirrors." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23294-the-rims-of-his-eyelids-were-burning-a-blow-received</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 12:49:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Jean Genet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23294-the-rims-of-his-eyelids-were-burning-a-blow-received]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rims of his eyelids were burning. A blow received straightens a man up and makes the body move forward, to return that blow, or a punch-to jump, to get a hard-on, to dance: to be alive.  But a blow received may also cause you to bend over, to shake, to fall down, to die.  When we see life, we call it beautiful.  When we see death, we call it ugly.  But it is more beautiful still to see oneself living at great speed, right up to the moment of death.  Detectives, poets, domestic servants and priests rely on abjection.  From it, they draw their power.  It circulates in their veins.  It nourishes them." -- Jean Genet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23297-she-was-happy-and-perfectly-in-line-with-the-tradition</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 13:01:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Jean Genet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23297-she-was-happy-and-perfectly-in-line-with-the-tradition]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was happy, and perfectly in line with the tradition of those women  they used to call &quot;ruined,&quot; &quot;fallen,&quot; feckless, bitches in heat, ravished dolls, sweet sluts, instant princesses, hot numbers, great lays, succulent morsels, everybody's darlings . . . " -- Jean Genet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23323-now-her-eyes-meet-mine-like-green-lightning-they-are-green</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:16:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Leopold von Sacher-Masoch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23323-now-her-eyes-meet-mine-like-green-lightning-they-are-green]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now her eyes meet mine like green lightning-they are green, these eyes of hers, whose power is so indescribable-green, but as are precious stones, or deep unfathomable mountain lakes." -- Leopold von Sacher-Masoch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23331-and-so-the-german-spirit-carousing-in-music-in-wonderful</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:18:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23331-and-so-the-german-spirit-carousing-in-music-in-wonderful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so the German spirit, carousing in music, in wonderful creations of sound, and wonderful beauties of feeling and mood that were never pressed home to reality, has left the greater part of its gifts to decay. None of us intellectuals is at home in reality. We are strange to it and hostile.

Assiduous and busy, care-ridden and light-hearted, intelligent and yet thoughtless, these butterflies lived a life at once childlike and raffiné; independent, not to be bought by every one, finding their account in good luck and fine weather, in love with life and yet clinging to it far less than the bourgeois, always ready to follow a fairy prince to his castle, always certain, though scarcely conscious of it, that a difficult and sad end was in store for them." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23332-once-it-happened-as-i-lay-awake-at-night-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:19:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23332-once-it-happened-as-i-lay-awake-at-night-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once it happened, as I lay awake at night, that I suddenly spoke in verses, in verses so beautiful and strange that I did not venture to think of writing them down, and then in the morning they vanished; and yet they lay hidden within me like the hard kernel within an old brittle husk." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23334-many-of-you-have-already-found-out-and-others-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:21:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23334-many-of-you-have-already-found-out-and-others-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many of you have already found out, and others will find out in the course of their lives, that truth eludes us if we do not concentrate our attention totally on it's pursuit. But even while it eludes us, the illusion of knowing it still lingers and leads to many misunderstandings. Also, truth seldom is pleasant; it is almost invariably bitter." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23336-he-suddenly-recalled-from-plato-s-symposium-people-were-hermaphrodites-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:22:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23336-he-suddenly-recalled-from-plato-s-symposium-people-were-hermaphrodites-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He suddenly recalled from Plato's Symposium: People were hermaphrodites until God split then in two, and now all the halves wander the world over seeking one another. Love is the longing for the half of ourselves we have lost." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2008 14:24:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/645-it-is-sometimes-an-appropriate-response-to-reality-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is sometimes an appropriate response to reality to go insane." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
