<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/89152-mar-a-rosa-reyero]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/89152-mar-a-rosa-reyero" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 09:57:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159131-it-s-an-universal-law---intolerance-is-the-first-sign-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 09:57:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[María rosa add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159131-it-s-an-universal-law---intolerance-is-the-first-sign-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's an universal law-- intolerance is the first sign of an inadequate education. An ill-educated person behaves with arrogant impatience, whereas truly profound education breeds humility." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282530-one-day-dostoevsky-threw-out-the-enigmatic-remark-beauty-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 09:58:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[María rosa add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282530-one-day-dostoevsky-threw-out-the-enigmatic-remark-beauty-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day Dostoevsky threw out the enigmatic remark: &quot;Beauty will save the world&quot;. What sort of a statement is that? For a long time I considered it mere words. How could that be possible? When in bloodthirsty history did beauty ever save anyone from anything? Ennobled, uplifted, yes - but whom has it saved?

There is, however, a certain peculiarity in the essence of beauty, a peculiarity in the status of art: namely, the convincingness of a true work of art is completely irrefutable and it forces even an opposing heart to surrender. It is possible to compose an outwardly smooth and elegant political speech, a headstrong article, a social program, or a philosophical system on the basis of both a mistake and a lie. What is hidden, what distorted, will not immediately become obvious.

Then a contradictory speech, article, program, a differently constructed philosophy rallies in opposition - and all just as elegant and smooth, and once again it works. Which is why such things are both trusted and mistrusted.

In vain to reiterate what does not reach the heart.

But a work of art bears within itself its own verification: conceptions which are devised or stretched do not stand being portrayed in images, they all come crashing down, appear sickly and pale, convince no one. But those works of art which have scooped up the truth and presented it to us as a living force - they take hold of us, compel us, and nobody ever, not even in ages to come, will appear to refute them.

So perhaps that ancient trinity of Truth, Goodness and Beauty is not simply an empty, faded formula as we thought in the days of our self-confident, materialistic youth? If the tops of these three trees converge, as the scholars maintained, but the too blatant, too direct stems of Truth and Goodness are crushed, cut down, not allowed through - then perhaps the fantastic, unpredictable, unexpected stems of Beauty will push through and soar &lt;i&gt;to that very same place&lt;/i&gt;, and in so doing will fulfil the work of all three?

In that case Dostoevsky's remark, &quot;Beauty will save the world&quot;, was not a careless phrase but a prophecy? After all &lt;i&gt;he&lt;/i&gt; was granted to see much, a man of fantastic illumination.

And in that case art, literature might really be able to help the world today?" -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86264-our-envy-of-others-devours-us-most-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 09:58:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[María rosa add a quote by Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86264-our-envy-of-others-devours-us-most-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our envy of others devours us most of all." -- Alexander Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95309-gradually-it-was-disclosed-to-me-that-the-line-separating</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 10:06:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[María rosa add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95309-gradually-it-was-disclosed-to-me-that-the-line-separating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gradually it was disclosed to me that the line separating good and evil passes not through states, not between classes, nor between political parties, but through every human heart" -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/762863-when-a-young-person-even-a-gifted-one-grows-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 23:22:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[María rosa add a quote by Sonia Sotormayor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/762863-when-a-young-person-even-a-gifted-one-grows-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a young person, even a gifted one, grows up without proximate living examples of what she may aspire to become--whether lawyer, scientist, artist, or leader in any realm--her goal remains abstract. Such models as appear in books or on the news, however inspiring or revered, are ultimately too remote to be real, let alone influential. But a role model in the flesh provides more than inspiration; his or her very existence is confirmation of possibilities one may have every reason to doubt, saying, 'Yes, someone like me can do this." -- Sonia Sotormayor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
