<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/891931-beck]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/891931-beck" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:36:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7006-why-do-you-want-a-letter-from-me-why-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:36:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7006-why-do-you-want-a-letter-from-me-why-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do you want a letter from me? Why don't you take the trouble to find out for yourselves what Christianity is? You take time to learn technical terms about electricity. Why don't you do as much for theology? Why do you never read the great writings on the subject, but take your information from the secular 'experts' who have picked it up as inaccurately as you? Why don't you learn the facts in this field as honestly as your own field? Why do you accept mildewed old heresies as the language of the church, when any handbook on church history will tell you where they came from?
Why do you balk at the doctrine of the Trinity - God the three in One - yet meekly acquiesce when Einstein tells you E=mc2? What makes you suppose that the expression &quot;God ordains&quot; is narrow and bigoted, while your own expression, &quot;Science demands&quot; is taken as an objective statement of fact?
You would be ashamed to know as little about internal combustion as you know about Christian beliefs.
I admit, you can practice Christianity without knowing much theology, just as you can drive a car without knowing much about internal combustion. But when something breaks down in the car, you go humbly to the man who understands the works; whereas if something goes wrong with religion, you merely throw the works away and tell the theologian he is a liar.
Why do you want a letter from me telling you about God? You will never bother to check on it or find out whether I'm giving you personal opinions or Christian doctrines. Don't bother. Go away and do some work and let me get on with mine." -- Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23619-things-men-have-made-with-wakened-hands-and-put-soft</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:39:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23619-things-men-have-made-with-wakened-hands-and-put-soft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things men have made with wakened hands, and put soft life into
are awake through years with transferred touch, and go on glowing
for long years.
And for this reason, some old things are lovely
warm still with the life of forgotten men who made them." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:46:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23624-i-read-i-say-i-study-and-read-i-bet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read,&quot; I say. &quot;I study and read. I bet I've read everything you read. Don't think I haven't. I consume libraries. I wear out spines and ROM-drives. I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it.&quot; My instincts concerning syntax and mechanics are better than your own, I can tell, with all due respect. But it transcends the mechanics. I'm not a machine. I feel and believe. I have opinions. Some of them are interesting. I could, if you'd let me, talk and talk." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13974-as-my-father-always-used-to-tell-me-you-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:50:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13974-as-my-father-always-used-to-tell-me-you-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As my father always used to tell me, 'You see, son, there's always someone in the world worse off than you.'  And I always used to think, 'So?" -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14045-i-suppose-he-must-have-taken-about-a-nine-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 10:52:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14045-i-suppose-he-must-have-taken-about-a-nine-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose he must have taken about a nine or something in hats. Shows what a rotten thing it is to let your brain develop too much." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 12:55:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My name is Mary Katherine Blackwood. I am eighteen years old, and I live with my sister Constance. I have often thought that with any luck at all, I could have been born a werewolf, because the two middle fingers on both my hands are the same length, but I have had to be content with what I had. I dislike washing myself, and dogs, and noise. I like my sister Constance, and Richard Plantagenet, and Amanita phalloides, the death-cup mushroom. Everyone else in our family is dead." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 13:53:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8776-maybe-we-all-live-life-at-too-high-a-pitch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe we all live life at too high a pitch, those of us who absorb emotional things all day, and as mere consequence we can never feel merely content: we have to be unhappy, or ecstatically, head-over-heels happy, and those states are difficult to achieve within a stable, solid relationship." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 13:54:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17245-quick-name-some-towns-in-new-jersey</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 17:16:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by James Thurber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17245-quick-name-some-towns-in-new-jersey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quick, name some towns in New Jersey" -- James Thurber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12617-i-like-living-i-have-sometimes-been-wildly-despairingly-acutely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 05:10:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Agatha Christi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12617-i-like-living-i-have-sometimes-been-wildly-despairingly-acutely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like living.  I have sometimes been wildly, despairingly, acutely miserable, racked with sorrow; but through it all I still know quite certainly that just to be alive is a grand thing." -- Agatha Christi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12606-i-believe-that-an-author-who-cannot-control-her-characters</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 06:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Margery Allingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12606-i-believe-that-an-author-who-cannot-control-her-characters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that an author who cannot control her characters is, like a mother who cannot control her children, not really fit to look after them." -- Margery Allingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33556-black-bears-rarely-attack-but-here-s-the-thing-sometimes-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 06:35:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33556-black-bears-rarely-attack-but-here-s-the-thing-sometimes-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Black bears rarely attack. But here's the thing. Sometimes they do. All bears are agile, cunning and immensely strong, and they are always hungry. If they want to kill you and eat you, they can, and pretty much whenever they want. That doesn't happen often, but - and here is the absolutely salient point - once would be enough." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2682-sometimes-i-have-loved-the-peacefulness-of-an-ordinary-sunday</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 04:51:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2682-sometimes-i-have-loved-the-peacefulness-of-an-ordinary-sunday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I have loved the peacefulness of an ordinary Sunday. It is like standing in a newly planted garden after a warm rain. You can feel the silent and invisible life." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 04:51:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Beck add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97674-i-m-writing-this-in-part-to-tell-you-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m writing this in part to tell you that if you ever wonder what you’ve done in your life, and everyone does wonder sooner or later, you have been God’s grace to me, a miracle, something more than a miracle. You may not remember me very well at all, and it may seem to you to be no great thing to have been the good child of an old man in a shabby little town you will no doubt leave behind. If only I had the words to tell you." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
