<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/892106-kate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/892106-kate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 12:40:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 12:40:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 12:40:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 22:05:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13907-reputation-is-what-other-people-know-about-you-honor-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reputation is what other people know about you. Honor is what you know about yourself." -- Lois McMaster Bujold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260218-the-only-real-prison-is-fear-and-the-only-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 17:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kate add a quote by Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260218-the-only-real-prison-is-fear-and-the-only-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only real prison is fear, and the only real freedom is freedom from fear" -- Aung San Suu Kyi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
