<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/893669-sabra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/893669-sabra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 21:16:04 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79096-i-was-trying-to-discover-examples-of-a-living-restoration</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2008 21:16:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sabra add a quote by Howard Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79096-i-was-trying-to-discover-examples-of-a-living-restoration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was trying to discover examples of a living restoration, trying to go beyond discussions about correct historic colors, materials, and techniques.  

I looked to the past for guidance, to find the graces we need to save.  I want to be an importer.  This is not nostalgia; I am not nostalgic.   I am not looking for a way back.  &quot;From where will a renewal come to us, to us who have devastated the whole earthly globe?&quot; asked Simone Weil.  &quot;Only from the past if we love it.&quot;

What I am looking for is the trick of having the same ax twice, for a restoration that renews the spirit, for work that transforms the worker.  We may talk of saving antique linens, species, or languages; but whatever we are intent on saving, when a restoration succeeds, we rescue ourselves.

-- Howard Mansfield, The Same Ax Twice:  Restoration and Renewal in a Throwaway Age" -- Howard Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83381-good-preservation-is-a-life-preserver-thrown-to-us-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 20:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sabra add a quote by Howard Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83381-good-preservation-is-a-life-preserver-thrown-to-us-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good preservation is a life preserver thrown to us in a shipwreck.  Good preservation keeps us in touch with the graces of this life.  It's bricks and mortar, yes.  It's arguments about true colors and authenticity and representation.  But true preservation is like the hand that shelters a fire from the wind.  It protects the spark of life.&quot;
  -- Howard Mansfield, The Same Ax, Twice" -- Howard Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
