<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/893686-alisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/893686-alisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 05:13:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191145-the-sadness-of-the-women-s-movement-is-that-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 05:13:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191145-the-sadness-of-the-women-s-movement-is-that-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sadness of the women's movement is that they don't allow the necessity of love. See, I don't personally trust any revolution where love is not allowed." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 07:11:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by bell hooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295254-usually-adult-males-who-are-unable-to-make-emotional-connections]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Usually adult males who are unable to make emotional connections with the women they choose to be intimate with are frozen in time, unable to allow themselves to love for fear that the loved one will abandon them.  If the first woman they passionately loved, the mother, was not true to her bond of love, then how can they trust that their partner will be true to love. Often in their adult relationships these men act out again and again to test their partner's love. While the rejected adolescent boy imagines that he can no longer receive his mother's love because he is not worthy, as a grown man he may act out in ways that are unworthy and yet demand of the woman in his life that she offer him unconditional love. This testing does not heal the wound of the past, it merely reenacts it, for ultimately the woman will become weary of being tested and end the relationship, thus reenacting the abandonment.  This drama confirms for many men that they cannot put their trust in love. They decide that it is better to put their faith in being powerful, in being dominant." -- bell hooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
