<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/894574-david-park]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/894574-david-park" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 10:28:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131739-do-you-really-want-to-be-happy-you-can-begin</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 10:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131739-do-you-really-want-to-be-happy-you-can-begin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you really want to be happy? You can begin by being appreciative of who you are and what you've got." -- Benjamin Hoff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37276-a-man-who-knows-how-little-he-knows-is-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 10:28:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37276-a-man-who-knows-how-little-he-knows-is-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who knows how little he knows is well, a man who knows how much he knows is sick. If, when you see the symptoms, you can tell, Your cure is quick.
A sound man knows that sickness makes him sick and before he catches it his cure is quick." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172764-there-is-a-story-i-would-like-to-tell-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2010 18:05:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172764-there-is-a-story-i-would-like-to-tell-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a story I would like to tell you about a woman who practices the invocation of the Buddha Amitabha's name. She is very tough, and she practices the invocation three times daily, using a wooden drum and a bell, reciting, &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha&quot; for one hour each time. When she arrives at one thousand times, she invites the bell to sound. (In Vietnamese, we don't say &quot;strike&quot; or &quot;hit&quot; a bell.) Although she has been doing this for ten years, her personality has not changed. She is still quite mean, shouting at people all the time.

A friend wanted to teach her a lesson, so one afternoon when she had just lit the incense, invited the bell to sound three times, and was beginning to recite &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha,&quot; he came to her door, and said, &quot;Mrs. Nguyen, Mrs. Nguyen!&quot; She found it very annoying because this was her time of practice, but he just stood at the front gate shouting her name. She said to herself, &quot;I have to struggle against my anger, so I will ignore that,&quot; and she went on, &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha, Namo Amitabha Buddha.&quot;

The gentleman continued to shout her name, and her anger became more and more oppressive. She struggled against it, wondering, &quot;Should I stop my recitation and go and give him a piece of my mind?&quot; But she continued chanting, and she struggled very hard. Fire mounted in her, but she still tried to chant &quot;Namo Amitabha Buddha.&quot; The gentleman knew it, and he continued to shout, &quot;Mrs. Nguyen! Mrs. Nguyen!&quot; 

She could not bear it any longer. She threw away the bell and the drum. She slammed the door, went out to the gate and said, &quot;Why, why do you behave like that? Why do you call my name hundreds of times like that?&quot; The gentleman smiled at her and said, &quot;I just called your name for ten minutes, and you are so angry. You have been calling the Buddha's name for ten years. Think how angry he must be!" -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189542-it-did-what-all-ads-are-supposed-to-do-create</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 11:48:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189542-it-did-what-all-ads-are-supposed-to-do-create]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It did what all ads are supposed to do: create an anxiety relievable by purchase." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416942-men-are-visually-aroused-by-women-s-bodies-and-less-sensitive</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 11:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Naomi Wolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416942-men-are-visually-aroused-by-women-s-bodies-and-less-sensitive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men are visually aroused by women's bodies and less sensitive to their arousal by women's personalities because they are trained early into that response, while women are less visually aroused and more emotionally aroused because that is their training. This asymmetry in sexual education maintains men's power in the myth: They look at women's bodies, evaluate, move on; their own bodies are not looked at, evaluated, and taken or passed over. But there is no &quot;rock called gender&quot; responsible for that; it can change so that real mutuality--an equal gaze, equal vulnerability, equal desire--brings heterosexual men and women together." -- Naomi Wolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417269-men-who-read-it-beauty-pornography-don-t-do-so-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2012 11:50:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Naomi Wolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417269-men-who-read-it-beauty-pornography-don-t-do-so-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men who read it [beauty pornography] don't do so because they want &lt;i&gt;women&lt;/i&gt; who look like that. The attraction of what they are holding is that it is &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; a woman, but a two-dimensional woman-shaped blank. The appeal of the material is not the fantasy that the model will come to life; it is precisely that she will not, ever. Her coming to life would ruin the vision. It is not about life.

Ideal beauty is ideal because it does not exist; The action lies in the gap between desire and gratification. Women are not perfect beauties without distance. That space, in a consumer culture, is a lucrative one. The beauty myth moves for men as a mirage, its power lies in its ever-receding nature. When the gap is closed, the lover embraces only his own disillusion." -- Naomi Wolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190746-bad-people-a-man-told-me-once-that-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 13:14:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert Bly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190746-bad-people-a-man-told-me-once-that-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["BAD PEOPLE
A man told me once that all the bad people
Were needed. Maybe not all, but your fingernails
You need; they are really claws, and we know
Claws. The sharks—what about them?
They make other fish swim faster. The hard-faced men
In black coats who chase you for hours
In dreams—that’s the only way to get you
To the shore. Sometimes those hard women
Who abandon you get you to say, “You.”
A lazy part of us is like a tumbleweed.
It doesn’t move on its own. Sometimes it takes
A lot of Depression to get tumbleweeds moving.
Then they blow across three or four States.
This man told me that things work together.
Bad handwriting sometimes leads to new ideas;
And a careless god—who refuses to let people
Eat from the Tree of Knowledge—can lead
To books, and eventually to us. We write
Poems with lies in them, but they help a little." -- Robert Bly]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220354-i-am-proud-only-of-those-days-that-pass-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 13:43:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[David add a quote by Robert Bly]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220354-i-am-proud-only-of-those-days-that-pass-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am proud only of those days that pass in
undivided tenderness." -- Robert Bly]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
