<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/89519-ab]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/89519-ab" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 02:49:56 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2838-a-writer-is-someone-for-whom-writing-is-more-difficult</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 02:49:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Thomas Mann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2838-a-writer-is-someone-for-whom-writing-is-more-difficult]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A writer is someone for whom writing is more difficult than it is for other people." -- Thomas Mann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 02:49:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18719-the-truth-will-set-you-free-but-not-until-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth will set you free. But not until it is finished with you." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101777-chair-or-no-chair-a-binary-relation-but-the-vicissitudes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 02:49:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Sarah Manguso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101777-chair-or-no-chair-a-binary-relation-but-the-vicissitudes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chair or no chair: a binary relation. But the vicissitudes of moving the body around are infinite. You never know what a person in a chair can do." -- Sarah Manguso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236752-suicide-is-after-all-the-opposite-of-the-poem</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 03:08:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236752-suicide-is-after-all-the-opposite-of-the-poem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suicide is, after all, the opposite of the poem." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236753-intimacy-says-the-phenomenologist-gaston-bachelard-is-the-highest-value</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 03:11:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Mark Doty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236753-intimacy-says-the-phenomenologist-gaston-bachelard-is-the-highest-value]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Intimacy, says the phenomenologist Gaston Bachelard, is the highest value. I resist this statement at first. What about artistic achievement, or moral courage, or heroism, or altruistic acts, or work in the cause of social change? What about wealth or accomplishment? And yet something about it rings true, finally—that what we want is to be brought into relationship, to be inside, within. Perhaps it’s true that nothing matters more to us than that." -- Mark Doty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236754-what-saves-a-man-is-to-take-a-step-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 03:15:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236754-what-saves-a-man-is-to-take-a-step-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What saves a man is to take a step. Then another step. It is always the same step, but you have to take it." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236756-if-you-have-any-young-friends-who-aspire-to-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 03:21:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236756-if-you-have-any-young-friends-who-aspire-to-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have any young friends who aspire to become writers, the second greatest favor you can do them is to present them with copies of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/33514.The_Elements_of_Style&quot;&gt;The Elements of Style&lt;/a&gt;. The first greatest, of course, is to shoot them now, while they’re happy." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237465-nowadays-an-artist-is-someone-who-makes-art-mean-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 13:29:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237465-nowadays-an-artist-is-someone-who-makes-art-mean-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nowadays, an artist is someone who makes art mean the things he does." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237467-you-are-an-over-excited-little-man-with-a-need-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2010 13:30:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Tom Stoppard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237467-you-are-an-over-excited-little-man-with-a-need-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are an over-excited little man, with a need for self-expression far beyond the scope of your natural gifts. This is not discreditable. Neither does it make you an artist." -- Tom Stoppard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 22:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by carson mccullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30407-first-of-all-love-is-a-joint-experience-between-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First of all, love is a joint experience between two persons — but the fact that it is a joint experience does not mean that it is a similar experience to the two people involved. There are the lover and the beloved, but these two come from different countries. Often the beloved is only a stimulus for all the stored-up love which had lain quiet within the lover for a long time hitherto. And somehow every lover knows this. He feels in his soul that his love is a solitary thing. He comes to know a new, strange loneliness and it is this knowledge which makes him suffer. So there is only one thing for the lover to do. He must house his love within himself as best he can; he must create for himself a whole new inward world — a world intense and strange, complete in himself. Let it be added here that this lover about whom we speak need not necessarily be a young man saving for a wedding ring — this lover can be man, woman, child, or indeed any human creature on this earth.

Now, the beloved can also be of any description. The most outlandish people can be the stimulus for love. A man may be a doddering great-grandfather and still love only a strange girl he saw in the streets of Cheehaw one afternoon two decades past. The preacher may love a fallen woman. The beloved may be treacherous, greasy-headed, and given to evil habits. Yes, and the lover may see this as clearly as anyone else — but that does not affect the evolution of his love one whit. A most mediocre person can be the object of a love which is wild, extravagant, and beautiful as the poison lilies of the swamp. A good man may be the stimulus for a love both violent and debased, or a jabbering madman may bring about in the soul of someone a tender and simple idyll. Therefore, the value and quality of any love is determined solely by the lover himself.

It is for this reason that most of us would rather love than be loved. Almost everyone wants to be the lover. And the curt truth is that, in a deep secret way, the state of being beloved is intolerable to many. The beloved fears and hates the lover, and with the best of reasons. For the lover is forever trying to strip bare his beloved. The lover craves any possible relation with the beloved, even if this experience can cause him only pain." -- carson mccullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244078-i-recall-an-august-afternoon-in-chicago-in-1973-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2010 00:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244078-i-recall-an-august-afternoon-in-chicago-in-1973-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I recall an August afternoon in Chicago in 1973 when I took my daughter, then seven, to see what Georgia O’Keeffe had done with where she had been. One of the vast O’Keeffe ‘Sky Above Clouds’ canvases floated over the back stairs in the Chicago Art Institute that day, dominating what seemed to be several stories of empty light, and my daughter looked at it once, ran to the landing, and kept on looking. &quot;Who drew it,&quot; she whispered after a while. I told her. &quot;I need to talk to her,&quot; she said finally." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18070-it-takes-a-lot-of-time-to-be-a-genius</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 00:53:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Gertrude Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18070-it-takes-a-lot-of-time-to-be-a-genius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a lot of time to be a genius. You have to sit around so much, doing nothing, really doing nothing." -- Gertrude Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245596-fate-intervened-some-of-us-that-day-she-led-inexorably</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2010 01:07:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245596-fate-intervened-some-of-us-that-day-she-led-inexorably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fate intervened. Some of us, that day, she led inexorably through the gates of death. Some of us, innocent and unsuspecting, took, unwillingly, that one last step to oblivion. Some of us took very little sugar." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246064-ach-tchekov-why-are-you-dead-why-can-t-i-talk</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 22:00:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246064-ach-tchekov-why-are-you-dead-why-can-t-i-talk]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ach, Tchekov! Why are you dead? Why can’t I talk to you in a big darkish room at late evening—where the light is green from the waving trees outside? I’d like to write a series of Heavens: that would be one." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33296-more-tears-are-shed-over-answered-prayers-than-unanswered-ones</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 22:10:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33296-more-tears-are-shed-over-answered-prayers-than-unanswered-ones]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["More tears are shed over answered prayers than unanswered ones." -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246090-em-forster-never-gets-any-further-than-warming-the-tea</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 02:59:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/246090-em-forster-never-gets-any-further-than-warming-the-tea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["EM Forster never gets any further than warming the tea pot... Is it not beautifully warm? Yes, but there ain't going to be no tea." -- Katherine Mansfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248862-those-who-have-suffered-much-become-very-bitter-or-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 00:08:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Will Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248862-those-who-have-suffered-much-become-very-bitter-or-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who have suffered much become very bitter or very gentle." -- Will Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250515-i-think-you-can-only-make-statements-like-she-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 22:03:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Jacqueline Rose]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250515-i-think-you-can-only-make-statements-like-she-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think you can only make statements like ‘She was pathological’ if you are absolutely sure of your own sanity, which I consider a morally unacceptable position." -- Jacqueline Rose]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251438-raise-high-the-roof-beam-carpenters-like-ares-comes-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 00:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Sappho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251438-raise-high-the-roof-beam-carpenters-like-ares-comes-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Raise high the roof beam, carpenters. Like Ares comes the bridegroom, taller far than a tall man." -- Sappho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221129-she-worries-over-the-way-her-love-for-me-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 03:15:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221129-she-worries-over-the-way-her-love-for-me-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She worries over the way her love for me comes and goes, appears and disappears.  She doubts its reality simply because it isn't as steadily pleasurable as a kitten.  God knows it is sad.  The human voice conspires to desecrate everything on earth." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181748-seymour-once-said-that-all-we-do-our-whole-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2010 03:15:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181748-seymour-once-said-that-all-we-do-our-whole-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seymour once said that all we do our whole lives is go from one little piece of Holy Ground to the next. Is he ever wrong?" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257800-don-t-be-very-frightened-marilla-i-was-walking-the-ridge-pole</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 04:04:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257800-don-t-be-very-frightened-marilla-i-was-walking-the-ridge-pole]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be very frightened, Marilla. I was walking the ridge-pole and I fell off. I suspect I have sprained my ankle. But, Marilla, I might have broken my neck. Let us look on the bright side of things." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257801-and-then-came-months-of-memories-connected-to-nothing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 04:08:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257801-and-then-came-months-of-memories-connected-to-nothing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And then came months of memories connected to nothing and telling me nothing, and in this ambiguous atmosphere I stopped thinking of him as doomed. The memories themselves were generally pleasant. For at least a week I kept reliving the time he removed a splinter from my foot using surgical tweezers. Strangely, during this same week, a black Labrador retriever was accompanying me around town, appearing out of nowhere and trotting alongside me to the subway or or the grocery store. As with the splinter memory, I had a sense of information being conveyed but through a medium too opaque to be grasped." -- Barbara Gowdy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257802-venture-too-far-for-love-she-tells-herself-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 04:11:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Michael Cunningham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257802-venture-too-far-for-love-she-tells-herself-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Venture too far for love, she tells herself, and you renounce citizenship in the country you've made for yourself." -- Michael Cunningham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131352-every-book-is-the-wreck-of-a-perfect-idea</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 21:52:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Iris Murdoch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131352-every-book-is-the-wreck-of-a-perfect-idea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every book is the wreck of a perfect idea." -- Iris Murdoch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2358-i-had-a-book-of-bible-stories-when-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 01:25:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Tony Kushner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2358-i-had-a-book-of-bible-stories-when-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had a book of Bible stories when I was a kid. There was a picture I'd look at twenty times every day: Jacob wrestles with the angel. I don't really remember the story, or why the wrestling --just the picture. Jacob is young and very strong. The angel is...a beautiful man, with golden hair and wings, of course. I still dream about it. Many nights. I'm...It's me. In that struggle. Fierce, and unfair. The angel is not human, and it holds nothing back, so how could anyone human win, what kind of a fight is that? It's not just. Losing means your soul thrown down in the dust, your heart torn out from God's. But you can't not lose." -- Tony Kushner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260072-i-m-not-interested-in-writing-short-stories-anything-that-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 02:53:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260072-i-m-not-interested-in-writing-short-stories-anything-that-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m not interested in writing short stories. Anything that doesn’t take years of your life and drive you to suicide hardly seems worth doing." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260080-now-is-a-time-for-dare-i-say-it-kindness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 03:10:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Margaret Edson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260080-now-is-a-time-for-dare-i-say-it-kindness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now is a time for, dare I say it, kindness. I thought being extremely smart would take care of it. But I see I have been found out." -- Margaret Edson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260081-it-s-a-release-to-know-that-in-spite-of-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2010 03:11:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by Henrik Ibsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260081-it-s-a-release-to-know-that-in-spite-of-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a release to know that in spite of everything a premeditated act of courage is still possible." -- Henrik Ibsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262401-you-can-t-argue-with-someone-who-believes-or-just-passionately</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2010 23:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[AB add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262401-you-can-t-argue-with-someone-who-believes-or-just-passionately]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't argue with someone who believes, or just passionately suspects, that the poet's function is not to write what he must write but, rather, to write what he would write if his life depended on his taking responsibility for writing what he must in a style designed to shut out as few of his old librarians as humanly possible." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
