<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/895460-jackie-price]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/895460-jackie-price" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 15:32:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49406-oh-no-he-does-not-he-does-not-read-james</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 15:32:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Shalom Auslander ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49406-oh-no-he-does-not-he-does-not-read-james]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh no he does not!  He does NOT read James Freaking Patterson.  Our salvation - our provider…we must be out of our minds. 
 
I happen to find Patterson thought provoking and suspenseful.
 
You what?  Did you just say you find James Patterson thought provoking and suspenseful?  Jesus Christ open your eyes!  Are you so desperate to believe that you're defending James Patterson?!" -- Shalom Auslander ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75304-is-is-therefore-not-an-exaggeration-to-say-that-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2008 12:58:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jackie add a quote by Sam Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75304-is-is-therefore-not-an-exaggeration-to-say-that-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is is, therefore, not an exaggeration to say that if the city of New York were suddenly replaced by a ball of fire, some significant percentage of the American population would see a silver-lining in the subsequent mushroom cloud, as it would suggest to them that the best thing that is ever going to happen was about to happen: the return of Christ.  It should be blindingly obvious that beliefs of this sort will do little to help us create a durable future for ourselves - socially, economically, environmentally, or geopolitically.  Imagine the consequences if any significant component of the US government actually believed that the world was about to end and that its ending would be glorious.  The fact that nearly half of the American population apparently believes this, purely on the basis of religion dogma, should be considered a moral and intellectual emergency." -- Sam Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
