<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/895690-julie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/895690-julie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 14:04:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753453-i-ve-demonstrated-an-impressive-resilience-in-the-face-of-valuable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 14:04:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Tim Kreider]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/753453-i-ve-demonstrated-an-impressive-resilience-in-the-face-of-valuable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've demonstrated an impressive resilience in the face of valuable life lessons, and the main thing I seem to have learned from this one is that I am capable of learning nothing from almost any experience, no matter how profound." -- Tim Kreider]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194758-perhaps-the-reason-we-so-often-experience-happiness-only-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2013 14:07:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Julie add a quote by Tim Kreider]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194758-perhaps-the-reason-we-so-often-experience-happiness-only-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the reason we so often experience happiness only in hindsight, and that chasing it is such a fool’s errand, is that happiness isn’t a goal in itself but is only an aftereffect. It’s the consequence of having lived in the way that we’re supposed to — by which I don’t mean ethically correctly so much as just consciously, fully engaged in the business of living. In this respect it resembles averted vision, a phenomena familiar to backyard astronomers whereby, in order to pick out a very faint star, you have to let your gaze drift casually to the space just next to it; if you look directly at it, it vanishes. And it’s also true, come to think of it, that the only stars we ever see are not the “real” stars, those cataclysms taking place in the present, but always only the light of the untouchable past." -- Tim Kreider]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
