<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/896080-kerstin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/896080-kerstin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 09:11:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801265-it-s-the-strangest-thing-about-being-human-to-know-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 09:11:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Claire Messud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801265-it-s-the-strangest-thing-about-being-human-to-know-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the strangest thing about being human: to know so much, to communicate so much, and yet always to fall so drastically short of clarity, to be, in the end, so isolate and inadequate.  Even when people try to say things, they say them poorly or obliquely, or they outright lie, sometimes because they're lying to you, but as often because they're lying to themselves." -- Claire Messud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/818825-subtle-and-coy-the-cemento-at-maalouf-s-did-not-speak</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 16:59:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Anthony Shadid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/818825-subtle-and-coy-the-cemento-at-maalouf-s-did-not-speak]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Subtle and coy, the cemento at Maalouf's did not speak of war, or frontiers, and the spaces they narrowed, but, rather, grandeur.  The tiles returned one to a realm where imagination, artistry, and craftsmanship were not only appreciated but given free reign, where what was unique and striking, or small and perfect, or wrought with care was desired, where gazed-upon objects were the products of peaceful hearts, hands long practiced and trained.  War ends the values and traditions that produce such treasures.  Nothing is maintained.  Cultures that may seem as durable as stone can break like glass, leaving all the things that held them together unattended.  I believe that the craftsman, the artist, the cook, and the silversmith are peacemakers.  They instill grace; they lull the world to calm." -- Anthony Shadid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577348-silence-is-an-easy-habit-but-it-doesn-t-come-naturally</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 05:04:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Kristen Iversen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/577348-silence-is-an-easy-habit-but-it-doesn-t-come-naturally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Silence is an easy habit.  But it doesn't come naturally.  Silence has to be cultivated, enforced by implication and innuendo, looks and glances, hints of dark consequence.  Silence is greedy.  It insists upon its own necessity.  It transcends generations." -- Kristen Iversen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316436-and-who-s-to-say-that-just-because-something-lasts-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 15:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Alice Steinbach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/316436-and-who-s-to-say-that-just-because-something-lasts-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And who's to say that just because something lasts only a short time, it has little value?" -- Alice Steinbach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75640-i-perceive-that-i-am-neither-a-planter-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 16:12:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by A. Bronson Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75640-i-perceive-that-i-am-neither-a-planter-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I perceive that I am neither a planter of the backwoods, pioneer, nor settler there, but an inhabitant of the Mind, and given to friendship and ideas.  The ancient society, the Old England of New England, Massachusetts for me." -- A. Bronson Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75765-action-and-blood-now-get-the-game-disdain-treads-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 03:42:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by A. Bronson Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75765-action-and-blood-now-get-the-game-disdain-treads-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Action and blood now get the game.  Disdain treads on the peaceful name." -- A. Bronson Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39800-life-is-a-train-of-moods-like-a-string-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 04:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39800-life-is-a-train-of-moods-like-a-string-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a train of moods like a string of beads; and as we pass through them they prove to be many colored lenses, which paint the world their own hue, and each shows us only what lies in its own focus." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 06:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84300-people-tend-to-think-that-happiness-is-a-stroke-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People tend to think that happiness is a stroke of luck, something that will descend like fine weather if you're fortunate. But happiness is the result of personal effort. You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it. You have to participate relentlessly." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157027-not-that-she-s-a-political-animal-she-s-just-an-ordinary</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 05:36:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Hans Fallada]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157027-not-that-she-s-a-political-animal-she-s-just-an-ordinary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Not that she's a political animal, she's just an ordinary woman, but as a woman she's of the view that you don't bring children into the world to have them shot." -- Hans Fallada]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303083-i-may-have-grown-up-in-the-age-of-aquarius</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2010 03:01:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Roy Peter Clark]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303083-i-may-have-grown-up-in-the-age-of-aquarius]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may have grown up in the Age of Aquarius, but I'm growing old in the Age of the Acronym." -- Roy Peter Clark]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325141-she-always-thought-americans-were-too-territorial-all-those-fences</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2010 04:25:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Dinaw Mengestu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/325141-she-always-thought-americans-were-too-territorial-all-those-fences]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She always thought Americans were too territorial.  'All those fences and flags,' she had once said, seeing very little difference between the two." -- Dinaw Mengestu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328935-in-an-environment-where-there-are-too-many-choices-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 03:13:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Rebecca D. Costa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328935-in-an-environment-where-there-are-too-many-choices-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In an environment where there are too many choices, too many decisions, too much information, and too many demands on our cognition, it pays to be judicious about the complexity we voluntarily sign up for.  When we make the decision to streamline our lives, we also create time and room to think with focus and intent.  In a complex world, time to stand back and look at the big picture, time to consider our options more carefully, time to make more deliberate decisions, and time to breathe are necessities for survival." -- Rebecca D. Costa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33229-critics-are-like-eunuchs-in-a-harem-they-know-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 04:05:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Brendan Behan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33229-critics-are-like-eunuchs-in-a-harem-they-know-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics are like eunuchs in a harem; they know how it's done, they've seen it done every day, but they're unable to do it themselves." -- Brendan Behan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17802-where-they-have-burned-books-they-will-end-in-burning</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 04:06:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Heinrich Heine ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17802-where-they-have-burned-books-they-will-end-in-burning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where they have burned books, they will end in burning human beings." -- Heinrich Heine ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403261-maybe-crazy-is-just-the-word-we-use-for-feelings</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 17:18:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403261-maybe-crazy-is-just-the-word-we-use-for-feelings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe crazy is just the word we use for feelings that will not be contained." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397115-here-is-one-of-the-worst-things-about-having-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 17:19:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397115-here-is-one-of-the-worst-things-about-having-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here is one of the worst things about having someone you love die: It happens again every single morning." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482477-and-yet-sometimes-she-worried-about-what-those-musty-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 16:16:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides, The Marriage Plot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/482477-and-yet-sometimes-she-worried-about-what-those-musty-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet sometimes she worried about what those musty old books were doing to her.  Some people majored in English to prepare for law school.  Others became journalists.  The smartest guy in the honors program, Adam Vogel, a child of academics, was planning on getting a Ph.D. and becoming an academic himself.  That left a large contingent of people majoring in English by default.  Because they weren't left-brained enough for science, because history was too dry, philosophy too difficult, geology too petroleum-oriented, and math too mathematical--because they weren't musical, artistic, financially motivated, or really all that smart, these people were pursuing university degrees doing something no different from what they'd done in first grade:  reading stories.  English was what people who didn't know what to major in majored in." -- Jeffrey Eugenides, The Marriage Plot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207745-there-are-lots-of-women-who-are-attracted-to-tyrannical</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 16:16:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Amos Oz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207745-there-are-lots-of-women-who-are-attracted-to-tyrannical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are lots of women who are attracted to tyrannical men.  Like moths to a flame.  And there are some women who do not need a hero or even a stormy lover but a friend.  Just remember that when you grow up.  Steer clear of the tryant lovers, and try to locate the ones who are looking for a man as a friend, not because they are feeling empty themselves but because they enjoy making you full too.  And remember that friendship between a woman and a man is something much more precious and rare than love: love is actually something quite gross and even clumsy compared to friendship.  Friendship includes a measure of sensitivity, attentiveness, generosity, and a finely tuned sense of moderation." -- Amos Oz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488740-being-an-adult-it-seemed-was-horrible-but-being-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 04:26:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Alison Espach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488740-being-an-adult-it-seemed-was-horrible-but-being-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being an adult, it seemed, was horrible.  But being a child was awful too, and moving from one state to the other only meant you were moving closer to death, with so much and so little to talk about all at the same time, and how was that even possible?" -- Alison Espach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491219-the-real-act-of-will-was-not-in-the-creating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 05:34:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Amy Waldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/491219-the-real-act-of-will-was-not-in-the-creating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real act of will was not in the creating of a garden but in the sustaining, the continuous stand against wildness." -- Amy Waldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488743-even-through-all-of-this-sometimes-i-wanted-to-lift</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 04:36:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by Alison Espach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/488743-even-through-all-of-this-sometimes-i-wanted-to-lift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even through all of this, sometimes I wanted to lift up her chin and say, &quot;Don't you see that is your dog?&quot;  Don't you see how we didn't want to have to love you, Laura?  Don't you see how you have to love things forever anyway, no matter if it shakes, or drools, or barks in the middle of the night, or throws up food, or dies, because even in death, he is still your dog?  You picked him out of a group and said, that is my dog, and the dog you picked shakes and drools and barks in the middle of the night, but you named him.  And for that reason you should never want to give him up, you should always be grateful since your dog is one of the few things in life that you actually can choose as your own." -- Alison Espach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366138-we-have-just-enough-religion-to-make-us-hate-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 16:47:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kerstin add a quote by David Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366138-we-have-just-enough-religion-to-make-us-hate-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have just enough religion to make us hate, but not enough to make us love." -- David Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
