<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/896470-james-alvino]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/896470-james-alvino" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 08:18:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53247-men-will-never-be-free-until-the-last-king-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 08:18:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Denis Diderot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53247-men-will-never-be-free-until-the-last-king-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men will never be free until the last king is strangled with the entrails of the last priest." -- Denis Diderot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19967-of-all-tyrannies-a-tyranny-sincerely-exercised-for-the-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:30:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19967-of-all-tyrannies-a-tyranny-sincerely-exercised-for-the-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all tyrannies, a tyranny sincerely exercised for the good of its victims may be the most oppressive. It would be better to live under robber barons than under omnipotent moral busybodies. The robber baron's cruelty may sometimes sleep, his cupidity may at some point be satiated; but those who torment us for our own good will torment us without end for they do so with the approval of their own conscience." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11649-the-america-of-my-time-line-is-a-laboratory-example</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 10:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11649-the-america-of-my-time-line-is-a-laboratory-example]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The America of my time line is a laboratory example of what can happen to democracies, what has eventually happened to all perfect democracies throughout all histories.  A perfect democracy, a ‘warm body’ democracy in which every adult may vote and all votes count equally, has no internal feedback for self-correction.  It depends solely on the wisdom and self-restraint of citizens… which is opposed by the folly and lack of self-restraint of other citizens.  What is supposed to happen in a democracy is that each sovereign citizen will always vote in the public interest for the safety and welfare of all.  But what does happen is that he votes his own self-interest as he sees it… which for the majority translates as ‘Bread and Circuses.’

‘Bread and Circuses’ is the cancer of democracy, the fatal disease for which there is no cure.  Democracy often works beautifully at first.  But once a state extends the franchise to every warm body, be he producer or parasite, that day marks the beginning of the end of the state.  For when the plebs discover that they can vote themselves bread and circuses without limit and that the productive members of the body politic cannot stop them, they will do so, until the state bleeds to death, or in its weakened condition the state succumbs to an invader—the barbarians enter Rome." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89101-those-who-make-peaceful-revolution-impossible-will-make-violent-revolution</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 13:52:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by John F. Kennedy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/89101-those-who-make-peaceful-revolution-impossible-will-make-violent-revolution]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who make peaceful revolution impossible will make violent revolution inevitable.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Remarks on the first anniversary of the Alliance for Progress&lt;/i&gt;, 13 March 1962]" -- John F. Kennedy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22425-the-american-republic-will-endure-until-the-day-congress-discovers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 12:55:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22425-the-american-republic-will-endure-until-the-day-congress-discovers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The American Republic will endure until the day Congress discovers that it can bribe the public with the public's money." -- Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 12:32:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26079-i-sincerely-believe-that-banking-establishments-are-more-dangerous-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 12:40:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26079-i-sincerely-believe-that-banking-establishments-are-more-dangerous-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sincerely believe that banking establishments are more dangerous than standing armies, and that the principle of spending money to be paid by posterity, under the name of funding, is but swindling futurity on a large scale." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
