<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/897073-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/897073-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:01:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28243-his-omnipotence-means-power-to-do-all-that-is-intrinsically</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:01:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28243-his-omnipotence-means-power-to-do-all-that-is-intrinsically]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["His Omnipotence means power to do all that is intrinsically possible, not to do the intrinsically impossible. You may attribute miracles to Him, but not nonsense. There is no limit to His power.

If you choose to say, 'God can give a creature free will and at the same time withhold free will from it,' you have not succeeded in saying anything about God: meaningless combinations of words do not suddenly acquire meaning simply because we prifex to them the two other words, 'God can.'

It remains true that all things are possible with God: the intrinsic impossibilities are not things but nonentities. It is no more possible for God than for the weakest of His creatures to carry out both of two mutually exclusive alternatives; not because His power meets an obstacle, but because nonsense remains nonsense even when we talk it about God." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28246-the-road-to-the-promised-land-runs-past-sinai-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:03:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28246-the-road-to-the-promised-land-runs-past-sinai-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The road to the promised land runs past Sinai. The moral law may exist to be transcended: but there is no transcending it for those who have not first admitted its claims up on them, and then tried with all their strength to meet that claim, and fairly and squarely faced the fact of their failure." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28247-the-human-spirit-will-not-even-begin-to-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:03:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28247-the-human-spirit-will-not-even-begin-to-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The human spirit will not even begin to try to surrender self-will as long as all seems to be well with it. Now error and sin both have this property, that the deeper they are the less their victim suspects their existence; they are masked evil. Pain is unmasked, unmistakable evil; every man knows that something is wrong when he is being hurt." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28249-nor-am-i-greatly-moved-by-jocular-inquiries-such-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28249-nor-am-i-greatly-moved-by-jocular-inquiries-such-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor am I greatly moved by jocular inquiries such as, 'Where will you put all the mosquitoes?' -- a question to be answered on its own level by pointing out that, if the worst came to worst, a heaven for mosquitoes and a hell for men could very conveniently be combined." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28252-the-mold-in-which-a-key-is-made-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:08:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28252-the-mold-in-which-a-key-is-made-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mold in which a key is made would be a strange thing, if you had never seen a key: and the key itself a strange thing if you had never seen a lock.  Your soul has a curious shape because it is a hollow made to fit a particular swelling in the infinite contours of the divine substance, or a key to unlock one of the doors in the house with many mansions.

Your place in heaven will seem to be made for you and you alone, because you were made for it -- made for it stitch by stitch as a glove is made for a hand." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28253-my-own-idea-for-what-it-is-worth-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2008 14:13:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28253-my-own-idea-for-what-it-is-worth-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My own idea, for what it is worth, is that all sadness which is not either arising from the repentance of a concrete sin and hastening towards concrete amendment or restitution, or else arising from pity and hastening to active assistance, is simply bad;  and I think we all sin by needlessly disobeying the apostolic injunction to 'rejoice' as much as by anything else.

Humility, after the first shock, is a cheerful virtue." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 13:34:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life. 
&quot; Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget, that until the day God will deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is contained in these two words, 'Wait and Hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31207-imagine-how-our-own-families-let-alone-the-world-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:08:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31207-imagine-how-our-own-families-let-alone-the-world-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine how our own families, let alone the world, would change if we vowed to keep faith with one another, strengthen one another, look for and accentuate the virtues in one another, and speak graciously concerning one another.  Imagine the cumulative effect if we treated each other with respect and acceptance, if we willingly provided support.  Such interactions practiced on a small scale would surely have a rippling effect throughout our homes and communities and, eventually, society at large." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31208-the-best-antidote-i-know-for-worry-is-work-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 10:10:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31208-the-best-antidote-i-know-for-worry-is-work-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best antidote I know for worry is work.  The best cure for weariness is the challenge of helping someone who is even more tired.  One of the great ironies of life is this: He or she who serves almost always benefits more than he or she who is served." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 21:36:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I declare after all there is no enjoyment like reading! How much sooner one tires of any thing than of a book! -- When I have a house of my own, I shall be miserable if I have not an excellent library." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32236-wild-roses-are-fairest-and-nature-a-better-gardener-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 21:40:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32236-wild-roses-are-fairest-and-nature-a-better-gardener-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wild roses are fairest, and nature a better gardener than art." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19092-i-am-not-afraid-of-storms-for-i-am-learning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 21:42:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19092-i-am-not-afraid-of-storms-for-i-am-learning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not afraid of storms, for I am learning how to sail my ship." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30786-child-child-do-you-not-see-for-each-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 21:43:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30786-child-child-do-you-not-see-for-each-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Child, child, do you not see?  For each of us comes a time when we must be more than what we are." -- Lloyd Alexander]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:20:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33329-the-willingness-to-forgive-is-a-sign-of-spiritual-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The willingness to forgive is a sign of spiritual and emotional maturity.  It is one of the great virtues to which we all should aspire.  Imagine a world filled with individuals willing both to apologize and to accept an apology.  Is there any problem that could not be solved among people who possessed the humility and largeness of spirit and soul to do either -- or both -- when needed?" -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33342-there-is-no-more-compelling-motivation-to-worthwhile-endeavor-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:30:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33342-there-is-no-more-compelling-motivation-to-worthwhile-endeavor-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no more compelling motivation to worthwhile endeavor than the knowledge that we are children of God, that God expects us to do something with our lives, and that He will give us help when help is sought." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33346-let-us-never-forget-to-pray-god-lives-he-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:32:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33346-let-us-never-forget-to-pray-god-lives-he-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us never forget to pray.  God lives.  He is near.  He is real.  He is not only aware of us but cares for us.  He is our Father.  He is accessible to all who will seek Him." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33351-the-remedy-for-most-marital-stress-is-not-in-divorce</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33351-the-remedy-for-most-marital-stress-is-not-in-divorce]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The remedy for most marital stress is not in divorce.  It is in repentance and forgiveness, in sincere expressions of charity and service.  It is not in separation.  It is in simple integrity that leads a man and a woman to square up their shoulders and meet their obligations.  It is found in the Golden Rule, a time-honored principle that should first and foremost find expression in marriage." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33353-if-we-are-worried-about-the-future-then-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 11:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33353-if-we-are-worried-about-the-future-then-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we are worried about the future, then we must look today at the upbringing of children." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34012-if-you-re-trying-to-be-miserable-it-s-important-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2008 09:08:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Bytheway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34012-if-you-re-trying-to-be-miserable-it-s-important-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're trying to be miserable, it's important you don't have any goals.  No school goals, personal goals, family goals.  Your only objective each day should be to inhale and exhale for sixteen hours before you go to bed again.  Don't read anything informative, don't listen to anything useful, don't do anything productive.  If you start achieving goals, you might start to feel a sense of excitement, then you might want to set another goal, and then your miserable mornings are through.  To maintain your misery, the idea of crossing off your goals should never cross your mind." -- John Bytheway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35572-if-our-testimonies-are-strong-onthis-point-and-if-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 09:58:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Bytheway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35572-if-our-testimonies-are-strong-onthis-point-and-if-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If our testimonies are strong onthis point and if we feel the absolute assurance that God loves us, we will change our questons.  We won't ask, 'Why did this happen?' or 'Why doesn't God care about me?'  Instead, our questions will become, 'What can I learn from this experience?' or 'How does the Lord want me to handle this?" -- John Bytheway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35573-if-someone-were-to-ask-whether-communications-skills-or-meekness</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 10:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Bytheway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35573-if-someone-were-to-ask-whether-communications-skills-or-meekness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If someone were to ask whether communications skills or meekness is most important to a marriage, I'd answer meekness, hands down.  You can be a superb communicator but still never have the humility to ask, 'Is it I?'  Communication skills are no substitute for Christlike attributes.  As Dr. Douglas Brinley has observed, 'Without theological perspectives, secular exercises designed to improve our relationship and our communication skills (the common tools of counselors and marriage books) will never work any permanent change in one's heart: they simply develop more clever and skilled fighters!" -- John Bytheway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36556-everyone-would-like-to-have-stronger-faith-by-themselves-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2008 07:52:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by John Bytheway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36556-everyone-would-like-to-have-stronger-faith-by-themselves-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone would like to have stronger faith.  By themselves, the scriptures may not strengthen your faith, but being faithful to what they teach, does.  In other words, faith cannot be separated from faithfulness." -- John Bytheway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40099-to-have-faith-in-christ-means-of-course-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 12:20:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40099-to-have-faith-in-christ-means-of-course-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[To have Faith in Christ] means, of course, trying to do all that He says.  There would be no sense in saying you trusted a person if you would not take his advice. Thus if you have really handed yourself over to Him, it must follow that you are trying to obey Him. But trying in a new way, a less worried way. Not doing these things in order to be saved, but because He has begun to save you already. Not hoping to get to Heaven as a reward for your actions, but inevitably wanting to act in a certain way because a first faint gleam of Heaven is already inside you." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 12:29:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6979-i-am-trying-here-to-prevent-anyone-saying-the-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am trying here to prevent anyone saying the really foolish thing that people often say about Him: I’m ready to accept Jesus as a great moral teacher, but I don’t accept his claim to be God. That is the one thing we must not say. A man who was merely a man and said the sort of things Jesus said would not be a great moral teacher. He would either be a lunatic — on the level with the man who says he is a poached egg — or else he would be the Devil of Hell. You must make your choice. Either this man was, and is, the Son of God, or else a madman or something worse. You can shut him up for a fool, you can spit at him and kill him as a demon or you can fall at his feet and call him Lord and God, but let us not come with any patronizing nonsense about his being a great human teacher. He has not left that open to us. He did not intend to." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40898-this-however-is-sure-nothing-is-really-lost-any-influence</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 12:28:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Horace Annesley Vachell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40898-this-however-is-sure-nothing-is-really-lost-any-influence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This, however, is sure: nothing is really lost.  Any influence for good, no matter how ephemeral, makes its mark: it helps to leaven the loaf of evil: it leaves a loophole, albeit a small one, for a future escape from bondage." -- Horace Annesley Vachell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40970-i-have-been-crying-she-replied-simply-and-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:50:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Horace Annesley Vachell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40970-i-have-been-crying-she-replied-simply-and-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have been crying,&quot; she replied, simply, &quot;and it has done me good.  It helps a woman you know, just as swearing helps a man." -- Horace Annesley Vachell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3312-women-and-cats-will-do-as-they-please-and-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women and cats will do as they please, and men and dogs should relax and get used to the idea." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62370-these-tales-without-exception-express-the-truth-that-justice-triumphs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 11:46:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gyula Illyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62370-these-tales-without-exception-express-the-truth-that-justice-triumphs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These tales, without exception, express the truth that justice triumphs in the end. They all contain the idea that it is worth while to fight for the truth, in any situation.
In this fight man is assisted by more powerful beings than ordinary mortals. And the triumph of justice is the only sense and consolation in this world. Indeed, the world itself started out with this hope. The human race received it long, long ago as a cradle-song." -- Gyula Illyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62374-the-life-of-the-hero-of-the-tale-is-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 11:50:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gyula Illyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62374-the-life-of-the-hero-of-the-tale-is-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The life of the hero of the tale is, at the outset, overshadowed by bitter and hopeless struggles; one doubts that the little swineherd will ever be able to vanquish the awful Dragon with the twelve heads.  And yet, ...truth and courage prevail and the youngest and most neglected son of the family, of the nation, of mankind, chops off all twelve heads of the Dragon, to the delight of our anxious hearts.  This exultant victory, towards which the hero of the tale always strives, is the hope and trust of the peasantry and of all oppressed peoples.  This hope helps them bear the burden of their destiny." -- Gyula Illyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62376-there-is-a-folk-tale-about-a-shoemaker-and-his-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2008 11:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Gyula Illyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62376-there-is-a-folk-tale-about-a-shoemaker-and-his-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a folk-tale about a shoemaker and his wife who were so poor that they had to send their many children out into the world to make a living.  The lads went through many a perilous adventure but came home in the end, unscathed, to help their mother.  They had always remembered their mother's advice and wise words; they often quoted them when they were in trouble, and in fact they recognized one another by them in foreign lands.
The countless peoples of the world may be looked upon as so many children sent out into the world.  They have gone through many adventures and hardships.  They have drifted apart and fallen out with one another, on many occasions.  They have failed to realize soon enough that they are brothers.
But now it seems that they are beginning to realize this -- at least to the extent that they are able to get acquainted with each other's fundamental natures -- through their stories and songs." -- Gyula Illyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
