<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/897030-louis]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/897030-louis" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:30:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17501-if-ye-love-wealth-better-than-liberty-the-tranquility-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:30:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Samuel Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17501-if-ye-love-wealth-better-than-liberty-the-tranquility-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ye love wealth better than liberty, the tranquility of servitude better than the animating contest of freedom, go home from us in peace. We ask not your counsels or arms. Crouch down and lick the hands which feed you. May your chains set lightly upon you, and may posterity forget that ye were our countrymen." -- Samuel Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23891-i-apprehend-no-danger-to-our-country-from-a-foreign</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:32:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Daniel Webster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23891-i-apprehend-no-danger-to-our-country-from-a-foreign]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I apprehend no danger to our country from a foreign foe. Our destruction, should it come at all, will be from another quarter. From the inattention of the people to the concerns of their government, from their carelessness and negligence, I must confess that I do apprehend some danger. I fear that they may place too implicit a confidence in their public servants, and fail properly to scrutinize their conduct; that in this way they may be made the dupes of designing men, and become the instruments of their own undoing. Make them intelligent, and they will be vigilant; give them the means of detecting the wrong, and they will apply the remedy." -- Daniel Webster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23892-i-am-for-doing-good-to-the-poor-but-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:33:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23892-i-am-for-doing-good-to-the-poor-but-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am for doing good to the poor, but...I think the best way of doing good to the poor, is not making them easy in poverty, but leading or driving them out of it. I observed...that the more public provisions were made for the poor, the less they provided for themselves, and of course became poorer. And, on the contrary, the less was done for them, the more they did for themselves, and became richer." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23893-the-powers-delegated-by-the-proposed-constitution-to-the-federal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:34:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23893-the-powers-delegated-by-the-proposed-constitution-to-the-federal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The powers delegated by the proposed Constitution to the federal government are few and defined. Those which are to remain in the State governments are numerous and indefinite. The former will be exercised principally on external objects, as war, peace, negotiation and foreign commerce. ... The powers reserved to the several States will extend to all the objects which in the ordinary course of affairs, concern the lives and liberties, and properties of the people, and the internal order, improvement and prosperity of the State." -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23894-democracy-must-be-something-more-than-two-wolves-and-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2008 09:36:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Louis add a quote by James Bovard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23894-democracy-must-be-something-more-than-two-wolves-and-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Democracy must be something more than two wolves and a sheep voting on what to have for dinner." -- James Bovard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
