<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898098-jeremy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898098-jeremy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:18:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:18:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day we slaughter our finest impulses. That is why we get a heartache when we read those lines written by the hand of a master and recognize them as our own, as the tender shoots which we stifled because we lacked the faith to believe in our own powers, our own criterion of truth and beauty. Every man, when he gets quiet, when he becomes desperately honest with himself, is capable of uttering profound truths. We all derive from the same source. there is no mystery about the origin of things. We are all part of creation, all kings, all poets, all musicians; we have only to open up, only to discover what is already there." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8321-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a-fellow-s-character-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:24:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Ronald Reagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8321-you-can-tell-a-lot-about-a-fellow-s-character-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can tell a lot about a fellow's character by his way of eating jellybeans. " -- Ronald Reagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 11:25:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395-a-world-of-if-s-but-it-would-make-no-difference</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2008 20:29:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeremy add a quote by Darren Shan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/395-a-world-of-if-s-but-it-would-make-no-difference]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A world of &quot;if&quot;s, but it would make no difference. If I could go back in time... but I couldn't. The past was behind me. The best thing now would be to stop looking over my shoulder. It was time to forget the past and look to the present and future." -- Darren Shan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
