<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898937-allie-taylor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898937-allie-taylor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 19:48:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517231-sometimes-you-want-to-say-i-love-you-but-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 19:48:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Jamie Weise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517231-sometimes-you-want-to-say-i-love-you-but-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you want to say, “I love you, but…”
Yet the “but” takes away the ‘I love you’. In love their are no ‘buts’ or ‘if’s’ or ‘when’. It’s just there, and always. No beginning, no end. It’s the condition-less state of the heart. Not a feeling that comes and goes at the whim of the emotions. It is there in our heart, a part of our heart…eventually grafting itself into each limb and cell of our bodies. Love changes our brain, the way we move and talk. Love lives in our spirit and graces us with its presence each day, until death.

To say “I love you, but….” is to say, “I did not love you at all”.

I say this to you now: I love you, with no beginning, no end. I love you as you have become an extra necessary organ in my body. I love you as only a girl could love a boy. Without fear. Without expectations. Wanting nothing in return, except that you allow me to keep you here in my heart, that I may always know your strength, your eyes, and your spirit that gave me freedom and let me fly." -- Jamie Weise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147271-on-the-other-hand-she-was-a-women-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 19:49:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Allie add a quote by Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147271-on-the-other-hand-she-was-a-women-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the other hand, she was a women with a million happy memories, who knew what it was like to experience true love and who was ready to experience more life, more love and make new memories. Whether it happened in ten months or ten years, Holly would obey Gerry's final message. Whatever lay ahead, she knew she would open her heart and follow where it led.
   In the meantime, she would just live." -- Cecelia Ahern]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
