<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898998-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/898998-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 12:46:38 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 12:46:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 12:48:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7-it-is-not-the-critic-who-counts-not-the-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not the critic who counts; not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles, or where the doer of deeds could have done them better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives valiantly; who errs, who comes short again and again, because there is no effort without error and shortcoming; but who does actually strive to do the deeds; who knows great enthusiasms, the great devotions; who spends himself in a worthy cause; who at the best knows in the end the triumph of high achievement, and who at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who neither know victory nor defeat." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 13:02:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5445-whereas-story-is-processed-in-the-mind-in-a-straightforward</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2008 16:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jasper Fforde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5445-whereas-story-is-processed-in-the-mind-in-a-straightforward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whereas story is processed in the mind in a straightforward manner, poetry bypasses rational thought and goes straight to the limbic system and lights it up like a brushfire.  It's the crack cocaine of the literary world." -- Jasper Fforde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56161-every-mother-should-be-a-true-artist-who-knows-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 22:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Frances Ellen Watkins Harper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56161-every-mother-should-be-a-true-artist-who-knows-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every mother should be a true artist, who knows how to weave into her child's life images of grace and beauty, the true poet capable of writing on the soul of childhood the harmony of love and truth, and teaching it how to produce the grandest of all poems - the poetry of a true and noble life." -- Frances Ellen Watkins Harper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 16:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22775-there-would-be-punishment-and-pain-and-there-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 11:01:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22775-there-would-be-punishment-and-pain-and-there-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...there would be punishment and pain, and there would be happiness, too. That was writing." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
