<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/899271-miss-rosebeetle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/899271-miss-rosebeetle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 17:47:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73879-nothing-can-be-given-or-taken-away-nothing-has-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 17:47:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73879-nothing-can-be-given-or-taken-away-nothing-has-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing can be given or taken away; nothing has been added or subtracted; nothing increased or diminished.  We stand on the same shore before the same mighty ocean.  The ocean of love.  There it is - in perpetuum.  As much in a broken blossom, the sound of a waterfall, the swoop of a carrion bird as in the thunderous artillery of the prophet.
We move with eyes shut and ears stopped; we smash walls where doors are waiting to open to the touch; we grope for ladders, forgetting that we have wings; we pray as if God were deaf and blind, as if He were in a space.  No wonder the angels in our midst are unrecognizable.
One day it will be pleasant to remember these things." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11708-information-is-not-knowledge-knowledge-is-not-wisdom-wisdom-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 17:48:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11708-information-is-not-knowledge-knowledge-is-not-wisdom-wisdom-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Information is not knowledge.
Knowledge is not wisdom.
Wisdom is not truth.
Truth is not beauty.
Beauty is not love.
Love is not music.
Music is THE BEST." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 17:49:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73883-what-is-this-gypsy-passion-for-separation-this-readiness-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 17:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73883-what-is-this-gypsy-passion-for-separation-this-readiness-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is this gypsy passion for separation, this
readiness to rush off when we've just met?
My head rests in my hands as I
realize, looking into the night

that no one turning over our letters has
yet understood how completely and
how deeply faithless we are, which is
to say: how true we are to ourselves." -- Marina Tsvetaeva]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33495-zippers-are-primal-and-modern-at-the-very-same-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 22:46:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33495-zippers-are-primal-and-modern-at-the-very-same-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Zippers are primal and modern at the very same time. On the one hand, your zipper is primitive and reptilian, on the other mechanical and slick. A zipper is where the Industrial Revolution meets the Cobra Cult, don't you think? Ahh. Little alligators of ecstasy, that's what zippers are. Sexy, too. Now your button, a button is prim and persnickety. There's somethin' Victorian about a row o' buttons. But a zipper, why a zipper is the very snake at the gate of Eden, waitin' to escort a true believer into the Garden. Faith, I should be sewin' more zippers into me garments, for I have many erogenous zones that require speedy access. Mmm, old zipper creeper, hanging head down like the carcass of a lizard; the phantom viper that we shun in daytime and communicate with at night." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2008 22:47:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beet is the most intense of vegetables. The radish, admittedly, is more feverish, but the fire of the radish is a cold fire, the fire of discontent not of passion. Tomatoes are lusty enough, yet there runs through tomatoes an undercurrent of frivolity. Beets are deadly serious.

Slavic peoples get their physical characteristics from potatoes, their smoldering inquietude from radishes, their seriousness from beets.

The beet is the melancholy vegetable, the one most willing to suffer. You can't squeeze blood out of a turnip...

The beet is the murderer returned to the scene of the crime. The beet is what happens when the cherry finishes with the carrot. The beet is the ancient ancestor of the autumn moon, bearded, buried, all but fossilized; the dark green sails of the grounded moon-boat stitched with veins of primordial plasma; the kite string that once connected the moon to the Earth now a muddy whisker drilling desperately for rubies.

The beet was Rasputin's favorite vegetable. You could see it in his eyes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77068-a-gentleman-is-someone-who-can-play-the-accordion-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 10:24:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Miss Rosebeetle add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77068-a-gentleman-is-someone-who-can-play-the-accordion-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A gentleman is someone who can play the accordion, but doesn't." -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
