<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/899724-tyler]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/899724-tyler" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 08:14:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71598-as-a-reader-i-loathe-introductions-introductions-inhibit-pleasure-they-kill</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 08:14:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71598-as-a-reader-i-loathe-introductions-introductions-inhibit-pleasure-they-kill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As a reader I loathe introductions...Introductions inhibit pleasure, they kill the joy of anticipation, they frustrate curiosity." -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103131-let-me-tell-you-this-when-social-workers-offer-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 22:52:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by samuel beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103131-let-me-tell-you-this-when-social-workers-offer-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me tell you this, when social workers offer you, free, gratis and for nothing, something to hinder you from swooning, which with them is an obsession, it is useless to recoil, they will pursue you to the ends of the earth, the vomitory in their hands. The Salvation Army is no better. Against the charitable gesture there is no defence, that I know of. You sink your head, you put out your hands all trembling and twined together and you say, Thank you, thank you lady, thank you kind lady. To him who has nothing it is forbidden not to relish filth." -- samuel beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2008 22:52:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23053-the-only-way-you-can-write-the-truth-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way you can write the truth is to assume that what you set down will never be read. Not by any other person, and not even by yourself at some later date. Otherwise you begin excusing yourself. You must see the writing as emerging like a long scroll of ink from the index finger of your right hand; you must see your left hand erasing it." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 15:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136905-at-the-most-one-could-say-that-his-chi-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 15:19:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Chinua Achebe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136905-at-the-most-one-could-say-that-his-chi-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the most one could say that his chi or  ...  personal god was good. But the Ibo people have a proverb that when a man says yes his chi says yes also.  Okonkwo said yes very strongly; so his chi agreed. " -- Chinua Achebe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163574-if-goodness-has-causes-it-is-not-goodness-if-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2009 09:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163574-if-goodness-has-causes-it-is-not-goodness-if-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If goodness has causes, it is not goodness; if it has effects, a reward, it is not goodness either.  So goodness is outside the chain of cause and effect." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33541-it-has-always-seemed-strange-to-me-the-things-we-admire</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 03:12:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33541-it-has-always-seemed-strange-to-me-the-things-we-admire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has always seemed strange to me...The things we admire in men, kindness and generosity, openness, honesty, understanding and feeling, are the concomitants of failure in our system. And those traits we detest, sharpness, greed, acquisitiveness, meanness, egotism and self-interest, are the traits of success. And while men admire the quality of the first they love the produce of the second." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46023-this-goodly-frame-the-earth-seems-to-me-a-sterile</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 20:54:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46023-this-goodly-frame-the-earth-seems-to-me-a-sterile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This goodly frame, the earth, seems to me a sterile promontory, this most excellent canopy, the air, look you, this brave o'erhanging firmament, this majestical roof fretted with golden fire, why, it appears no other thing to me than a foul and pestilent congregation of vapours. What a piece of work is a man! how noble in reason! how infinite in faculty! in form and moving how express and admirable! in action how like an angel! in apprehension how like a god! the beauty of the world! the paragon of animals! And yet, to me, what is this quintessence of dust?" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14543-do-you-not-know-i-am-a-woman-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 20:55:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14543-do-you-not-know-i-am-a-woman-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you not know I am a woman? when I think, I must speak." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32227-the-truth-is-part-of-me-is-every-age-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 22:52:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32227-the-truth-is-part-of-me-is-every-age-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, part of me is every age. I’m a three-year-old, I’m a five-year-old, I’m a thirty-seven-year-old, I’m a fifty-year-old. I’ve been through all of them, and I know what it’s like. I delight in being a child when it’s appropriate to be a child. I delight in being a wise old man when it’s appropriate to be a wise old man. Think of all I can be! I am every age, up to my own." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177343-you-get-them-wrong-before-you-meet-them-while-you-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2009 22:56:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Philip Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177343-you-get-them-wrong-before-you-meet-them-while-you-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You get them wrong before you meet them, while you're anticipating meeting them; you get them wrong while you're with them; and then you go home to tell somebody else about the meeting and you get them all wrong again. Since the same generally goes for them with you, the whole thing is really a dazzling illusion. ... The fact remains that getting people right is not what living is all about anyway. It's getting them wrong that is living, getting them wrong and wrong and wrong and then, on careful reconsideration, getting them wrong again. That's how we know we're alive: we're wrong. Maybe the best thing would be to forget being right or wrong about people and just go along for the ride. But if you can do that -- well, lucky you." -- Philip Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218226-i-have-no-will-of-my-own-never-did-limp</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 04:49:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Anton Chekhov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218226-i-have-no-will-of-my-own-never-did-limp]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have no will of my own.  Never did.  Limp and lily-livered, I always obey - is it possible that's attractive to women?" -- Anton Chekhov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298406-the-facts-were-strongly-behind-his-client-but-the-legal</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 08:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Ghandi Palanithurai]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298406-the-facts-were-strongly-behind-his-client-but-the-legal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The facts were strongly behind his client. But the legal battle could be drawn out for months; no one stood to gain except the lawyers. Ghandi was not interested in making a profit out of legal briefs and empty arguments. He was determined to serve the best interests of both sides. Dada Abdulla and his opponent were blood relations, and every day the case dragged on only drove in deeper the wedge that was splitting their family in two. With much talking Ghandi persuaded both sides to submit to arbitration and settle out of court. Even more talking was necessary to get Dada Abdulla to agree on terms which would not bankrupt the loser, but in the end both sides were satisfied. Ghandi was ecstatic. &quot;I had learnt,&quot; he exclaimed, &quot;the true practice of law. I had learnt to find out the better side of human nature and to enter men's hearts. I realized that the true function of a lawyer was to unite parties riven asunder." -- Ghandi Palanithurai]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298409-do-not-worry-in-the-least-about-yourself-leave-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 08:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tyler add a quote by Mahatma Ghandi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298409-do-not-worry-in-the-least-about-yourself-leave-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not worry in the least about yourself, leave all worry to God,' - this appears to be the commandment in all religions.
  This need not frighten anyone. He who devotes himself to service with a clear conscience, will day by day grasp the necessity for it in greater measure, and will continually grow richer in faith. The path of service can hardly be trodden by one who is not prepared to renounce self-interest, and to recognize the conditions of his birth. Consciously or unconsciously, every one of us does render some service or other. If we cultivate the habit of doing this service deliberately, our desire for service will steadily grow stronger, and will make not only for our own happiness but that of the world at large." -- Mahatma Ghandi]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
