<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/900360-sadia-nishu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/900360-sadia-nishu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 14:44:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53225-ever-has-it-been-that-love-knows-not-its-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 14:44:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53225-ever-has-it-been-that-love-knows-not-its-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ever has it been that love knows not its own depth until the hour of separation." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 10:57:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62235-i-am-good-but-not-an-angel-i-do-sin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am good, but not an angel. I do sin, but I am not the devil. I am just a small girl in a big world trying to find someone to love." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 10:58:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/270950-this-life-is-what-you-make-it-no-matter-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This life is what you make it. No matter what, you're going to mess up sometimes, it's a universal truth. But the good part is you get to decide how you're going to mess it up. Girls will be your friends - they'll act like it anyway. But just remember, some come, some go. The ones that stay with you through everything - they're your true best friends. Don't let go of them. Also remember, sisters make the best friends in the world. As for lovers, well, they'll come and go too. And baby, I hate to say it, most of them - actually pretty much all of them are going to break your heart, but you can't give up because if you give up, you'll never find your soulmate. You'll never find that half who makes you whole and that goes for everything. Just because you fail once, doesn't mean you're gonna fail at everything. Keep trying, hold on, and always, always, always believe in yourself, because if you don't, then who will, sweetie? So keep your head high, keep your chin up, and most importantly, keep smiling, because life's a beautiful thing and there's so much to smile about." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239692-some-women-choose-to-follow-men-and-some-women-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 11:07:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Lady Gaga]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239692-some-women-choose-to-follow-men-and-some-women-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some women choose to follow men, and some women choose to follow their dreams. If you're wondering which way to go, remember that your career will never wake up and tell you that it doesn't love you anymore." -- Lady Gaga]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117992-a-guy-and-a-girl-can-be-just-friends-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 11:15:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117992-a-guy-and-a-girl-can-be-just-friends-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A guy and a girl can be just friends, but at one point or another, they will fall for each other...Maybe temporarily, maybe at the wrong time, maybe too late, or maybe forever" -- Dave Matthews Band]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2013 11:16:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 18:03:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Lao Tzu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2279-being-deeply-loved-by-someone-gives-you-strength-while-loving]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage." -- Lao Tzu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 18:03:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 18:06:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer believed in the idea of soul mates, or love at first sight.  But I was beginning to believe that a very few times in your life, if you were lucky, you might meet someone who was exactly right for you.  Not because he was perfect, or because you were, but because your combined flaws were arranged in a way that allowed two separate beings to hinge together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360880-i-ve-been-fighting-to-be-who-i-am-all-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 18:11:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Stephanie Lennox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360880-i-ve-been-fighting-to-be-who-i-am-all-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’ve been fighting to be who I am all my life. What’s the point of being who I am, if I can’t have the person who was worth all the fighting for?" -- Stephanie Lennox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45978-even-though-you-may-want-to-move-forward-in-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 18:36:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Mary Manin Morrissey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45978-even-though-you-may-want-to-move-forward-in-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even though you may want to move forward in your life, you may have one foot on the brakes.  In order to be free, we must learn how to let go.  Release the hurt.  Release the fear.  Refuse to entertain your old pain.  The energy it takes to hang onto the past is holding you back from a new life.  What is it you would let go of today?" -- Mary Manin Morrissey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20928-who-are-you-to-judge-the-life-i-live-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2013 16:00:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20928-who-are-you-to-judge-the-life-i-live-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who are you to judge the life I live?
I know I'm not perfect
-and I don't live to be-
but before you start pointing fingers...
make sure you hands are clean!" -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234256-i-believe-that-two-people-are-connected-at-the-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 11:31:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sadia add a quote by Julia Roberts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234256-i-believe-that-two-people-are-connected-at-the-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that two people are connected at the heart, and it doesn't matter what you do, or who you are or where you live; there are no boundaries or barriers if two people are destined to be together." -- Julia Roberts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
