<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/900895-e]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/900895-e" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 09:41:36 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262810-this-story-was-written-many-moons-ago-under-an-apple</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 09:41:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by M. M. Kaye]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/262810-this-story-was-written-many-moons-ago-under-an-apple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This story was written many moons ago under an apple tree in an orchard in Kent,  which is one of England's prettiest counties . . . I had read at least twenty of the [fairy tales] when I noticed something that had never struck me before--I suppose because I had always taken it for granted.  All the princesses, apart from such rare exceptions as Snow White, were blond, blue-eyed, and beautiful, with lovely figures and complexions and extravagantly long hair.  This struck me as most unfair, and suddenly I began to wonder just how many handsome young princes would have asked a king for the hand of his daughter if that daughter had happened to be gawky, snub-nosed, and freckled, with shortish mouse-colored hair?  None, I suspected.  They would all have been of chasing after some lissome Royal Highness with large blue eyes and yards of golden hair and probably nothing whatever between her ears!  It was in that moment that a story about a princess who turned out to be ordinary jumped into my mind, and the very next morning I took my pencil box and a large rough-notebook down to the orchard and, having settled myself under an apple tree in full bloom, began to write . . . the day was warm and windless and without a cloud in the sky.  A perfect day and a perfect place to write a fairy story." -- M. M. Kaye]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
