<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/901248-isabell]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/901248-isabell" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 11:10:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149605-we-are-all-of-us-denying-or-fulfilling-prayers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 11:10:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isabell add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149605-we-are-all-of-us-denying-or-fulfilling-prayers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all of us denying or fulfilling prayers – and men in their careless deeds walk amidst invisible outstretched arms and pleadings made in vain." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694106-quite-quite-she-thought-with-a-little-sigh-it-s-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2013 05:07:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isabell add a quote by Tove Jansson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/694106-quite-quite-she-thought-with-a-little-sigh-it-s-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Quite, quite,' she thought with a little sigh. 'It's always like this in their adventures. To save and be saved. I wish somebody would write a story sometime about the people who warm up the heroes afterward." -- Tove Jansson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302911-three-passions-simple-but-overwhelmingly-strong-have-governed-my-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:09:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isabell add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302911-three-passions-simple-but-overwhelmingly-strong-have-governed-my-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Three passions, simple but overwhelmingly strong, have governed my life: the longing for love, the search for knowledge, and unbearable pity for the suffering of mankind. These passions, like great winds, have blown me hither and thither, in a wayward course, over a great ocean of anguish, reaching to the very verge of despair.

 I have sought love, first, because it brings ecstasy - ecstasy so great that I would often have sacrificed all the rest of life for a few hours of this joy. I have sought it, next, because it relieves loneliness--that terrible loneliness in which one shivering consciousness looks over the rim of the world into the cold unfathomable lifeless abyss. I have sought it finally, because in the union of love I have seen, in a mystic miniature, the prefiguring vision of the heaven that saints and poets have imagined. This is what I sought, and though it might seem too good for human life, this is what--at last--I have found.

With equal passion I have sought knowledge. I have wished to understand the hearts of men. I have wished to know why the stars shine. And I have tried to apprehend the Pythagorean power by which number holds sway above the flux. A little of this, but not much, I have achieved.

 Love and knowledge, so far as they were possible, led upward toward the heavens. But always pity brought me back to earth. Echoes of cries of pain reverberate in my heart. Children in famine, victims tortured by oppressors, helpless old people a burden to their sons, and the whole world of loneliness, poverty, and pain make a mockery of what human life should be. I long to alleviate this evil, but I cannot, and I too suffer.

 This has been my life. I have found it worth living, and would gladly live it again if the chance were offered me." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198277-i-never-had-a-biological-sister-yet-the-more-closely</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 04:11:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Isabell add a quote by Chieko N. Okazaki]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1198277-i-never-had-a-biological-sister-yet-the-more-closely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never had a biological sister, yet the more closely I work with women in the Church, the more surely I know there is a spiritual sisterhood." -- Chieko N. Okazaki]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
