<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/901689-jensen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/901689-jensen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 15:18:48 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 15:18:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228-the-road-goes-ever-on-and-on-down-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 15:19:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228-the-road-goes-ever-on-and-on-down-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Road goes ever on and on
Down from the door where it began.
Now far ahead the Road has gone,
And I must follow, if I can,
Pursuing it with eager feet,
Until it joins some larger way
Where many paths and errands meet.
And whither then? I cannot say" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100682-i-figured-i-could-get-a-job-at-a-filling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2010 03:33:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100682-i-figured-i-could-get-a-job-at-a-filling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I figured I could get a job at a filling station somewhere, putting gas and oil in people's cars. I didn't care what kind of job it was, though. Just so people didn't know me and I didn't know anybody. I thought what I'd do was, I'd pretend I was one of those deaf-mutes. That way I wouldn't have to have any goddam stupid useless conversations with anybody. If anybody wanted to tell me something, they'd have to write it on a piece of paper and shove it over to me. They'd get bored as hell doing that after a while, and then I'd be through with having conversations for the rest of my life. Everybody'd think I was just a poor deaf-mute bastard and they'd leave me alone." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44840-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 12:37:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by Bill Hicks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44840-the-world-is-like-a-ride-in-an-amusement-park]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is like a ride in an amusement park. And when you choose to go on it you think it's real because that's how powerful our minds are. And the ride goes up and down and round and round. It has thrills and chills and it's very brightly coloured and it's very loud and it's fun, for a while. Some people have been on the ride for a long time and they begin to question: &quot;Is this real, or is this just a ride?&quot; And other people have remembered, and they come back to us, they say, &quot;Hey, don't worry, don't be afraid, ever, because this is just a ride.&quot; And we kill those people." -- Bill Hicks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12280-the-illusion-of-freedom-will-continue-as-long-as-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2011 16:03:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12280-the-illusion-of-freedom-will-continue-as-long-as-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The illusion of freedom will continue as long as it's profitable to continue the illusion. At the point where the illusion becomes too expensive to maintain, they will just take down the scenery, they will pull back the curtains, they will move the tables and chairs out of the way and you will see the brick wall at the back of the theater." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244131-a-child-free-from-the-guilt-of-ownership-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 08:49:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244131-a-child-free-from-the-guilt-of-ownership-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A child free from the guilt of ownership and the burden of economic competition will grow up with the will to do what needs doing and the capacity for joy in doing it. It is useless work that darkens the heart. The delight of the nursing mother, of the scholar, of the successful hunter, of the good cook, of the skilful maker, of anyone doing needed work and doing it well, - this durable joy is perhaps the deepest source of human affection and of sociality as a whole." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2012 14:37:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414235-a-culture-is-no-better-than-its-woods</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 01:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jensen add a quote by W.H. Auden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/414235-a-culture-is-no-better-than-its-woods]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a culture is no better than its woods" -- W.H. Auden]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
