<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/902399-melissa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/902399-melissa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 05:01:07 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150387-wasn-t-that-the-point-of-the-book-for-women-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 05:01:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150387-wasn-t-that-the-point-of-the-book-for-women-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wasn't that the point of the book?  For women to realize, We are just two people.  Not that much separates us.  Not nearly as much as I'd thought." -- Kathryn Stockett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188420-when-i-speak-of-home-i-speak-of-the-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 12:19:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188420-when-i-speak-of-home-i-speak-of-the-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I speak of home, I speak of the place where in default of a better--those I love are gathered together; and if that place where a gypsy's tent, or a barn, I should call it by the same good name notwithstanding." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42876-it-isn-t-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2012 09:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42876-it-isn-t-as-bad-as-you-sometimes-think-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't as bad as you sometimes think it is. It all works out. Don't worry. I say that to myself every morning. It all works out in the end. Put your trust in God, and move forward with faith and confidence in the future. The Lord will not forsake us. He will not forsake us. If we will put our trust in Him, if we will pray to Him, if we will live worthy of His blessings, He will hear our prayers." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 06:33:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Melissa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21101-do-you-think-i-am-an-automaton-a-machine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I am an automaton? — a machine without feelings? and can bear to have my morsel of bread snatched from my lips, and my drop of living water dashed from my cup? Do you think, because I am poor, obscure, plain, and little, I am soulless and heartless? You think wrong! — I have as much soul as you — and full as much heart! And if God had gifted me with some beauty and much wealth, I should have made it as hard for you to leave me, as it is now for me to leave you. I am not talking to you now through the medium of custom, conventionalities, nor even of mortal flesh: it is my spirit that addresses your spirit; just as if both had passed through the grave, and we stood at God's feet, equal — as we are!" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
