<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/904335-abigail]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/904335-abigail" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:43:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25207-he-did-not-know-what-to-say-in-the-face</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:43:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldor Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25207-he-did-not-know-what-to-say-in-the-face]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He did not know what to say in the face of such sorrow. He sat in silence by his sister's side in the spring verdure, which was too young; and the hidden strings in his breast began to quiver; and to sound.
This was the first time that he had ever looked into the labyrinth of the human soul." -- Halldor Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25206-the-tyranny-of-mankind-it-was-like-the-obstinate-drip</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldor Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25206-the-tyranny-of-mankind-it-was-like-the-obstinate-drip]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tyranny of mankind; it was like the obstinate drip of water falling on a stone and hollowing it little by little; and this drip continued, falling obstinately, falling without pause on the souls of the children." -- Halldor Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54272-but-sometimes-illumination-comes-to-our-rescue-at-the-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54272-but-sometimes-illumination-comes-to-our-rescue-at-the-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But sometimes illumination comes to our rescue at the very moment when all seems lost; we have knocked at every door and they open on nothing until, at last, we stumble unconsciously against the only one through which we can enter the kingdom we have sought in vain a hundred years - and it opens." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42531-but-what-revealed-to-me-all-of-a-sudden-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42531-but-what-revealed-to-me-all-of-a-sudden-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what revealed to me all of a sudden the Princess's love was a trifling incident upon which I shall not dwell here, for it forms part of quite another story, in which M. de Charlus allowed a Queen to die rather than miss an appointment with the hairdresser who was to singe his hair for the benefit of an omnibus conductor who filled him with alarm." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25264-few-people-take-an-interest-in-iceland-but-in-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by W H Auden ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25264-few-people-take-an-interest-in-iceland-but-in-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few people take an interest in Iceland, but in those few the interest is passionate." -- W H Auden ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25261-a-wise-man-once-said-that-next-to-losing-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldor Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25261-a-wise-man-once-said-that-next-to-losing-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A wise man once said that next to losing its mother, there is nothing more healthy for a child than to lose its father." -- Halldor Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25212-he-continued-on-on-to-the-glacier-towards-the-dawn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25212-he-continued-on-on-to-the-glacier-towards-the-dawn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He continued on, on to the glacier, towards the dawn, from ridge to ridge, in deep, new-fallen snow, paying no heed to the storms that might pursue him. As a child he had stood by the seashore at Ljósavík and watched the waves soughing in and out, but now he was heading away from the sea. &quot;Think of me when you are in glorious sunshine.&quot; Soon the sun of the day of resurrection will shine on the bright paths where she awaits her poet.
And beauty shall reign alone." -- Halldór Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108036-be-near-me-when-my-light-is-low-when-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108036-be-near-me-when-my-light-is-low-when-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be near me when my light is low,
When the blood creeps, and the nerves prick
And tingle; and the heart is sick,
And all the wheels of Being slow.

Be near me when the sensuous frame
Is rack'd with pangs that conquer trust;
And Time, a maniac scattering dust,
And Life, a fury slinging flame.

Be near me when my faith is dry,
And men the flies of latter spring,
That lay their eggs, and sting and sing
And weave their petty cells and die.

Be near me when I fade away,
To point the term of human strife,
And on the low dark verge of life
The twilight of eternal day." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108037-what-is-a-nation</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Timothy Baycroft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108037-what-is-a-nation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is a nation?" -- Timothy Baycroft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60598-i-met-murder-on-the-way---he-had-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60598-i-met-murder-on-the-way---he-had-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I met Murder on the way -
He had a mask like Castlereagh" -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38149-death-be-not-proud-death-be-not-proud-though-some</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by John Donne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38149-death-be-not-proud-death-be-not-proud-though-some]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Death Be Not Proud&lt;/b&gt;

Death, be not proud, though some have called thee 
Mighty and dreadful, for thou art not so;
For those, whom thou think'st thou dost overthrow,
Die not, poor Death, nor yet canst thou kill me.
From rest and sleep, which but thy picture[s] be,
Much pleasure, then from thee much more must flow,
And soonest our best men with thee do go,
Rest of their bones, and soul's delivery.
Thou'rt slave to Fate, chance, kings, and desperate men,
And dost with poison, war, and sickness dwell,
And poppy, or charms can make us sleep as well,
And better than thy stroke ;  why swell'st thou then?
One short sleep past, we wake eternally,
And Death shall be no more; Death, thou shalt die." -- John Donne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111819-one-boy-s-footprints-are-not-long-in-being-lost-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111819-one-boy-s-footprints-are-not-long-in-being-lost-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One boy's footprints are not long in being lost in the snow, in the steadily falling snow of the shortest day, the longest night; they are lost as soon as they are made. And once again the heath is clothed in drifting white. And there is no ghost, save the one ghost that lives in the heart of a motherless boy, till his footprints disappear." -- Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111817-when-the-boat-had-gone-a-few-oar-strokes-away-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111817-when-the-boat-had-gone-a-few-oar-strokes-away-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the boat had gone a few oar-strokes away from land they were still standing on the beach, gazing after the boy whom an unknown woman had left naked in their arms. They were holding hands, and other people gave way before them, and I could see no one except them. Or were they perhaps so extraordinary that other people melted away and vanished into thin air around them?
When I had clambered up with my bag onto the deck of the mail-boat North Star, I saw them walking back together on their way home: on the way to our turnstile-gate; home to Brekkukot, our house which was to be razed to the ground tomorrow. They were walking hand in hand, like children." -- Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207251-ma-urinn-finnur-a-sem-hann-leitar-a-og-s-sem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207251-ma-urinn-finnur-a-sem-hann-leitar-a-og-s-sem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maðurinn finnur það sem hann leitar að, og sá sem trúir á draug finnur draug." -- Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207253-fegur-in-og-mannl-fi-eru-tveir-elskendur-sem-f-ekki-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207253-fegur-in-og-mannl-fi-eru-tveir-elskendur-sem-f-ekki-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fegurðin og mannlífið eru tveir elskendur sem fá ekki að hittast." -- Halldór Kiljan Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214898-do-you-suppose-that-it-is-within-your-power-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214898-do-you-suppose-that-it-is-within-your-power-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you suppose that it is within your power to insult me? You evidently are not aware to whom you are speaking? Do you imagine that the envenomed spittle of five hundred little gentlemen of your type, heaped one upon another, would succeed in slobbering so much as the tips of my august toes?" -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217423-hann-s-strax-a-etta-var-mannsbein-egar-hann-n-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Arnaldur Indriðason]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217423-hann-s-strax-a-etta-var-mannsbein-egar-hann-n-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hann sá strax að þetta var mannsbein þegar hann náði því af barninu, sem setið hafði á gólfinu og tuggið á því." -- Arnaldur Indriðason]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65378-embi-and-you-re-supposed-to-be-so-good-at-mending</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65378-embi-and-you-re-supposed-to-be-so-good-at-mending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Embi: And you're supposed to be so good at mending primuses, pastor Jón!

Pastor Jón: And correspondingly bad at Baroque art. 

Embi: How do you know there are 133 pieces? Who has had time to dismantle this work of art so carefully? Or to count the bits?

Pastor Jón: No one is so busy that he hasn't the time to dismantle a work of art. Then scholars wake up and count the pieces. " -- Halldór Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239178-but-to-ask-pity-of-our-body-is-like-discoursing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239178-but-to-ask-pity-of-our-body-is-like-discoursing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But to ask pity of our body is like discoursing in front of an octopus, for which our words can have no more meaning than the sound of the tides, and with which we should be appalled to find ourselves condemned to live." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239181-nor-did-these-society-people-add-to-elstir-s-work-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2010 04:45:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239181-nor-did-these-society-people-add-to-elstir-s-work-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nor did these society people add to Elstir's work in their mind's eye that temporal perspective which enabled them to like, or at least to look without discomfort at, Chardin's painting. And yet the older among them might have reminded themselves that in the course of their lives they had gradually seen, as the years bore them away from it, the unbridgeable gulf between what they considered a masterpiece by Ingres and what they had supposed must forever remain a &quot;horror&quot; (Manet's &lt;i&gt;Olympia&lt;/i&gt;, for example) shrink until the two canvases seemed like twins. But we never learn, because we lack the wisdom to work backwards from the particular to the general, and imagine ourselves always to be faced with an experience which has no precedents in the past." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252316-and-now-at-last-authentic-word-i-bring-witnessed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 11:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by James Thomson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252316-and-now-at-last-authentic-word-i-bring-witnessed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now at last authentic word I bring,
Witnessed by every dead and living thing;
Good tidings of great joy for you, for all:
There is no God; no Fiend with names divine
Made us and tortures us; if we must pine,
It is to satiate no Being's gall.

It was the dark delusion of a dream,
That living Person conscious and supreme,
Whom we must curse for cursing us with life;
Whom we must curse because the life he gave
Could not be buried in the quiet grave,
Could not be killed by poison or the knife.

This little life is all we must endure,
The grave's most holy peace is ever sure,
We fall asleep and never wake again;
Nothing is of us but the mouldering flesh,
Whose elements dissolve and merge afresh
In earth, air, water, plants, and other men.

We finish thus; and all our wretched race
Shall finish with its cycle, and give place
To other beings with their own time-doom:
Infinite aeons ere our kind began;
Infinite aeons after the last man
Has joined the mammoth in earth's tomb and womb." -- James Thomson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252322-how-the-moon-triumphs-through-the-endless-nights-how-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 11:46:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by James Thomson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252322-how-the-moon-triumphs-through-the-endless-nights-how-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How the moon triumphs through the endless nights!
How the stars throb and glitter as they wheel
Their thick processions of supernal lights
Around the blue vault obdurate as steel!
And men regard with passionate awe and yearning
The mighty marching and the golden burning,
And think the heavens respond to what they feel.

Boats gliding like dark shadows of a dream
Are glorified from vision as they pass
The quivering moonbridge on the deep black stream;
Cold windows kindle their dead glooms of glass
To restless crystals; cornice dome and column
Emerge from chaos in the splendour solemn;
Like faery lakes gleam lawns of dewy grass.

With such a living light these dead eyes shine,
These eyes of sightless heaven, that as we gaze
We read a pity, tremulous, divine,
Or cold majestic scorn in their pure rays:
Fond man! they are not haughty, are not tender;
There is no heart or mind in all their splendour,
They thread mere puppets all their marvellous maze." -- James Thomson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252327-who-is-most-wretched-in-this-dolorous-place-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 11:52:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by James Thomson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252327-who-is-most-wretched-in-this-dolorous-place-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who is most wretched in this dolorous place?
I think myself; yet I would rather be
My miserable self than He, than He
Who formed such creatures to His own disgrace.

The vilest thing must be less vile than Thou
From whom it had its being, God and Lord!
Creator of all woe and sin! abhorred
Malignant and implacable! I vow

That not for all Thy power furled and unfurled,
For all the temples to Thy glory built,
Would I assume the ignominious guilt
Of having made such men in such a world.

As if a Being, God or Fiend, could reign,
At once so wicked, foolish and insane,
As to produce men when He might refrain!

The world rolls round for ever like a mill;
It grinds out death and life and good and ill;
It has no purpose, heart or mind or will.

While air of Space and Time's full river flow
The mill must blindly whirl unresting so:
It may be wearing out, but who can know?

Man might know one thing were his sight less dim;
That it whirls not to suit his petty whim,
That it is quite indifferent to him.

Nay, does it treat him harshly as he saith?
It grinds him some slow years of bitter breath,
Then grinds him back into eternal death." -- James Thomson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253850-the-novelist-s-happy-discovery-was-to-think-of-substituting-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 05:03:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253850-the-novelist-s-happy-discovery-was-to-think-of-substituting-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The novelist’s happy discovery was to think of substituting for those opaque sections, impenetrable by the human spirit, their equivalent in immaterial sections, things, that is, which the spirit can assimilate to itself. After which it matters not that the actions, the feelings of this new order of creatures appear to us in the guise of truth, since we have made them our own, since it is in ourselves that they are happening, that they are holding in thrall, while we turn over, feverishly, the pages of the book, our quickened breath and staring eyes. And once the novelist has brought us to that state, in which, as in all purely mental states, every emotion is multiplied ten-fold, into which his book comes to disturb us as might a dream, but a dream more lucid, and of a more lasting impression than those which come to us in sleep; why, then, for the space of an hour he sets free within us all the joys and sorrows in the world, a few of which, only, we should have to spend years of our actual life in getting to know, and the keenest, the most intense of which would never have been revealed to us because the slow course of their development stops our perception of them." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255239-the-farm-brook-ran-down-from-the-mountain-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 05:47:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abigail add a quote by Halldór Laxness]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255239-the-farm-brook-ran-down-from-the-mountain-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The farm brook ran down from the mountain in a straight line for the fold then swerved to the west to go its way down into the marshes. There were two knee-high falls in it and two pools, knee-deep. At the bottom there was shingle, pebbles and sand. It ran in many curves. Each curve had its own tone, but not one of them was dull; the brook was merry and music-loving, like youth, but yet with various strings, and it played its music without thought of any audience and did not care though no one heard for a hundred years, like the true poet." -- Halldór Laxness]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
