<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/905895-mike]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/905895-mike" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:41:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62562-the-future-you-have-tomorrow-won-t-be-the-same-future</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:41:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62562-the-future-you-have-tomorrow-won-t-be-the-same-future]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future you have, tomorrow, won't be the same future you had, yesterday." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283739-may-i-never-be-complete-may-i-never-be-content</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:42:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283739-may-i-never-be-complete-may-i-never-be-content]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May I never be complete. May I never be content. May I never be perfect." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126250-rant-would-tell-people-you-re-a-different-human-being-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:45:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126250-rant-would-tell-people-you-re-a-different-human-being-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rant would tell people: 'You're a different human being to everybody you meet." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47780-you-grow-up-to-become-living-proof-of-your-parents</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47780-you-grow-up-to-become-living-proof-of-your-parents]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You grow up to become living proof of your parents' limitations. Their less-than masterpiece." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151827-picture-anybody-growing-up-so-stupid-he-didn-t-know-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 14:48:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151827-picture-anybody-growing-up-so-stupid-he-didn-t-know-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Picture anybody growing up so stupid he didn't know that hope is just another phase you'll grow out of." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105466-what-do-you-believe-i-believe-that-the-last-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 10:13:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105466-what-do-you-believe-i-believe-that-the-last-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do you believe?
I believe that the last and the first suffer equally. Pari passu.
Equally?
It is not alone in the dark of death that all souls are one soul.
Of what would you repent?
Nothing.
Nothing?
One thing. I spoke with bitterness about my life and I said that I would take my own part against the slander of oblivion and against the monstrous facelessness of it and that I would stand a stone in the very void where all would read my name. Of that vanity I recant all." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231860-and-what-happens-then-when-after-you-re-dead-dont-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 10:14:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231860-and-what-happens-then-when-after-you-re-dead-dont-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what happens then?
When?
After you're dead.
Dont nothing happen. You're dead.
You told me once you believed in God.
The old man waved his hand. Maybe, he said. I got no reason to think he believes in me. Oh I'd like to see him for a minute if I could.
What would you say to him?
Well, I think I'd just tell him. I'd say: Wait a minute. Wait just one minute before you start in on me. Before you say anything, there's just one thing I'd like to know. And he'll say: what's that? And then I'm goin to ast him: What did you have me in that crapgame down there for anyway? I couldnt put any part of it together.
Suttree smiled. What do you think he'll say?
The ragpicker spat and wiped his mouth. I dont believe he can answer it. I dont believe there is an answer. " -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449666-wrap-me-in-the-weathers-of-the-earth-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 10:15:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449666-wrap-me-in-the-weathers-of-the-earth-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wrap me in the weathers of the earth, I will be hard and hard. My face will turn rain like the stones." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5138-people-were-always-getting-ready-for-tomorrow-i-didn-t-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 06:29:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5138-people-were-always-getting-ready-for-tomorrow-i-didn-t-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People were always getting ready for tomorrow. I didn't believe in that. Tomorrow wasn't getting ready for them. It didn't even know they were there." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144251-but-there-are-no-absolutes-in-human-misery-and-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 06:33:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144251-but-there-are-no-absolutes-in-human-misery-and-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there are no absolutes in human misery and things can always get worse" -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236515-he-had-divested-himself-of-the-little-cloaked-godlet-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 14:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236515-he-had-divested-himself-of-the-little-cloaked-godlet-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had divested himself of the little cloaked godlet and his other amulets in a place where they would not be found in his lifetime and he'd taken for talisman the simple human heart within him." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333065-he-looked-at-a-world-of-incredible-loveliness-old-distaff</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 14:05:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333065-he-looked-at-a-world-of-incredible-loveliness-old-distaff]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He looked at a world of incredible loveliness. Old distaff Celt's blood in some back chamber of his brain moved him to discourse with the birches, with the oaks. A cool green fire kept breaking in the woods and he could hear the footsteps of the dead. Everything had fallen from him. He scarce could tell where his being ended or the world began nor did he care. He lay on his back in the gravel, the earth's core sucking his bones, a moment's giddy vertigo with this illusion of falling outward through blue and windy space, over the offside of the planet, hurtling through the high thin cirrus." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133826-suttree-stood-among-the-screaming-leaves-and-called-the-lightning</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 17:49:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133826-suttree-stood-among-the-screaming-leaves-and-called-the-lightning]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Suttree stood among the screaming leaves and called the lightning down.  It cracked and boomed about and he pointed out the darkened heart within him and cried for light.  If there be any art in the weathers of this earth.  Or char these bones to coal.  If you can, if you can. A blackened rag in the rain." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622005-mr-suttree-it-is-our-understanding-that-at-curfew-rightly</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 18:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/622005-mr-suttree-it-is-our-understanding-that-at-curfew-rightly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Suttree it is our understanding that at curfew rightly decreed by law and in that hour wherein night draws to its proper close and the new day commences and contrary to conduct befitting a person of your station you betook yourself to various low places within the shire of McAnally and there did squander several ensuing years in the company of thieves, derelicts, miscreants, pariahs, poltroons, spalpeens, curmudgeons, clotpolls, murderers, gamblers, bawds, whores, trulls, brigands, topers, tosspots, sots and archsots, lobcocks, smellsmocks, runagates, rakes, and other assorted and felonious debauchees.

I was drunk, cried Suttree." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633429-he-lifted-the-slice-of-cake-and-bit-into-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 18:41:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633429-he-lifted-the-slice-of-cake-and-bit-into-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He lifted the slice of cake and bit into it and turned the page. The old musty album with its foxed and crumbling paper seemed to breathe a reek of the vault, turning up one by one these dead faces with their wan and loveless gaze out toward the spinning world, masks of incertitude before the cold glass eye of the camera or recoiling before this celluloid immortality or faces simply staggered into gaga by the sheer velocity of time. Old distaff kin coughed up out of the vortex, thin and cracked and macled and a bit redundant. The landscapes, old backdrops, redundant too, recurring unchanged as if they inhabited another medium than the dry pilgrims shored up on them. Blind moil in the earth's nap cast up in an eyeblink between becoming and done. I am, I am. An artifact of prior races." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666465-i-ve-seen-all-i-want-to-see-and-i-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2014 18:47:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/666465-i-ve-seen-all-i-want-to-see-and-i-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've seen all I want to see and I know all I want to know. I just look forward to death.
He might hear you, Suttree said.
I wisht he would, said the ragpicker. He glared out across the river with his redrimmed eyes at the town where dusk was settling in. As if death might be hiding in that quarter.
No one wants to die.
Shit, said the ragpicker. Here's one that's sick of livin. Would you give all you own?
The ragman eyed him suspiciously but he did not smile. It wont be long, he said. An old man's days are hours. 
And what happens then?
When?
After you're dead.
Dont nothin happen. You're dead.
You told me once you believed in God.
The old man waved his hand. Maybe, he said. I got no reason to think he believes in me. Oh I'd like to see him for a minute if I could.
What would you say to him?
Well, I think I'd just tell him. I'd say: Wait a minute. Wait just one minute before you start in on me. Before you say anything, there's just one thing I'd like to know. And he'll say: What's that? And then I'm goin to ast him: What did you have me in that crapgame down there for anyway? I couldnt put any part of it together.
Suttree smiled. What do you think he'll say?
The ragpicker spat and wiped his mouth. I dont believe he can answer it, he said. I dont believe there is a answer." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 03:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22938-it-was-the-nature-of-his-profession-that-his-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the nature of his profession that his experience with death should be greater than for most and he said that while it was true that time heals bereavement it does so only at the cost of the slow extinction of those loved ones from the heart's memory which is the sole place of their abode then or now. Faces fade, voices dim. Seize them back, whispered the sepulturero. Speak with them. Call their names. Do this and do not let sorrow die for it is the sweetening of every gift." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181127-hard-weather-says-the-old-man-so-let-it-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 03:46:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181127-hard-weather-says-the-old-man-so-let-it-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hard weather, says the old man.  So let it be.  Wrap me in the weathers of the earth, I will be hard and hard.  My face will wash rain like the stones.  " -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:55:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23134-so-everything-is-necessary-every-least-thing-this-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything is necessary. Every least thing. This is the hard lesson. Nothing can be dispensed with. Nothing despised. Because the seams are hid from us, you see. The joinery. The way in which the world is made. We have no way to know what could be taken away. What omitted. We have no way to tell what might stand and what might fall." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177625-things-separate-from-their-stories-have-no-meaning-they-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:56:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177625-things-separate-from-their-stories-have-no-meaning-they-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things separate from their stories have no meaning.  They are only shapes.  Of a certain size and color.  A certain weight.  When their meaning has become lost to us they no longer have even a name.  The story on the other hand can never be lost from its place in the world for it is that place." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98849-he-said-that-men-believe-the-blood-of-the-slain</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:56:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98849-he-said-that-men-believe-the-blood-of-the-slain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He said that men believe the blood of the slain to be of no consequence but that the wolf knows better. He said that the wolf is a being of great order and that it knows what men do not: that there is no order in this world save that which death has put there." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159826-he-told-the-boy-that-although-he-was-hu-rfano-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:58:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159826-he-told-the-boy-that-although-he-was-hu-rfano-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He told the boy that although he was huérfano still he must cease his wanderings and make for himself some place in the world because to wander in this way would become for him a passion and by this passion he would become estranged from men and so ultimately from himself. He said that the world could only be known as it existed in men's hearts. For while it seemed a place which contained men it was in reality a place contained within them and therefore to know it one must look there and come to know those hearts and to do this one must live with men and not simply pass among them. He said that while the huérfano might feel that he no longer belonged among men he must set this feeling aside for he contained within him a largeness of spirit which men could see and that men would wish to know him and that the world would need him even as he needed the world for they were one. Lastly he said that while this itself was a good thing like all good things it was also a danger. Then he removed his hands from the boy's saddle and stepped away and stood. The boy thanked him for his words but he said that he was in fact not an orphan and then he thanked the women standing there and turned the horse and rode out. They stood watching him go. As he passed the last of the brush wickiups he turned and looked back and as he did so the old man called out to him. Eres, he said. Eres huérfano." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498657-he-said-that-whether-a-man-s-life-was-writ-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 14:59:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498657-he-said-that-whether-a-man-s-life-was-writ-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He said that whether a man's life was writ in a book someplace or whether it took its form day by day was one and the same for it had but one reality and that was the living of it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283885-a-bad-map-is-worse-than-no-map-at-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 15:00:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283885-a-bad-map-is-worse-than-no-map-at-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a bad map is worse than no map at all for it engendered in the traveler a false confidence and might easily cause him to set aside these instincts which would otherwise guide him if he would but place himself in their care. He said that to follow a false map was to invite disaster. He gestured at the sketching in the dirt. As if to invite them to behold its futility. The second man on the bench nodded his agreement in this and said that the map in question was a folly and that the dogs in the street would piss upon it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585942-he-took-up-her-stiff-head-out-of-the-leaves</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 15:04:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/585942-he-took-up-her-stiff-head-out-of-the-leaves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He took up her stiff head out of the leaves and held it or he reached to hold what cannot be held, what already ran among the mountains at once terrible and of a great beauty, like flowers that feed on flesh. What blood and bone are made of but can themselves not make on any altar nor by any wound of war. What we may well believe has power to cut and shape and hollow out the dark form of the world surely if wind can, if rain can. But which cannot be held never be held and is no flower but is swift and a huntress and the wind itself is in terror of it and the world cannot lose it." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
