<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/90743-gala]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/90743-gala" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 19:32:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65268-i-really-think-i-write-about-everyday-life-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 19:32:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Edward Gorey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65268-i-really-think-i-write-about-everyday-life-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really think I write about everyday life. I don't think I'm quite as odd as others say I am. Life is intrinsically, well, boring and dangerous at the same time. At any given moment the floor may open up. Of course, it almost never does; that's what makes it so boring." -- Edward Gorey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31519-concerning-trees-and-leaves-there-s-a-real-power-here-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 19:32:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31519-concerning-trees-and-leaves-there-s-a-real-power-here-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Concerning trees and leaves... there's a real power here. It is amazing that trees can turn gravel and bitter salts into these soft-lipped lobes, as if I were to bite down on a granite slab and start to swell, bud and flower. Every year a given tree creates absolutely from scratch ninety-nine percent of its living parts. Water lifting up tree trunks can climb one hundred and fifty feet an hour; in full summer a tree can, and does, heave a ton of water every day. A big elm in a single season might make as many as six million leaves, wholly intricate, without budging an inch; I couldn't make one. A tree stands there, accumulating deadwood, mute and rigid as an obelisk, but secretly it seethes, it splits, sucks and stretches; it heaves up tons and hurls them out in a green, fringed fling. No person taps this free power; the dynamo in the tulip tree pumps out even more tulip tree, and it runs on rain and air." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9846-you-can-safely-assume-you-ve-created-god-in-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:01:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9846-you-can-safely-assume-you-ve-created-god-in-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can safely assume you've created God in your own image when it turns out that God hates all the same people you do." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:01:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For some of us, books are as important as almost anything else on earth.  What a miracle it is that out of these small, flat, rigid squares of paper unfolds world after world after world, worlds that sing to you, comfort and quiet or excite you.  Books help us understand who we are and how we are to behave.  They show us what community and friendship mean; they show us how to live and die." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14009-and-for-all-this-nature-is-never-spent-there-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:02:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Gerard Manley Hopkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14009-and-for-all-this-nature-is-never-spent-there-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And for all this, nature is never spent;  
There lives the dearest freshness deep down things;          
And though the last lights off the black West went  
Oh, morning, at the brown brink eastward, springs—  
Because the Holy Ghost over the bent  
World broods with warm breast and with ah! bright wings." -- Gerard Manley Hopkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61159-the-beautiful-feeling-after-writing-a-poem-is-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:03:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61159-the-beautiful-feeling-after-writing-a-poem-is-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beautiful feeling after writing a poem is on the whole better even than after sex, and that's saying a lot." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126945-sometimes-i-fly-like-an-eagle-but-with-the-wings</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:04:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126945-sometimes-i-fly-like-an-eagle-but-with-the-wings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I fly like an eagle but with the wings of a wren" -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7143-remember-the-time-you-feel-lonely-is-the-time-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:04:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7143-remember-the-time-you-feel-lonely-is-the-time-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember: the time you feel lonely is the time you most need to be by yourself. Life's cruelest irony." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10941-my-secret-is-that-i-need-god-that-i-am-sick</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:05:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Douglas Coupland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10941-my-secret-is-that-i-need-god-that-i-am-sick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My secret is that I need God—that I am sick and can no longer make it alone. I need God to help me give, because I no longer seem to be capable of giving; to help me be kind, as I no longer seem capable of kindness; to help me love, as I seem beyond being able to love." -- Douglas Coupland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106636-when-you-love-a-man-he-becomes-more-than-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:06:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Gwendolyn Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/106636-when-you-love-a-man-he-becomes-more-than-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you love a man, he becomes more than a body. His physical limbs expand, and his outline recedes, vanishes. He is rich and sweet and right. He is part of the world, the atmosphere, the blue sky and the blue water" -- Gwendolyn Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:42:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13750-if-only-it-were-all-so-simple-if-only-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only it were all so simple! If only there were evil people somewhere insidiously committing evil deeds, and it were necessary only to separate them from the rest of us and destroy them. But the line dividing good and evil cuts through the heart of every human being. And who is willing to destroy a piece of his own heart?" -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23334-many-of-you-have-already-found-out-and-others-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23334-many-of-you-have-already-found-out-and-others-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many of you have already found out, and others will find out in the course of their lives, that truth eludes us if we do not concentrate our attention totally on it's pursuit. But even while it eludes us, the illusion of knowing it still lingers and leads to many misunderstandings. Also, truth seldom is pleasant; it is almost invariably bitter." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79236-i-read-for-growth-firmly-believing-that-what-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:44:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Twyla Tharp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79236-i-read-for-growth-firmly-believing-that-what-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read for growth, firmly believing that what you are today and what you will be in five years depends on two things: the people you meet and the books you read." -- Twyla Tharp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121456-it-is-extremely-arrogant-and-very-foolish-to-think-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:44:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Twyla Tharp]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121456-it-is-extremely-arrogant-and-very-foolish-to-think-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is extremely arrogant and very foolish to think that you can ever outwit your audience. " -- Twyla Tharp]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53287-the-care-of-the-earth-is-our-most-ancient-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:58:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53287-the-care-of-the-earth-is-our-most-ancient-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The care of the Earth is our most ancient and most worthy, and after all our most pleasing responsibility. To cherish what remains of it and to foster its renewal is our only hope." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 20:59:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2071-one-of-the-most-important-resources-that-a-garden-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the most important resources that a garden makes available for use, is the gardener's own body. A garden gives the body the dignity of working in its own support. It is a way of rejoining the human race." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8757-if-something-doesn-t-creep-into-a-drawing-that-you-re-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 21:06:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Edward Gorey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8757-if-something-doesn-t-creep-into-a-drawing-that-you-re-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If something doesn't creep into a drawing that you're not prepared for, you might as well not have drawn it." -- Edward Gorey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 21:15:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9748-no-long-term-marriage-is-made-easily-and-there-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No long-term marriage is made easily, and there have been times when I've been so angry or so hurt that I thought my love would never recover. And then, in the midst of near despair, something has happened beneath the surface. A bright little flashing fish of hope has flicked silver fins and the water is bright and suddenly I am returned to a state of love again — till next time. I've learned that there will always be a next time, and that I will submerge in darkness and misery, but that I won't stay submerged. And each time something has been learned under the waters; something has been gained; and a new kind of love has grown. The best I can ask for is that this love, which has been built on countless failures, will continue to grow. I can say no more than that this is mystery, and gift, and that somehow or other, through grace, our failures can be redeemed and blessed." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67382-you-cannot-write-for-children-they-re-much-too-complicated-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 22:11:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Maurice Sendak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67382-you-cannot-write-for-children-they-re-much-too-complicated-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You cannot write for children. They're much too complicated. You can only write books that are of interest to them. " -- Maurice Sendak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 09:20:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37188-i-don-t-want-to-go-on-being-a-root-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 23:52:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37188-i-don-t-want-to-go-on-being-a-root-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to go on being a root in the dark,
vacillating, stretched out, shivering with sleep,
downward, in the soaked guts of the earth,
absorbing and thinking, eating each day." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4691-the-days-aren-t-discarded-or-collected-they-are-bees-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 23:54:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4691-the-days-aren-t-discarded-or-collected-they-are-bees-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The days aren't discarded or collected, they are bees
that burned with sweetness or maddened
the sting: the struggle continues,
the journeys go and come between honey and pain.
No, the net of years doesn't unweave: there is no net.
They don't fall drop by drop from a river: there is no river.
Sleep doesn't divide life into halves,
or action, or silence, or honor:
life is like a stone, a single motion,
a lonesome bonfire reflected on the leaves,
an arrow, only one, slow or swift, a metal
that climbs or descends burning in your bones." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 10:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254298-i-am-struck-by-how-sharing-our-weakness-and-difficulties</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 21:08:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Jean Vanier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254298-i-am-struck-by-how-sharing-our-weakness-and-difficulties]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am struck by how sharing our weakness and difficulties is more nourishing to others than sharing our qualities and successes." -- Jean Vanier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254271-the-response-to-war-is-to-live-like-brothers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 21:10:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Jean Vanier]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254271-the-response-to-war-is-to-live-like-brothers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The response to war is to live like brothers and sisters. The response to injustice is to share. The response to despair is a limitless trust and hope. The response to prejudice and hatred is forgiveness. To work for community is to work for humanity. To work for peace is to work for a true political solution; it is to work for the Kingdom of God. It is to work to enable every one to live and taste the secret joys of the human person united to the eternal." -- Jean Vanier]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220680-of-course-thanks-to-the-house-a-great-many-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2012 13:36:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Gaston Bachelard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220680-of-course-thanks-to-the-house-a-great-many-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of course, thanks to the house, a great many of our memories are housed, and if the house is a bit elaborate, if it has a cellar and a garret, nooks and corridors, our memories have refuges that are all the more clearly delineated. All our lives we come back to them in our daydreams. A psychoanalyst should, therefore, turn his attention to this simple localization of our memories. I should like to give the name of topoanalysis to this auxiliary of pyschoanalysis. Topoanalysis, then would be the systematic psychological study of the sites of our intimate lives." -- Gaston Bachelard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6234-nature-is-a-haunted-house--but-art--is-a-house-that-tries</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 10:34:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gala add a quote by Emily Dickinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6234-nature-is-a-haunted-house--but-art--is-a-house-that-tries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nature is a haunted house--but Art--is a house that tries to be haunted." -- Emily Dickinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
