<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/90797-jeff]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/90797-jeff" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 10:52:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55254-i-know-it-s-long-but-the-whole-thing-is-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2008 10:52:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by William Blake]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55254-i-know-it-s-long-but-the-whole-thing-is-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it's long, but the whole thing is my favorite literary anything--it's from &quot;The Four Zoas&quot;

I am made to sow the thistle for wheat; the nettle for a nourishing dainty
I have planted a false oath in the earth, it has brought forth a poison tree
I have chosen the serpent for a councellor &amp; the dog for a schoolmaster to my children
I have blotted out from light &amp; living the dove &amp; the nightingale
And I have caused the earthworm to beg from door to door			
I have taught the thief a secret path into the house of the just
I have taught pale artifice to spread his nets upon the morning
My heavens are brass my earth is iron my moon a clod of clay
My sun a pestilence burning at noon &amp; a vapor of death in night

What is the price of Experience do men buy it for a song			
Or wisdom for a dance in the street?  No it is bought with the price
Of all that a man hath his house his wife his children
Wisdom is sold in the desolate market where none come to buy
And in the withered field where the farmer plows for bread in vain

It is an easy thing to triumph in the summers sun				
And in the vintage &amp; to sing on the waggon loaded with corn
It is an easy thing to talk of patience to the afflicted
To speak the laws of prudence to the houseless wanderer
To listen to the hungry ravens cry in wintry season
When the red blood is filled with wine &amp; with the marrow of lambs	
It is an easy thing to laugh at wrathful elements
To hear a dog howl at the wintry door, the ox in the slaughter house moan
To see a god on every wind &amp; a blessing on every blast
To hear the sounds of love in the thunder storm that destroys our enemies house
To rejoice in the blight that covers his field, &amp; the sickness that cuts off his children

While our olive &amp; vine sing &amp; laugh round our door &amp; our children bring fruits 	and flowers
Then the groans &amp; the dolor are quite forgotten &amp; the slave grinding at the mill
And the captive in chains &amp; the poor in the prison, &amp; the soldier in the field
When the shattered bone hath laid him groaning among the happier dead

It is an easy thing to rejoice in the tents of prosperity			
Thus could I sing &amp; thus rejoice, but it is not so with me!" -- William Blake]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166448-they-heard-somewhere-in-that-tenantless-night-a-bell-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 15:36:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166448-they-heard-somewhere-in-that-tenantless-night-a-bell-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They heard somewhere in that tenantless night a bell that tolled and ceased where no bell was and they rode out on the round dais of the earth which alone was dark and no light to it and which carried their figures and bore them up into the swarming stars so that they rode not under but among them and they rode at once jaunty and circumspect, like thieves newly loosed in that dark electric, like young thieves in a glowing orchard, loosely jacketed against the cold and ten thousand worlds for the choosing." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200103-ah-not-to-be-cut-off-not-through-the-slightest</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 15:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/200103-ah-not-to-be-cut-off-not-through-the-slightest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah, not to be cut off,
not through the slightest partition
shut out from the law of the stars.
The inner -- what is it?
if not the intensified sky,
hurled through with birds and deep
with the winds of homecoming." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119739-up-up-and-quit-your-books-is-not-an-adjuration</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 18:25:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Joseph Wood Krutch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119739-up-up-and-quit-your-books-is-not-an-adjuration]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Up up and quit your books' is not an adjuration commonly thought advisable in universities but there are occasions    -- as for instance, when studying Wordsworth when it might be advisable." -- Joseph Wood Krutch]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
