<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/907919-ellen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/907919-ellen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 11:50:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302502-it-occurs-to-me-that-just-as-the-carthaginians-hired</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2010 11:50:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302502-it-occurs-to-me-that-just-as-the-carthaginians-hired]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It occurs to me that just as the Carthaginians hired mercenaries to do their fighting for them, we Americans being in mercenaries to do our hard and humble work. I hope we may not be overwhelmed one day by peoples not too proud or too lazy or too soft to bend to the earth and pick up the things we eat." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244513-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-an-earthquake</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 08:37:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Louis de Bernières]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244513-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-an-earthquake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness. It erupts like an earthquake and then subsides. And when it subsides you have to make a decision. You have to work out whether your roots have become so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part. Because this is what love is. Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion. That is just being &quot;in love&quot; which any of us can convince ourselves we are. Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident. Your mother and I had it, we had roots that grew towards each other underground, and when all the pretty blossom had fallen from our branches we found that we were one tree and not two." -- Louis de Bernières]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 07:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53993-i-think-if-it-is-true-that-there-are-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think... if it is true that 
there are as many minds as there 
are heads, then there are as many 
kinds of love as there are hearts." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413703-i-could-see-how-you-could-do-extreme-things-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 12:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413703-i-could-see-how-you-could-do-extreme-things-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could see how you could do extreme things for the person you loved. Adam One said that when you loved a person, that love might not always get returned the way you wanted, but it was a good thing anyway because love went out all around you like an energy wave, and a creature you didn't know would be helped by it." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701238-according-to-adam-one-the-fall-of-man-was-multidimensional</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2014 12:47:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/701238-according-to-adam-one-the-fall-of-man-was-multidimensional]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to Adam One, the Fall of Man was multidimensional. The ancestral primates fell out of the trees; then they fell from vegetarianism into meat-eating. Then they fell from instinct into reason, and thus into technology; from simple signals into complex grammar, and thus into humanity; from firelessness into fire, and thence into weaponry; and from seasonal mating into an incessant sexual twitching. Then they fell from a joyous life in the moment into the anxious contemplation of the vanished past and the distant future." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
