<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/907910-jason]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/907910-jason" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 12:12:50 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30564-in-chloe-a-great-city-the-people-who-move-through</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 12:12:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30564-in-chloe-a-great-city-the-people-who-move-through]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Chloe, a great city, the people who move through the streets are all strangers.  At each encounter, they imagine a thousand things about one another; meetings which could take place between them, conversations, surprises, caresses, bites.  But no one greets anyone; eyes lock for a second, then dart away, seeking other eyes, never stopping.
	
A girl comes along, twirling a parasol on her shoulder, and twirling slightly also her rounded hips.  A woman in black comes along, showing her full age, her eyes restless beneath her veil, her lips trembling.  At tattooed giant comes along; a young man with white hair; a female dwarf; two girls, twins, dressed in coral.  Something runs among them, an exchange of glances link lines that connect one figure with another and draws arrows, stars, triangles, until all combinations are used up in a moment, and other characters come on to the scene: a blind man with a cheetah on a leash, a courtesan with an ostrich-plume fan, an ephebe, a Fat Woman.  And thus, when some people happen to find themselves together, taking shelter from the rain under an arcade, or crowding beneath an awning of the bazaar, or stopping to listen to the band in the square, meetings, seductions, copulations, orgies are consummated among them without a word exchanged, without a finger touching anything, almost without an eye raised.  

	A voluptuous vibration constantly stirs Chloe, the most chaste of cities.  If men and women began to live their ephemeral dreams, every phantom would become a person with whom to begin a story of pursuits, pretenses, misunderstandings, clashes, oppressions, and the carousel of fantasies would stop." -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30958-conditioned-to-ecstasy-the-poet-is-like-a-gorgeous-unknown</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 12:25:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30958-conditioned-to-ecstasy-the-poet-is-like-a-gorgeous-unknown]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Conditioned to ecstasy, the poet is like a gorgeous unknown bird mired in the ashes of thought. If he succeeds in freeing himself, it is to make a sacrificial flight to the sun. His dreams of a regenerate world are but the reverberations of his own fevered pulse beats. He imagines the world will follow him, but in the blue he finds himself alone. Alone but surrounded by his creations; sustained, therefore, to meet the supreme sacrifice. The impossible has been achieved; the duologue of author with Author is consummated. And now forever through the ages the song expands, warming all hearts, penetrating all minds. At the periphery the world is dying away; at the center it glows like a live coal. In the great solar heart of the universe the golden birds are gathered in unison. There it is forever dawn, forever peace, harmony and communion. Man does not look to the sun in vain; he demands light and warmth not for the corpse which he will one day discard but for his inner being. His greatest desire is to burn with ecstasy, to commerge his little flame with the central fire of the universe. If he accords the angels wings so that they may come to him with messages of peace, harmony and radiance from worlds beyond, it is only to nourish his own dreams of flight, to sustain his own belief that he will one day reach beyond himself, and on wings of gold. One creation matches another; in essence they are all alike. The brotherhood of man consists not in thinking alike, nor in acting alike, but in aspiring to praise creation. The song of creation springs from the ruins of earthly endeavor. The outer man dies away in order to reveal the golden bird which is winging its way toward divinity." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16188-someone-told-me-the-delightful-story-of-the-crusader-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 16:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16188-someone-told-me-the-delightful-story-of-the-crusader-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone told me the delightful story of the crusader who put a chastity belt on his wife and gave the key to his best friend for safekeeping, in case of his death. He had ridden only a few miles away when his friend, riding hard, caught up with him, saying 'You gave me the wrong key!" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9919-my-first-time-i-jacked-off-i-thought-i-d-invented</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 16:33:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9919-my-first-time-i-jacked-off-i-thought-i-d-invented]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My first time I jacked off, I thought I'd invented it. I looked down at my sloppy handful of junk and thought, This is going to make me rich." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8451-sex-is-good-but-not-as-good-as-fresh-sweet</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 16:35:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8451-sex-is-good-but-not-as-good-as-fresh-sweet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex is good, but not as good as fresh sweet corn." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16148-what-does-one-want-when-one-is-engaged-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 16:38:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Marquis de Sade]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16148-what-does-one-want-when-one-is-engaged-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What does one want when one is engaged in the sexual act? That everything around you give you its utter attention, think only of you, care only for you...every man wants to be a tyrant when he fornicates." -- Marquis de Sade]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9903-but-truly-i-have-wept-too-much-the-dawns-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 16:44:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9903-but-truly-i-have-wept-too-much-the-dawns-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, truly, I have wept too much! The Dawns are heartbreaking. Every moon is atrocious and every sun bitter." -- Arthur Rimbaud]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38211-season-late-day-late-sun-just-down-and-the-sky</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 11:49:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38211-season-late-day-late-sun-just-down-and-the-sky]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Season late, day late, sun just down, and the sky
Cold gunmetal but with a wash of live rose, and she,
From water the color of sky except where
Her motion has fractured it to shivering splinters of silver,
Rises. Stands on the raw grass. Against
The new-curdling night of spruces, nakedness
Glimmers and, at bosom and flank, drips
With fluent silver. The man,
 
Some ten strokes out, but now hanging
Motionless in the gunmetal water, feet
Cold with the coldness of depth, all
History dissolving from him, is
Nothing but an eye. Is an eye only. Sees
 
The body that is marked by his use, and Time's,
Rise, and in the abrupt and unsustaining element of air,
Sway, lean, grapple the pond-bank. Sees
How, with that posture of female awkwardness that is,
And is the stab of, suddenly perceived grace, breasts bulge down in
The pure curve of their weight and buttocks
Moon up and, in swelling unity,
Are silver and glimmer. Then
 
The body is erect, she is herself, whatever
Self she may be, and with an end of the towel grasped in each hand,
Slowly draws it back and forth across back and buttocks, but
With face lifted toward the high sky, where
The over-wash of rose color now fails. Fails, though no star
Yet throbs there. The towel, forgotten,
Does not move now. The gaze
Remains fixed on the sky. The body,
 
Profiled against the darkness of spruces, seems
To draw to itself, and condense in its whiteness, what light
In the sky yet lingers or, from
The metallic and abstract severity of water, lifts. The body,
With the towel now trailing loose from one hand, is
A white stalk from which the face flowers gravely toward the high sky.
This moment is non-sequential and absolute, and admits
Of no definition, for it
Subsumes all other, and sequential, moments, by which
Definition might be possible. The woman,
 
Face yet raised, wraps,
With a motion as though standing in sleep,
The towel about her body, under her breasts, and,
Holding it there hieratic as lost Egypt and erect,
Moves up the path that, stair-steep, winds
Into the clamber and tangle of growth. Beyond
The lattice of dusk-dripping leaves, whiteness
Dimly glimmers, goes. Glimmers and is gone, and the man,
 
Suspended in his darkling medium, stares
Upward where, though not visible, he knows
She moves, and in his heart he cries out that, if only
He had such strength, he would put his hand forth
And maintain it over her to guard, in all
Her out-goings and in-comings, from whatever
Inclemency of sky or slur of the world's weather
Might ever be. In his heart he cries out. Above
 
Height of the spruce-night and heave of the far mountain, he sees
The first star pulse into being. It gleams there.
 
I do not know what promise it makes him. " -- Robert Penn Warren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38212-my-wife-with-the-hair-of-a-wood-fire-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2008 11:50:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38212-my-wife-with-the-hair-of-a-wood-fire-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My wife with the hair of a wood fire
With the thoughts of heat lightning
With the waist of an hourglass
With the waist of an otter in the teeth of a tiger
My wife with the lips of a cockade and of a bunch of stars of the last magnitude
With the teeth of tracks of white mice on the white earth
With the tongue of rubbed amber and glass
My wife with the tongue of a stabbed host
With the tongue of a doll that opens and closes its eyes
With the tongue of an unbelievable stone
My wife with the eyelashes of strokes of a child's writing
With brows of the edge of a swallow's nest
My wife with the brow of slates of a hothouse roof
And of steam on the panes
My wife with shoulders of champagne
And of a fountain with dolphin-heads beneath the ice
My wife with wrists of matches
My wife with fingers of luck and ace of hearts
With fingers of mown hay
My wife with armpits of marten and of beechnut
And of Midsummer Night
Of privet and of an angelfish nest
With arms of seafoam and of riverlocks
And of a mingling of the wheat and the mill
My wife with legs of flares
With the movements of clockwork and despair
My wife with calves of eldertree pith
My wife with feet of initials
With feet of rings of keys and Java sparrows drinking
My wife with a neck of unpearled barley
My wife with a throat of the valley of gold
Of a tryst in the very bed of the torrent
With breasts of night
My wife with breasts of a marine molehill
My wife with breasts of the ruby's crucible
With breasts of the rose's spectre beneath the dew
My wife with the belly of an unfolding of the fan of days
With the belly of a gigantic claw
My wife with the back of a bird fleeing vertically
With a back of quicksilver
With a back of light
With a nape of rolled stone and wet chalk
And of the drop of a glass where one has just been drinking
My wife with hips of a skiff
With hips of a chandelier and of arrow-feathers
And of shafts of white peacock plumes
Of an insensible pendulum
My wife with buttocks of sandstone and asbestos
My wife with buttocks of swans' backs
My wife with buttocks of spring
With the sex of an iris
My wife with the sex of a mining-placer and of a platypus
My wife with a sex of seaweed and ancient sweetmeat
My wife with a sex of mirror
My wife with eyes full of tears
With eyes of purple panoply and of a magnetic needle
My wife with savanna eyes
My wife with eyes of water to he drunk in prison
My wife with eyes of wood always under the axe
My wife with eyes of water-level of level of air earth and fire" -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55606-night-train-miami-florida-atlanta-georgia-raleigh-north-carolina-miami</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 15:47:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by James Brown, &quot;Night Train&quot;]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55606-night-train-miami-florida-atlanta-georgia-raleigh-north-carolina-miami]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Night train
Miami, Florida
Atlanta, Georgia
Raleigh, North Carolina
Miami, Florida
Atlanta, Georgia
Raleigh, North Carolina
Washington D.C.

Or West Virginia, too
Butte, Montana
Philadelphia
New York City
Boston, Massachussets
And I don't get to New Orleans
Whole in a roof
Night train" -- James Brown, &quot;Night Train&quot;]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63567-most-of-my-friends-like-words-too-well-they-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 09:45:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Jack Spicer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63567-most-of-my-friends-like-words-too-well-they-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of my friends like words too well. They set them under the blinding light of the poem and try to extract every possible connotation from each of them, every temporary pun, every direct or indirect connection - as if a word could become an object by mere addition of consequences. Others pick up words from the streets, from their bars, from their offices and display them proudly in their poems as if they were shouting, &quot;See what I have collected from the American language. Look at my butterflies, my stamps, my old shoes!&quot; What does one do with all this crap?" -- Jack Spicer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7187-see-how-weak-prose-is-presently-i-shall-go-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 09:45:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Jack Spicer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7187-see-how-weak-prose-is-presently-i-shall-go-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["See how weak prose is.... Presently I shall go to a bar and there one or two poets will speak to me and I to them and we will try to destroy each other or attract each other and nothing will happen because we will be speaking in prose." -- Jack Spicer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125280-holy-spirits-you-walk-up-there-in-the-light-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 14:02:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Friedrich Holderlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125280-holy-spirits-you-walk-up-there-in-the-light-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Holy spirits, you walk up there
     in the light, on soft earth.
          Shining god-like breezes
               touch upon you gently,
                    as a woman's fingers
                         play music on holy strings.

Like sleeping infants the gods
     breathe without any plan;
          the spirit flourishes continually
               in them, chastely kept,
                    as in a small bud,
                         and their holy eyes
                              look out in still
                                   eternal clearness.

A place to rest
     isn't given to us.
          Suffering humans
               decline and blindly fall
                    from one hour to the next,
                         like water thrown
                              from cliff to cliff,
                                   year after year,
                                        down into the Unknown." -- Friedrich Holderlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116512-all-the-fruit-is-ripe-plunged-in-fire-cooked-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 14:04:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Friedrich Holderlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116512-all-the-fruit-is-ripe-plunged-in-fire-cooked-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the fruit is ripe, plunged in fire, cooked,
And they have passed their test on earth, and one law is this:
That everything curls inward, like snakes,
Prophetic, dreaming on
The hills of heaven. And many things
Have to stay on the shoulders like a load
of failure. However the roads
Are bad. For the chained elements,
Like horses, are going off to the side,
And the old
Laws of the earth. And a longing
For disintegration constantly comes. Many things however
Have to stay on the shoulders. Steadiness is essential.
Forwards, however, or backwards we will
Not look. Let us learn to live swaying
As in a rocking boat on the sea." -- Friedrich Holderlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125282-the-sexual-eagle-exults-he-will-gild-the-earth-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 14:11:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125282-the-sexual-eagle-exults-he-will-gild-the-earth-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sexual eagle exults he will gild the earth once more
his descending wing
his ascending wing sways imperceptibly the sleeves of the peppermint
and all the water's adorable undress
Days are counted so clearly
that the mirror has yielded to a froth of fronds
of the sky i see but one star
now around us there is only the milk describing its dizzy ellipsis
from which sometimes soft intuition with pupils of eyed agate
rises to poke its umbrella tip in the mud of the electric light
then great reaches cast anchor stretch out in the depths of my closed eyes
icebergs radiating the customs of all the worlds yet to come
bron from a fragment of you fragment unkown and iced on the wing
your existence the giant bouquet escaping fr4om my arms
is badly tied it didgs out walls unrolls the stairs of houses
loses its leaves in the show windows of the street
to gether the news i am always leaving to gather the news
the newspaper is glass today and if letters no longer arrive
it's that the train has been consumed
the great incision of the emerald which gaave birth to the foliage
is scarred for always the sawdust of blinding snow
and the quarries of flesh are sounding along on the first shelf
reversed on this shelf
i take the impression of death and life
to the liquid air" -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54981-ain-t-no-sense-worryin-about-the-things-you-got-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 17:51:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Mickey Rivers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54981-ain-t-no-sense-worryin-about-the-things-you-got-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ain't no sense worryin' about the things you got control over, 'cause if you got control over 'em, ain't no sense worryin'. And ain't no sense worryin' about the things you don't got control over, 'cause if you don't got control over 'em, ain't no sense worryin'." -- Mickey Rivers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109037-i-never-think-of-policemen-s-wives-their-beauty-maddens-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2009 17:54:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Kyril Bonfiglioli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109037-i-never-think-of-policemen-s-wives-their-beauty-maddens-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never think of policemen's wives; their beauty maddens me like wine." -- Kyril Bonfiglioli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132019-bed-is-the-only-place-for-protracted-telephoning-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 02:05:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Kyril Bonfiglioli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132019-bed-is-the-only-place-for-protracted-telephoning-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bed is the only place for protracted telephoning. It is also execellently suited to reading, sleeping and listening to canaries. It is not a good place for sex: sex should take place in armchairs, or in bathrooms, or on lawns which have been brushed but not too recently mown, or on sandy beaches if you happen to have been circumcised. If you are too tired to have intercourse except in bed you are probably too tired anyway and should be husbanding your strength." -- Kyril Bonfiglioli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134640-to-poke-its-umbrella-tip-in-the-mud-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 02:10:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134640-to-poke-its-umbrella-tip-in-the-mud-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["to poke its umbrella tip in the mud of the electric light " -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132497-the-pure-playfulness-of-certain-wholly-whimsical-portions-of-charles</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 02:11:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132497-the-pure-playfulness-of-certain-wholly-whimsical-portions-of-charles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The pure playfulness of certain wholly whimsical portions of (Charles) Cros’s work should not obscure the fact that at the center of some of his most beautiful poems a revolver is leveled straight at us." -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132496-past-and-future-monopolize-the-poet-s-sensory-and-intellectual-faculties</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 02:11:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Andre Breton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132496-past-and-future-monopolize-the-poet-s-sensory-and-intellectual-faculties]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Past and future monopolize the poet’s sensory and intellectual faculties, detached from the immediate spectacle. These two philtres become utterly clear the moment one stops being hypnotized by the cloudy precipitate constituted by the world of today." -- Andre Breton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134749-the-traditional-statement-about-language-is-that-it-is-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 14:51:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Jacques Derrida]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134749-the-traditional-statement-about-language-is-that-it-is-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The traditional statement about language is that it is in itself living, and that writing is the dead part of language." -- Jacques Derrida]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56108-life-the-machine-the-human-soul-a-75mm-breech-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 17:33:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Blaise Cendrars]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56108-life-the-machine-the-human-soul-a-75mm-breech-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life
The machine
The human soul
A 75mm breech
My portrait" -- Blaise Cendrars]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138211-i-used-the-word-prose-in-the-trans-siberian-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2009 12:02:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Blaise Cendrars]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138211-i-used-the-word-prose-in-the-trans-siberian-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used the word 'prose' in the Trans-Siberian in the early Latin sense of &lt;i&gt;prosa dictu&lt;/i&gt;. Poem seemed to me too pretentious, too narrow. Prose is more open, popular." -- Blaise Cendrars]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138887-i-moved-through-the-days-like-a-severed-head-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 20:49:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Amy Hempel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138887-i-moved-through-the-days-like-a-severed-head-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I moved through the days like a severed head that finishes a sentence." -- Amy Hempel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139961-skirting-the-river-road-my-forenoon-walk-my-rest-skyward</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2009 19:25:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/139961-skirting-the-river-road-my-forenoon-walk-my-rest-skyward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["SKIRTING the river road, (my forenoon walk, my rest,)	 
Skyward in air a sudden muffled sound, the dalliance of the eagles,	 
The rushing amorous contact high in space together,	 
The clinching interlocking claws, a living, fierce, gyrating wheel,	 
Four beating wings, two beaks, a swirling mass tight grappling,	         5
In tumbling turning clustering loops, straight downward falling,	 
Till o’er the river pois’d, the twain yet one, a moment’s lull,	 
A motionless still balance in the air, then parting, talons loosing,	 
Upward again on slow-firm pinions slanting, their separate diverse flight,	 
She hers, he his, pursuing." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140324-poetry-is-a-will-to-put-things-right-an-imaginary</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 21:53:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Aase Berg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140324-poetry-is-a-will-to-put-things-right-an-imaginary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry is a will to put things right, an imaginary solution, a way of avoiding a catastrophe that already happened. Poetry is an escape, perhaps intelligent, perhaps idiotic, from a senile situation. It is a dialectical movement, it keeps tearing open the wounds while trying to heal them. Here we see the only acceptable path open up towards an existence worthy of human beings. Here the seriousness is unfaltering and absolute. Where it will lead no one knows." -- Aase Berg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143667-my-friend-isabel-says-when-you-re-writing-even-a-short</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 19:03:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Sarah Manguso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143667-my-friend-isabel-says-when-you-re-writing-even-a-short]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;My friend Isabel says, When you’re writing even a short novel, with at least a couple of subplots, and God only knows how many characters, your brain holds the volume of it beyond the ability of your consciousness.

Of course&lt;/i&gt;." -- Sarah Manguso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149812-the-beat-generation-that-was-a-vision-that-we-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2009 15:16:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149812-the-beat-generation-that-was-a-vision-that-we-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Beat Generation, that was a vision that we had, John Clellon Holmes and I, and Allen Ginsberg in an even wilder way, in the late forties, of a generation of crazy, illuminated hipsters suddenly rising and roaming America, serious, bumming and hitchhiking everywhere, ragged, beatific, beautiful in an ugly graceful new way--a vision gleaned from the way we had heard the word 'beat' spoken on streetcorners on Times Square and in the Village, in other cities in the downtown city night of postwar America--beat, meaning down and out but full of intense conviction--We'd even heard old 1910 Daddy Hipsters of the streets speak the word that way, with a melancholy sneer--It never meant juvenile delinquents, it meant characters of a special spirituality who didn't gang up but were solitary Bartlebies staring out the dead wall window of our civilization--the subterraneans heroes who'd finally turned from the 'freedom' machine of the West and were taking drugs, digging bop, having flashes of insight, experiencing the 'derangement of the senses,' talking strange, being poor and glad, prophesying a new style for American culture, a new style (we thought), a new incantation--The same thing was almost going on in the postwar France of Sartre and Genet and what's more we knew about it--But as to the actual existence of a Beat Generation, chances are it was really just an idea in our minds--We'd stay up 24 hours drinking cup after cup of black coffee, playing record after record of Wardell Gray, Lester Young, Dexter Gordon, Willie Jackson, Lennie Tristano and all the rest, talking madly about that holy new feeling out there in the streets- -We'd write stories about some strange beatific Negro hepcat saint with goatee hitchhiking across Iowa with taped up horn bringing the secret message of blowing to other coasts, other cities, like a veritable Walter the Penniless leading an invisible First Crusade- -We had our mystic heroes and wrote, nay sung novels about them, erected long poems celebrating the new 'angels' of the American underground--In actuality there was only a handful of real hip swinging cats and what there was vanished mightily swiftly during the Korean War when (and after) a sinister new kind of efficiency appeared in America, maybe it was the result of the universalization of Television and nothing else (the Polite Total Police Control of Dragnet's 'peace' officers) but the beat characters after 1950 vanished into jails and madhouses, or were shamed into silent conformity, the generation itself was shortlived and small in number." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16024-the-shadow-proves-the-sunshine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2009 12:47:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jason add a quote by Switchfoot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16024-the-shadow-proves-the-sunshine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The shadow proves the sunshine." -- Switchfoot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
