<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/908088-karen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/908088-karen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:34:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475014-if-this-were-fiction-could-even-the-most-brilliant-novelist</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2012 08:34:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by P.D. James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475014-if-this-were-fiction-could-even-the-most-brilliant-novelist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If this were fiction, could even the most brilliant novelist contrive to make credible so short a period in which pride had been subdued and prejudice overcome?" -- P.D. James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730343-the-condition-of-women-in-a-nation-is-the-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 05:17:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Ngũgĩ wa Thiong'o]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730343-the-condition-of-women-in-a-nation-is-the-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The condition of women in a nation is the real measure of its progress." -- Ngũgĩ wa Thiong'o]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730350-why-did-africa-let-europe-cart-away-millions-of-africa-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 05:24:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Ngũgĩ wa Thiong'o]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/730350-why-did-africa-let-europe-cart-away-millions-of-africa-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why did Africa let Europe cart away millions of Africa's souls from the continent to the four corners of the wind? How could Europe lord it over a continent ten times its size? Why does needy Africa continue to let its wealth meet the needs of those outside its borders and then follow behind with hands outstretched for a loan of the very wealth it let go? How did we arrive at this, that the best leader is the one that knows how to beg for a share of what he has already given away at the price of a broken tool? Where is the future of Africa?" -- Ngũgĩ wa Thiong'o]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626030-but-of-course-you-might-be-asking-yourself-am-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 06:00:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626030-but-of-course-you-might-be-asking-yourself-am-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But, of course, you might be asking yourself, 'Am I a feminist? I might not be. I don't know! I still don't know what it is! I'm too knackered and confused to work it out. That curtain pole really still isn't up! I don't have time to work out if I am a women's libber! There seems to be a lot to it. WHAT DOES IT MEAN?'
I understand. 
So here is the quick way of working out if you're a feminist. Put your hand in your pants.

a) Do you have a vagina? and
b) Do you want to be in charge of it?

If you said 'yes' to both, then congratulations! You're a feminist." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626235-it-s-difficult-to-see-the-glass-ceiling-because-it-s-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2013 06:00:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Caitlin Moran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/626235-it-s-difficult-to-see-the-glass-ceiling-because-it-s-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's difficult to see the glass ceiling because it's made of glass. Virtually invisible. What we need is for more birds to fly above it and shit all over it, so we can see it properly." -- Caitlin Moran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706414-there-is-an-unfair-responsibility-that-comes-with-being-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 08:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706414-there-is-an-unfair-responsibility-that-comes-with-being-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is an unfair responsibility that comes with being an only child - you grow up knowing you aren't allowed to disappoint, you're not even allowed to die. There isn't a replacement toddling around; you're it. It makes you desperate to be flawless, and it also makes you drunk with the power. In such ways are despots made." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719716-americans-are-pushy-obnoxious-neurotic-crass---anything-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 05:49:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Karen add a quote by Maria Semple]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/719716-americans-are-pushy-obnoxious-neurotic-crass---anything-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Americans are pushy, obnoxious, neurotic, crass - anything and everything - the full catastrophe as our friend Zorba might say. Canadians are none of that. The way you might fear a cow sitting down in the middle of the street during rush hour, that's how I fear Canadians. To Canadians, everyone is equal. Joni Mitchell is interchangeable with a secretary at open-mic night. Frank Gehry is no greater than a hack pumping out McMansions on AutoCAD. John Candy is no funnier than Uncle Lou when he gets a couple of beers in him. No wonder the only Canadians anyone's ever heard of are the ones who have gotten the hell out. Anyone with talent who stayed would be flattened under an avalanche of equality. The thing Canadians don't understand is that some people are extraordinary and should be treated as such." -- Maria Semple]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
