<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/909064-katie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/909064-katie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:45:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59451-why-didn-t-i-learn-to-treat-everything-like-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:45:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59451-why-didn-t-i-learn-to-treat-everything-like-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why didn't I learn to treat everything like it was the last time. My greatest regret was how much I believed in the future." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:45:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12278-i-think-and-think-and-think-i-ve-thought-myself-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think and think and think, I‘ve thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47078-i-went-to-a-tattoo-parlor-and-had-yes-written</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:46:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47078-i-went-to-a-tattoo-parlor-and-had-yes-written]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to a tattoo parlor and had YES written onto the palm of my left hand, and NO onto my right palm, what can I say, it hasn't made my life wonderful, its made life possible, when I rub my hands against each other in the middle of winter I am warming myself with the friction of YES and NO, when I clap my hands I am showing my appreciation through the uniting and parting of YES and NO, I signify &quot;book&quot; by peeling open my hands, every book, for me, is the balance of YES and NO, even this one, my last one, especially this one. Does it break my heart, of course, every moment of every day, into more pieces than my heart was made of, I never thought of myself as quiet, much less silent, I never thought about things at all, everything changed, the distance that wedged itself between me and my happiness wasn't the world, it wasn't the bombs and burning buildings, it was me, my thinking, the cancer of never letting go, is ignorance bliss, I don't know, but it's so painful to think, and tell me, what did thinking ever do for me, to what great place did thinking ever bring me? I think and think and think, I've thought myself out of happiness one million times, but never once into it." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47075-we-slept-in-the-same-bed-there-was-never-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:46:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47075-we-slept-in-the-same-bed-there-was-never-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We slept in the same bed.
There was never a right time to say it.
It was always unnecessary.
The books in my father's shed were sighing.
The sheets were rising and falling around me with Anna's breathing.
I thought about waking her.
but it was unnecessary.
There would be other nights.
And how can you say I love you to someone you love?
I rolled onto my side and fell asleep next to her.
Here is the point of everything I have been trying to tell you...
It's always necessary.
I love you,..." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16198-love-is-blind-they-say-sex-is-impervious-to-reason</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:48:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16198-love-is-blind-they-say-sex-is-impervious-to-reason]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is blind, they say; sex is impervious to reason and mocks the power of all philosophers. But, in fact, a person's sexual choice is the result and sum of their fundamental convictions. Tell me what a person finds sexually attractive and I will tell you their entire philosophy of life. Show me the person they sleep with and I will tell you their valuation of themselves. No matter what corruption they're taught about the virtue of selflessness, sex is the most profoundly selfish of all acts, an act which they cannot perform for any motive but their own enjoyment - just try to think of performing it in a spirit of selfless charity! - an act which is not possible in self-abasement, only in self-exultation, only on the confidence of being desired and being worthy of desire. It is an act that forces them to stand naked in spirit, as well as in body, and accept their real ego as their standard of value. They will always be attracted to the person who reflects their deepest vision of themselves, the person whose surrender permits them to experience - or to fake - a sense of self-esteem .. Love is our response to our highest values - and can be nothing else." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:50:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10715-i-have-the-choice-of-being-constantly-active-and-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2009 21:50:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10715-i-have-the-choice-of-being-constantly-active-and-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have the choice of being constantly active and happy or introspectively passive and sad. Or I can go mad by ricocheting in between." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
