<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/909713-jailynn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/909713-jailynn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:18:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20606-the-homemaker-has-the-ultimate-career-all-other-careers-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:18:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20606-the-homemaker-has-the-ultimate-career-all-other-careers-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The homemaker has the ultimate career.  All other careers exist for one purpose only - and that is to support the ultimate career.  " -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 23:40:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all the world hated you and believed you wicked, while your own conscience approved of you and absolved you from guilt, you would not be without friends." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:37:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18290-they-spoke-almost-as-loud-as-feeling-and-that-clamoured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They spoke almost as loud as Feeling: and that clamoured wildly. &quot;Oh, comply!&quot; it said. &quot;Think of his misery; think of his danger — look at his state when left alone; remember his headlong nature; consider the recklessness following on despair — soothe him; save him; love him; tell him you love him and will be his. Who in the world cares for you? or who will be injured by what you do?&quot;

Still indomitable was the reply — &quot;I care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself. I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. I will hold to the principles received by me when I was sane, and not mad — as I am now. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth? They have a worth — so I have always believed; and if I cannot believe it now, it is because I am quite insane — quite insane: with my veins running fire, and my heart beating faster than I can count its throbs. Preconceived opinions, foregone determinations, are all I have this hour to stand by: there I plant my foot." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5897-for-like-a-shaft-clear-and-cold-the-thought-pierced</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:39:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5897-for-like-a-shaft-clear-and-cold-the-thought-pierced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For like a shaft, clear and cold, the thought pierced him that in the end the Shadow was only a small and passing thing: there was light and high beauty for ever beyond its reach." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22760-what-do-you-fear-lady-aragorn-asked-a-cage-owyn</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22760-what-do-you-fear-lady-aragorn-asked-a-cage-owyn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What do you fear, lady?&quot; [Aragorn] asked. 
&quot;A cage,&quot; [Éowyn] said. &quot;To stay behind bars, until use and old age accept them, and all chance of doing great deeds is gone beyond recall or desire." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:44:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14414-we-re-so-busy-watching-out-for-what-s-just-ahead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 00:59:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14414-we-re-so-busy-watching-out-for-what-s-just-ahead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're so busy watching out for what's just ahead of us that we don't take time to enjoy where we are." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24219-there-s-never-enough-time-to-do-all-the-nothing-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:01:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24219-there-s-never-enough-time-to-do-all-the-nothing-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's never enough time to do all the nothing you want." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:04:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10682-you-don-t-have-a-soul-doctor-you-are-a-soul]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a soul, Doctor. You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; a soul. You &lt;i&gt;have&lt;/i&gt; a body, temporarily." -- Walter M. Miller Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6493-a-children-s-story-that-can-only-be-enjoyed-by-children</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:04:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6493-a-children-s-story-that-can-only-be-enjoyed-by-children]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A children's story that can only be enjoyed by children is not a good children's story in the slightest." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:05:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6439-if-we-find-ourselves-with-a-desire-that-nothing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we find ourselves with a desire that nothing in this world can satisfy, the most probable explanation is that we were made for another world." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:09:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23974-it-is-a-good-rule-after-reading-a-new-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:10:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23974-it-is-a-good-rule-after-reading-a-new-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a good rule after reading a new book, never to allow yourself another new one till you have read an old one in between." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416-make-it-a-rule-never-to-give-a-child-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2008 01:14:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416-make-it-a-rule-never-to-give-a-child-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make it a rule never to give a child a book you would not read yourself." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43211-a-man-who-tells-secrets-or-stories-must-think-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 12:40:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43211-a-man-who-tells-secrets-or-stories-must-think-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who tells secrets or stories must think of who is hearing or reading, for a story has as many versions as it has readers. Everyone takes what he wants or can from it and thus changes it to his measure. Some pick out parts and reject the rest, some strain the story through their mesh of prejudice, some paint it with their own delight. A story must have some points of contact with the reader to make him feel at home in it. Only then can he accept wonders." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43210-are-cats-strange-animals-or-do-they-so-resemble-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 12:42:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43210-are-cats-strange-animals-or-do-they-so-resemble-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are cats strange animals or do they so resemble us that we find them curious as we do monkeys?" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43215-let-s-say-that-when-i-was-a-little-baby-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 12:44:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43215-let-s-say-that-when-i-was-a-little-baby-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's say that when I was a little baby, and all my bones soft and malleable, I was put in a small Episcopal cruciform box and so took my shape. Then, when I broke out of the box, the way a baby chick escapes an egg, is it strange that I had the shape of a cross? Have you ever noticed that chickens are roughly egg-shaped?" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138810-there-is-more-beauty-in-truth-even-if-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2008 13:32:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138810-there-is-more-beauty-in-truth-even-if-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is more beauty in truth, even if it is a dreadful beauty. The storytellers at the city gate twist life so that it looks sweet to the lazy and the stupid and the weak, and this only strengthens their infirmities and teaches nothing, cures nothing, nor does it let the heart soar." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 14:26:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you take a book with you on a journey,&quot; Mo had said when he put the first one in her box, &quot;an odd thing happens: The book begins collecting your memories. And forever after you have only to open that book to be back where you first read it. It will all come into your mind with the very first words: the sights you saw in that place, what it smelled like, the ice cream you ate while you were reading it... yes, books are like flypaper—memories cling to the printed page better than anything else." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 14:26:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23452-isn-t-it-odd-how-much-fatter-a-book-gets-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it odd how much fatter a book gets when you've read it several times?&quot; Mo had said...&quot;As if something were left between the pages every time you read it.  Feelings, thoughts, sounds, smells...and then, when you look at the book again many years later, you find yourself there, too, a slightly younger self, slightly different, as if the book had preserved you like a pressed flower...both strange and familiar." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35424-this-book-taught-me-once-and-for-all-how-easily</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 14:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35424-this-book-taught-me-once-and-for-all-how-easily]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This book taught me, once and for all, how easily you can escape this world with the help of words!  You can find friends between the pages of a book, wonderful friends." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50285-the-world-was-a-terrible-place-cruel-pitiless-dark-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 14:27:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50285-the-world-was-a-terrible-place-cruel-pitiless-dark-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world was a terrible place, cruel, pitiless, dark as a bad dream. Not a good place to live. Only in books could you find pity, comfort, happiness - and love. Books loved anyone who opened them, they gave you security and friendship and didn't ask anything in return; they never went away, never, not even when you treated them badly." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131173-but-will-you-not-have-a-house-to-care-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2009 18:51:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Gloria Whelan ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131173-but-will-you-not-have-a-house-to-care-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But will you not have a house to care for?  Meals to cook?  Children whining for this or that?  Will you have time for the work?&quot;  &quot;I'll make time,&quot;  I promised. &quot;The house will not always be so clean, the cooking may be a little hasty, and the whining children will sit on my lap and I'll sing to them while I work." -- Gloria Whelan ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:17:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11895-one-final-paragraph-of-advice-do-not-burn-yourselves-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One final paragraph of advice: do not burn yourselves out. Be as I am - a reluctant enthusiast....a part-time crusader, a half-hearted fanatic. Save the other half of yourselves and your lives for pleasure and adventure. It is not enough to fight for the land; it is even more important to enjoy it. While you can. While it’s still here. So get out there and hunt and fish and mess around with your friends, ramble out yonder and explore the forests, climb the mountains, bag the peaks, run the rivers, breathe deep of that yet sweet and lucid air, sit quietly for a while and contemplate the precious stillness, the lovely, mysterious, and awesome space. Enjoy yourselves, keep your brain in your head and your head firmly attached to the body, the body active and alive, and I promise you this much; I promise you this one sweet victory over our enemies, over those desk-bound men and women with their hearts in a safe deposit box, and their eyes hypnotized by desk calculators. I promise you this; You will outlive the bastards." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26457-i-can-t-imagine-a-man-really-enjoying-a-book-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:17:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26457-i-can-t-imagine-a-man-really-enjoying-a-book-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't imagine a man really enjoying a book and reading it only once." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11996-eating-and-reading-are-two-pleasures-that-combine-admirably</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:07:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11996-eating-and-reading-are-two-pleasures-that-combine-admirably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eating and reading are two pleasures that combine admirably." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19969-do-not-let-us-mistake-necessary-evils-for-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 16:08:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19969-do-not-let-us-mistake-necessary-evils-for-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not let us mistake necessary evils for good." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479475-first-you-start-carrying-a-man-satchel-next-thing-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 18:44:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/479475-first-you-start-carrying-a-man-satchel-next-thing-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["First, you start carrying a man satchel. Next thing you know, you're running around in a bathrobe and pink bunny slippers, chasing chickens with a weed whacker." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165279-because-i-rant-not-neither-rave-of-what-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 22:15:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by R.D. Blackmore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165279-because-i-rant-not-neither-rave-of-what-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...because I rant not, neither rave of what I feel, can you be so shallow as to dream that I feel nothing? " -- R.D. Blackmore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394660-matthew-much-to-his-own-surprise-was-enjoying-himself-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 22:17:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jailynn add a quote by L. M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/394660-matthew-much-to-his-own-surprise-was-enjoying-himself-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Matthew, much to his own surprise, was enjoying himself. Like most quiet folks he liked talkative people when they were willing to do the talking themselves and did not expect him to keep up his end of it." -- L. M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
