<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/910729-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/910729-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 23:14:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 23:14:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64329-we-re-all-going-to-die-all-of-us-what-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're all going to die, all of us, what a circus! That alone should make us love each other but it doesn't. We are terrorized and flattened by trivialities, we are eaten up by nothing." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61063-the-netherworld-is-timeless-and-unchanging-and-boring----much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:07:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Christopher Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61063-the-netherworld-is-timeless-and-unchanging-and-boring----much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The netherworld is timeless and unchanging, and boring -- much like a doctor's waiting room." -- Christopher Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7599-people-living-deeply-have-no-fear-of-death</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 22:31:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7599-people-living-deeply-have-no-fear-of-death]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People living deeply have no fear of death." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62576-is-that-why-you-ve-been-pushing-me-away-because-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:07:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anne Bishop]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62576-is-that-why-you-ve-been-pushing-me-away-because-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is that why you've been pushing me away? Because of how you &lt;i&gt;look?&lt;/i&gt; [...] I waited for you my whole life. Yearned for you my whole life. After Tersa told me you were coming, I spent &lt;i&gt;seven hundred years&lt;/i&gt; searching for you[....] I never gave a damn what you looked like--tall, short, fat, thin, plain, beautiful, ugly. Why would I care about what you looked like? The flesh was the shell that housed the glory[....] Even if I couldn't be your physical lover, there are other ways to be a lover and I know them all. So don't stand there and tell me how you feel depends on &lt;i&gt;how you look!&lt;/i&gt;" -- Anne Bishop]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48851-i-have-always-essentially-been-waiting-waiting-to-become-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:07:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Shauna Niequist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48851-i-have-always-essentially-been-waiting-waiting-to-become-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always, essentially, been waiting. Waiting to become something else, waiting to be that person I always thought I was on the verge of becoming, waiting for that life I thought I would have. In my head, I was always one step away. In high school, I was biding my time until I could become the college version of myself, the one my mind could see so clearly. In college, the post-college “adult” person was always looming in front of me, smarter, stronger, more organized. Then the married person, then the person I’d become when we have kids. For twenty years, literally, I have waited to become the thin version of myself, because that’s when life will really begin.
And through all that waiting, here I am. My life is passing, day by day, and I am waiting for it to start. I am waiting for that time, that person, that event when my life will finally begin.
I love movies about “The Big Moment” – the game or the performance or the wedding day or the record deal, the stories that split time with that key event, and everything is reframed, before it and after it, because it has changed everything. I have always wanted this movie-worthy event, something that will change everything and grab me out of this waiting game into the whirlwind in front of me. I cry and cry at these movies, because I am still waiting for my own big moment. I had visions of life as an adventure, a thing to be celebrated and experienced, but all I was doing was going to work and coming home, and that wasn’t what it looked like in the movies.
John Lennon once said, “Life is what happens when you’re busy making other plans.” For me, life is what was happening while I was busy waiting for my big moment. I was ready for it and believed that the rest of my life would fade into the background, and that my big moment would carry me through life like a lifeboat.
The Big Moment, unfortunately, is an urban myth. Some people have them, in a sense, when they win the Heisman or become the next American Idol. But even that football player or that singer is living a life made up of more than that one moment. Life is a collection of a million, billion moments, tiny little moments and choices, like a handful of luminous, glowing pearl. It takes so much time, and so much work, and those beads and moments are so small, and so much less fabulous and dramatic than the movies.
But this is what I’m finding, in glimpses and flashes: this is it. This is it, in the best possible way. That thing I’m waiting for, that adventure, that move-score-worthy experience unfolding gracefully. This is it. Normal, daily life ticking by on our streets and sidewalks, in our houses and apartments, in our beds and at our dinner tables, in our dreams and prayers and fights and secrets – this pedestrian life is the most precious thing any of use will ever experience." -- Shauna Niequist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48852-believe-that-this-way-of-living-this-focus-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:08:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Shauna Niequist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48852-believe-that-this-way-of-living-this-focus-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["believe that this way of living, this focus on the present, the daily, the tangible, this intense concentration not on the news headlines but on the flowers growing in your own garden, the children growing in your own home, this way of living has the potential to open up the heavens, to yield a glittering handful of diamonds where a second ago there was coal. This way of living and noticing and building and crafting can crack through the movie sets and soundtracks that keep us waiting for our own life stories to begin, and set us free to observe the lives we have been creating all along without ever realizing it.
I don’t want to wait anymore. I choose to believe that there is nothing more sacred or profound than this day. I choose to believe that there may be a thousand big moments embedded in this day, waiting to be discovered like tiny shards of gold. The big moments are the daily, tiny moments of courage and forgiveness and hope that we grab on to and extend to one another. That’s the drama of life, swirling all around us, and generally I don’t even see it, because I’m too busy waiting to become whatever it is I think I am about to become. The big moments are in every hour, every conversation, every meal, every meeting.
The Heisman Trophy winner knows this. He knows that his big moment was not when they gave him the trophy. It was the thousand times he went to practice instead of going back to bed. It was the miles run on rainy days, the healthy meals when a burger sounded like heaven. That big moment represented and rested on a foundation of moments that had come before it.
I believe that if we cultivate a true attention, a deep ability to see what has been there all along, we will find worlds within us and between us, dreams and stories and memories spilling over. The nuances and shades and secrets and intimations of love and friendship and marriage an parenting are action-packed and multicolored, if you know where to look.
Today is your big moment. Moments, really. The life you’ve been waiting for is happening all around you. The scene unfolding right outside your window is worth more than the most beautiful painting, and the crackers and peanut butter that you’re having for lunch on the coffee table are as profound, in their own way, as the Last Supper. This is it. This is life in all its glory, swirling and unfolding around us, disguised as pedantic, pedestrian non-events. But pull of the mask and you will find your life, waiting to be made, chosen, woven, crafted.
Your life, right now, today, is exploding with energy and power and detail and dimension, better than the best movie you have ever seen. You and your family and your friends and your house and your dinner table and your garage have all the makings of a life of epic proportions, a story for the ages. Because they all are. Every life is.
You have stories worth telling, memories worth remembering, dreams worth working toward, a body worth feeding, a soul worth tending, and beyond that, the God of the universe dwells within you, the true culmination of super and natural. 
You are more than dust and bones.
You are spirit and power and image of God.
And you have been given Today." -- Shauna Niequist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25525-as-long-as-nothing-happens-between-them-the-memory-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:08:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25525-as-long-as-nothing-happens-between-them-the-memory-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...as long as nothing happens between them, the memory is cursed with what hasn't happened." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164499-men-trust-god-by-risking-rejection-women-trust-god-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:08:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Carolyn McCulley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164499-men-trust-god-by-risking-rejection-women-trust-god-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men trust God by risking rejection. Women trust God by waiting." -- Carolyn McCulley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:09:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Gregory Corso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119514-standing-on-a-street-corner-waiting-for-no-one-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Standing on a street corner waiting for no one is power." -- Gregory Corso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164750-it-is-very-strange-that-the-years-teach-us-patience</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:10:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Elizabeth Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164750-it-is-very-strange-that-the-years-teach-us-patience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is very strange that the years teach us patience - that the shorter our time, the greater our capacity for waiting." -- Elizabeth Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112000-we-must-be-willing-to-let-go-of-the-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:11:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112000-we-must-be-willing-to-let-go-of-the-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must be willing to let go of the life we have planned, so as to have the life that is waiting for us." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:12:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:12:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3549-there-is-never-a-time-or-place-for-true-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, throbbing moment." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 09:01:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:12:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/778-it-is-not-a-lack-of-love-but-a-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:12:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/777-love-never-dies-a-natural-death-it-dies-because-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love never dies a natural death. It dies because we don't know how to replenish its source. It dies of blindness and errors and betrayals. It dies of illness and wounds; it dies of weariness, of witherings, of tarnishings." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1946-tis-better-to-have-loved-and-lost-than-never-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:13:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1946-tis-better-to-have-loved-and-lost-than-never-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tis better to have loved and lost
Than never to have loved at all." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:13:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:13:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:15:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2846-and-the-day-came-when-the-risk-to-remain-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And the day came when the risk to remain tight in a bud was more painful than the risk it took to blossom." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2061-life-shrinks-or-expands-in-proportion-to-one-s-courage</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:15:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2061-life-shrinks-or-expands-in-proportion-to-one-s-courage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:15:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2787-we-write-to-taste-life-twice-in-the-moment-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We write to taste life twice, in the moment and in retrospect." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:15:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13421-how-wrong-is-it-for-a-woman-to-expect-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How wrong is it for a woman to expect the man to build the world she wants, rather than to create it herself?" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:15:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2216-luxury-is-not-a-necessity-to-me-but-beautiful-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Luxury is not a necessity to me, but beautiful and good things are." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:17:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21573-i-am-only-responsible-for-my-own-heart-you-offered</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:17:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21573-i-am-only-responsible-for-my-own-heart-you-offered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am only responsible for my own heart, you offered yours up for the smashing my darling.  Only a fool would give out such a vital organ" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:17:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the backstabbing co-worker to the meddling sister-in-law, you are in charge of how you react to the people and events in your life. You can either give negativity power over your life or you can choose happiness instead. Take control and choose to focus on what is important in your life. Those who cannot live fully often become destroyers of life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:28:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15244-there-were-always-in-me-two-women-at-least-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There were always in me, two women at least, one woman desperate and bewildered, who felt she was drowning and another who would leap into a scene, as upon a stage, conceal her true emotions because they were weaknesses, helplessness, despair, and present to the world only a smile, an eagerness, curiosity, enthusiasm, interest." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3511-throw-your-dreams-into-space-like-a-kite-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:28:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3511-throw-your-dreams-into-space-like-a-kite-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Throw your dreams into space like a kite, and you do not know what it will bring back, a new life, a new friend, a new love, a new country." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64155-we-do-not-grow-absolutely-chronologically-we-grow-sometimes-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2009 14:28:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64155-we-do-not-grow-absolutely-chronologically-we-grow-sometimes-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not grow absolutely, chronologically. We grow sometimes in one dimension, and not in another; unevenly. We grow partially. We are relative. We are mature in one realm, childish in another. The past, present, and future mingle and pull us backward, forward, or fix us in the present. We are made up of layers, cells, constellations." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
