<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/911622-james]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/911622-james" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 13:44:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520382-when-you-call-yourself-an-indian-or-a-muslim-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 13:44:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Jiddu Krishnamurti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/520382-when-you-call-yourself-an-indian-or-a-muslim-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you call yourself an Indian or a Muslim or a Christian or a European, or anything else, you are being violent. Do you see why it is violent? Because you are separating yourself from the rest of mankind. When you separate yourself by belief, by nationality, by tradition, it breeds violence. So a man who is seeking to understand violence does not belong to any country, to any religion, to any political party or partial system; he is concerned with the total understanding of mankind." -- Jiddu Krishnamurti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282966-asana-now-i-shall-instruct-you-regarding-the-nature-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 11:23:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Swami Lakshmanjoo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282966-asana-now-i-shall-instruct-you-regarding-the-nature-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["ASANA 

Now I shall instruct you regarding the nature of asana or seat. Although by 'asana' is generally meant the erect posture assumed in meditation, this is not its central or essential meaning. When I use the word 'asana' I do not mean the various forms of asana’s such as Padmasana, Vajrasana, Svastikasana, or Bhadrasana. By 'asana' I mean something else, and this is what I want to explain to you.

First let me speak to you about breath; about the inhaling breath-apana, and the exhaling breath-prana. Breath is extremely important in meditation; particularly the central breath-madhyama-pranan, which is neither prana nor apana. It is the center of these two, the point existing between the inhaling and exhaling breaths. This center point cannot be held by any physical means, as a material object can be held by the hand. The center between the two breaths can be held only by knowledge-jnana – not discursive knowledge, but by knowledge which is awareness. When this central point is held by continuously refreshed awareness – which is knowledge and which is achieved through devotion to the Lord – that is, in the true sense settling into your asana.

“On the pathway of your breath maintain continuously refreshed and full awareness on and in the center of breathing in and breathing out. This is internal asana.&quot; (Netra Tantra)

Asana, therefore, is the gradual dawning in the spiritual aspirant of the awareness which shines in the central point found between inhaling and exhaling.

This awareness is not gained by that person who is full of prejudice, avarice, or envy. Such a person, filled with all such negative qualities, cannot concentrate. The prerequisite of this glorious achievement is, therefore, the purification of your internal egoity. It must become pure, clean, and crystal clear. After you have purged your mind of all prejudice and have started settling with full awareness into that point between the two breaths, then you are settling into your asana.

“When in breathing in and breathing out you continue to maintain your awareness in continuity on and in the center between the incoming and outgoing breath, your breath will spontaneously and progressively become more and more refined. At that point you are driven to another world. This is pranayama.&quot; (Netra Tantra)

After settling in the asana of meditation arises the refined practice of pranayama. ‘Pranayama’ does not mean inhaling and exhaling vigorously like a bellow. Like asana, pranayama is internal and very subtle. There is a break less continuity in the traveling of your awareness from the point of asana into the practice of pranayama. When through your awareness you have settled in your asana, you automatically enter into the practice of pranayama.

Our Masters have indicated that there are two principle forms of this practice of ‘asana-pranayama’, i.e. cakrodaya and ajapa-gayatri. In the practice of ajapa-gayatri you are to maintain continuously refreshed full awareness-(anusandhana) in the center of two breaths, while breathing in and out slowly and silently. Likewise in the practice of cakrodaya you must maintain awareness, which is continually fresh and new, filled with excitement and vigor, in the center of the two breaths – you are to breathe in and out slowly, but in this case with sound." -- Swami Lakshmanjoo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2010 06:48:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/756-this-is-what-you-shall-do-love-the-earth-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you shall do; Love the earth and sun and the animals, despise riches, give alms to every one that asks, stand up for the stupid and crazy, devote your income and labor to others, hate tyrants, argue not concerning God, have patience and indulgence toward the people, take off your hat to nothing known or unknown or to any man or number of men, go freely with powerful uneducated persons and with the young and with the mothers of families, read these leaves in the open air every season of every year of your life, re-examine all you have been told at school or church or in any book, dismiss whatever insults your own soul, and your very flesh shall be a great poem and have the richest fluency not only in its words but in the silent lines of its lips and face and between the lashes of your eyes and in every motion and joint of your body." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245562-tomber-amoureux-to-fall-in-love-does-it-occur-suddenly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2010 20:53:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Czeslaw Milosz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245562-tomber-amoureux-to-fall-in-love-does-it-occur-suddenly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomber amoureux. To fall in love. Does it occur suddenly or gradually? If gradually, when is the moment “already”? I would fall in love with a monkey made of rags. With a plywood squirrel. With a botanical atlas. With an oriole. With a ferret. With a marten in a picture. With the forest one sees to the right when riding in a cart to Jaszuny. With a poem by a little-known poet. With human beings whose names still move me. And always the object of love was enveloped in erotic fantasy or was submitted, as in Stendhal, to a “cristallisation,” so it is frightful to think of that object as it was, naked among the naked things, and of the fairy tales about it one invents. Yes, I was often in love with something or someone. Yet falling in love is not the same as being able to love. That is something different." -- Czeslaw Milosz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58970-but-for-their-cries-the-herons-would-be-lost-amidst</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 07:21:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Chiyo Ni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58970-but-for-their-cries-the-herons-would-be-lost-amidst]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But for their cries,
The herons would be lost
Amidst the morning snow." -- Chiyo Ni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250495-mi-amado-las-monta-as-los-valles-solitarios-nemorosos-las-nsulas</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 18:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by St. John of the Cross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250495-mi-amado-las-monta-as-los-valles-solitarios-nemorosos-las-nsulas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mi Amado, las montañas,
los valles solitarios nemorosos,
las ínsulas extrañas,
los ríos sonorosos,
el silbo de los aires amorosos,
la noche sosegada
en par de los levantes de la aurora,
la música callada,
la soledad sonora,
la cena que recrea y enamora.

     ~ San Juan de la Cruz" -- St. John of the Cross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167324-i-really-should-come-with-a-warning-label</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 18:42:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Tom Upton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167324-i-really-should-come-with-a-warning-label]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really should come with a warning label." -- Tom Upton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232557-seated-alone-by-shadowy-bamboos-i-strum-my-lyre-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2012 18:42:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Wang Wei]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/232557-seated-alone-by-shadowy-bamboos-i-strum-my-lyre-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Seated alone by shadowy bamboos,

I strum my lyre and laugh aloud;

None know that I am here, deep in the woods;

Only the bright moon comes to shine on me.

" -- Wang Wei]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271571-in-my-craft-or-sullen-art-exercised-in-the-still</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 22:09:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Dylan Thomas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271571-in-my-craft-or-sullen-art-exercised-in-the-still]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In my craft or sullen art
Exercised in the still night
When only the moon rages
And the lovers lie abed
With all their griefs in their arms,
I labour by singing light
Not for ambition or bread
Or the strut and trade of charms
On the ivory stages
But for the common wages
Of their most secret heart.
Not for the proud man apart
From the raging moon I write
On these spindrift pages
Nor for the towering dead
With their nightingales and psalms
But for the lovers, their arms
Round the griefs of the ages,
Who pay no praise or wages
Nor heed my craft or art." -- Dylan Thomas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273317-the-book-that-i-shall-make-people-read-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 19:35:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Meher Baba]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273317-the-book-that-i-shall-make-people-read-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The book that I shall make people read
is the book of the heart,
which holds the key
to the mystery of life" -- Meher Baba]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140008-if-i-do-not-take-my-intellectual-vocation-seriously-putting</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2010 19:09:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Raimundo Panikkar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140008-if-i-do-not-take-my-intellectual-vocation-seriously-putting]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...if I do not take my intellectual vocation seriously, putting it before everything else even at the risk of appearing inhuman, then I am also incapable of helping people in more concrete and proximate ways. Conversely, if I am not alert and ready to save people from a conflagration, that is to say, if I do not take my spiritual calling in all earnestness, sacrificing to it all else, even my own life, then I shall be unable to help in rescuing the manuscript. If I do not involve myself in the concrete issues of my time, and if I do not open my house to all the winds of the world, then anything I produce from an ivory tower will be barren and cursed. Yet if I do not shut doors and windows in order to concentrate on this work, then I will not be able to offer anything of value to my neighbors." -- Raimundo Panikkar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302887-to-learn-about-a-pine-tree-go-to-a-pine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 22:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Bashō]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/302887-to-learn-about-a-pine-tree-go-to-a-pine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To learn about a pine tree go to a pine; to learn about a bamboo stalk, go to to a bamboo." -- Bashō]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254693-stay-together-learn-the-flowers-go-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2010 21:46:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Gary Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254693-stay-together-learn-the-flowers-go-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["stay together
learn the flowers
go light" -- Gary Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220358-the-last-ever-dolphin-message-was-misinterpreted-as-a-surprisingly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 08:20:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220358-the-last-ever-dolphin-message-was-misinterpreted-as-a-surprisingly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The last ever dolphin message was misinterpreted as a surprisingly sophisticated attempt to do a double-backwards-somersault through a hoop whilst whistling the 'Star Spangled Banner', but in fact the message was this: &lt;i&gt;So long and thanks for all the fish.&lt;/i&gt;" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314-i-was-working-on-the-proof-of-one-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 23:45:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314-i-was-working-on-the-proof-of-one-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was working on the proof of one of my poems all the morning, and took out a comma. In the afternoon I put it back again." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118609-where-is-that-man-who-has-forgotten-words-that-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 22:47:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Chuang Tsu]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118609-where-is-that-man-who-has-forgotten-words-that-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where is that man who has forgotten words that I may have a word with him?" -- Chuang Tsu]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250625-i-want-my-life-to-be-mystifying-she-declared-although</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 07:47:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/250625-i-want-my-life-to-be-mystifying-she-declared-although]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want my life to be mystifying,&quot; she declared, although she didn't know what she meant." -- Sonya Hartnett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29762-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 06:16:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29762-all-that-we-are-is-the-result-of-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that we are is the result of what we have thought. The mind is everything. What we think, we become." -- Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31648-like-the-air-god-s-grace-is-available-to-us-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 06:16:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31648-like-the-air-god-s-grace-is-available-to-us-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like the air, God's Grace is available to us. It is permeating every fibre of Being and the Being of the entire universe. When we take our attention to that Being, finer than the finest, then we establish ourselves on the level of God's Grace. Immediately we just enjoy. Life is Bliss!" -- Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126194-experience-shows-that-being-is-the-essential-basic-nature-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 06:16:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126194-experience-shows-that-being-is-the-essential-basic-nature-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Experience shows that Being is the essential, basic nature of the mind; but, since It commonly remains in tune with the senses projecting outwards toward the manifested realms of creation, the mind misses or fails to appreciate its own essential nature, just as the eyes are unable to see themselves. " -- Maharishi Mahesh Yogi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 06:08:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19563-from-the-backstabbing-co-worker-to-the-meddling-sister-in-law-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the backstabbing co-worker to the meddling sister-in-law, you are in charge of how you react to the people and events in your life. You can either give negativity power over your life or you can choose happiness instead. Take control and choose to focus on what is important in your life. Those who cannot live fully often become destroyers of life." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48436-be-calm-god-awaits-you-at-the-door</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 18:54:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48436-be-calm-god-awaits-you-at-the-door]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be calm. God awaits you at the door." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51262-our-goal-should-be-to-live-life-in-radical-amazement</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 11:18:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51262-our-goal-should-be-to-live-life-in-radical-amazement]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our goal should be to live life in radical amazement.  ....get up in the morning and look at the world in a way that takes nothing for granted.  Everything is phenomenal; everything is incredible; never treat life casually.  To be spiritual is to be amazed." -- Abraham Joshua Heschel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 08:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19421-if-you-can-t-explain-it-to-a-six-year-old]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't explain it to a six year old, you don't understand it yourself." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51938-sex-is-the-consolation-you-have-when-you-can-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2013 09:34:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51938-sex-is-the-consolation-you-have-when-you-can-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["sex is the consolation you have when you can't have love" -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 18:20:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 17:06:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[James add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
