<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/911601-sharon-lfrog1386]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/911601-sharon-lfrog1386" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 15:47:10 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188587-sometimes-you-can-t-let-go-of-the-past-without-facing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 15:47:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Gail Tsukiyama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188587-sometimes-you-can-t-let-go-of-the-past-without-facing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you can’t let go of the past without facing it again." -- Gail Tsukiyama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71899-i-am-old-enough-to-know-only-too-well-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 15:47:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Lisa See]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71899-i-am-old-enough-to-know-only-too-well-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am old enough to know only too well my good and bad qualities, which were often one in the same." -- Lisa See]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193682-we-re-told-that-men-are-strong-brave-but-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 15:50:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Lisa See]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193682-we-re-told-that-men-are-strong-brave-but-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're told that men are strong &amp; brave, but I think women know how to endure, accept defeat &amp; bear physical &amp; mental agony much better than men." -- Lisa See]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 19:02:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2012 19:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9131-if-you-tell-the-truth-you-don-t-have-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you tell the truth, you don't have to remember anything." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108613-in-order-to-succeed-your-desire-for-success-should-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 15:01:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Bill Cosby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108613-in-order-to-succeed-your-desire-for-success-should-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure. " -- Bill Cosby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 07:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon/ LFrog1386 add a quote by Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214560-you-know-i-do-believe-in-magic-i-was-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, I do believe in magic. I was born and raised in a magic time, in a magic town, among magicians. Oh, most everybody else didn’t realize we lived in that web of magic, connected by silver filaments of chance and circumstance. But I knew it all along. When I was twelve years old, the world was my magic lantern, and by its green spirit glow I saw the past, the present and into the future. You probably did too; you just don’t recall it. See, this is my opinion: we all start out knowing magic. We are born with whirlwinds, forest fires, and comets inside us. We are born able to sing to birds and read the clouds and see our destiny in grains of sand. But then we get the magic educated right out of our souls. We get it churched out, spanked out, washed out, and combed out. We get put on the straight and narrow and told to be responsible. Told to act our age. Told to grow up, for God’s sake. And you know why we were told that? Because the people doing the telling were afraid of our wildness and youth, and because the magic we knew made them ashamed and sad of what they’d allowed to wither in themselves.

After you go so far away from it, though, you can’t really get it back. You can have seconds of it. Just seconds of knowing and remembering. When people get weepy at movies, it’s because in that dark theater the golden pool of magic is touched, just briefly. Then they come out into the hard sun of logic and reason again and it dries up, and they’re left feeling a little heartsad and not knowing why. When a song stirs a memory, when motes of dust turning in a shaft of light takes your attention from the world, when you listen to a train passing on a track at night in the distance and wonder where it might be going, you step beyond who you are and where you are. For the briefest of instants, you have stepped into the magic realm.

That’s what I believe.

The truth of life is that every year we get farther away from the essence that is born within us. We get shouldered with burdens, some of them good, some of them not so good. Things happen to us. Loved ones die. People get in wrecks and get crippled. People lose their way, for one reason or another. It’s not hard to do, in this world of crazy mazes. Life itself does its best to take that memory of magic away from us. You don’t know it’s happening until one day you feel you’ve lost something but you’re not sure what it is. It’s like smiling at a pretty girl and she calls you “sir.” It just happens.

These memories of who I was and where I lived are important to me. They make up a large part of who I’m going to be when my journey winds down. I need the memory of magic if I am ever going to conjure magic again. I need to know and remember, and I want to tell you." -- Robert R. McCammon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
