<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/912372-rupa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/912372-rupa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 23:11:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31464-i-can-live-alone-if-self-respect-and-circumstances-require-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 23:11:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31464-i-can-live-alone-if-self-respect-and-circumstances-require-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can live alone, if self-respect, and circumstances require me so to do. I need not sell my soul to buy bliss. I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all extraneous delights should be withheld, or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 23:11:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 23:12:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44541-laws-and-principles-are-not-for-the-times-when-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour ... If at my convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15587-hope-and-optimism-are-different-optimism-tends-to-be-based</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 16:59:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Cornell West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15587-hope-and-optimism-are-different-optimism-tends-to-be-based]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope and optimism are different. Optimism tends to be based on the notion that there's enough evidence out there to believe things are gonna be better, much more rational, deeply secular, whereas hope looks at the evidence and says, &quot;It doesn't look good at all. Doesn't look good at all. Gonna go beyond the evidence to create new possibilities based on visions that become contagious to allow people to engage in heroic actions always against the odds, no guarantee whatsoever.&quot; That's hope. I'm a prisoner of hope, though. Gonna die a prisoner of hope." -- Cornell West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182076-when-he-thought-of-her-it-rather-amazed-him-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 09:57:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182076-when-he-thought-of-her-it-rather-amazed-him-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When he thought of her, it rather amazed him, that he had let that girl with her violin go. Now, of course, he saw that her self-effacing proposal was quite irrelevant. All she had needed was the certainty of his love, and his reassurance that there was no hurry when a lifetime lay ahead of them. Love and patience- if only he had had them both at once- would surely have seen them both through." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54455-this-is-how-the-entire-course-of-life-can-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 09:57:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54455-this-is-how-the-entire-course-of-life-can-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how the entire course of life can be changed – by doing nothing. On Chesil beach he could have called out to Florence, he could have gone after her. He did not know, or would not have cared to know, that as she ran away from him, certain in her distress that she was about to lose him, she had never loved him more, or more hopelessly, and that the sound of his voice would have been a deliverance, and she would have turned back. Instead, he stood in cold and righteous silence in the summer’s dusk, watching her hurry along the shore, the sound of her difficult progress lost to the breaking of small waves, until she was blurred, receding against the immense straight road of shingle gleaming in the pallid light." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525273-marriage-is-the-triumph-of-imagination-over-intelligence-second-marriage</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 18:06:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rupa add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/525273-marriage-is-the-triumph-of-imagination-over-intelligence-second-marriage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Marriage is the triumph of imagination over intelligence. Second marriage is the triumph of hope over experience." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
