<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/913080-tennisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/913080-tennisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:38:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:38:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to get through life is to laugh your way through it. You either have to laugh or cry. I prefer to laugh. Crying gives me a headache." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:40:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it is hard for you young mothers to believe that almost before you can turn around the children will be gone and you will be alone with your husband.  You had better be sure you are developing the kind of love and friendship that will be delightful and enduring.  Let the children learn from your attitude that he is important.  Encourage him.  Be kind.  It is a rough world, and he, like everyone else, is fighting to survive.  Be cheerful.  Don't be a whiner." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:42:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We women have a lot to learn about simplifying our lives.  We have to decide what is important and then move along at a pace that is comfortable for us.  We have to develop the maturity to stop trying to prove something.  We have to learn to be content with what we are." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:43:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Henri Nouwen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1392-when-we-honestly-ask-ourselves-which-person-in-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we honestly ask ourselves which person in our lives mean the most to us, we often find that it is those who, instead of giving advice, solutions, or cures, have chosen rather to share our pain and touch our wounds with a warm and tender hand. The friend who can be silent with us in a moment of despair or confusion, who can stay with us in an hour of grief and bereavement, who can tolerate not knowing, not curing, not healing and face with us the reality of our powerlessness, that is a friend who cares." -- Henri Nouwen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:44:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55092-i-ve-learned-that-no-matter-what-happens-or-how-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that no matter what happens, or how bad it seems today, life does go on, and it will be better tomorrow. I've learned that you can tell a lot about a person by the way he/she handles these three things: a rainy day, lost luggage, and tangled Christmas tree lights. I've learned that regardless of your relationship with your parents, you'll miss them when they're gone from your life. I've learned that making a &quot;living&quot; is not the same thing as making a &quot;life.&quot; I've learned that life sometimes gives you a second chance. I've learned that you shouldn't go through life with a catcher's mitt on both hands; you need to be able to throw something back. I've learned that whenever I decide something with an open heart, I usually make the right decision. I've learned that even when I have pains, I don't have to be one. I've learned that every day you should reach out and touch someone. People love a warm hug, or just a friendly pat on the back. I've learned that I still have a lot to learn. I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110300-the-friend-who-holds-your-hand-and-says-the-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110300-the-friend-who-holds-your-hand-and-says-the-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The friend who holds your hand and says the wrong thing is made of dearer stuff than the one who stays away." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127-a-friend-is-one-to-whom-one-may-pour-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2009 08:54:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tennisa add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127-a-friend-is-one-to-whom-one-may-pour-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A friend is one to whom one may pour out the contents of one's heart, chaff and grain together, knowing that gentle hands will take and sift it, keep what is worth keeping, and with a breath of kindness, blow the rest away." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
