<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/914186-christy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/914186-christy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 12:08:20 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174623-if-you-hold-back-on-the-emotions--if-you-don-t-allow</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2012 12:08:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174623-if-you-hold-back-on-the-emotions--if-you-don-t-allow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you hold back on the emotions--if you don't allow yourself to go all the way through them--you can never get to being detached, you're too busy being afraid. You're afraid of the pain, you're afraid of the grief. You're afraid of the vulnerability that loving entails. But by throwing yourself into these emotions, by allowing yourself to dive in, all the way, over your heard even, you experience them fully and completely." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115834-i-think-i-fell-in-love-with-her-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 05:53:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115834-i-think-i-fell-in-love-with-her-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I fell in love with her, a little bit. Isn't that dumb? But it was like I knew her. Like she was my oldest, dearest friend. The kind of person you can tell anything to, no matter how bad, and they'll still love you, because they know you. I wanted to go with her. I wanted her to notice me. And then she stopped walking. Under the moon, she stopped. And looked at us. She looked at me. Maybe she was trying to tell me something; I don't know. She probably didn't even know I was there. But I'll always love her. All my life." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111546-as-lovers-the-difference-between-men-and-women-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 06:01:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111546-as-lovers-the-difference-between-men-and-women-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As lovers, the difference between men and women is that women can love all day long, but men only at times." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111556-when-a-woman-loves-you-she-s-not-satisfied-until-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 06:16:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111556-when-a-woman-loves-you-she-s-not-satisfied-until-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a woman loves you she's not satisfied until she possesses your soul. Because she's weak, she has a rage for domination, and nothing less will satisfy her." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165233-do-you-take-pride-in-your-hurt-does-it-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2012 06:32:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165233-do-you-take-pride-in-your-hurt-does-it-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you take pride in your hurt?  Does it make you seem large and tragic?  ...Well, think about it.  Maybe you're playing a part on a great stage with only yourself as audience." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2012 16:23:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 13:52:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12366-death-must-be-so-beautiful-to-lie-in-the-soft]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death must be so beautiful. To lie in the soft brown earth, with the grasses waving above one's head, and listen to silence. To have no yesterday, and no tomorrow. To forget time, to forgive life, to be at peace." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163773-it-hurts-to-let-go-sometimes-it-seems-the-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 20:14:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Henry Rollins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163773-it-hurts-to-let-go-sometimes-it-seems-the-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It hurts to let go. Sometimes it seems the harder you try to hold on to something or someone the more it wants to get away. You feel like some kind of criminal for having felt, for having wanted. For having wanted to be wanted. It confuses you, because you think that your feelings were wrong and it makes you feel so small because it's so hard to keep it inside when you let it out and it doesn't coma back. You're left so alone that you can't explain. Damn, there's nothing like that, is there? I've been there and you have too. You're nodding your head." -- Henry Rollins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217302-the-most-confused-we-ever-get-is-when-we-re-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 23:26:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217302-the-most-confused-we-ever-get-is-when-we-re-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most confused we ever get is when we're trying to convince our heads of something our heart knows is a lie." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 16:05:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318941-the-truth-is-unless-you-let-go-unless-you-forgive</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2013 08:30:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318941-the-truth-is-unless-you-let-go-unless-you-forgive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, unless you let go, unless you forgive yourself, unless you forgive the situation, unless you realize that the situation is over, you cannot move forward." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137522-the-truly-scary-thing-about-undiscovered-lies-is-that-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 20:06:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Cheryl Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137522-the-truly-scary-thing-about-undiscovered-lies-is-that-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truly scary thing about undiscovered lies is that they have a greater capacity to diminish us than exposed ones. They erode our strength, our self-esteem, our very foundation." -- Cheryl Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52749-i-gave-him-my-heart-and-he-took-and-pinched</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 21:07:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52749-i-gave-him-my-heart-and-he-took-and-pinched]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I gave him my heart, and he took and pinched it to death; and flung it back to me. People feel with their hearts, Ellen, and since he has destroyed mine, I have not power to feel for him." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125336-here-s-something-else-to-think-about-calling-when-you-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 08:32:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Greg Behrendt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125336-here-s-something-else-to-think-about-calling-when-you-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's something else to think about: calling when you say you're going to is the very first brick in the house you are building of love and trust. If he can't lay this one stupid brick down, you ain't never gonna have a house baby, and it's cold outside." -- Greg Behrendt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235985-cold-flu-looks-nothing-in-front-of-cancer-complications-in-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 17:34:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Neeraj Sabharwal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235985-cold-flu-looks-nothing-in-front-of-cancer-complications-in-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cold flu looks nothing in front of cancer...complications in our personal life is like a flu and killing people on name of God or borders or countries is cancer...you can help this planet...there are ways...willingness is an action

We are one...the only difference is ...few are awake, few are ready to wake up and few are just ignorant and time is coming when there will be no choice for those who is ignorant because of suffering and pain ....

Bigger EGO is always drawn to Bigger Ego so many times Bigger ego ignores the important message being delivered by not a famous person.

Love heals...Love not from mind...deep from heart....Mind brings games and play around with relationships...Something sacred deep from heart....L ♥ V E...Unconditional...No business of give and take....unconditional giving....

Don't be afraid and run away from loneliness and start seeking securities....Try to enjoy every part of it and then you will see ...Loneliness turned into something which we never want to loose....investigate your feeling when you feel lonely

We always want something in return...we have made LOVE a business...I did it too in the past that's why I know it...this is the reason that we should change...you change, I change....everyone should think again on the way of living life and thinking and specially who thinks they know what life is.

2 births in the same life....physical and spiritual....you break the bondage (psychologically) with physical attributes of life ( detached state of mind) and try to find real &quot;maksad&quot; (purpose) of your existence as Being not Doing

If you want to enjoy your relationship with your special one then please keep these tools handy:1) Patience2) Trust3) Freedom4) Honesty5) Respect

we are all stars... twinkling with love and when there is love then there is no conflict

4 letters L ♥ V E ..imagine these letters on your hand and try to feel the deep meaning and power of these letters...feel the love you have for this life...start from there and spread love to everyone you see or meet...LOVE" -- Neeraj Sabharwal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 09:23:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198195-it-is-a-long-way-to-ireland-janet-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a long way to Ireland, Janet, and I am sorry to send my little friend on such weary travels: but if I can't do better, how is it to be helped? Are you anything akin to me, do you think, Jane?&quot;

I could risk no sort of answer by this time: my heart was still. 

&quot;Because, he said, &quot;I sometimes have a queer feeling with regard to you - especially when you are near me, as now: it is as if I had a string somewhere under my left ribs, tightly and inextricably knotted to a similar string situated in the corresponding quarter of your little frame. And if that boisterous channel, and two hundred miles or so of land some broad between us, I am afraid that cord of communion will be snapt; and then I've a nervous notion I should take to bleeding inwardly. As for you, - you'd forget me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263084-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 19:36:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263084-when-you-love-someone-you-do-not-love-them-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you love someone, you do not love them all the time, in exactly the same way, from moment to moment. It is an impossibility. It is even a lie to pretend to. And yet this is exactly what most of us demand. We have so little faith in the ebb and flow of life, of love, of relationships. We leap at the flow of the tide and resist in terror its ebb. We are afraid it will never return. We insist on permanency, on duration, on continuity; when the only continuity possible, in life as in love, is in growth, in fluidity - in freedom, in the sense that the dancers are free, barely touching as they pass, but partners in the same pattern.

The only real security is not in owning or possessing, not in demanding or expecting, not in hoping, even. Security in a relationship lies neither in looking back to what was in nostalgia, nor forward to what it might be in dread or anticipation, but living in the present relationship and accepting it as it is now. Relationships must be like islands, one must accept them for what they are here and now, within their limits - islands, surrounded and interrupted by the sea, and continually visited and abandoned by the tides." -- Anne Morrow Lindbergh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 17:46:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as a thief loves a gallery and as a crow loves a murder, as a cloud loves bats and as a range loves braes. I will love you as misfortune loves orphans, as fire loves innocence and as justice loves to sit and watch while everything goes wrong. I will love you as a battlefield loves young men and as peppermints love your allergies, and I will love you as the banana peel loves the shoe of a man who was just struck by a shingle falling off a house. I will love you as a volunteer fire department loves rushing into burning buildings and as burning buildings love to chase them back out, and as a parachute loves to leave a blimp and as a blimp operator loves to chase after it.
I will love you as a dagger loves a certain person’s back, and as a certain person loves to wear dagger proof tunics, and as a dagger proof tunic loves to go to a certain dry cleaning facility, and how a certain employee of a dry cleaning facility loves to stay up late with a pair of binoculars, watching a dagger factory for hours in the hopes of catching a burglar, and as a burglar loves sneaking up behind people with binoculars, suddenly realizing that she has left her dagger at home. I will love you as a drawer loves a secret compartment, and as a secret compartment loves a secret, and as a secret loves to make a person gasp, and as a gasping person loves a glass of brandy to calm their nerves, and as a glass of brandy loves to shatter on the floor, and as the noise of glass shattering loves to make someone else gasp, and as someone else gasping loves a nearby desk to lean against, even if leaning against it presses a lever that loves to open a drawer and reveal a secret compartment. I will love you until all such compartments are discovered and opened, and until all the secrets have gone gasping into the world. I will love you until all the codes and hearts have been broken and until every anagram and egg has been unscrambled.
I will love you until every fire is extinguised and until every home is rebuilt from the handsomest and most susceptible of woods, and until every criminal is handcuffed by the laziest of policemen. I will love until M. hates snakes and J. hates grammar, and I will love you until C. realizes S. is not worthy of his love and N. realizes he is not worthy of the V. I will love you until the bird hates a nest and the worm hates an apple, and until the apple hates a tree and the tree hates a nest, and until a bird hates a tree and an apple hates a nest, although honestly I cannot imagine that last occurrence no matter how hard I try. I will love you as we grow older, which has just happened, and has happened again, and happened several days ago, continuously, and then several years before that, and will continue to happen as the spinning hands of every clock and the flipping pages of every calendar mark the passage of time, except for the clocks that people have forgotten to wind and the calendars that people have forgotten to place in a highly visible area. I will love you as we find ourselves farther and farther from one another, where we once we were so close that we could slip the curved straw, and the long, slender spoon, between our lips and fingers respectively.
I will love you until the chances of us running into one another slip from slim to zero, and until your face is fogged by distant memory, and your memory faced by distant fog, and your fog memorized by a distant face, and your distance distanced by the memorized memory of a foggy fog. I will love you no matter where you go and who you see, no matter where you avoid and who you don’t see, and no matter who sees you avoiding where you go. I will love you no matter what happens to you, and no matter how I discover what happens to you, and no matter what happens to me as I discover this, and now matter how I am discovered after what happens to me as I am discovering this." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237830-yes-i-was-infatuated-with-you-i-am-still-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 20:04:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237830-yes-i-was-infatuated-with-you-i-am-still-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, I was infatuated with you: I am still. No one has ever heightened such a keen capacity of physical sensation in me. I cut you out because I couldn't stand being a passing fancy. Before I give my body, I must give my thoughts, my mind, my dreams. And you weren't having any of those." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368163-she-was-feeling-the-pressure-of-the-world-outside-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2014 19:45:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/368163-she-was-feeling-the-pressure-of-the-world-outside-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was feeling the pressure of the world outside and she wanted to see him and feel his presence beside her and be reassured that she was doing the right thing after all." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/895805-the-true-purpose-of-the-strong-is-to-promote-greater</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 20:00:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christy add a quote by Christian D. Larson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/895805-the-true-purpose-of-the-strong-is-to-promote-greater]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true purpose of the strong is to promote greater strength in the weak, and not to keep the weak in that state where they are at the mercy of the strong." -- Christian D. Larson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
