<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/915448-rishi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/915448-rishi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:39:49 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:39:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never put off till tomorrow what may be done day after tomorrow just as well&quot;. 

From: &quot;More Maxims of Mark" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:40:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no friend as loyal as a book." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:41:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361858-he-s-not-perfect-you-aren-t-either-and-the-two-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He’s not perfect. You aren’t either, and the two of you will never be perfect. But if he can make you laugh at least once, causes you to think twice, and if he admits to being human and making mistakes, hold onto him and give him the most you can. He isn’t going to quote poetry, he’s not thinking about you every moment, but he will give you a part of him that he knows you could break. Don’t hurt him, don’t change him, and don’t expect for more than he can give. Don’t analyze. Smile when he makes you happy, yell when he makes you mad, and miss him when he’s not there. Love hard when there is love to be had. Because perfect guys don’t exist, but there’s always one guy that is perfect for you." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:42:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124071-you-know-the-world-is-going-crazy-when-the-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:43:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Chris Rock]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124071-you-know-the-world-is-going-crazy-when-the-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know the world is going crazy when the best rapper is a white guy, the best golfer is a black guy, the tallest guy in the NBA is Chinese, the Swiss hold the America's Cup, France is accusing the U.S. of arrogance, Germany doesn't want to go to war, and the three most powerful men in America are named &quot;Bush&quot;, &quot;Dick&quot;, and &quot;Colin.&quot; Need I say more?" -- Chris Rock]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4258-when-his-life-was-ruined-his-family-killed-his-farm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:44:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4258-when-his-life-was-ruined-his-family-killed-his-farm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When his life was ruined, his family killed, his farm destroyed, Job knelt down on the ground and yelled up to the heavens, &quot;Why god? Why me?&quot; and the thundering voice of God answered, There's just something about you that pisses me off." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 00:55:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rishi add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169599-i-ve-never-been-lonely-i-ve-been-in-a-room---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've never been lonely. I've been in a room -- I've felt suicidal. I've been depressed. I've felt awful -- awful beyond all -- but I never felt that one other person could enter that room and cure what was bothering me...or that any number of people could enter that room. In other words, loneliness is something I've never been bothered with because I've always had this terrible itch for solitude. It's being at a party, or at a stadium full of people cheering for something, that I might feel loneliness. I'll quote Ibsen, &quot;The strongest men are the most alone.&quot; I've never thought, &quot;Well, some beautiful blonde will come in here and give me a fuck-job, rub my balls, and I'll feel good.&quot; No, that won't help. You know the typical crowd, &quot;Wow, it's Friday night, what are you going to do? Just sit there?&quot; Well, yeah. Because there's nothing out there. It's stupidity. Stupid people mingling with stupid people. Let them stupidify themselves. I've never been bothered with the need to rush out into the night. I hid in bars, because I didn't want to hide in factories. That's all. Sorry for all the millions, but I've never been lonely. I like myself. I'm the best form of entertainment I have. Let's drink more wine!" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
