<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/916927-ryan]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/916927-ryan" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 09:48:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2012 09:48:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1231-be-kind-for-everyone-you-meet-is-fighting-a-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a harder battle." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27602-cultivate-an-attitude-of-happiness-cultivate-a-spirit-of-optimism</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:14:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27602-cultivate-an-attitude-of-happiness-cultivate-a-spirit-of-optimism]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cultivate an attitude of happiness. Cultivate a spirit of optimism. Walk with faith, rejoicing in the beauties of nature, in the goodness of those you love, in the testimony which you carry in your heart concerning things divine." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79805-our-opportunities-to-give-of-ourselves-are-indeed-limitless-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:15:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79805-our-opportunities-to-give-of-ourselves-are-indeed-limitless-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our opportunities to give of ourselves are indeed limitless, but they are also perishable. There are hearts to gladden. There are kind words to say. There are gifts to be given. There are deeds to be done. There are souls to be saved.

As we remember that “when ye are in the service of your fellow beings ye are only in the service of your God,” (Mosiah 2:17) we will not find ourselves in the unenviable position of Jacob Marley’s ghost, who spoke to Ebenezer Scrooge in Charles Dickens’s immortal &quot;Christmas Carol.&quot; Marley spoke sadly of opportunities lost. Said he: 'Not to know that any Christian spirit working kindly in its little sphere, whatever it may be, will find its mortal life too short for its vast means of usefulness. Not to know that no space of regret can make amends for one life’s opportunity misused! Yet such was I! Oh! such was I!'

Marley added: 'Why did I walk through crowds of fellow-beings with my eyes turned down, and never raise them to that blessed Star which led the Wise Men to a poor abode? Were there no poor homes to which its light would have conducted me!'

Fortunately, as we know, Ebenezer Scrooge changed his life for the better. I love his line, 'I am not the man I was.'

Why is Dickens’ &quot;Christmas Carol&quot; so popular? Why is it ever new? I personally feel it is inspired of God. It brings out the best within human nature. It gives hope. It motivates change. We can turn from the paths which would lead us down and, with a song in our hearts, follow a star and walk toward the light. We can quicken our step, bolster our courage, and bask in the sunlight of truth. We can hear more clearly the laughter of little children. We can dry the tear of the weeping. We can comfort the dying by sharing the promise of eternal life. If we lift one weary hand which hangs down, if we bring peace to one struggling soul, if we give as did the Master, we can—by showing the way—become a guiding star for some lost mariner." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103528-the-laughter-of-the-world-is-merely-loneliness-pathetically-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:15:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103528-the-laughter-of-the-world-is-merely-loneliness-pathetically-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The laughter of the world is merely loneliness pathetically trying to reassure itself." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83915-like-the-vital-rudder-of-a-ship-we-have-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:17:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83915-like-the-vital-rudder-of-a-ship-we-have-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like the vital rudder of a ship, we have been provided a way to determine the direction we travel. The lighthouse of the Lord beckons to all as we sail the seas of life. Our home port is the celestial kingdom of God. Our purpose is to steer an undeviating course in that direction. A man without a purpose is like a ship without a rudder—never likely to reach home port. To us comes the signal: Chart your course, set your sail, position your rudder, and proceed." -- Thomas S. Monson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27607-we-must-not-falter-nor-weary-in-well-doing-we-must</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:18:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27607-we-must-not-falter-nor-weary-in-well-doing-we-must]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must not falter nor weary in well-doing. We must lengthen our stride. Not only is our own eternal welfare at stake, but also the eternal welfare of many of our brothers and sisters who are not now members of this, the true Church. I thrill to the words of the Prophet Joseph Smith in a letter that he sent to the Church from Nauvoo on September 6, 1842: 'Shall we not go on in so great a cause? Go forward. … Courage … and on, on to the victory!" -- Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62463-do-not-allow-yourselves-to-be-made-to-feel-inadequate</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:18:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Marvin. J. Ashton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62463-do-not-allow-yourselves-to-be-made-to-feel-inadequate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not allow yourselves to be made to feel inadequate or frustrated because you cannot do everything others seem to be accomplishing.  Only you and your Father in Heaven know your needs, strengths, and desires.  Around this knowledge your personal course must be charted and your chioces made." -- Marvin. J. Ashton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27604-perseverance-means-to-continue-in-a-given-course-until-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:18:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27604-perseverance-means-to-continue-in-a-given-course-until-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perseverance means to continue in a given course until we have reached a goal or objective, regardless of obstacles, opposition, and other counterinfluences...Perseverance is a positive, active characteristic...It gives us hope by helping us realize that the righteous suffer no failure except in giving up and no longer trying." -- Joseph B. Wirthlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27609-you-can-wake-up-every-day-looking-forward-to-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:19:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Julie B. Beck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27609-you-can-wake-up-every-day-looking-forward-to-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can wake up every day looking forward to new adventures with hope smiling brightly before you because you have a Savior. You are baptized in His Church.... You just need to stay in, pressing forward with a brightness of hope to your heavenly home." -- Julie B. Beck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120963-we-re-not-alone--at-least-we-re-alone-only-if-we-choose</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:19:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/120963-we-re-not-alone--at-least-we-re-alone-only-if-we-choose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're not alone--at least, we're alone only if we choose to be alone.  We're alone only if we choose to go through life relying solely on our own strength rather than learning to draw upon the power of God.  " -- Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144633-god-not-only-loves-the-obedient---he-enlightens-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:19:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144633-god-not-only-loves-the-obedient---he-enlightens-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God not only loves the obedient - He enlightens them." -- Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118533-thus-when-we-plead-for-the-gift-of-charity-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:19:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118533-thus-when-we-plead-for-the-gift-of-charity-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thus, when we plead for the gift of charity, we aren't asking for lovely feelings toward someone who bugs us or someone who has injured or wounded us.  We are actually pleading for our very natures to be changed, for our character and disposition to become more and more like the Savior's, so that we literally feel as He would feel and thus do what He would do." -- Sheri L. Dew]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95243-any-task-in-life-is-easier-if-we-approach-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:20:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Richard L. Evans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95243-any-task-in-life-is-easier-if-we-approach-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any task in life is easier if we approach it with the one at a time attitude. ... To cite a whimsical saying; 'If you chase two rabbits, both of them will escape.' No one is adequate to do everything all at once. We have to select what is important, what is possible, and begin where we are, with what we have. And if we beginand if we keep going the weight, the worry, the doubt, the depression will begin to lift .... We can't do everything always, but we can do something now, and doing something will help to lift the weight and lessen the worry, 'The beginning,' said Plato, 'is the most important part." -- Richard L. Evans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66003-to-be-or-not-to-be-that-is-not-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:20:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Truman G. Madsen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66003-to-be-or-not-to-be-that-is-not-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be or not to be?'  That is not the question.  What is the question?  The question is not one of being, but of becoming.  'To become more or not to become more'  This is the question faced by each intelligence in our universe." -- Truman G. Madsen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431932-you-are-good-but-it-is-not-enough-just-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:21:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431932-you-are-good-but-it-is-not-enough-just-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are good. But it is not enough just to be good. You must be good for something. You must contribute good to the world. The world must be a better place for your presence. And the good that is in you must be spread to others… In this world so filled with problems, so constantly threatened by dark and evil challenges, you can and must rise above mediocrity, above indifference. You can become involved and speak with a strong voice for that which is right." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212360-when-we-know-who-we-are-and-what-we-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:25:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Julie B. Beck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212360-when-we-know-who-we-are-and-what-we-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we know who we are and what we are supposed to do, it is easier to make important decisions about education, careers, and marriage. It is easier to shine our light in our families, with our friends, and in all other places." -- Julie B. Beck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498748-mothers-who-know-do-less-they-permit-less-of-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:27:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Julie B. Beck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/498748-mothers-who-know-do-less-they-permit-less-of-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mothers who know do less. They permit less of what will not bear good fruit eternally. They allow less media in their homes, less distraction, less activity that draws their children away from their home. Mothers who know are willing to live on less and consume less of the world’s goods in order to spend more time with their children—more time eating together, more time working together, more time reading together, more time talking, laughing, singing, and exemplifying. These mothers choose carefully and do not try to choose it all." -- Julie B. Beck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574103-the-ability-to-qualify-for-receive-and-act-on-personal</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 19:27:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ryan add a quote by Julie B. Beck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/574103-the-ability-to-qualify-for-receive-and-act-on-personal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ability to qualify for, receive, and act on personal revelation is the single most important skill that can be acquired in this life." -- Julie B. Beck]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
