<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/917328-woosung]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/917328-woosung" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 13:33:32 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26383-stephen-covey-in-his-book-the-8th-habit-decribes-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2008 13:33:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Woosung add a quote by Chip Heath &amp; Dan Heath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26383-stephen-covey-in-his-book-the-8th-habit-decribes-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stephen Covey, in his book The 8th Habit, decribes a poll of 23,000 employees drawn from a number of companies and industries. He reports the poll's findings:

    * Only 37 percent said they have a clear understanding of what their organization is trying to achieve and why
    * Only one in five was enthusiastic about their team's and their organization's goals
    * Only one in five said they had a clear &quot;line of sight&quot; between their tasks and their team's and organization's goals
    * Only 15 percent felt that their organization fully enables them to execute key goals
    * Only 20 percent fully trusted the organization they work for



Then, Covey superimposes a very human metaphor over the statistics. He says, &quot;If, say, a soccer team had these same scores, only 4 of the 11 players on the field would know which goal is theirs. Only 2 of the 11 would care. Only 2 of the 11 would know what position they play and know exactly what they are supposed to do. And all but 2 players would, in some way, be competing against their own team members rather than the opponent." -- Chip Heath &amp; Dan Heath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
