<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921168-robert]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921168-robert" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 04:51:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137330-you-see-they-think-they-re-saving-you-and-you-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 04:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by BHUTTO BENAZIR]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137330-you-see-they-think-they-re-saving-you-and-you-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You see, they think they're saving you, and you think you're saving them.  That's where the trouble starts.  Someone says, 'I saved you, now here's what I want.' And its the same with big countries and little ones, religious leaders and their followers, even husbands and wives.  When things really work, though, it's because people realize that this is a lie, that, really, we all save one another.  It's the way of the world.  Things work out for the best when everyone makes it, together, when we manage to save each other. (from The Way of the World)" -- BHUTTO BENAZIR]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137652-things-will-go-wrong-at-times-you-can-t-always-control</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 09:09:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Tony Dungy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137652-things-will-go-wrong-at-times-you-can-t-always-control]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things will go wrong at times.  You can't always control your attitude, approach, and response.  You options are to complain or to look ahead and figure out how to make the situation better" -- Tony Dungy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2009 05:08:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/298-a-day-without-sunshine-is-like-you-know-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A day without sunshine is like, you know, night." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161216-honestly-i-m-not-sure-how-much-longer-i-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 05:12:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Nic Sheff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161216-honestly-i-m-not-sure-how-much-longer-i-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["  Honestly, I'm not sure how much longer I can keep doing this.  It's like there are seven candles lit in my stomach.  One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.  Seven candles burning and smoking - lit - seven flames of doubt, fear, sorrow, pain, waste, hopelessness, despair.  They turn my insides black with soot and ash.  There is something at the back of my eyes- a pressure building, building, building - hot like the flames of seven candles, which no amount of breath can extinguish.
  I imagine drinking glasses of water.  One, two, three four, five, six, seven.  I dive into the clearest pool.  I drown myself in the coarse, dry sand.  I swallow handfuls of crushed white salt, but the flames burn still - brighter, hotter, deeper.  Sweat runs in delicate patterns down my back, over my crooked spine and jutting hips.  I scratch at the wounds these last weeks have left, but I can't break free of them.  The flies gather and vultures circle overhead.  The fire eats away my flesh.  The fire spreads.  The fire runs through my veins.  The fire courses beneath my muscles -  my tendons - the marrow of my bones.
  I sit rocking on the street corner.  No, I can't keep doing this.  I just can't." -- Nic Sheff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169766-blindness-is-a-traveling-exhibit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2009 22:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Kuusisto Stephen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/169766-blindness-is-a-traveling-exhibit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Blindness is a traveling exhibit." -- Kuusisto Stephen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206596-the-lesson-here-is-very-simple-but-it-is-striking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2009 04:24:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Robert add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206596-the-lesson-here-is-very-simple-but-it-is-striking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The lesson here is very simple.  But it is striking how often it is overlooked.  We are so caught in the myths of the best and the brightest and the self-made that we think outliers spring naturally from the earth.  We look at the young Bill Gates and marvel that our world allowed that thirteen-year-old to become a fabulously successful entrepreneur.  But that's the wrong lesson.  Our world only allowed one thirteen-year-old unlimited access to a time sharing terminal in 1968.  If a million teenagers had been given the same opportunity, how many more Microsofts would we have today?" -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
