<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921145-elizabeth]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921145-elizabeth" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:46:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10819-take-risks-that-is-really-what-life-is-about-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Linda Olsson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10819-take-risks-that-is-really-what-life-is-about-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take risks!  That is really what life is about.  We must pursue our own happiness.  Nobody has ever lived our lives; ther are no guidelines.  Trust your instincts.  Accept nothing but the best.  But then also look for it carefully.  Don't allow it to slip between your fingers.  Sometimes, good things come to us in a such a quiet fashion.  And nothing comes complete.  It is what we make of whatever we encounter that determines the outcome.  What we choose to see, what we choose to save.  And what we choose to remember.  Never foget that all the love in your life is there, inside you, always." -- Linda Olsson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27981-you-think-the-dead-we-loved-truly-ever-leave-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27981-you-think-the-dead-we-loved-truly-ever-leave-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think the dead we loved truly ever leave us? You think that we don't recall them more clearly in times of great trouble?" -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183211-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:51:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183211-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an idea that the only thing which makes it possible to regard this world we live in without disgust is the beauty which now and then men create out of the chaos. The pictures they paint, the music they compose, the books they write, and the lives they lead. Of all these the richest in beauty is the beautiful life. That is the perfect work of art." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10024-once-in-my-father-s-bookshop-i-heard-a-regular-customer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in my father's bookshop, I heard a regular customer say that few things leave a deeper mark on a reader than the first book that finds its way into his heart.  Those first images, the echo of words we think we have left behind, accompany us throughout our lives and sculpt a palace in our memory to which, sooner or later—no matter how many books we read, how many worlds we discover, or how much we learn or forget—we will return." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 19:28:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30119-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2011 17:10:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30119-i-have-an-idea-that-the-only-thing-which-makes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an idea that the only thing which makes it possible to regard this world we live in without disgust is the beauty which now and then men create out of the chaos." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2940-to-choose-doubt-as-a-philosophy-of-life-is-akin</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 07:54:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Yann Martel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2940-to-choose-doubt-as-a-philosophy-of-life-is-akin]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To choose doubt as a philosophy of life is akin to choosing immobility as a means of transportation." -- Yann Martel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294220-most-people-are-blind-to-magic-they-move-thru-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 16:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Lev Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294220-most-people-are-blind-to-magic-they-move-thru-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most people are blind to magic. They move thru a blank and empty world. They’re bored with their lives and there’s nothing they can do about it. They’re eaten alive by longing and they’re dead before they die." -- Lev Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398356-she-sounds-like-someone-who-spends-a-lot-of-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 17:56:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398356-she-sounds-like-someone-who-spends-a-lot-of-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She sounds like someone who spends a lot of time in libraries, which are the best sorts of people." -- Catherynne M. Valente]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75567-humanity-can-be-roughly-divided-into-three-sorts-of-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 10:32:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Elizabeth Goudge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/75567-humanity-can-be-roughly-divided-into-three-sorts-of-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity can be roughly divided into three sorts of people - those who find comfort in literature, those who find comfort in personal adornment, and those who find comfort in food;" -- Elizabeth Goudge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591083-work-hard-do-good-be-incredible</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 05:05:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/591083-work-hard-do-good-be-incredible]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Work hard. Do good. Be incredible!" -- Cheryl Strayed]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 15:24:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442778-someone-needs-to-tell-those-tales-when-the-battles-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone needs to tell those tales.  When the battles are fought and won and lost, when the pirates find their treasures and the dragons eat their foes for breakfast with a nice cup of Lapsang souchong, someone needs to tell their bits of overlapping narrative.  There's magic in that.  It's in the listener, and for each and every ear it will be different, and it will affect them in ways they can never predict.  From the mundane to the profound.  You may tell a tale that takes up residence in someone's soul, becomes their blood and self and purpose.  That tale will move them and drive them and who knows what they might do because of it, because of your words.  That is your role, your gift.  Your sister may be able to see the future, but you yourself can shape it, boy.  Do not forget that... there are many kinds of magic, after all." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475691-most-maidens-are-perfectly-capable-of-rescuing-themselves-in-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 15:25:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/475691-most-maidens-are-perfectly-capable-of-rescuing-themselves-in-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most maidens are perfectly capable of rescuing themselves in my experience, at least the ones worth something, in any case." -- Erin Morgenstern]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532899-i-do-not-know-at-this-point-whether-joshua-joseph</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 10:47:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Nick Harkaway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/532899-i-do-not-know-at-this-point-whether-joshua-joseph]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not know, at this point, whether Joshua Joseph Spork is the man of my life. He could be. I have given it considerable thought. The jury is still out. The issue between you and me is that you wish to deprive me of the opportunity to find out. Joe Spork is not yours to give or to withhold from me, Mr. Cummerbund. He is &lt;em&gt;mine&lt;/em&gt;, until I decide otherwise. You have caused him grief, sullied his name, and you have hurt him. If anyone is going to make him weep, or lie about him, or even do bad things to him, it is &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt;." -- Nick Harkaway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502976-like-wine-proven-al-magic-had-its-own-distinctive-terroir-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2012 05:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Lev Grossman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502976-like-wine-proven-al-magic-had-its-own-distinctive-terroir-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like wine, Provençal magic had its own distinctive terroir. It was rich and chaotic and romantic. It was a night-magic, confabulated out of moons and silver, wine and blood, knights and fairies, wind and rivers and forests. It concerned itself with good and evil but also with the vast intermediate realm in between, the realm of mischief." -- Lev Grossman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55779-to-be-more-precise-it-was-the-color-of-heartache</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 17:47:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55779-to-be-more-precise-it-was-the-color-of-heartache]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be more precise it was the color of heartache." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293652-it-is-also-true-that-his-hair-had-a-reddish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 17:49:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/293652-it-is-also-true-that-his-hair-had-a-reddish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is also true that his hair had a reddish tinge and, as everybody knows, no one with red hair can ever truly be said to be handsome." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281017-he-gave-her-his-heart-she-took-it-and-placed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2013 17:53:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Susanna Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/281017-he-gave-her-his-heart-she-took-it-and-placed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He gave her his heart. She took it and placed it quietly in the pocket of her gown. No one observed what she did." -- Susanna Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 05:47:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never get a cup of tea large enough or a book long enough to suit me." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57437-i-have-come-home-at-last-this-is-my-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 05:50:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57437-i-have-come-home-at-last-this-is-my-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have come home at last! This is my real country! I belong here. This is the land I have been looking for all my life, though I never knew it till now...Come further up, come further in!" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255733-he-felt-her-heart-beating-against-his-chest-the-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 19:02:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/255733-he-felt-her-heart-beating-against-his-chest-the-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He felt her heart beating against his chest.  The moment began to transmute, and he wondered if there was something he should do.  He wondered if he should kiss her.  He wondered if he wanted to kiss her, and he realized that he truly didn't know." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21556-he-had-noticed-that-events-were-cowards-they-didn-t-occur</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2013 19:02:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21556-he-had-noticed-that-events-were-cowards-they-didn-t-occur]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had noticed that events were cowards: they didn't occur singly, but instead they would run in packs and leap out at him all at once." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153948-to-live-is-to-change-to-acquire-the-words-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 04:31:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/153948-to-live-is-to-change-to-acquire-the-words-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is to change, to acquire the words of a story, and that is the only celebration we mortals really know." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127900-there-are-three-things-and-three-things-only-that-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 18:27:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127900-there-are-three-things-and-three-things-only-that-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three things, and three things only, that can lift the pain of mortality and ease the ravages of life.  These are wine, women and song." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25022-old-stories-would-tell-how-weavers-would-kill-each-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 19:06:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by China Miéville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25022-old-stories-would-tell-how-weavers-would-kill-each-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Old stories would tell how Weavers would kill each other over aesthetic disagreements, such as whether it was prettier to destroy an army of a thousand men or to leave it be, or whether a particular dandelion should or should not be plucked. For a Weaver, to think was to think aesthetically. To act--to Weave--was to bring about more pleasing patterns. They did not eat physical food: they seemed to subsist on the appreciation of beauty." -- China Miéville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2682-sometimes-i-have-loved-the-peacefulness-of-an-ordinary-sunday</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 06:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2682-sometimes-i-have-loved-the-peacefulness-of-an-ordinary-sunday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I have loved the peacefulness of an ordinary Sunday. It is like standing in a newly planted garden after a warm rain. You can feel the silent and invisible life." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45016-this-is-an-interesting-planet-it-deserves-all-the-attention</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 06:24:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45016-this-is-an-interesting-planet-it-deserves-all-the-attention]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is an interesting planet.  It deserves all the attention you can give it." -- Marilynne Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 10:49:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/973323-i-hope-that-in-this-year-to-come-you-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope that in this year to come, you make mistakes. Because if you are making mistakes...you're Doing Something." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5352-to-be-mad-is-to-feel-with-excruciating-intensity-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 07:27:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5352-to-be-mad-is-to-feel-with-excruciating-intensity-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be mad is to feel with excruciating intensity the sadness and joy of a time which has not arrived or has already been. And to protect their delicate vision of that other time, madmen  will justify their condition with touching loyalty, and surround it with a thousand distractive schemes. These schemes, in turn, drive them deeper and deeper into the darkness and light (which is their mortification and their reward), and confront them with a choice. They may either slacken and fall back, accepting the relief of a rational view and the approval of others, or they may push on, and, by falling, arise. When and if by their unforgivable stubbornness they finally burst through to worlds upon worlds of motionless light, they are no longer called afflicted or insane. They are called saints." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196688-they-gave-themselves-up-to-the-stars-the-way-swimmers</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 07:27:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Mark Helprin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/196688-they-gave-themselves-up-to-the-stars-the-way-swimmers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They gave themselves up to the stars the way swimmers can surrender to the waves, and the stars took them without resistance." -- Mark Helprin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
