<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921360-steve-malley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/921360-steve-malley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 20:00:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 20:00:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44156-the-human-spirit-must-prevail-over-technology</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 20:01:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44156-the-human-spirit-must-prevail-over-technology]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The human spirit must prevail over technology." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2008 19:06:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18830-finish-each-day-and-be-done-with-it-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could.  Some blunders and absurdities no doubt crept in; forget them as soon as you can. Tomorrow is a new day.  You shall begin it serenely and with too high a spirit to be encumbered with your old nonsense." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44160-it-isn-t-necessary-to-have-relatives-in-kansas-city-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 20:04:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44160-it-isn-t-necessary-to-have-relatives-in-kansas-city-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It isn't necessary to have relatives in Kansas City in order to be unhappy." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44161-your-greatest-power---the-things-that-you-keep-silently</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2008 20:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Elinor MacDonald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44161-your-greatest-power---the-things-that-you-keep-silently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your Greatest Power - The things that you keep silently telling yourself are your most important conversations. Whatever you habitually dwell on in your mind, you will become, express, or experience. Your subconscious mind will be your best friend or your worst enemy. Everything depends on the way you train it and the use you make of it. ... your freedom to think, choose, reason, and decide for yourself. It shapes your destiny and determines the attraction and repulsion in your life. Guard its portals well. It is your hope of heaven." -- Elinor MacDonald]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
