<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/922164-diana-passy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/922164-diana-passy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:05:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:05:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593072-os-chap-us-tamb-m-servem-para-isso-para-esconder-o-cabelo</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:05:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Juan Pablo Villalobos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593072-os-chap-us-tamb-m-servem-para-isso-para-esconder-o-cabelo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Os chapéus também servem para isso, para esconder o cabelo. Não só quando se trata de um penteado feio, porque o melhor é esconder o cabelo sempre, até com penteados que dizem ser bonitos. O cabelo é uma parte morta do corpo. Por exemplo: quando você corta o cabelo, não dói. E, se não dói, é porque está morto. Quando alguém o puxa sim que dói, mas o que dói não é o cabelo, mas o couro cabeludo da cabeça. Pesquisei isso nas pesquisas livres com Mazatzin. O cabelo é como um cadáver que você traz em cima da cabeça enquanto está vivo. Além do mais é um cadáver fulminante, que cresce sem parar, o que é muito sórdido. Talvez quando você se converte em cadáver o cabelo já não seja sórdido, mas antes sim. Isso é o melhor dos hipopótamos anões da Libéria, que eles são calvos." -- Juan Pablo Villalobos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592414-dar-um-passo-pode-ser-fruto-de-uma-decis-o-complexa</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:05:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by José Luís Peixoto]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/592414-dar-um-passo-pode-ser-fruto-de-uma-decis-o-complexa]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dar um passo pode ser fruto de uma decisão complexa. Há a possibilidade de seguir para a direita ou para a esquerda, posso continuar em frente ou voltar para trás, desfazer. Cada escolha lançará uma cadeia de resultados. Mal comparado, é como acordar na estação Sèvres-Lecourbe e não ter mapa do metro, nunca ter estado ali, não saber sequer onde se está, não saber sequer o que é o metro. Ter de aprender tudo. Ao fim de um tempo, com sorte, conversando com pedintes cegos, tocadores de concertina, talvez se consiga chegar à conclusão que se quer ir para a estação Ourcq, esse é o lugar onde se poderá ser feliz, mas como encontrar o caminho sem mapa, sem conhecer linhas e ligações? É possível arrastar a vida inteira no metro de Paris e nunca passar por Ourcq. É também possível passar por lá e não reconhecer que é ali que se quer sair." -- José Luís Peixoto]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385500-you-will-become-way-less-concerned-with-what-other-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:06:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/385500-you-will-become-way-less-concerned-with-what-other-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will become way less concerned with what other people think of you when you realize how seldom they do." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630825-the-46-year-old-recipient-of-the-jarvik-ix-exterior-artificial-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:06:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630825-the-46-year-old-recipient-of-the-jarvik-ix-exterior-artificial-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The 46-year-old recipient of the Jarvik IX Exterior Artificial Heart was actively window shopping in Cambridge, Massachusetts’ fashionable Har­vard Square when a transvestite purse snatcher, a drug addict with a crimi­nal record all too well known to public officials, bizarrely outfitted in a strapless cocktail dress, spike heels, tattered feather boa, and auburn wig, brutally tore the life sustaining purse from the woman’s unwitting grasp.
The active, alert woman gave chase to the purse snatching ‘woman’ for as long as she could, plaintively shouting to passers by the words ‘Stop her! She stole my heart!’ on the fashionable sidewalk crowded with shop­pers, reportedly shouting repeatedly, ‘She stole my heart, stop her!’ In response to her plaintive calls, tragically, misunderstanding shoppers and passers by merely shook their heads at one another, smiling knowingly at what they ignorantly presumed to be yet another alternative lifestyle’s re­lationship gone sour. A duo of Cambridge, Massachusetts, patrolmen, whose names are being withheld from Moment’s dogged queries, were publicly heard to passively quip, ‘Happens all the time,’ as the victimized woman staggered frantically past in the wake of the fleet transvestite, shouting for help for her stolen heart." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427079-cpus-cayce-pollard-units-that-s-what-damien-calls-the-clothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:09:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427079-cpus-cayce-pollard-units-that-s-what-damien-calls-the-clothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["CPUs. Cayce Pollard Units. That’s what Damien calls the clothing she wears. CPUs are either black, white, or gray, and ideally seem to have come into this world without human intervention.
 
What people take for relentless minimalism is a side effect of too much exposure to the reactor-cores of fashion. This has resulted in a remorseless paring-down of what she can and will wear. She is, literally, allergic to fashion. She can only tolerate things that could have been worn, to a general lack of comment, during any year between 1945 and 2000. She’s a design-free zone, a one-woman school of anti whose very austerity periodically threatens to spawn its own cult." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177245-he-took-a-duck-in-the-face-at-250-knots</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2012 20:43:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177245-he-took-a-duck-in-the-face-at-250-knots]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He took a duck in the face at 250 knots." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627800-were-he-now-still-among-the-living-dr-incandenza-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 20:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/627800-were-he-now-still-among-the-living-dr-incandenza-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Were he now still among the living, Dr. Incandenza would now describe tennis in the paradoxical terms of what’s now called ‘Extra-Linear Dynamics.’ And Schtitt, whose knowledge of formal math is probably about equivalent to that of a Taiwanese kindergartner, nevertheless seemed to know what Hopman and van der Meer and Bollettieri seemed not to know: that locating beauty and art and magic and improvement and keys to excellence and victory in the prolix flux of match play is not a fractal matter of reducing chaos to a pattern. Seemed intuitively to sense that it was a matter not of reduction at all, but — perversely — of expansion, the aleatory flutter of uncontrolled, metastatic growth — each well-shot ball admitting of n possible responses, n² responses to those responses, and on into what Incandenza would articulate to anyone who shared both his backgrounds as a Cantorian continuum of infinities of possible move and response, Cantorian and beautiful because infoliating, contained, this diagnate infinity of infinities of choice and execution, mathematically uncontrolled but humanly contained, bounded by the talent and imagination of self and opponent, bent in on itself by the containing boundaries of skill and imagination that brought one player finally down, that kept both from winning, that made it, finally, a game, these boundaries of self." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172107-it-s-of-some-interest-that-the-lively-arts-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2012 21:25:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172107-it-s-of-some-interest-that-the-lively-arts-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s of some interest that the lively arts of the millenial U.S.A. treat anhedonia and internal emptiness as hip and cool. It’s maybe the vestiges of the Romantic glorification of Weltschmerz, which means world-weariness or hip ennui. Maybe it’s the fact that most of the arts here are produced by world-weary and sophisticated older people and then consumed by younger people who not only consume art but study it for clues on how to be cool, hip - and keep in mind that, for kids and younger people, to be hip and cool is the same as to be admired and accepted and included and so Unalone. Forget so-called peer-pressure. It’s more like peer-hunger. No? We enter a spiritual puberty where we snap to the fact that the great transcendent horror is loneliness, excluded encagement in the self. Once we’ve hit this age, we will now give or take anything, wear any mask, to fit, be part-of, not be Alone, we young. The U.S. arts are our guide to inclusion. A how-to. We are shown how to fashion masks of ennui and jaded irony at a young age where the face is fictile enough to assume the shape of whatever it wears. And then it’s stuck there, the weary cynicism that saves us from gooey sentiment and unsophisticated naivete. Sentiment equals naïveté on this continent...

...Hal, who’s empty but not dumb, theorizes privately that what passes for hip cynical transcendence of sentiment is really some kind of fear of being really human, since to be really human (at least as he conceptualizes it) is probably to be unavoidably sentimental and naive and goo-prone and generally pathetic, is to be in some basic interior way forever infantile, some sort of not-quite-right-looking infant dragging itself anaclitically around the map, with big wet eyes and froggy-soft skin, huge skull, gooey drool. One of the really American things about Hal, probably, is the way he despises what it is he’s really lonely for: this hideous internal self, incontinent of sentiment and need, that pules and writhes just under the hip empty mask, anhedonia." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427523-every-new-medium-transforms-the-nature-of-human-thought-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 08:57:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by James Gleick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/427523-every-new-medium-transforms-the-nature-of-human-thought-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every new medium transforms the nature of human thought. In the long run, history is the story of information becoming aware of itself." -- James Gleick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745896-an-essential-difference-between-british-and-american-punk-bands-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 16:14:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Clinton Heylin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/745896-an-essential-difference-between-british-and-american-punk-bands-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An essential difference between British and American punk bands can be found in their respective views of rock &amp; roll history. The British bands took a deliberately anti-intellectual stance, refuting any awareness of, or influence from, previous exponents of the form. The New York and Cleveland bands saw themselves as self-consciously drawing on and extending an existing tradition in American rock &amp; roll. 
(...)
A second difference between the British and American punk scenes was their relative gestation periods. The British weekly music press was reviewing Sex Pistols shows less than three months after their cacophonous debut. Within a year of the Pistols' first performance they had a record deal, with the 'major' label EMI. Within six months of their first gigs the Damned and the Clash also secured contracts, the latter with CBS. The CBGBs scene went largely ignored by the American music industry until 1976 -- two years after the debuts of Television, the Ramones and Blondie. Even then only Television signed to an established label." -- Clinton Heylin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796747-if-the-early-english-and-la-punk-bands-shared-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2013 19:19:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Clinton Heylin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/796747-if-the-early-english-and-la-punk-bands-shared-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the early English and LA punk bands shared a common sound, the New York bands just shared the same clubs. As such, while the English scene never became known as the '100 Club' sound, CBGBs was the solitary common component in the New York bands' development, transcended once they had outgrown the need to play the club. Even their supposed musical heritage was not exactly common -- the Ramones preferring the Dolls/Stooges to Television's Velvets/Coltrane to Blondie's Stones/Brit-Rock. Though the scene had been built up as a single movement, when commercial implications began to sink in, the differences that separated the bands became far more important than the similarities which had previously bound them together.
In the two years following the summer 1975 festival, CBGBs had become something of an ideological battleground, if not between the bands then between their critical proponents. The divisions between a dozen bands, all playing the same club, all suffering the same hardships, all sharing the same love of certain central bands in the history of rock &amp; roll, should not have been that great. But the small scene very quickly partitioned into art-rockers and exponents of a pure let's-rock aesthetic." -- Clinton Heylin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/831203-i-liked-myths-they-weren-t-adult-stories-and-they-weren-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 08:02:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/831203-i-liked-myths-they-weren-t-adult-stories-and-they-weren-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I liked myths.  They weren't adult stories and they weren't children's stories.  They were better than that.  They just &lt;i&gt;were&lt;/i&gt;." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/833316-i-attempt-all-day-at-work-not-to-think-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 14:49:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/833316-i-attempt-all-day-at-work-not-to-think-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I attempt all day, at work, not to think about what lies ahead, but this costs me so much effort that there is nothing left for my work. I handle telephone calls so badly that after a while the switchboard operator refuses to connect me. So I had better say to myself, Go ahead and polish the silverware beautifully, then lay it out ready on the sideboard and be done with it. Because I polish it in my mind all day long—this is what torments me (and doesn't clean the silver)." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714058-matthew-had-called-her-harmless-harmless-and-being-with-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2013 07:05:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by E. Lockhart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/714058-matthew-had-called-her-harmless-harmless-and-being-with-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Matthew had called her harmless. Harmless. And being with him made Frankie feel squashed into a box - a box where she was expected to be sweet and sensitive (but not oversensitive); a box for young and pretty girls who were not as bright or as powerful as their boyfriends. A box for people who were not forces to be reckoned with.

Frankie wanted to be a force." -- E. Lockhart]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117477-it-is-better-to-be-alone-she-figures-than-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 19:38:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diana add a quote by E. Lockhart]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117477-it-is-better-to-be-alone-she-figures-than-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be alone, she figures, than to be with someone who can't see who you are.  It is better to lead than to follow.  It is better to speak up than stay silent.  It is better to open doors than to shut them on people.

She will not be simple and sweet.  She will not be what people tell her to be.  That Bunny Rabbit is dead." -- E. Lockhart]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
