<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/922718-christopher]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/922718-christopher" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 01:06:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231855-if-it-is-not-beautiful-for-someone-it-does-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 01:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by William Gaddis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231855-if-it-is-not-beautiful-for-someone-it-does-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If it is not beautiful for someone, it does not exist." -- William Gaddis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110045-how-how-fragile-situations-are-but-not-tenuous-delicate</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 01:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by William Gaddis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110045-how-how-fragile-situations-are-but-not-tenuous-delicate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How ... how fragile situations are.  But not tenuous.  Delicate, but not flimsy, not indulgent.  Delicate, that's why they keep breaking, they must break and you must get the pieces together and show it before it breaks again, or put them aside for a moment when something else breaks and turn to that, and all this keeps going on.  That's why most writing now, if you read it they go on one two three four and tell you what happened like newspaper accounts, no adjectives, no long sentences, no tricks they pretend, and they finally believe that they really believe that the way they saw it is the way it is ... it never takes your breath away, telling you things you already know, laying everything out flat, as though the terms and the time, and the nature and the movement of everything were secrets of the same magnitude.  They write for people who read with the surface of their minds, people with reading habits that make the smallest demands on them, people brought up reading for facts, who know what's going to come next and want to know what's coming next, and get angry at surprises.  Clarity's essential, and detail, no fake mysticism, the facts are bad enough.  But we're embarrassed for people who tell too much, and tell it without surprise.  How does he know what happened? unless it's one unshaven man alone in a boat, changing I to he, and how often do you get a man alone in a boat, in all this ... all this ... Listen, there are so many delicate fixtures, moving toward you, you'll see.  Like a man going into a dark room, holding his hands down guarding his parts for fear of a table corner, and ... Why, all this around us is for people who can keep their balance only in the light, where they move as though nothing were fragile, nothing tempered by possibility, and all of a sudden bang! something breaks.  Then you have to stop and put the pieces together again.   But you never can put them back together quite the same way.  You stop when you can and expose things, and leave them within reach, and others come  on by themselves, and they break, and even then you may put the pieces aside just out of reach until you can bring them back and show them, put together slightly different, maybe a little more enduring, until you've broken it and picked up the pieces enough times, and you have the whole thing in all its dimensions.  But the discipline, the detail, it's just ... sometimes the accumulation is too much to bear." -- William Gaddis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 07:39:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56944-the-moral-test-of-government-is-how-that-government-treats</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 22:39:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Hubert H. Humphrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56944-the-moral-test-of-government-is-how-that-government-treats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moral test of government is how that government treats those who are in the dawn of life, the children; those who are in the twilight of life, the elderly; and those who are in shadows of life, the sick, the needy, and the handicapped." -- Hubert H. Humphrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117121-compassion-is-not-weakness-and-concern-for-the-unfortunate-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 22:39:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Hubert H. Humphrey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117121-compassion-is-not-weakness-and-concern-for-the-unfortunate-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is not weakness, and concern for the unfortunate is not socialism." -- Hubert H. Humphrey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26485-i-ve-got-death-inside-me-it-s-just-a-question-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 20:47:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26485-i-ve-got-death-inside-me-it-s-just-a-question-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've got death inside me. It's just a question of whether or not I can outlive it." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118577-how-strange-it-is-we-have-these-deep-terrible-lingering</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2011 20:50:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118577-how-strange-it-is-we-have-these-deep-terrible-lingering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How strange it is. We have these deep terrible lingering fears about ourselves and the people we love. Yet we walk around, talk to people, eat and drink. We manage to function. The feelings are deep and real. Shouldn't they paralyze us? How is it we can survive them, at least for a little while? We drive a car, we teach a class. How is it no one sees how deeply afraid we were, last night, this morning? Is it something we all hide from each other, by mutual consent? Or do we share the same secret without knowing it? Wear the same disguise?" -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523688-genius-is-nothing-more-nor-less-than-childhood-recaptured-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 00:06:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/523688-genius-is-nothing-more-nor-less-than-childhood-recaptured-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Genius is nothing more nor less than childhood recaptured at will." -- Charles Baudelaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381955-compassion-hurts-when-you-feel-connected-to-everything-you-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 18:44:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by Andrew Boyd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381955-compassion-hurts-when-you-feel-connected-to-everything-you-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion hurts. When you feel connected to everything, you also feel responsible for everything. And you cannot turn away. Your destiny is bound with the destinies of others. You must either learn to carry the Universe or be crushed by it. You must grow strong enough to love the world, yet empty enough to sit down at the same table with its worst horrors." -- Andrew Boyd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77244-journalism-is-printing-what-someone-else-does-not-want-printed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2013 22:38:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Christopher add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77244-journalism-is-printing-what-someone-else-does-not-want-printed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Journalism is printing what someone else does not want printed: everything else is public relations." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
