<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/923923-erik]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/923923-erik" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:18:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:18:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1396-isn-t-it-enough-to-see-that-a-garden-is-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it enough to see that a garden is beautiful without having to believe that there are fairies at the bottom of it too?" -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:20:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13070-if-knowledge-can-create-problems-it-is-not-through-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:21:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Isaac Asimov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13070-if-knowledge-can-create-problems-it-is-not-through-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If knowledge can create problems, it is not through ignorance that we can solve them." -- Isaac Asimov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4676-the-man-who-does-not-do-his-own-thinking-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:22:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Robert Ingersoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4676-the-man-who-does-not-do-his-own-thinking-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who does not do his own thinking is a slave, and is a traitor to himself and to his fellowmen." -- Robert Ingersoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50079-there-are-in-nature-neither-rewards-nor-punishments-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:22:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Robert G. Ingersoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50079-there-are-in-nature-neither-rewards-nor-punishments-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are in nature neither rewards nor punishments — there are consequences." -- Robert G. Ingersoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:23:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:23:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2312-i-have-observed-indeed-generally-that-while-in-protestant-countries]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have observed, indeed, generally, that while in protestant countries the defections from the Platonic Christianity of the priests is to Deism, in catholic countries they are to Atheism. [author:Diderot|11004], [author:D'Alembert|3295333], [author:D’Holbach|1228712], [author:Condorcet|6420223], are known to have been among the most virtuous of men. Their virtue, then, must have had some other foundation than the love of God.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to Thomas Law, 13 June 1814&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:23:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10730-4-religion-your-reason-is-now-mature-enough-to-examine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["4. Religion. Your reason is now mature enough to examine this object. In the first place, divest yourself of all bias in favor of novelty &amp; singularity of opinion... shake off all the fears &amp; servile prejudices, under which weak minds are servilely crouched. &lt;b&gt;Fix reason firmly in her seat, and call to her tribunal every fact, every opinion. Question with boldness even the existence of a God; because, if there be one, he must more approve of the homage of reason, than that of blindfolded fear&lt;/b&gt;. You will naturally examine first, the religion of your own country. Read the Bible, then as you would read [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The facts which are within the ordinary course of nature, you will believe on the authority of the writer, as you do those of the same kind in [author:Livy|2840091] and [author:Tacitus|2936846]. The testimony of the writer weighs in their favor, in one scale, and their not being against the laws of nature, does not weigh against them. But those facts in the Bible which contradict the laws of nature, must be examined with more care, and under a variety of faces. Here you must recur to the pretensions of the writer to inspiration from God. Examine upon what evidence his pretensions are founded, and whether that evidence is so strong, as that its falsehood would be more improbable than a change in the laws of nature, in the case he relates. For example in the book of Joshua we are told the sun stood still several hours. Were we to read that fact in [author:Livy|2840091] or [author:Tacitus|2936846] we should class it with their showers of blood, speaking of statues, beasts, &amp;c. But it is said that the writer of that book was inspired. Examine therefore candidly what evidence there is of his having been inspired. The pretension is entitled to your inquiry, because millions believe it. On the other hand you are astronomer enough to know how contrary it is to the law of nature that a body revolving on its axis as the earth does, should have stopped, should not by that sudden stoppage have prostrated animals, trees, buildings, and should after a certain time have resumed its revolution, &amp; that without a second general prostration. Is this arrest of the earth's motion, or the evidence which affirms it, most within the law of probabilities? You will next read the New Testament. It is the history of a personage called Jesus. Keep in your eye the opposite pretensions: 1, of those who say he was begotten by God, born of a virgin, suspended &amp; reversed the laws of nature at will, &amp; ascended bodily into heaven; and 2, of those who say he was a man of illegitimate birth, of a benevolent heart, enthusiastic mind, who set out without pretensions to divinity, ended in believing them, and was punished capitally for sedition, by being gibbeted, according to the Roman law, which punished the first commission of that offence by whipping, &amp; the second by exile, or death &lt;i&gt;in fureâ&lt;/i&gt;.

...Do not be frightened from this inquiry by any fear of its consequences. If it ends in a belief that there is no God, you will find incitements to virtue in the comfort and pleasantness you feel in its exercise, and the love of others which it will procure you... In fine, I repeat, you must lay aside all prejudice on both sides, and neither believe nor reject anything, because any other persons, or description of persons, have rejected or believed it... I forgot to observe, when speaking of the New Testament, that you should read all the histories of Christ, as well of those whom a council of ecclesiastics have decided for us, to be Pseudo-evangelists, as those they named Evangelists. Because these Pseudo-evangelists pretended to inspiration, as much as the others, and you are to judge their pretensions by your own reason, and not by the reason of those ecclesiastics. Most of these are lost...

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to his nephew, Peter Carr, advising him in matters of religion, 1787&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13367-i-d-rather-be-a-rising-ape-than-a-falling-angel</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:25:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13367-i-d-rather-be-a-rising-ape-than-a-falling-angel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd rather be a rising ape than a falling angel." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2008 17:27:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11285-god-does-not-play-dice-with-the-universe-he-plays]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God does not play dice with the universe; He plays an ineffable game of His own devising, which might be compared, from the perspective of any of the other players [i.e. everybody], to being involved in an obscure and complex variant of poker in a pitch-dark room, with blank cards, for infinite stakes, with a Dealer who won't tell you the rules, and who &lt;i&gt;smiles all the time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 06:10:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14627-war-must-be-while-we-defend-our-lives-against-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 06:11:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14627-war-must-be-while-we-defend-our-lives-against-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War must be, while we defend our lives against a destroyer who would devour all; but I do not love the bright sword for its sharpness, nor the arrow for its swiftness, nor the warrior for his glory. I love only that which they defend." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4454-three-rings-for-the-elven-kings-under-the-sky-seven-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 06:12:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4454-three-rings-for-the-elven-kings-under-the-sky-seven-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Three Rings for the Elven-kings under the sky,
 Seven for the Dwarf-lords in halls of stone,
Nine for Mortal Men, doomed to die,
 One for the Dark Lord on his dark throne
In the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie.
 One Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them,
 One Ring to bring them all and in the darkness bind them.
In the Land of Mordor where the Shadows lie." -- J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145825-faith-n-belief-without-evidence-in-what-is-told-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 06:29:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145825-faith-n-belief-without-evidence-in-what-is-told-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Faith, n.&lt;/b&gt; Belief without evidence in what is told by one who speaks without knowledge, of things without parallel." -- Ambrose Bierce]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172230-the-doctrine-that-future-happiness-depends-upon-belief-is-monstrous</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 08:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Robert Ingersoll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172230-the-doctrine-that-future-happiness-depends-upon-belief-is-monstrous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The doctrine that future happiness depends upon belief is monstrous. It is the infamy of infamies. The notion that faith in Christ is to be rewarded by an eternity of bliss, while a dependence upon reason, observation and experience merits everlasting pain, is too absurd for refutation, and can be relieved only by that unhappy mixture of insanity and ignorance, called 'faith." -- Robert Ingersoll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3882-for-me-it-is-far-better-to-grasp-the-universe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 08:55:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3882-for-me-it-is-far-better-to-grasp-the-universe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For me, it is far better to grasp the Universe as it really is than to persist in delusion, however satisfying and reassuring." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50379-extraordinary-claims-require-extraordinary-evidence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2010 08:55:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Erik add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50379-extraordinary-claims-require-extraordinary-evidence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Extraordinary claims require extraordinary evidence." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
