<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/924067-crystal]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/924067-crystal" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:59:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1924-books-are-the-ultimate-dumpees-put-them-down-and-they-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:59:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1924-books-are-the-ultimate-dumpees-put-them-down-and-they-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the ultimate Dumpees: put them down and they’ll wait for you forever; pay attention to them and they always love you back." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:59:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20112-when-adults-say-teenagers-think-they-are-invincible-with-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When adults say, &quot;Teenagers think they are invincible&quot; with that sly, stupid smile on their faces, they don't know how right they are. We need never be hopeless, because we can never be irreparably broken. We think that we are invincible because we are. We cannot be born, and we cannot die. Like all energy, we can only change shapes and sizes and manifestations. They forget that when they get old. They get scared of losing and failing. But that part of us greater than the sum of our parts cannot begin and cannot end, and so it cannot fail." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142604-what-is-the-point-of-being-alive-if-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 17:59:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142604-what-is-the-point-of-being-alive-if-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is the point of being alive if you don't at least try to do something remarkable?" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105972-what-a-treacherous-thing-to-believe-that-a-person-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 21:50:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105972-what-a-treacherous-thing-to-believe-that-a-person-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What a treacherous thing to believe that a person is more than a person." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113977-did-you-know-that-for-pretty-much-the-entire-history</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:50:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113977-did-you-know-that-for-pretty-much-the-entire-history]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Did you know that for pretty much the entire history of the human species, the average life span was less than thirty years? You could count on ten years or so of real adulthood, right? There was no planning for retirement, There was no planning for a career. There was no planning. No time for plannning. No time for a future. But then the life spans started getting longer, and people started having more and more future. And now life has become the future. Every moment of your life is lived for the future--you go to high school so you can go to college so you can get a good job so you can get a nice house so you can afford to send your kids to college so they can get a good job so they can get a nice house so they can afford to send their kids to college." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135497-you-know-your-problem-quentin-you-keep-expecting-people-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know your problem, Quentin? You keep expecting people not to be themselves. I mean, I could hate you for being massively unpunctual and for never being interested in anything other than Margo Roth Spiegelman, and for, like, never asking me about how it's going with my girlfriend - but I don't give a shit, man, because you're you. My parents have a shit ton of black Santas, but that's okay. They're them. I'm too obsessed with a reference website to answer my phone sometimes when my friends call, or my girlfriend. That's okay, too. That's me. You like me anyway. And I like you. You're funny, and you're smart, and you may show up late, but you always show up eventually." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240693-isn-t-it-also-that-on-some-fundamental-level-we-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:52:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240693-isn-t-it-also-that-on-some-fundamental-level-we-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it also that on some fundamental level we find it difficult to understand that other people are human beings in the same way that we are? We idealize them as gods or dismiss them as animals." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142580-nothing-really-mattered-that-much-not-the-good-things-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:53:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142580-nothing-really-mattered-that-much-not-the-good-things-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing really mattered that much, not the good things and not the bad ones.  We were in the business of mutual amusement, and we were reasonably prosperous." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278372-i-always-thought-of-it-like-you-said-that-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:53:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/278372-i-always-thought-of-it-like-you-said-that-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always thought of it like you said, that all the strings inside him broke. But there are a thousand ways to look at it: maybe the strings break, or maybe our ships sink, or maybe we’re grass—our roots so interdependent that no one is dead as long as someone is alive. We don’t suffer from a shortage of metaphors, is what I mean. But you have to be careful which metaphor you choose, because it matters. If you choose the strings, then you’re imagining a world in which you can become irreparably broken. If you choose the grass, you’re saying that we are all infinitely interconnected, that we can use these root systems not only to understand one another but to become one another. The metaphors have implications. Do you know what I mean?" -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240691-in-the-end-i-had-to-call-myself-a-faggot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:57:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240691-in-the-end-i-had-to-call-myself-a-faggot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, I had to call myself a faggot, which really annoyed me, because 1. I don't think that word should ever be used by anyone, let alone me, and 2. As it happens, I am not gay, and furthermore, 3. Chuck Parson made it out like calling yourself a faggot was the ultimate humiliation, even though there's nothing at all embarrassing about being gay." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357892-all-along-not-only-since-she-left-but-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 22:58:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357892-all-along-not-only-since-she-left-but-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All along — not only since she left, but for a decade before — I had been imagining her without listening, without knowing that she made as a poor a window as I did. And so I could not imagine her as a person who could feel fear, who could feel isolated in a roomful of people, who could be shy about her record collection because it was too personal to share. Someone who might have read travel books to escape having to live in the town that so many people escape to. Someone who — because no one thought she was a person — had no one to really talk to." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10624-don-t-ever-tell-anybody-anything-if-you-do-you-start</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 23:06:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Crystal add a quote by J. D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10624-don-t-ever-tell-anybody-anything-if-you-do-you-start]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't ever tell anybody anything.  If you do, you start missing everybody." -- J. D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
