<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/924684-heather]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/924684-heather" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 15:17:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 15:17:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12379-i-believe-that-everything-happens-for-a-reason-people-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that everything happens for a reason. People change so that you can learn to let go, things go wrong so that you appreciate them when they're right, you believe lies so you eventually learn to trust no one but yourself, and sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 12:51:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150453-we-either-make-ourselves-miserable-or-we-make-ourselves-strong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We either make ourselves miserable, or we make ourselves strong. The amount of work is the same." -- Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2415-the-trick-is-in-what-one-emphasizes-we-either-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2014 12:52:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2415-the-trick-is-in-what-one-emphasizes-we-either-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trick is in what one emphasizes. We either make ourselves miserable, or we make ourselves happy. The amount of work is the same." -- Carlos Castaneda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79736-grief-can-destroy-you---or-focus-you-you-can-decide</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 07:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79736-grief-can-destroy-you---or-focus-you-you-can-decide]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grief can destroy you --or focus you. You can decide a relationship was all for nothing if it had to end in death, and you alone. OR you can realize that every moment of it had more meaning than you dared to recognize at the time, so much meaning it scared you, so you just lived, just took for granted the love and laughter of each day, and didn't allow yourself to consider the sacredness of it. But when it's over and you're alone, you begin to see that it wasn't just a movie and a dinner together, not just watching sunsets together, not just scrubbing a floor or washing dishes together or worrying over a high electric bill. It was everything, it was the why of life, every event and precious moment of it. The answer to the mystery of existence is the love you shared sometimes so imperfectly, and when the loss wakes you to the deeper beauty of it, to the sanctity of it, you can't get off your knees for a long time, you're driven to your knees not by the weight of the loss but by gratitude for what preceded the loss. And the ache is always there, but one day not the emptiness, because to nurture the emptiness, to take solace in it, is to disrespect the gift of life." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7849-the-only-way-out-of-the-labyrinth-of-suffering-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 11:34:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Heather add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7849-the-only-way-out-of-the-labyrinth-of-suffering-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way out of the labyrinth of suffering is to forgive." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
