<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/926781-glenda]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/926781-glenda" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 06:27:41 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2009 06:27:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23652-my-name-is-mary-katherine-blackwood-i-am-eighteen-years]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My name is Mary Katherine Blackwood. I am eighteen years old, and I live with my sister Constance. I have often thought that with any luck at all, I could have been born a werewolf, because the two middle fingers on both my hands are the same length, but I have had to be content with what I had. I dislike washing myself, and dogs, and noise. I like my sister Constance, and Richard Plantagenet, and Amanita phalloides, the death-cup mushroom. Everyone else in our family is dead." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184695-i-like-my-body-when-it-is-with-your-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 14:02:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by e.e. cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184695-i-like-my-body-when-it-is-with-your-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["i like my body when it is with your
body. It is so quite new a thing.
Muscles better and nerves more.
i like your body. i like what it does,
i like its hows. i like to feel the spine
of your body and its bones, and the trembling
-firm-smooth ness and which i will
again and again and again
kiss, i like kissing this and that of you,
i like, slowly stroking the, shocking fuzz
of your electric fur, and what-is-it comes
over parting flesh ... And eyes big love-crumbs,

and possibly i like the thrill

of under me you so quite new." -- e.e. cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598568-one-thing-you-who-had-secure-or-happy-childhoods-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 23:00:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Piers Anthony]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/598568-one-thing-you-who-had-secure-or-happy-childhoods-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing you who had secure or happy childhoods should understand about those of us who did not. We who control our feelings, who avoid conflicts at all costs, or seem to seek them. Who are hypersensitive, self-critical, compulsive, workaholic, and above all survivors. We are not that way from perversity, and we cannot just relax and let it go. We’ve learned to cope in ways you never had to." -- Piers Anthony]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529414-the-more-we-try-to-live-in-the-world-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 20:34:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Glenda add a quote by Alan Wilson Watts]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529414-the-more-we-try-to-live-in-the-world-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more we try to live in the world of words, the more we feel isolated and alone, the more all the joy and liveliness of things is exchanged for mere certainty and security. On the other hand, the more we are forced to admit that we actually live in the real world, the more we feel ignorant, uncertain, and insecure about everything." -- Alan Wilson Watts]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
