<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/927041-jen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/927041-jen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:35:06 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151643-bird-by-bird-buddy-just-take-it-bird-by-bird</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:35:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151643-bird-by-bird-buddy-just-take-it-bird-by-bird]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bird by bird, buddy. Just take it bird by bird." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53287-the-care-of-the-earth-is-our-most-ancient-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:37:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53287-the-care-of-the-earth-is-our-most-ancient-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The care of the Earth is our most ancient and most worthy, and after all our most pleasing responsibility. To cherish what remains of it and to foster its renewal is our only hope." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770717-assurance-you-will-never-be-alone-you-hear-so-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:55:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by William Stafford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/770717-assurance-you-will-never-be-alone-you-hear-so-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Assurance:
You will never be alone, you hear so deep a sound when autumn comes. Yellow
pulls across the hills and thrums, or in the silence after lightning before it says its names-and then the clouds' wide-mouthed apologies. You were aimed from birth: you will never be alone. Rain will come, a gutter filled, an Amazon, long aisles-you never heard so deep a sound, moss on rock, and years. You turn your head- that's what the silence meant: you're not alone. The whole wide world pours down." -- William Stafford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151644-the-lost-women-i-need-to-know-their-names-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:37:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Lucille Clifton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151644-the-lost-women-i-need-to-know-their-names-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the lost women

I need to know their names
those women I would have walked with,
jauntily the way men go in groups
swinging their arms, and the ones
those sweating women whom I would have joined
After a hard game to chew the fat
what would we have called each other laughing
joking into our beer? where are my gangs,
my teams, my mislaid sisters?
all the women who could have known me,
where in the world are their names?
" -- Lucille Clifton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60678-there-are-two-spiritual-dangers-in-not-owning-a-farm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:37:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Aldo Leopold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60678-there-are-two-spiritual-dangers-in-not-owning-a-farm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two spiritual dangers in not owning a farm. One is the danger of supposing that breakfast comes from the grocery, and the other that heat comes from the furnace." -- Aldo Leopold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109867-love-the-quick-profit-the-annual-raise-vacation-with-pay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love the quick profit, the annual raise,
vacation with pay. Want more
of everything ready-made. Be afraid
to know your neighbors and to die.

And you will have a window in your head.
Not even your future will be a mystery
any more. Your mind will be punched in a card
and shut away in a little drawer.

When they want you to buy something
they will call you. When they want you
to die for profit they will let you know.
So, friends, every day do something
that won’t compute. Love the Lord.
Love the world. Work for nothing.
Take all that you have and be poor.
Love someone who does not deserve it.

Denounce the government and embrace
the flag. Hope to live in that free
republic for which it stands.
Give your approval to all you cannot
understand. Praise ignorance, for what man
has not encountered he has not destroyed.

Ask the questions that have no answers.
Invest in the millenium. Plant sequoias.
Say that your main crop is the forest
that you did not plant,
that you will not live to harvest.

Say that the leaves are harvested
when they have rotted into the mold.
Call that profit. Prophesy such returns.
Put your faith in the two inches of humus
that will build under the trees
every thousand years.

Listen to carrion — put your ear
close, and hear the faint chattering
of the songs that are to come.
Expect the end of the world. Laugh.
Laughter is immeasurable. Be joyful
though you have considered all the facts.
So long as women do not go cheap
for power, please women more than men.

Ask yourself: Will this satisfy
a woman satisfied to bear a child?
Will this disturb the sleep
of a woman near to giving birth?

Go with your love to the fields.
Lie down in the shade. Rest your head
in her lap. Swear allegiance
to what is nighest your thoughts.

As soon as the generals and the politicos
can predict the motions of your mind,
lose it. Leave it as a sign
to mark the false trail, the way
you didn’t go.

Be like the fox
who makes more tracks than necessary,
some in the wrong direction.
Practice resurrection." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151645-nexus-i-wrote-stubbornly-into-the-evening-at-the-window</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:37:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Rita Dove]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151645-nexus-i-wrote-stubbornly-into-the-evening-at-the-window]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nexus

I wrote stubbornly into the evening.
At the window, a giant praying mantis
rubbed his monkey wrench head against the glass,
begging vacantly with pale eyes;

and the commas leapt at me like worms
or miniature scythes blackened with age.
the praying mantis screeched louder,
his ragged jaws opening into formlessness.

I walked outside;
the grass hissed at my heels.
Up ahead in the lapping darkness
he wobbled, magnified and absurdly green,
a brontosaurus, a poet." -- Rita Dove]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53288-a-community-is-the-mental-and-spiritual-condition-of-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 23:21:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53288-a-community-is-the-mental-and-spiritual-condition-of-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A community is the mental and spiritual condition of knowing that the place is shared, and that the people who share the place define and limit the possibilities of each other's lives. It is the knowledge that people have of each other, their concern for each other, their trust in each other, the freedom with which they come and go among themselves." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 23:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130070-you-have-been-given-questions-to-which-you-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been given questions to which you cannot be given answers. You will have to live them out - perhaps a little at a time.'
And how long is that going to take?'
I don't know. As long as you live, perhaps.'
That could be a long time.'
I will tell you a further mystery,' he said. 'It may take longer." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151646-no-settled-family-or-community-has-ever-called-its-home</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 23:24:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151646-no-settled-family-or-community-has-ever-called-its-home]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No settled family or community has ever called its home place an “environment.” None has ever called its feeling for its home place “biocentric” or “anthropocentric.” None has ever thought of its connection to its home place as “ecological,” deep or shallow. The concepts and insights of the ecologists are of great usefulness in our predicament, and we can hardly escape the need to speak of “ecology” and “ecosystems.” But the terms themselves are culturally sterile. They come from the juiceless, abstract intellectuality of the universities which was invented to disconnect, displace, and disembody the mind. The real names of the environment are the names of rivers and river valleys; creeks, ridges, and mountains; towns and cities; lakes, woodlands, lanes roads, creatures, and people.

And the real name of our connection to this everywhere different and differently named earth is “work.” We are connected by work even to the places where we don’t work, for all places are connected; it is clear by now that we cannot exempt one place from our ruin of another. The name of our proper connection to the earth is “good work,” for good work involves much giving of honor. It honors the source of its materials; it honors the place where it is done; it honors the art by which it is done; it honors the thing that it makes and the user of the made thing. Good work is always modestly scaled, for it cannot ignore either the nature of individual places or the differences between places, and it always involves a sort of religious humility, for not everything is known. Good work can be defined only in particularity, for it must be defined a little differently for every one of the places and every one of the workers on the earth.

The name of our present society’s connection to the earth is “bad work” – work that is only generally and crudely defined, that enacts a dependence that is ill understood, that enacts no affection and gives no honor. Every one of us is to some extent guilty of this bad work. This guilt does not mean that we must indulge in a lot of breast-beating and confession; it means only that there is much good work to be done by every one of us and that we must begin to do it." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2009 23:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44140-for-some-of-us-books-are-as-important-as-almost]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For some of us, books are as important as almost anything else on earth.  What a miracle it is that out of these small, flat, rigid squares of paper unfolds world after world after world, worlds that sing to you, comfort and quiet or excite you.  Books help us understand who we are and how we are to behave.  They show us what community and friendship mean; they show us how to live and die." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10523-there-are-some-who-can-live-without-wild-things-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:35:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Aldo Leopold]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10523-there-are-some-who-can-live-without-wild-things-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some who can live without wild things and some who cannot." -- Aldo Leopold]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 20:42:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jen add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
