<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/927696-cassie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/927696-cassie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 14:42:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23391-everyone-must-dream-we-dream-to-give-ourselves-hope-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 14:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cassie add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23391-everyone-must-dream-we-dream-to-give-ourselves-hope-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone must dream. We dream to give ourselves hope. To stop dreaming - well, that's like saying you can never change your fate. Isn't that true?" -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2009 15:39:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Cassie add a quote by Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156779-we-will-go-out-into-the-world-and-plant-gardens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We will go out into the world and plant gardens and orchards to the horizons, we will build roads through the mountains and across the deserts, and terrace the mountains and irrigate the deserts until there will be garden everywhere, and plenty for all, and there will be no more empires or kingdoms, no more caliphs, sultans, emirs, khans, or zamindars, no more kings or queens or princes, no more quadis or mullahs or ulema, no more slavery and no more usury, no more property and no more taxes, no more rich and no more poor, no killing or maiming or torture or execution, no more jailers and no more prisoners, no more generals, soldiers, armies or navies, no more patriarchy, no more caste, no more hunger, no more suffering than what life brings us for being born and having to die, and then we will see for the first time what kind of creatures we really are." -- Kim Stanley Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
