<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/928391-kris-wells]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/928391-kris-wells" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 11:22:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66093-in-all-of-living-have-much-fun-and-laughter-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 11:22:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66093-in-all-of-living-have-much-fun-and-laughter-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In all of living, have much fun and laughter.  Life is to be enjoyed, not just endured." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 07:42:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Sam Levenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15618-for-attractive-lips-speak-words-of-kindness-emsp-for-lovely-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For Attractive lips, speak words of kindness.
&amp;emsp;For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people.
&amp;emsp;For a slim figure, share your food with the hungry.
&amp;emsp;For beautiful hair, let a child run their fingers through it once a day.
&amp;emsp;For poise, walk with the knowledge that you never walk alone. 
&amp;emsp;People, more than things, have to be restored, renewed, revived, reclaimed, and redeemed. Remember, if you ever need a helping hand, you will find one at the end of each of your arms.
&amp;emsp;As you grow older, you will discover that you have two hands, one for helping yourself and the other for helping others." -- Sam Levenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164-it-is-one-of-the-blessings-of-old-friends-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 21:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164-it-is-one-of-the-blessings-of-old-friends-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is one of the blessings of old friends that you can afford to be stupid with them." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 21:03:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1388-a-ship-is-safe-in-harbor-but-that-s-not-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2010 21:04:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by William G.T. Shedd]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1388-a-ship-is-safe-in-harbor-but-that-s-not-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A ship is safe in harbor, but that's not what ships are for." -- William G.T. Shedd]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:47:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26665-i-don-t-want-to-drive-up-to-the-pearly-gates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to drive up to the pearly gates in a shiny sports car, wearing beautifully, tailored clothes, my hair expertly coiffed, and with long, perfectly manicured fingernails.
I want to drive up in a station wagon that has mud on the wheels from taking kids to scout camp.
I want to be there with a smudge of peanut butter on my shirt from making sandwiches for a sick neighbors children.
I want to be there with a little dirt under my fingernails from helping to weed someone's garden.
I want to be there with children's sticky kisses on my cheeks and the tears of a friend on my shoulder.
I want the Lord to know I was really here and that I really lived." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:48:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/92240-we-women-have-a-lot-to-learn-about-simplifying-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We women have a lot to learn about simplifying our lives.  We have to decide what is important and then move along at a pace that is comfortable for us.  We have to develop the maturity to stop trying to prove something.  We have to learn to be content with what we are." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309360-life-is-full-of-change-honey-that-s-how-we-learn</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 22:02:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Beth Hoffman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309360-life-is-full-of-change-honey-that-s-how-we-learn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is full of change, honey. That's how we learn and grow.  When we're born, the Good Lord gives each of us a Life Book.  Chapter by chapter, we live and learn... When a chapter of your Life Book is complete, your spirit knows it's time to turn the page so a new chapter can begin.  Even when you're scared or think you're not ready, your spirit knows you are." -- Beth Hoffman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 21:43:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who imagines that bliss is normal is going to waste a lot of time running around shouting that he has been robbed. The fact is that most putts don’t drop, most beef is tough, most children grow up to be just like people, most successful marriages require a high degree of mutual toleration, and most jobs are more often dull than otherwise. Life is just like an old time rail journey ... delays, sidetracks, smoke, dust, cinders, and jolts, interspersed only occasionally by beautiful vistas and thrilling bursts of speed. The trick is to thank the Lord for letting you have the ride." -- Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2011 19:53:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13641-imagine-yourself-as-a-living-house-god-comes-in-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine yourself as a living house. God comes in to rebuild that house. At first, perhaps, you can understand what He is doing. He is getting the drains right and stopping the leaks in the roof and so on; you knew that those jobs needed doing and so you are not surprised. But presently He starts knocking the house about in a way that hurts abominably and does not seem to make any sense. What on earth is He up to? The explanation is that He is building quite a different house from the one you thought of - throwing out a new wing here, putting on an extra floor there, running up towers, making courtyards. You thought you were being made into a decent little cottage: but He is building a palace. He intends to come and live in it Himself." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70022-if-for-a-while-the-harder-you-try-the-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 21:55:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70022-if-for-a-while-the-harder-you-try-the-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If for a while the harder you try, the harder it gets, take heart. So it has been with the best people who ever lived. (The Inconvenient Messiah, BYU Speeches, Feb 15, 1982)" -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354763-don-t-you-quit-you-keep-walking-you-keep-trying-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 21:56:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kris add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354763-don-t-you-quit-you-keep-walking-you-keep-trying-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you quit. You keep walking, you keep trying, there is help and happiness ahead. Some blessings come soon. Some come late. Some don't come until heaven. But for those who embrace the gospel of Jesus Christ, they come. It will be alright in the end. Trust God and believe in Good Things to Come." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
