<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/928782-bill-reilly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/928782-bill-reilly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:19:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 09:19:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5504-once-you-have-tasted-flight-you-will-forever-walk-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once you have tasted flight, you will forever walk the earth with your eyes turned skyward, for there you have been, and there you will always long to return." -- Leonardo da Vinci]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710998-the-man-who-has-faith-in-logic-is-always-cuckolded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 09:23:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Alexander Theroux]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/710998-the-man-who-has-faith-in-logic-is-always-cuckolded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who has faith in logic is always cuckolded by reality." -- Alexander Theroux]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417755-spirituality-is-recognizing-and-celebrating-that-we-are-all-inextricably</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2014 14:04:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Brené Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417755-spirituality-is-recognizing-and-celebrating-that-we-are-all-inextricably]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Spirituality is recognizing and celebrating that we are all inextricably connected to each other by a power greater than all of us, and that our connection to that power and to one another is grounded in love and compassion. Practicing spirituality brings a sense of perspective, meaning and purpose to our lives." -- Brené Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333558-you-are-beautiful-like-demolition-just-the-thought-of-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 15:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bill add a quote by Henry Rollins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333558-you-are-beautiful-like-demolition-just-the-thought-of-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are beautiful like demolition. Just the thought of you draws my knuckles white. I don’t need a god. I have you and your beautiful mouth, your hands holding onto me, the nails leaving unfelt wounds, your hot breath on my neck. The taste of your saliva. The darkness is ours. The nights belong to us. Everything we do is secret. Nothing we do will ever be understood; we will be feared and kept well away from. It will be the stuff of legend, endless discussion and limitless inspiration for the brave of heart. It’s you and me in this room, on this floor. Beyond life, beyond morality. We are gleaming animals painted in moonlit sweat glow. Our eyes turn to jewels and everything we do is an example of spontaneous perfection. I have been waiting all my life to be with you. My heart slams against my ribs when I think of the slaughtered nights I spent all over the world waiting to feel your touch. The time I annihilated while I waited like a man doing a life sentence. Now you’re here and everything we touch explodes, bursts into bloom or burns to ash. History atomizes and negates itself with our every shared breath. I need you like life needs life. I want you bad like a natural disaster. You are all I see. You are the only one I want to know." -- Henry Rollins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
