<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930270-luciana-d-andretta]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930270-luciana-d-andretta" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:07:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:07:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3355-at-times-you-have-to-leave-the-city-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:08:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Alan Alda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3355-at-times-you-have-to-leave-the-city-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At times you have to leave the city of your comfort and go into the wilderness of your intuition. What you'll discover will be wonderful. What you'll discover is yourself." -- Alan Alda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:10:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20852-baseball-is-like-church-many-attend-few-understand</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:13:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Leo Durocher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20852-baseball-is-like-church-many-attend-few-understand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Baseball is like church. Many attend, few understand." -- Leo Durocher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24366-ray-people-will-come-ray-they-ll-come-to-iowa-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:14:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Phil Robinson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24366-ray-people-will-come-ray-they-ll-come-to-iowa-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ray, people will come Ray. They'll come to Iowa for reasons they can't even fathom. They'll turn up your driveway not knowing for sure why they're doing it. They'll arrive at your door as innocent as children, longing for the past. Of course, we won't mind if you look around, you'll say. It's only $20 per person. They'll pass over the money without even thinking about it: for it is money they have and peace they lack. And they'll walk out to the bleachers; sit in shirtsleeves on a perfect afternoon. They'll find they have reserved seats somewhere along one of the baselines, where they sat when they were children and cheered their heroes. And they'll watch the game and it'll be as if they dipped themselves in magic waters. The memories will be so thick they'll have to brush them away from their faces. People will come Ray. The one constant through all the years, Ray, has been baseball. America has rolled by like an army of steamrollers. It has been erased like a blackboard, rebuilt and erased again. But baseball has marked the time. This field, this game: it's a part of our past, Ray. It reminds of us of all that once was good and it could be again. Oh.. people will come Ray. People will most definitely come." -- Phil Robinson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16425-next-to-music-beer-was-best</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:14:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Carson McCullers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16425-next-to-music-beer-was-best]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next to music, beer was best." -- Carson McCullers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 07:16:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49348-all-of-us-i-suspect-imagine-that-a-world-exists</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2008 14:01:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by James Atlas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49348-all-of-us-i-suspect-imagine-that-a-world-exists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of us, I suspect, imagine that a world exists from which we alone have been excluded; all of us have our noses pressed against the glass. But if we contemplate our own lives, not the phantom life on the other side, we might find things in them to envy-a family that’s intact; a job we like; excellent health (the thing we take for granted and on which all happiness depends). Good fortune is there, however sporadic, however modest, however difficult to achieve. The trick is to recognize it." -- James Atlas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 07:46:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Luciana add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
