<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930246-tombom-p]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930246-tombom-p" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 09:38:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245858-an-ugliness-unfurled-in-the-moonlight-and-soft-shadow-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 09:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by Yukio Mishima]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/245858-an-ugliness-unfurled-in-the-moonlight-and-soft-shadow-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An ugliness unfurled in the moonlight and soft shadow and suffused the whole world. If I were an amoeba, he thought, with an infinitesimal body, I could defeat ugliness. A man isn’t tiny or giant enough to defeat anything." -- Yukio Mishima]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 14:54:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2476-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-and-to-morrow-creeps-in-this-petty-pace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To-morrow, and to-morrow, and to-morrow,
Creeps in this petty pace from day to day,
To the last syllable of recorded time;
And all our yesterdays have lighted fools
The way to dusty death. Out, out, brief candle!
Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player,
That struts and frets his hour upon the stage,
And then is heard no more. It is a tale
Told by an idiot, full of sound and fury,
Signifying nothing." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435090-it-is-practically-a-matter-of-life-or-death-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 17:54:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by Lordess Demonica]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/435090-it-is-practically-a-matter-of-life-or-death-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is practically a matter of life or death for a True Cock Worshiper to taste pre-cum." -- Lordess Demonica]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179193-the-intense-horror-of-nightmare-came-over-me-i-tried</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 09:14:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179193-the-intense-horror-of-nightmare-came-over-me-i-tried]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The intense horror of nightmare came over me: I tried to draw back my arm, but the hand clung to it, and a most melancholy voice sobbed, 'Let me in - let me in!' 'Who are you?' I asked, struggling, meanwhile, to disengage myself. 'Catherine Linton,' it replied, shiveringly (why did I think of LINTON? I had read EARNSHAW twenty times for Linton) - 'I'm come home: I'd lost my way on the moor!' As it spoke, I discerned, obscurely, a child's face looking through the window." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882952-to-be-kaspar-hauser-is-to-long-at-every-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 09:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by Steven Millhauser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882952-to-be-kaspar-hauser-is-to-long-at-every-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be Kaspar Hauser is to long, at every moment of your dubious existence, with every fiber of your questionable being, not to be Kaspar Hauser. It’s to long to leave yourself completely behind, to vanish from your own sight. Does this surprise you? It is of course what you have taught me to desire. And I am a diligent student. With your help I have furnished myself inside and out. My thoughts are yours. These words are yours. Even my black and bitter tears are yours, for I shed them at the thought of the life I never had, which is to say, your life, ladies and gentlemen of Nuremberg. My deepest wish is not to be an exception. My deepest wish is not to be a curiosity, an object of wonder. It is to be unremarkable. To become you—to sink into you—to merge with you until you cannot tell me from yourselves; to be uninteresting; to be nothing at all; to experience the ecstasy of mediocrity—is it so much to ask? You who have helped me to advance so far, won’t you lead me to the promised land, the tranquil land of the ordinary, the banal, the boring? Not to be Kaspar Hauser, not to be the enigma of Europe, not to be the wild boy in the tower, the man without a childhood, the young man without a youth, the monster born in the middle of his life, but to be you, to be you, to be nothing but you! This is my vision of paradise. And although the very existence of such a vision reveals nothing so much as my distance, which widens into an abyss even as I try to fling myself across, still I am not without hope." -- Steven Millhauser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674709-the-problem-with-quotes-on-the-internet-is-you-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 16:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tombom add a quote by Joseph Stalin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/674709-the-problem-with-quotes-on-the-internet-is-you-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem with quotes on the internet is you never know if they are genuine." -- Joseph Stalin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
