<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930385-kristi-dixon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930385-kristi-dixon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 10:03:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95118-next-day-tarrou-set-to-work-and-enrolled-a-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 10:03:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95118-next-day-tarrou-set-to-work-and-enrolled-a-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next day Tarrou set to work and enrolled a first team of workers, soon to be followed by many others.
However, it is not the narrator's intention to ascribe to these sanitary groups more importance than their due.  Doubtless today many of our fellow citizens are apt to yield to the temptation of exaggerating the services they rendered.  But the narrator is inclined to think that by attributing overimportance to praiseworthy actions one may, by implication, be paying indirect but potent homage to the worse side of human nature.  For this attitude implies that such actions shine out as rare exceptions, while callousness and apathy are the general rule.
The narrator does not share that view.   The evil that is in the world always comes of ignorance, and good intentions may do as much harm as malevolence, if they lack understanding. On the whole, men are more good than bad; that, however, isn't the real point. But they are more or less ignorant, and it is this that we call vice or virtue; the most incorrigible vice being that of an ignorance that fancies it knows everything and therefore claims for itself the right to kill." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393651-i-do-not-consider-myself-less-ignorant-than-most-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 18:41:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristi add a quote by Herman Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/393651-i-do-not-consider-myself-less-ignorant-than-most-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not consider myself less ignorant than most people. I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books. I have begun to listen to the teachings my blood whispers to me. My story is not a pleasant one; it is neither sweet nor harmonious, as invented stories are; it has the taste of nonsense and chaos, of madness and dreams -- like the lives of all men who stop deceiving themselves." -- Herman Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
