<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930349-catherine]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930349-catherine" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:32:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30809-a-face-that-has-the-marks-of-having-lived-intensely</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:32:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Doris Ulmann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30809-a-face-that-has-the-marks-of-having-lived-intensely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A face that has the marks of having lived intensely, that expresses some phase of life, some dominant quality or intellectual power, constitutes for me an interesting face.  For this reason the face of an older person, perhaps not beautiful in the strictest sense, is usually more appealing than the face of a younger person who has scarcely been touched by life." -- Doris Ulmann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 04:37:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50162-living-in-a-constant-chase-after-gain-compels-people-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50162-living-in-a-constant-chase-after-gain-compels-people-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Living in a constant chase after gain compels people to expend their spirit to the point of exhaustion in continual pretense and overreaching and anticipating other.  Virtue has come to consist of doing something in less time that someone else.  Hours in which honesty is permitted have become rare, and when they arrive one is tired and does not only want to &quot;let oneself go&quot; but actually wishes to stretch out as long and wide and ungainly as one happens to be...  Soon we may well reach the point where people can no longer give in to the desire for a vita contemplativa (that is, taking a walk with ideas and friends) without self-contempt and a bad conscience." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165398-there-s-good-self-consciousness-and-then-there-s-toxic-paralyzing-raped-by-psychic-bedouins-self-</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 13:35:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/165398-there-s-good-self-consciousness-and-then-there-s-toxic-paralyzing-raped-by-psychic-bedouins-self-]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's good self-consciousness, and then there's toxic, paralyzing, raped-by-psychic-Bedouins self-consciousness." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807-the-place-to-improve-the-world-is-first-in-one-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2013 06:15:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/807-the-place-to-improve-the-world-is-first-in-one-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The place to improve the world is first in one's own heart and head and hands, and then work outward from there." -- Robert M. Pirsig]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233422-the-belief-that-unhappiness-is-selfless-and-happiness-is-selfish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 00:40:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Catherine add a quote by Gretchen Rubin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233422-the-belief-that-unhappiness-is-selfless-and-happiness-is-selfish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The belief that unhappiness is selfless and happiness is selfish is misguided.  It's more selfless to act happy.  It takes energy, generosity, and discipline to be unfailingly lighthearted, yet everyone takes the happy person for granted.  No one is careful of his feelings or tries to keep his spirits high. He seems self-sufficient; he becomes a cushion for others.  And because happiness seems unforced, that person usually gets no credit." -- Gretchen Rubin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
