<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930514-kenneth-goldman]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930514-kenneth-goldman" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 09:43:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260732-pinky-lumbers-caught-fire-quicker-than-steak-on-a-barbecue</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2010 09:43:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/260732-pinky-lumbers-caught-fire-quicker-than-steak-on-a-barbecue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pinky Lumbers caught fire quicker than steak on a barbecue.  He heaved and squirmed tryin' to scream,  but his mouth was too crammed with bed sheet, so instead he just gagged.  But his struggles didn't last long,  and Honey and me,  we just stood there and watched his flesh fold over on itself stinking like bad pork . . ." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 16:21:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8287-i-have-not-failed-i-ve-just-found-10-000-ways-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." -- Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757531-a-kiss-is-such-an-amazing-thing----so-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 20:49:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757531-a-kiss-is-such-an-amazing-thing----so-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A kiss is such an amazing thing -- So simple, so complex.  The only human act that gives while it receives. Mouth to mouth, it almost seems the eating of one another. Maybe that’s all we are, food for each other. Why, I believe there’s a poem in there somewhere. Another kiss to inspire my muse, Desirée, and I’ll tell you something else you don’t know." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757533-from-the-short-story-and-anthology-containing-it-donny-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 20:52:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757533-from-the-short-story-and-anthology-containing-it-donny-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the short story (and anthology containing it)  DONNY DOESN'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE :

Donny acted like he didn’t hear me. “You can’t send your mom off into eternity looking like that, Artie. She wouldn’t like it.” He reached into my mother’s casket, shoved his fingers into her mouth like it was the most logical thing in the world.
 “Donny, you can’t --!”
 “I’m just making her look right, Artie. It’s what she would want.” He tugged hard at my mom’s lips. I knew they were cold because I had kissed them a few moments earlier, and for a moment I felt convinced my friend had completely lost his mind. But when I looked inside Mom’s casket I knew Donny had done something only a best friend would think to do. My mother was smiling again. And she looked just the way I remembered her, the way I would always want to remember her. I got so choked up I couldn’t talk for a few minutes.
  Finally I managed, “My mother always told me you could make her smile." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757539-from-lady-in-waiting-in-the-anthology-the-morgue</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 20:59:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757539-from-lady-in-waiting-in-the-anthology-the-morgue]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From &quot;Lady In Waiting&quot;  in the anthology The Morgue :

Now I have yet to meet the corpse could hold up its end of a conversation, so at most I might whistle while fixin’ one up ‘stead of engagin’ myself in any small talk that’s goin’ to be so one-sided anyways. But Cindy Flowers’ corpse weren’t no ordinary body when it walked upright, and it sure weren’t ordinary just because it was lyin’ before me in a pine wood box. So for the first time I felt the need to get a few things said to one of our visitors, and I leaned down to get myself real close to her face. Her eyes was closed ‘cause Pa had already sewed her lids shut." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757542-from-lunchtime-at-the-justice-cafe-the-waitress-snarled</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2013 21:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/757542-from-lunchtime-at-the-justice-cafe-the-waitress-snarled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From &quot;Lunchtime At The Justice Cafe&quot; :

The waitress snarled a grin that lasted just long enough to show a mouthful of stained yellowed teeth, then turned suddenly serious. “‘Course I’m not the one to talk about these folks, I ‘spose. You see, I used to do a bit of eavesdroppin’ in my day before the sheriff put a stop to that.”    She lifted the stringy blond hair from the side of her face, the opposite side from where she had hidden her pencil. There was a small hole about the size of a quarter where her ear should have been. “As you can see, Mr. McAllister, Sheriff Sweet puts a fairly high price on mindin’ your own business in Justice,”  she added, refilling his cup. “You want some pie?”  " -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948370-you-can-t-blame-yourself-for-what-socrates-did-those-birds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 05:58:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948370-you-can-t-blame-yourself-for-what-socrates-did-those-birds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can’t blame yourself for what Socrates did. Those birds came because he wanted them to come, at least a part of him did. The pissed off part. Let that roll around in your brain for a while.”
Jamie considered this.  “No, Eddie. The hurt part, that’s what did it.”
The crow shrieked again. It seemed louder, and that meant it was closer. Or maybe it was another crow, maybe several. Jamie and Eddie looked toward the sky, listening to the screams.  Jamie spoke first.
“We can’t let it happen again. We may be the only ones who know the truth about what Socrates can do.”
 “That thought probably has occurred to Socrates too." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948376-socrates-is-flying-no-he-is-soaring-the-wings-behind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 06:23:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kenneth add a quote by Ken Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/948376-socrates-is-flying-no-he-is-soaring-the-wings-behind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socrates is flying. No, he is soaring. The wings behind him beat in a calming rhythm while the cool air rushes past. His wings are all that matter, snapping at the rushing wind like the sails of some great sea vessel, the feathery appendages all he is and all he will ever want to be.
His back muscles flex with the effort that takes him high above the ground. He  feels the effort, of course, but sweeping into the sky does not require much of one. The sensation is pleasurable, even exhilarating.  With flight there is freedom beyond description, an ecstasy bordering on sexual.
He has only one destination, and that is to soar higher, to no longer be a prisoner of the earth. Here destinations seem irrelevant, the world below small. Flying exceeds every pleasure he knows. In the immense forever of  blue sky, all that matters is flight and his ability to climb higher.
Up and up and up..." -- Ken Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
