<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930886-bridget]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/930886-bridget" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:18:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339538-she-soon-says-you-re-my-best-friend-ed-you-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:18:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/339538-she-soon-says-you-re-my-best-friend-ed-you-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She soon says, &quot;You're my best friend, Ed.&quot;
You can kill a man with those words.
No gun.
No bullets.
Just words and a girl." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168019-sometimes-you-read-a-book-so-special-that-you-want</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:20:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168019-sometimes-you-read-a-book-so-special-that-you-want]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you read a book so special that you want to carry it around with you for months after you've finished just to stay near it." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125106-elmore-leonard-s-ten-rules-of-writing-1-never-open-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:21:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Elmore Leonard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125106-elmore-leonard-s-ten-rules-of-writing-1-never-open-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elmore Leonard's Ten Rules of Writing

1. Never open a book with weather.
2.  Avoid prologues.
3. Never use a verb other than &quot;said&quot; to carry dialogue.
4. Never use an adverb to modify the verb &quot;said”…he admonished gravely.
5. Keep your exclamation points under control. You are allowed no more than two or three per 100,000 words of prose. 
6. Never use the words &quot;suddenly&quot; or &quot;all hell broke loose.&quot;
7. Use regional dialect, patois, sparingly.
8. Avoid detailed descriptions of characters.
9. Don't go into great detail describing places and things.
10. Try to leave out the part that readers tend to skip.

My most important rule is one that sums up the 10.

If it sounds like writing, I rewrite it." -- Elmore Leonard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317472-do-we-spend-most-of-our-days-trying-to-remember</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:22:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317472-do-we-spend-most-of-our-days-trying-to-remember]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do we spend most of our days trying to remember or to forget? Do we spend most of our time running towards or away from our lives?" -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235101-see-cameron-the-only-things-i-care-about-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:23:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/235101-see-cameron-the-only-things-i-care-about-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["See, Cameron. The only things I care about in this life are me, you, Mum, Dad, Steve and Sarah. And maybe Miffy. The rest of the world means nothing to me. The rest of the world can rot.'
Am I like that too?'
You? No way.' There's a slight gap in his words. 'And that's your problem. You care about everything.'
He's right.
I do." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555094-i-m-gonna-hunt-my-life-down-and-grab-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:23:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Markus Zusak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/555094-i-m-gonna-hunt-my-life-down-and-grab-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm gonna hunt my life down and grab it." -- Markus Zusak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249679-listen-god-love-everything-you-love---and-a-mess</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:26:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249679-listen-god-love-everything-you-love---and-a-mess]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen, God love everything you love - and a mess of stuff you don't. But more than anything else, God love admiration.

You saying God vain? I ast.

Naw, she say. Not vain, just wanting to share a good thing. I think it pisses God off if you walk by the color purple in a field somewhere and don't notice it.

What it do when it pissed off? I ast.

Oh, it make something else. People think pleasing God is all God care about. But any fool living in the world can see it always trying to please us back." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533567-here-s-the-thing-say-shug-the-thing-i-believe-god</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 07:28:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Bridget add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/533567-here-s-the-thing-say-shug-the-thing-i-believe-god]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's the thing, say Shug. The thing I believe. God is inside you and inside everybody else. You come into the world with God. But only them that search for it inside find it. And sometimes it just manifest itself even if you not looking, or don't know what you looking for. Trouble do it for most folks, I think. Sorrow, lord. Feeling like shit.

It? I ast.

Yeah, It. God ain't a he or a she, but a It.

But what do it look like? I ast.

Don't look like nothing, she say. It ain't a picture show. It ain't something you can look at apart from anything else, including yourself. I believe God is everything, say Shug. Everything that is or ever was or ever will be. And when you can feel that, and be happy to feel that, you've found It.

Shug a beautiful something, let me tell you. She frown a little, look out cross the yard, lean back in her chair, look like a big rose. She say, My first step from the old white man was trees. Then air. Then birds. Then other people. But one day when I was sitting quiet and feeling like a motherless child, which I was, it come to me: that feeling of being part of everything, not separate
at all. I knew that if I cut a tree, my arm would bleed. And I laughed and I cried and I run all around the house. I knew just what it was. In fact, when it happen, you can't miss it. It sort of like you know what, she say, grinning and rubbing high up on my thigh.

Shug! I say.

Oh, she say. God love all them feelings. That's some of the best stuff God did. And when you know God loves 'em you enjoys 'em a lot more. You can just relax, go with everything that's going, and praise God by liking what you like.

God don't think it dirty? I ast.

Naw, she say. God made it. Listen, God love everything you love? and a mess of stuff you don't. But more than anything else, God love admiration.

You saying God vain? I ast.

Naw, she say. Not vain, just wanting to share a good thing. I think it pisses God off if you walk by the color purple in a field somewhere and don't notice it.

What it do when it pissed off? I ast.

Oh, it make something else. People think pleasing God is all God care about. But any fool living in the world can see it always trying to please us back.

Yeah? I say.

Yeah, she say. It always making little surprises and springing them on us when us least expect.

You mean it want to be loved, just like the bible say.

Yes, Celie, she say. Everything want to be loved. Us sing and dance, make faces and give flower bouquets, trying to be loved. You ever notice that trees do everything to git attention we do, except walk?

Well, us talk and talk bout God, but I'm still adrift. Trying to chase that old white man out of my head. I been so busy thinking bout him I never truly notice nothing God make. Not a blade of corn (how it do that?) not the color purple (where it come from?). Not the little wildflowers. Nothing. Now that my eyes opening, I feels like a fool. Next to any little scrub of a bush in my yard, Mr. ____s evil sort of shrink. But not altogether. Still, it is like Shug say, You have to git man off your eyeball, before you can see anything a'tall.

Man corrupt everything, say Shug. He on your box of grits, in your head, and all over the radio. He try to make you think he everywhere.

Soon as you think he everywhere, you think he God. But he ain't. Whenever you trying to pray, and man plop himself on the other end of it, tell him to git lost, say Shug. Conjure up flowers, wind,water, a big rock.

But this hard work, let me tell you. He been there so long, he don't want to budge. He threaten lightening, floods and earthquakes. Us fight. I hardly pray at all. Every time I conjure up a rock, I throw it.

Amen" -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
