<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931082-arminius]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931082-arminius" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 07:28:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41951-da-mihi-castitatem-et-continentiam-sed-noli-modo-give-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 07:28:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41951-da-mihi-castitatem-et-continentiam-sed-noli-modo-give-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Da mihi castitatem et continentiam, sed noli modo (Give me chastity and continence, but not just yet)!" -- Augustine of Hippo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923-always-do-what-is-right-it-will-gratify-half-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2008 18:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/923-always-do-what-is-right-it-will-gratify-half-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always do what is right. It will gratify half of mankind and astound the other." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109873-a-well-adjusted-person-is-one-who-makes-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 07:33:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Alexander Hamilton ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109873-a-well-adjusted-person-is-one-who-makes-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A well adjusted person is one who makes the same mistake twice without getting nervous." -- Alexander Hamilton ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5842-it-is-better-to-be-alone-than-in-bad-company</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:01:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by George Washington]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5842-it-is-better-to-be-alone-than-in-bad-company]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is better to be alone than in bad company." -- George Washington]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109878-a-slender-acquaintance-with-the-world-must-convince-every-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by George Washington ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109878-a-slender-acquaintance-with-the-world-must-convince-every-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A slender acquaintance with the world must convince every man that actions, not words, are the true criterion of the attachment of friends." -- George Washington ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109879-most-men-seem-to-live-according-to-sense-rather-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:06:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Saint Thomas Aquinas ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109879-most-men-seem-to-live-according-to-sense-rather-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men seem to live according to sense rather than reason." -- Saint Thomas Aquinas ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109884-a-crown-is-merely-a-hat-that-lets-the-rain</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:15:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Frederick The Great ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109884-a-crown-is-merely-a-hat-that-lets-the-rain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A crown is merely a hat that lets the rain in." -- Frederick The Great ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109889-if-russians-knew-how-to-read-they-would-write-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:24:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Catherine The Great]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109889-if-russians-knew-how-to-read-they-would-write-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Russians knew how to read  they would write me off. " -- Catherine The Great]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109890-they-say-great-themes-make-great-novels-but-what-these</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2008 08:26:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by John O'Hara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/109890-they-say-great-themes-make-great-novels-but-what-these]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say great themes make great novels.. but what these young writers don't understand is that there is no greater theme than men and women." -- John O'Hara]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172553-it-takes-a-good-man-to-prevent-a-catastrophe-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2009 09:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Richelieu Three Musketeers By Duma]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172553-it-takes-a-good-man-to-prevent-a-catastrophe-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a good man to prevent a catastrophe, and a great man to make use of one." -- Richelieu Three Musketeers By Duma]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2010 17:50:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Garrison Keillor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5979-anyone-who-thinks-sitting-in-church-can-make-you-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who thinks sitting in church can make you a Christian must also think that sitting in a garage can make you a car." -- Garrison Keillor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20795-the-poor-go-to-war-to-fight-and-die-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 16:03:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Plutarch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20795-the-poor-go-to-war-to-fight-and-die-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The poor go to war, to fight and die for the delights, riches, and superfluities of others." -- Plutarch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2256-all-truth-passes-through-three-stages-first-it-is-ridiculed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 18:15:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2256-all-truth-passes-through-three-stages-first-it-is-ridiculed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All truth passes through three stages: First, it is ridiculed; Second, it is violently opposed; Third, it is accepted as self-evident." -- Arthur Schopenhauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166244-you-think-man-can-destroy-the-planet-what-intoxicating-vanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:57:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Michael Crichton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166244-you-think-man-can-destroy-the-planet-what-intoxicating-vanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think man can destroy the planet? What intoxicating vanity. Let me tell you about our planet. Earth is four-and-a-half-billion-years-old. There's been life on it for nearly that long, 3.8 billion years. Bacteria first; later the first multicellular life, then the first complex creatures in the sea, on the land. Then finally the great sweeping ages of animals, the amphibians, the dinosaurs, at last the mammals, each one enduring millions on millions of years, great dynasties of creatures rising, flourishing, dying away -- all this against a background of continuous and violent upheaval. Mountain ranges thrust up, eroded away, cometary impacts, volcano eruptions, oceans rising and falling, whole continents moving, an endless, constant, violent change, colliding, buckling to make mountains over millions of years. Earth has survived everything in its time. It will certainly survive us. If all the nuclear weapons in the world went off at once and all the plants, all the animals died and the earth was sizzling hot for a hundred thousand years, life would survive, somewhere: under the soil, frozen in Arctic ice. Sooner or later, when the planet was no longer inhospitable, life would spread again. The evolutionary process would begin again. It might take a few billion years for life to regain its present variety. Of course, it would be very different from what it is now, but the earth would survive our folly, only we would not. If the ozone layer gets thinner, ultraviolet radiation sears the earth, so what? Ultraviolet radiation is good for life. It's powerful energy. It promotes mutation, change. Many forms of life will thrive with more UV radiation. Many others will die out. Do you think this is the first time that's happened? Think about oxygen. Necessary for life now, but oxygen is actually a metabolic poison, a corrosive glass, like fluorine. When oxygen was first produced as a waste product by certain plant cells some three billion years ago, it created a crisis for all other life on earth. Those plants were polluting the environment, exhaling a lethal gas. Earth eventually had an atmosphere incompatible with life. Nevertheless, life on earth took care of itself. In the thinking of the human being a hundred years is a long time. A hundred years ago we didn't have cars, airplanes, computers or vaccines. It was a whole different world, but to the earth, a hundred years is nothing. A million years is nothing. This planet lives and breathes on a much vaster scale. We can't imagine its slow and powerful rhythms, and we haven't got the humility to try. We've been residents here for the blink of an eye. If we're gone tomorrow, the earth will not miss us." -- Michael Crichton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188569-if-you-don-t-know-history-then-you-don-t-know-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2013 10:59:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Arminius add a quote by Michael Crichton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188569-if-you-don-t-know-history-then-you-don-t-know-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't know history, then you don't know anything. You are a leaf that doesn't know it is part of a tree. " -- Michael Crichton]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
