<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931648-ellen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931648-ellen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 22:01:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167829-you-can-t-own-a-human-being-you-can-t-lose-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 22:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167829-you-can-t-own-a-human-being-you-can-t-lose-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't own a human being. You can't lose what you don't own. Suppose you did own him. Could you really love somebody who was absolutely nobody without you? You really want somebody like that? Somebody who falls apart when you walk out the door? You don't, do you? And neither does he. You're turning over your whole life to him. Your whole life, girl. And if it means so little to you that you can just give it away, hand it to him, then why should it mean any more to him? He can't value you more than you value yourself." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53456-the-art-of-losing-isn-t-hard-to-master-so-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 22:09:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Elizabeth Bishop]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53456-the-art-of-losing-isn-t-hard-to-master-so-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The art of losing isn't hard to master;
so many things seem filled with the intent
to be lost that their loss is no disaster.

Lose something every day.  Accept the fluster
of lost door keys, the hour badly spent.
The art of losing isn't hard to master.

Then practice losing farther, losing faster:
places, and names, and where it was you meant
to travel.  None of these will bring disaster.

I lost my mother's watch.  And look! my last, or
next-to-last, of three loved houses went.
The art of losing isn't hard to master.

I lost two cities, lovely ones.  And, vaster,
some realms I owned, two rivers, a continent.
I miss them, but it wasn't a disaster.

---Even losing you (the joking voice, a gesture
I love) I shan't have lied.  It's evident
the art of losing's not too hard to master
though it may look like (Write it!) like disaster." -- Elizabeth Bishop]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123271-the-middle-path-makes-me-wary-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 03:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Terry Tempest Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123271-the-middle-path-makes-me-wary-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The middle path makes me wary. . . . But in the middle of my life, I am coming to see the middle path as a walk with wisdom where conversations of complexity can be found, that the middle path is the path of movement. . . . In the right and left worlds, the stories are largely set. . . . We become missionaries for a position . . . practitioners of the missionary position. Variety is lost. Diversity is lost. Creativity is lost in our inability to make love with the world." -- Terry Tempest Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640120-the-eyes-of-the-future-are-looking-back-at-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 03:07:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Terry Tempest Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/640120-the-eyes-of-the-future-are-looking-back-at-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The eyes of the future are looking back at us and they are praying for us to see beyond our own time. They are kneeling with hands clasped that we might act with restraint, that we might leave room for the life that is destined to come. To protect what is wild is to protect what is gentle. Perhaps the wilderness we fear is the pause between our own heartbeats, the silent space that says we live only by grace. Wilderness lives by this same grace. Wild mercy is in our hands." -- Terry Tempest Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 15:10:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ellen add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24015-you-do-not-have-to-be-good-you-do-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You do not have to be good.
You do not have to walk on your knees
for a hundred miles through the desert, repenting.
You only have to let the soft animal of your body 
love what it loves.
Tell me about despair, yours, and I will tell you mine.
Meanwhile the world goes on.
Meanwhile the sun and the clear pebbles of the rain
are moving across the landscapes,
over the prairies and the deep trees,
the mountains and the rivers.
Meanwhile the wild geese, high in the clean blue air,
are heading home again.
Whoever you are, no matter how lonely,
the world offers itself to your imagination,
calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting –
over and over announcing your place
in the family of things." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
