<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931848-angela]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/931848-angela" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 13:42:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151627-jessica-for-god-s-sake-he-said-allow-me-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 13:42:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Beth Fantaskey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151627-jessica-for-god-s-sake-he-said-allow-me-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jessica. For god's sake,&quot; he said. &quot;Allow me to do at least one common courtesy for you. In spite ow what 'women's lib' teaches you, chivalry does not imply that women are powerless. On the contrary, chivalry is an admission of women's superiority. An acknowledgment of &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; power over &lt;i&gt;us&lt;/i&gt;. This is the only form of servitude a Vladescu ever practices, and I perform it gladly for you. You, in turn, are obligated to accept graciously." -- Beth Fantaskey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38462-there-is-nothing-better-than-a-friend-unless-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2009 10:58:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Linda Grayson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38462-there-is-nothing-better-than-a-friend-unless-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing better than a friend, unless it is a friend with chocolate." -- Linda Grayson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 16:23:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5169-what-really-knocks-me-out-is-a-book-that-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What really knocks me out is a book that, when you're all done reading it, you wish the author that wrote it was a terrific friend of yours and you could call him up on the phone whenever you felt like it. That doesn't happen much, though." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 16:24:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2010 16:24:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2467-you-can-never-get-a-cup-of-tea-large-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never get a cup of tea large enough or a book long enough to suit me." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24054-a-nice-girl-should-never-go-anywhere-without-a-loaded</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 17:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24054-a-nice-girl-should-never-go-anywhere-without-a-loaded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A nice girl should never go anywhere without a loaded gun and a big knife.&quot; ~ Sarah Agnes Prine" -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96405-i-might-like-to-have-someone-courting-me-but-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 18:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96405-i-might-like-to-have-someone-courting-me-but-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I might like to have someone courting me. But it would have to be someone who is a square shooter and who has a train load of courage. And it would have to be someone who doesn't have to talk down to folks to feel good, or to tell a person they are worthless ifthey just made a mistake. And he'd have to be not too thin. Why, I remember hugging [my brother] Ernest was like warpping your arms around a fence post,and I love Ernest, but I want a man who can hold me down in a wind. Maybe he'd have to be pretty stubborn. I don't have any use for a man that isn't stubborn. Likely a stubborn fellow will stay with you through thick and thin, and a spineless one will take off, or let his heart wander." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36088-and-he-likes-to-torment-me-and-laughs-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 18:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36088-and-he-likes-to-torment-me-and-laughs-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And he likes to torment me, and laughs when I get upset when he does. No, of course not. I do not love Jack Elliot. He is low and coarse and a soldier, and not the kind of man I want to spend my life with." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175384-i-said-well-looks-like-he-s-pretty-ornery-i-wonder</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 18:02:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175384-i-said-well-looks-like-he-s-pretty-ornery-i-wonder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said, Well, looks like he's pretty ornery.  I wonder where he gets it?

&quot;Jack just shrugged and kissed my cheek, and then whispered in my ear, He gets it from his mother." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159562-we-begin-to-notice-besides-our-particular-sinful-act-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 07:21:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by CS Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159562-we-begin-to-notice-besides-our-particular-sinful-act-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["we begin to notice  besides our particular sinful act, our sinfulness; begin to be alarmed not only about what we do, but about what we are.  This may sound rather difficult, so I will try to make it clear from my own case.  When I come to my evening prayers and try to reckon up the sins of the day, nine times out of ten the most obvious one is some sin against charity; I have sulked or snapped or sneered or snubbed or stormed. And the excuse that immediately springs to my mind is that the provocation was so sudden and unexpected; I was caught off my guard, I had not time to collect myself.  Now that may be an extenuating circumstance as regards those particular acts: they would obviously be worse if they had been deliberate and premeditated.  On the other hand, surely what a man does when he is taken off his guard is the best evidence for what sort of a man he is?  Surely what pops out before the man has time to put on a disguise is the truth? If there are rats in the cellar you are most likely to see them if you go in very suddenly.  But the suddenness does not creat the rats: it only prevents them from hiding.  In the same way the suddenness of the provocation does not make me an ill-tempered man; it only shows me what an ill-tempered man I am.  The rats are always there in the cellar, but if you go in shouting and noisily they will have taken cover before you switch on the light.  " -- CS Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391678-taking-up-marriage-is-a-good-excuse-for-taking-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 02:57:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angela add a quote by Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/391678-taking-up-marriage-is-a-good-excuse-for-taking-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Taking up marriage is a good excuse for taking up cursing, I think." -- Nancy E. Turner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
