<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/93234-kimberly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/93234-kimberly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:23:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:23:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In each of us lie good and bad, light and dark, art and pain, choice and regret, cruelty and sacrifice. We’re each of us our own chiaroscuro, our own bit of illusion fighting to emerge into something solid, something real. We’ve got to forgive ourselves that. I must remember to forgive myself. Because there is a lot of grey to work with. No one can live in the light all the time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2286-you-can-never-really-know-someone-completely-that-s-why-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2286-you-can-never-really-know-someone-completely-that-s-why-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can never really know someone completely. That’s why it’s the most terrifying thing in the world, really—taking someone on faith, hoping they’ll take you on faith too. It’s such a precarious balance, It’s a wonder we do it at all. And yet.." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51058-it-doesn-t-have-to-be-on-valentine-s-day-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:29:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by David Levithan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51058-it-doesn-t-have-to-be-on-valentine-s-day-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't have to be on Valentine's Day.  It doesn't have to be by the time you turn eighteen or thirty-three or fifty-nine.  It doesn't have to conform to whatever is usual.  It doesn't have to be kismet at once, or rhapsody by the third date.
It just has to be.  In time.  In place.  In spirit.
It just has to be." -- David Levithan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60254-there-s-no-such-thing-as-ready-she-says-there-s-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 12:30:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60254-there-s-no-such-thing-as-ready-she-says-there-s-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s no such thing as ready,” she says. “There’s only willing." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26438-there-are-no-safe-choices-only-other-choices</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 16:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26438-there-are-no-safe-choices-only-other-choices]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no safe choices. Only other choices." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149213-but-forgiveness-i-ll-hold-on-to-that-fragile-slice-of-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 16:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149213-but-forgiveness-i-ll-hold-on-to-that-fragile-slice-of-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But forgiveness...I'll hold on to that fragile slice of hope and keep it close, remembering that in each of us lie good and bad, light and dark, art and pain, choice and regret, cruelty and sacrifice. We're each of us our own chiaroscuro, our own bit of illusion fighting to emerge into something solid, something real. We've got to forgive ourselves that. I must remember to forgive myself. Because there's an awful lot of gray to work with. No one can live in the light all the time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116825-i-hope-that-one-day-you-will-have-the-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 16:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116825-i-hope-that-one-day-you-will-have-the-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope that one day you will have the experience of doing something you do not understand for someone you love." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 16:44:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84711-in-bed-that-night-i-invented-a-special-drain-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 16:48:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kimberly add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84711-in-bed-that-night-i-invented-a-special-drain-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In bed that night I invented a special drain that would be underneath every pillow in New York, and would connect to the reservoir. Whenever people cried themselves to sleep, the tears would all go to the same place, and in the morning the weatherman could report if the water level of the Reservoir of Tears had gone up or down, and you could know if New York is in heavy boots." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
