<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/934470-danielle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/934470-danielle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:03:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41972-no-reason-to-mention-my-peculiarities-my-wandering-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:03:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by jeffrey eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41972-no-reason-to-mention-my-peculiarities-my-wandering-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["no reason to mention my peculiarities, my wandering in the maze these many years, shut away from sight. and from love, too." -- jeffrey eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16175-something-is-wrong-here-sex-has-been-with-us-since</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:19:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Xaviera Hollander]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16175-something-is-wrong-here-sex-has-been-with-us-since]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Something is wrong here: sex has been with us since the human race began its existence, yet I would estimate that 90 percent of human beings still suffer enormous inhibitions in this area." -- Xaviera Hollander]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16174-in-the-symphony-of-love-the-lost-chord-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:21:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Ruth Herschberger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16174-in-the-symphony-of-love-the-lost-chord-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the symphony of love, the lost chord is a small organ lying somewhat north of the vagina." -- Ruth Herschberger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16134-the-first-two-facts-which-a-healthy-boy-or-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16134-the-first-two-facts-which-a-healthy-boy-or-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first two facts which a healthy boy or girl feels about sex are these: first that it is beautiful and then that it is dangerous." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22202-america-does-not-know-the-difference-between-money-and-sex</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:23:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Peter Kreeft]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22202-america-does-not-know-the-difference-between-money-and-sex]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America does not know the difference between money and sex. It treats sex like money because it treats sex as a medium of exchange, and it treats money like sex because it expects its money to get pregnant and reproduce." -- Peter Kreeft]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16182-one-thing-i-ve-learned-in-all-these-years-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:23:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Norman Mailer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16182-one-thing-i-ve-learned-in-all-these-years-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One thing I've learned in all these years is not to make love when you really don't feel it; there's probably nothing worse you can do to yourself than that." -- Norman Mailer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16192-my-mom-says-do-you-know-what-the-aids-memorial</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:30:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16192-my-mom-says-do-you-know-what-the-aids-memorial]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mom says, &quot;Do you know what the AIDS memorial quilt is all about?&quot;
Jump to how much I hate my brother at this moment.
I bought this fabric because I thought it would make a nice panel for Shane,&quot; Mom says. &quot;We just ran into some problems with what to sew on it.&quot;
Give me amnesia.
Flash.
Give me new parents.
Flash.
Your mother didn't want to step on any toes,&quot; Dad says. He twists a drumstick off and starts scraping the meat onto a plate. &quot;With gay stuff you have to be so careful since everything means something in secret code. I mean, we didn't want to give people the wrong idea.&quot;
My Mom leans over to scoop yams onto my plate, and says, &quot;Your father wanted a black border, but black on a field of blue would mean Shane was excited by leather sex, you know, bondage and discipline, sado and masochism.&quot; She says, &quot;Really, those panels are to help the people left behind.&quot;
Strangers are going to see us and see Shane's name,&quot; my dad says. &quot;We didn't want them thinking things.&quot;
The dishes all start their slow clockwise march around the table. The stuffing. The olives. The cranberry sauce. &quot;I wanted pink triangles but all the panels have pink triangles,&quot; my mom says. &quot;It's the Nazi symbol for homosexuals.&quot; She says,&quot;Your father suggested black triangles, but that would mean Shane was a lesbian. It looks like female pubic hair. The black triangle does.&quot;
My father says, &quot;Then I wanted a green border, but it turns out that would mean Shane was a male prostitute.&quot;
My mom says, &quot;We almost chose a red border, but that would mean fisting.  Brown would mean either scat or rimming, we couldn't figure which.&quot;
Yellow,&quot; my father says, &quot;means watersports.&quot;
A lighter shade of blue,&quot; Mom says, &quot;would mean just regular oral sex.&quot;
Regular white,&quot; my father says, &quot;would mean anal. White could also mean Shane was excited by men wearing underwear.&quot;  He says, &quot;I can't remember which.&quot;
My mother passes me the quilted chicken with the rolls still warm inside.
We're supposed to sit and eat with Shane dead all over the table in front of us.
Finally we just gave up,&quot; my mom says, &quot;and I made a nice tablecloth out of the material.&quot;
Between the yams and the stuffing, Dad looks down at his plate and says, &quot;Do you know about rimming?&quot;
I know it isn't table talk.
And fisting?&quot; my mom asks.
I say, I know. I don't mention Manus and his vocational porno magazines.
We sit there, all of us around a blue shroud with the turkey more like a big dead baked animal than ever, the stuffing chock full of organs you can still recognize, the heart and gizzard and liver, the gravy thick with cooked fat and blood. The flower centerpiece could be a casket spray.
Would you pass the butter, please?&quot; my mother says. To my father she says, &quot;Do you know what felching is?" -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 05:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26620-we-waste-time-looking-for-the-perfect-lover-instead-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We waste time looking for the perfect lover, instead of creating the perfect love." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16184-young-people-are-moving-away-from-feeling-guilty-about-sleeping</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:33:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Margaret Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16184-young-people-are-moving-away-from-feeling-guilty-about-sleeping]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Young people are moving away from feeling guilty about sleeping with somebody to feeling guilty if they are *not* sleeping with someone." -- Margaret Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16204-anyone-who-calls-it-sexual-intercourse-can-t-possibly-be-interested</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:33:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Allan Sherman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16204-anyone-who-calls-it-sexual-intercourse-can-t-possibly-be-interested]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who calls it &quot;sexual intercourse&quot; can't possibly be interested in actually doing it. You might as well announce you're ready for lunch by proclaiming, &quot;I'd like to do some masticating and enzyme secreting." -- Allan Sherman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2475-she-wore-her-sexuality-with-an-older-woman-s-ease-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by zadie smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2475-she-wore-her-sexuality-with-an-older-woman-s-ease-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She wore her sexuality with an older woman's ease, and not like an awkward purse, never knowing how to hold it, where to hang it, or when to just put it down." -- zadie smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9477-a-man-can-sleep-around-no-questions-asked-but-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Joan Rivers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9477-a-man-can-sleep-around-no-questions-asked-but-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man can sleep around, no questions asked, but if a woman makes nineteen or twenty mistakes she's a tramp." -- Joan Rivers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16188-someone-told-me-the-delightful-story-of-the-crusader-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:36:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16188-someone-told-me-the-delightful-story-of-the-crusader-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone told me the delightful story of the crusader who put a chastity belt on his wife and gave the key to his best friend for safekeeping, in case of his death. He had ridden only a few miles away when his friend, riding hard, caught up with him, saying 'You gave me the wrong key!" -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16208-sex-is-an-emotion-in-motion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16208-sex-is-an-emotion-in-motion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sex is an emotion in motion." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8496-don-t-wreck-a-sublime-chocolate-experience-by-feeling-guilty-chocolate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Lora Brody]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8496-don-t-wreck-a-sublime-chocolate-experience-by-feeling-guilty-chocolate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't wreck a sublime chocolate experience by feeling guilty.
Chocolate isn't like premarital sex. It will not make you pregnant.
And it always feels good." -- Lora Brody]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:39:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3058-to-love-at-all-is-to-be-vulnerable-love-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love at all is to be vulnerable. Love anything and your heart will be wrung and possibly broken. If you want to make sure of keeping it intact you must give it to no one, not even an animal. Wrap it carefully round with hobbies and little luxuries; avoid all entanglements. Lock it up safe in the casket or coffin of your selfishness. But in that casket, safe, dark, motionless, airless, it will change. It will not be broken; it will become unbreakable, impenetrable, irredeemable. To love is to be vulnerable." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2008 21:39:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3616-i-am-nothing-special-of-this-i-am-sure-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am nothing special, of this I am sure. I am a common man with common thoughts and I've led a common life. There are no monuments dedicated to me and my name will soon be forgotten, but I've loved another with all my heart and soul, and to me, this has always been enough.." -- Nicholas Sparks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
