<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/935006-danielle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/935006-danielle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 16:08:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73185-what-did-it-feel-like-i-wondered-to-love-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 16:08:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73185-what-did-it-feel-like-i-wondered-to-love-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What did it feel like, I wondered, to love someone that much? So much that you couldn't even control yourself when they came close, as if you might just break free of whatever was holding you and throw yourself at them with enough force to easily overwhelm you both." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 16:14:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, I don’t know how the world broke. And I don’t know if there’s a God who can help us fix it. But the fact that the world is broken - I absolutely believe that. Just look around us. Every minute - every single second - there are a million things you could be thinking about. A million things you could be worrying about. Our world - don’t you just feel we’re becoming more fragmented? I used to think that when I got older, the world would make so much more sense. But you know what? The older I get, the more confusing it is to me. The more complicated it is. Harder. You’d think we’d be getting better at it. But there’s just more and more chaos. The pieces - they’re everywhere. And nobody knows what to do about it. I find myself grasping, Nick. You know that feeling? That feeling when you just want the right thing to fall into the right place, not only because it’s right, but because it would mean that such a thing is still possible? I want to believe that." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 09:42:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23342-it-s-dark-now-and-i-am-very-tired-i-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s dark now and I am very tired. I love you, always. Time is nothing." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20650-she-was-wearing-a-pair-of-my-pajamas-with-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2009 18:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20650-she-was-wearing-a-pair-of-my-pajamas-with-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was wearing a pair of my pajamas with the sleeves rolled up. When she laughed I wanted her again. A minute later she asked me if I loved her. I told her it didn't mean anything but that I didn't think so. She looked sad. But as we were fixing lunch, and for no apparent reason, she laughed in such a way that I kissed her." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32545-albert-camus-wrote-that-the-only-serious-question-is-whether</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2009 14:17:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32545-albert-camus-wrote-that-the-only-serious-question-is-whether]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Albert Camus wrote that the only serious question is whether to kill yourself or not.
Tom Robbins wrote that the only serious question is whether time has a beginning and an end.
Camus clearly got up on the wrong side of bed, and Robbins must have forgotten to set the alarm.
There is only one serious question. And that is: Who knows how to make love stay?
Answer me that and I will tell you whether or not to kill yourself." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2009 18:32:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Danielle add a quote by Jay Asher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6453-you-don-t-know-what-goes-on-in-anyone-s-life-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t know what goes on in anyone’s life but your own. And when you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re not messing with just that part. Unfortunately, you can’t be that precise and selective. When you mess with one part of a person’s life, you’re messing with their entire life. Everything. . . affects everything." -- Jay Asher]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
