<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/936046-jessica]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/936046-jessica" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 10:55:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181830-elizabeth-and-darcy-merely-looked-at-one-another-in-awkward</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 10:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Seth Grahame-Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/181830-elizabeth-and-darcy-merely-looked-at-one-another-in-awkward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Elizabeth and
Darcy merely looked at one another in awkward silence, until the latter reached both arms around
her. She was frozen-&quot;What does he mean to do?&quot; she thought. But his intentions were
respectable, for Darcy merely meant to retrieve his Brown Bess, which Elizabeth had affixed to
her back during her walk. She remembered the lead ammunition in her pocket and offered it to
him. &quot;Your balls, Mr. Darcy?&quot; He reached out and closed her hand around them, and offered,
&quot;They belong to you, Miss Bennet.&quot; Upon this, their colour changed, and they were forced to look
away from one another, lest they laugh." -- Seth Grahame-Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57713-a-pious-man-explained-to-his-followers-it-is-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2009 10:55:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57713-a-pious-man-explained-to-his-followers-it-is-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A pious man explained to his followers: 'It is evil to take lives and noble to save them.  Each day I pledge to save a hundred lives.  I drop my net in the lake and scoop out a hundred fishes.  I place the fishes on the bank, where they flop and twirl. &quot;Don't be scared,&quot; I tell those fishes.  &quot;I am saving you from drowning.&quot;  Soon enough, the fishes grow calm and lie still.  Yet, sad to say, I am always too late.  The fishes expire.  And because it is evil to waste anything, I take those dead fishes to market and I sell them for a good price.  With the money I receive, I buy more nets so I can save more fishes." -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 20:51:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/769-books-are-the-quietest-and-most-constant-of-friends-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the quietest and most constant of friends; they are the most accessible and wisest of counselors, and the most patient of teachers." -- Charles W. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 20:52:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6856-if-one-cannot-enjoy-reading-a-book-over-and-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one cannot enjoy reading a book over and over again, there is no use in reading it at all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361745-i-promise-you-nothing-is-as-chaotic-as-it-seems</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 12:31:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361745-i-promise-you-nothing-is-as-chaotic-as-it-seems]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I promise you nothing is as chaotic as it seems. Nothing is worth diminishing your health. Nothing is worth poisoning yourself into stress, anxiety, and fear." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7730-reality-is-the-leading-cause-of-stress-amongst-those-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 12:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Jane Wagner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7730-reality-is-the-leading-cause-of-stress-amongst-those-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is the leading cause of stress amongst those in touch with it." -- Jane Wagner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130390-old-marley-was-as-dead-as-a-doornail-mind-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2013 11:10:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jessica add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130390-old-marley-was-as-dead-as-a-doornail-mind-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Old Marley was as dead as a doornail.

Mind!  I don't mean to say that, of my own knowledge, what there is particularly dead about a doornail.  I might have been inclined, myself, to regard a coffin-nail as the deadest piece of ironmongery in the trade.  But the wisdom of our ancestors is in the simile; and my unhallowed hands shall not disturb it, or the Country's done for.  You will therefore permit me to repeat, emphatically, that Marley was as dead as a doornail." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
