<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/936648-marina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/936648-marina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 09:47:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64517-that-i-discovered-the-deed-that-intends-me-that-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 09:47:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by Martin Buber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64517-that-i-discovered-the-deed-that-intends-me-that-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That I discovered the deed that intends me, that, this movement of my freedom, reveals the mystery to me. But this, too, that I cannot accomplish it the way I intended it, this resistance also reveals the mystery to me. He that forgets all being caused as he decides from the depths, he that puts aside possessions and cloak and steps bare before the countenance--this free human being encounters fate as the counter-image of his freedom. It is not his limit but his completion; freedom and fate embrace each other to form meaning; and given meaning, fate--with its eyes, hitherto severe, suddenly full of light--looks like grace itself." -- Martin Buber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64522-this-is-it-i-think-this-is-it-right-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 10:09:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64522-this-is-it-i-think-this-is-it-right-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is it, I think, this is it, right now, the present, this empty gas station, here, this western wind, this tang of coffee on the tongue, and I am petting the puppy, I am watching the mountain. And the second I verbalize this awareness in my brain, I cease to see the mountain or feel the puppy. I am opaque, so much black asphalt. But at the same second, the second I know I've lost it, I also realize that the puppy is still squirming on his back under my hand. Nothing has changed for him. He draws his legs down to stretch the skin taut so he feels every fingertip's stroke along his furred and arching side, his flank, his flung-back throat.
     I sip my coffee. I look at the mountain, which is still doing its tricks, as you look at a still-beautiful face belonging to a person who was once your lover in another country years ago: with fond nostalgia, and recognition, but no real feeling save a secret astonishment that you are now strangers. Thanks. For the memories. It is ironic that the one thing that all religions recognize as separating us from our creator--our very self-consciousness--is also the one thing that divides us from our fellow creatures. It was a bitter birthday present from evolution, cutting us off at both ends. I get in the car and drive home." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65088-this-was-the-last-time-i-ever-saw-my-mother</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2008 05:00:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65088-this-was-the-last-time-i-ever-saw-my-mother]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This was the last time I ever saw my mother alive. Just the same, this picture gets all mixed up in my mind with pictures I had of her when she was younger. The way I always see her is the way she used to be on Sunday afternoon, say, when the old folks were talking after the big Sunday dinner. I always see her wearing pale blue. She'd be sitting on the sofa. And my father would be sitting in the easy chair, not far from her. And the living room would be full of church folks and relatives. There they sit, in chairs all around the living room, and the night is creeping up outside, but nobody knows it yet. You can see the darkness growing against the windowpanes and you hear the street noises every now and again, or maybe the jangling beat of a tambourine from one of the churches close by, but it's real quiet in the room. For a moment nobody's talking, but every face looks darkening, like the sky outside. And my mother rocks a little from the waist, and my father's eyes are closed. Everyone is looking at something a child can't see. For a minute they've forgotten the children. Maybe a kid is lying on the rug, half asleep. Maybe somebody's got a kid in his lap and is absent-mindedly stroking the kid's head. Maybe there's a kid, quiet and big-eyed, curled up in a big chair in the corner. The silence, the darkness coming, and the darkness in the faces frighten the child obscurely. He hopes that the hand which strokes his forehead will never stop-- will never die. He hopes that there will never come a time when the old folks won't be sitting around the living room, talking about where they've come from, and what they've seen, and what's happened to them and their kinfolk.

But something deep and watchful in the child knows that this is bound to end, is already ending. In a moment someone will get up and turn on the light. Then the old folks will remember the children and they won't talk anymore that day. And when light fills the room, the child is filled with darkness. He knows that every time this happens he's moved just a little closer to that darkness outside. The darkness outside is what the old folks have been talking about. It's what they've come from. It's what they endure. The child knows that they won't talk anymore because if he knows too much about what's happened to them, he'll know too much too soon, about what's going to happen to him." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633090-i-looked-out-the-window-and-saw-the-street-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 11:52:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by Kevin Powers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633090-i-looked-out-the-window-and-saw-the-street-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I looked out the window and saw the street and railroad tracks, the woods beyond. Beyond the woods, the county of which they were a part. And so on, until it all dissolved into the larger thing: my mother's house becoming every other house as I once had seen it, sitting atop the southern end of a broad river valley, close enough to the the mountains that every few years a scared black bear would wander down into the remaining forest, and close enough to the ocean that those early English settlers took it as the farthest point they'd go upstream, the geology of the place preventing them from having any choice other than the one wherein they said, &quot;We are lost; therefore we will call this home.&quot; And close enough that as a child I had been teased by older kids who said if I only tried hard enough I would smell salt water, and I, believing, stood among the light poles and the gulls in the parking lots of A&amp;Ps and cried when I knew that it was true despite the fact that they had meant to lie, as children sometimes do." -- Kevin Powers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633092-i-could-tell-from-anna-s-face-that-she-had-already</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 11:54:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by Colum McCann]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/633092-i-could-tell-from-anna-s-face-that-she-had-already]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I could tell from Anna's face that she had already told him about dancing in Saint Petersburg and that the memory weighed on her heavily. What monstrous things, our pasts, especially when they have been lovely. She had told a secret and now had the sadness of wondering how much deeper she might dig in order to keep the first secret fed." -- Colum McCann]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630961-you-don-t-owe-prettiness-to-anyone-not-to-your-boyfriend-spouse-partner</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 11:55:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marina add a quote by Erin McKean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/630961-you-don-t-owe-prettiness-to-anyone-not-to-your-boyfriend-spouse-partner]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You don’t owe prettiness to anyone. Not to your boyfriend/spouse/partner, not to your co-workers, especially not to random men on the street. You don’t owe it to your mother, you don’t owe it to your children, you don’t owe it to civilization in general. Prettiness is not a rent you pay for occupying a space marked ‘female’." -- Erin McKean]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
