<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/937394-rachel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/937394-rachel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:22 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308389-a-mother-s-body-remembers-her-babies--the-folds-of-soft-flesh</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308389-a-mother-s-body-remembers-her-babies--the-folds-of-soft-flesh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A mother's body remembers her babies--the folds of soft flesh, the softly furred scalp against her nose. Each child has its own entreaties to body and soul. It's the last one, though, that overtakes you. I can't dare say I loved the others less, but my first three were all babies at once, and motherhood dismayed me entirely. . . . That's how it is with the firstborn, no matter what kind of mother you are--rich, poor, frazzled half to death or sweetly content. A first child is your own best food forward, and how you do cheer those little feet as they strike out. You examine every turn of flesh for precocity, and crow it to the world. 

But the last one: the baby who trails her scent like a flag of surrender through your life when there will be no more coming after--oh, that's love by a different name. She is the babe you hold in your arms for an hour after she's gone to sleep. If you put her down in the crib, she might wake up changed and fly away. So instead you rock by the window, drinking the light from her skin, breathing her exhaled dreams. Your heart bays to the double crescent moons of closed lashes on her cheeks. She's the one you can't put down." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84130-god-warns-us-not-to-love-any-earthly-thing-above</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84130-god-warns-us-not-to-love-any-earthly-thing-above]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God warns us not to love any earthly thing above Himself, and yet He sets in a mother's heart such a fierce passion for her babes that I do not comprehend how He can test us so." -- Geraldine Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121271-here-in-my-heart-my-happiness-my-house-here-inside</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121271-here-in-my-heart-my-happiness-my-house-here-inside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here in my heart, my happiness, my house.
Here inside the lighted window is my love, my hope, my life.
Peace is my companion on the pathway winding to the threshold.
Inside this portal dwells new strength in the security, serenity, and radiance of those I love above life itself.
Here two will build new dreams--dreams that tomorrow will come true.
The world over, these are the thoughts at eventide when footsteps turn ever homeward.
In the haven of the hearthside is rest and peace and comfort." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195861-the-function-of-the-british-army-in-the-novels-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Salmon Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195861-the-function-of-the-british-army-in-the-novels-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The function of the British army in the novels of Jane Austen is to look cute at parties." -- Salmon Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308266-for-six-years-from-age-nineteen-until-i-turned-twenty-five</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:13:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308266-for-six-years-from-age-nineteen-until-i-turned-twenty-five]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For six years, from age nineteen until I turned twenty-five, I did not sleep uninterrupted through a single night. . . . I felt lucky to get my shoes on the right feet. . . . I moved forward only, thinking each morning anew that we were leaving the worst behind." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54052-i-entirely-agree-that-a-historian-ought-to-be-precise</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:13:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54052-i-entirely-agree-that-a-historian-ought-to-be-precise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I entirely agree that a historian ought to be precise in detail; but unless you take all the characters and circumstances into account, you are reckoning without the facts. The proportions and relations of things are just as much facts as the things themselves." -- Dorothy L. Sayers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17901-anyone-who-imagines-that-bliss-is-normal-is-going-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyone who imagines that bliss is normal is going to waste a lot of time running around shouting that he has been robbed. The fact is that most putts don’t drop, most beef is tough, most children grow up to be just like people, most successful marriages require a high degree of mutual toleration, and most jobs are more often dull than otherwise. Life is just like an old time rail journey ... delays, sidetracks, smoke, dust, cinders, and jolts, interspersed only occasionally by beautiful vistas and thrilling bursts of speed. The trick is to thank the Lord for letting you have the ride." -- Jenkin Lloyd Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54053-today-mr-darcy-is-a-vampire</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54053-today-mr-darcy-is-a-vampire]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today, Mr. Darcy is a vampire." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168246-in-the-long-run-our-most-deeply-held-desires-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 23:10:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Bruce C. Hafen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/168246-in-the-long-run-our-most-deeply-held-desires-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the long run, our most deeply held desires will govern our choices, one by one and day by day, until our lives finally add up to what we have really wanted most--for good or otherwise. We can indeed have eternal life, if we really want it, so long as we don't want something else more." -- Bruce C. Hafen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194729-for-those-of-us-who-suspect-all-the-mysteries-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 21:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194729-for-those-of-us-who-suspect-all-the-mysteries-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those of us who suspect all the mysteries of life are contained in the microcosm of the family, that personal relationships prefigure all else, the work of Jane Austen is the Rosetta stone of literature." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194979-there-are-some-writers-who-wrote-too-much-there-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 21:19:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Margaret Drabble]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194979-there-are-some-writers-who-wrote-too-much-there-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are some writers who wrote too much. There are others who wrote enough. There are yet others who wrote nothing like enough to satisfy their admirers, and Jane Austen is certainly one of these." -- Margaret Drabble]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195862-jane-austen-i-feel-that-i-am-approaching-dangerous-ground</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 20:24:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Arnold Bennett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195862-jane-austen-i-feel-that-i-am-approaching-dangerous-ground]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane Austen? I feel that I am approaching dangerous ground. The reputation of Jane Austen is surrounded by cohorts of defenders who are ready to do murder for their sacred cause." -- Arnold Bennett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195863-there-would-be-more-genuine-rejoicing-at-the-discovery-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:36:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Margaret Drabble]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195863-there-would-be-more-genuine-rejoicing-at-the-discovery-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There would be more genuine rejoicing at the discovery of a complete new novel by Jane Austen than any other literary discovery, short of a new major play by Shakespeare." -- Margaret Drabble]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308402-some-mothers-are-kissing-mothers-and-some-are-scolding-mothers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2010 09:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/308402-some-mothers-are-kissing-mothers-and-some-are-scolding-mothers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some mothers are kissing mothers and some are scolding mothers, but it is love just the same, and most mothers kiss and scold together" -- Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352261-my-dogs-can-t-do-anything--and-what-a-relief-i-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:04:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Amy Chua]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352261-my-dogs-can-t-do-anything--and-what-a-relief-i-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My dogs can't do anything--and what a relief. I don't make any demands of them, and I don't try to shape them or their future. For the most part, I trust them to make the right choices for themselves. I always look forward to seeing them, and I love just watching them sleep. What a great relationship." -- Amy Chua]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352265-one-unexpected-bonus-of-motherhood-is-the-visual-beauty-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:11:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jaroldeen Edwards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352265-one-unexpected-bonus-of-motherhood-is-the-visual-beauty-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One unexpected bonus of motherhood is the visual beauty. I am enchanted by the sights of my children, the tones of skin, the clear eyes, the grace, the curve of a hand and cheek, to see them racing across the back lawn in a certain slant of light." -- Jaroldeen Edwards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352266-the-glories-of-a-new-baby-are-beyond-description</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 22:12:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Jaroldeen Edwards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352266-the-glories-of-a-new-baby-are-beyond-description]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The glories of a new baby are beyond description." -- Jaroldeen Edwards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383238-i-think-that-love-is-more-like-a-light-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 14:10:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/383238-i-think-that-love-is-more-like-a-light-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think that love is more like a light that you carry. At first childish happiness keeps it lighted and after that romance. Then motherhood lights it and then duty . . . and maybe after that sorrow. You wouldn't think that sorrow could be a light, would you, dearie? But it can. And then after that, service lights it. Yes. . . . I think that is what love is to a woman . . . a lantern in her hand." -- Bess Streeter Aldrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517910-everything-in-all-the-books-i-once-pored-over-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 23:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/517910-everything-in-all-the-books-i-once-pored-over-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything in all the books I once pored over is finished for me now. Penelope Leach. T. Berry Brazelton. Dr. Spock. The ones on sibling rivalry and sleeping through the night and early-childhood education, all grown obsolete. Along with ‘Goodnight Moon’ and ‘Where the Wild Things Are,’ they are battered, spotted, well used. But I suspect that if you flipped the pages dust would rise like memories. . . . The biggest mistake I made is the one that most of us make. . . .I did not live in the moment enough. This is particularly clear now that the moment is gone, captured only in photographs. There is one picture of the three of [my children] sitting in the grass on a quilt in the shadow of the swing set on a summer day, ages 6, 4, and 1. And I wish I could remember what we ate, and what we talked about, and how they sounded, and how they looked when they slept that night. I wish I had not been in such a hurry to get on to the next thing: dinner, bath, book bed. I wish I had treasured the doing a little more and the getting it done a little less." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558536-in-the-tapestry-of-childhood-what-stands-out-is-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 21:02:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Kim John Payne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558536-in-the-tapestry-of-childhood-what-stands-out-is-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the tapestry of childhood, what stands out is not the splashy, blow-out trips to Disneyland but the common threads that run throughout and repeat: the family dinners, nature walks, reading together at bedtime, Saturday morning pancakes." -- Kim John Payne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294864-we-all-want-to-do-something-to-mitigate-the-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 21:33:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/294864-we-all-want-to-do-something-to-mitigate-the-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We all want to do something to mitigate the pain of loss or to turn grief into something positive, to find a silver lining in the clouds. But I believe there is real value in just standing there, being still, being sad." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51220-you-know-it-s-not-the-world-that-was-my-oppressor</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 10:05:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51220-you-know-it-s-not-the-world-that-was-my-oppressor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, it's not the world that was my oppressor, because what the world does to you, if the world does it to you long enough and effectively enough, you begin to do to yourself." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133515-when-spring-came-even-the-false-spring-there-were-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 22:27:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rachel add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133515-when-spring-came-even-the-false-spring-there-were-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When spring came, even the false spring, there were no problems except where to be happiest.  The only thing that could spoil a day was people and if you could keep from making engagements, each day had no limits.  People were always the limiters of happiness except for the very few that were as good as spring itself." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
