<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/938148-ruchi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/938148-ruchi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 01:17:45 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 01:17:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2209-the-question-isn-t-who-is-going-to-let-me-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question isn't who is going to let me; it's who is going to stop me." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28598-oh-what-a-tangled-web-we-weave-when-first-we-practice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2012 01:17:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Walter Scott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28598-oh-what-a-tangled-web-we-weave-when-first-we-practice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, what a tangled web we weave...when first we practice to deceive." -- Walter Scott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5826-my-dear-i-don-t-give-a-damn</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:39:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5826-my-dear-i-don-t-give-a-damn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My dear, I don't give a damn." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 09:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2491-i-ll-think-of-it-tomorrow-at-tara-i-can-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'll think of it tomorrow, at Tara. I can stand it then. Tomorrow, I'll think of some way to get him back. After all, tomorrow is another day." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81605-after-all-tomorrow-is-another-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 10:56:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81605-after-all-tomorrow-is-another-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After all, tomorrow is another day!" -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 10:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328189-i-will-love-you-as-a-thief-loves-a-gallery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will love you as a thief loves a gallery and as a crow loves a murder, as a cloud loves bats and as a range loves braes. I will love you as misfortune loves orphans, as fire loves innocence and as justice loves to sit and watch while everything goes wrong. I will love you as a battlefield loves young men and as peppermints love your allergies, and I will love you as the banana peel loves the shoe of a man who was just struck by a shingle falling off a house. I will love you as a volunteer fire department loves rushing into burning buildings and as burning buildings love to chase them back out, and as a parachute loves to leave a blimp and as a blimp operator loves to chase after it.
I will love you as a dagger loves a certain person’s back, and as a certain person loves to wear dagger proof tunics, and as a dagger proof tunic loves to go to a certain dry cleaning facility, and how a certain employee of a dry cleaning facility loves to stay up late with a pair of binoculars, watching a dagger factory for hours in the hopes of catching a burglar, and as a burglar loves sneaking up behind people with binoculars, suddenly realizing that she has left her dagger at home. I will love you as a drawer loves a secret compartment, and as a secret compartment loves a secret, and as a secret loves to make a person gasp, and as a gasping person loves a glass of brandy to calm their nerves, and as a glass of brandy loves to shatter on the floor, and as the noise of glass shattering loves to make someone else gasp, and as someone else gasping loves a nearby desk to lean against, even if leaning against it presses a lever that loves to open a drawer and reveal a secret compartment. I will love you until all such compartments are discovered and opened, and until all the secrets have gone gasping into the world. I will love you until all the codes and hearts have been broken and until every anagram and egg has been unscrambled.
I will love you until every fire is extinguised and until every home is rebuilt from the handsomest and most susceptible of woods, and until every criminal is handcuffed by the laziest of policemen. I will love until M. hates snakes and J. hates grammar, and I will love you until C. realizes S. is not worthy of his love and N. realizes he is not worthy of the V. I will love you until the bird hates a nest and the worm hates an apple, and until the apple hates a tree and the tree hates a nest, and until a bird hates a tree and an apple hates a nest, although honestly I cannot imagine that last occurrence no matter how hard I try. I will love you as we grow older, which has just happened, and has happened again, and happened several days ago, continuously, and then several years before that, and will continue to happen as the spinning hands of every clock and the flipping pages of every calendar mark the passage of time, except for the clocks that people have forgotten to wind and the calendars that people have forgotten to place in a highly visible area. I will love you as we find ourselves farther and farther from one another, where we once we were so close that we could slip the curved straw, and the long, slender spoon, between our lips and fingers respectively.
I will love you until the chances of us running into one another slip from slim to zero, and until your face is fogged by distant memory, and your memory faced by distant fog, and your fog memorized by a distant face, and your distance distanced by the memorized memory of a foggy fog. I will love you no matter where you go and who you see, no matter where you avoid and who you don’t see, and no matter who sees you avoiding where you go. I will love you no matter what happens to you, and no matter how I discover what happens to you, and no matter what happens to me as I discover this, and now matter how I am discovered after what happens to me as I am discovering this." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291124-i-think-therefore-i-am-is-the-statement-of-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 01:46:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291124-i-think-therefore-i-am-is-the-statement-of-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;I&gt;I think, therefore I am&lt;/i&gt; is the statement of an intellectual who underrates toothaches. &lt;i&gt;I feel, therefore I am&lt;/i&gt; is a truth much more universally valid, and it applies to everything that's alive. My self does not differ substantially from yours in terms of its thought. Many people, few ideas: we all think more or less the same, and we exchange, borrow, steal thoughts from one another. However, when someone steps on my foot, only I feel the pain. The basis of the self is not thought but suffering, which is the most fundamental of all feelings. While it suffers, not even a cat can doubt its unique and uninterchangeable self. In intense suffering the world disappears and each of us is alone with his self. Suffering is the university of egocentrism." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43084-whenever-someone-who-knows-you-disappears-you-lose-one-version</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:50:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43084-whenever-someone-who-knows-you-disappears-you-lose-one-version]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever someone who knows you disappears, you lose one version of yourself. Yourself as you were seen, as you were judged to be. Lover or enemy, mother or friend, those who know us construct us, and their several knowings slant the different facets of our characters like diamond-cutter's tools. Each such loss is a step leading to the grave, where all versions blend and end." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:50:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/127555-i-am-the-sum-total-of-everything-that-went-before]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the sum total of everything that went before me, of all I have been seen done, of everything done-to-me. I am everyone everything whose being-in-the-world affected was affected by mine. I am anything that happens after I'm gone which would not have happened if I had not come." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63575-there-s-nothing-mysterious-about-it-he-s-not-working-at-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:52:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63575-there-s-nothing-mysterious-about-it-he-s-not-working-at-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing mysterious about it, He's not working at all. He's playing. Or else He's forgotten all about us. That's the kind of God you people talk about, a country bumpkin, a clumsy, bungling, brainless, conceited, uncouth hayseed. Good God, how much reverence can you have for a Supreme Being who finds it necessary to include such phenomena as phlegm and tooth decay in His divine system of Creation? What in the world was running through that warped, evil, scatological mind of His when He robbed old people of the power to control their bowel movements? Why in the world did He ever create pain?" -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142392-when-i-look-up-i-see-people-cashing-in-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:53:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Joseph Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142392-when-i-look-up-i-see-people-cashing-in-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look up, I see people cashing in. I don't see heaven or saints or angels. I see people cashing in on every decent impulse and every human tragedy." -- Joseph Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140154-the-planet-is-fine-the-people-are-fucked</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:53:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140154-the-planet-is-fine-the-people-are-fucked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The planet is fine. The people are fucked." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2981-happiness-in-intelligent-people-is-the-rarest-thing-i-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:56:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2981-happiness-in-intelligent-people-is-the-rarest-thing-i-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness in intelligent people is the rarest thing I know." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17569-you-will-never-be-happy-if-you-continue-to-search</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:56:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17569-you-will-never-be-happy-if-you-continue-to-search]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will never be happy if you continue to search for what happiness consists of. You will never live if you are looking for the meaning of life." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110552-there-s-nothing-like-deep-breaths-after-laughing-that-hard-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:56:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110552-there-s-nothing-like-deep-breaths-after-laughing-that-hard-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing like deep breaths after laughing that hard. Nothing in the world like a sore stomach for the right reasons." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1961-the-road-not-taken-two-roads-diverged-in-a-yellow</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:57:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1961-the-road-not-taken-two-roads-diverged-in-a-yellow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Road Not Taken

Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both	
And be one traveler, long I stood	
And looked down one as far as I could	
To where it bent in the undergrowth;	        
 
Then took the other, as just as fair,	
And having perhaps the better claim,	
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;	
Though as for that the passing there	
Had worn them really about the same,	        
 
And both that morning equally lay	
In leaves no step had trodden black.	
Oh, I kept the first for another day!	
Yet knowing how way leads on to way,	
I doubted if I should ever come back.	        
 
I shall be telling this with a sigh	
Somewhere ages and ages hence:	
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I—	
I took the one less traveled by,	
And that has made all the difference." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7985-some-say-the-world-will-end-in-fire-some-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:58:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7985-some-say-the-world-will-end-in-fire-some-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some say the world will end in fire,
Some say in ice.
From what I've tasted of desire,
I hold with those who favor fire. 
But if it had to perish twice
I think I know enough of hate
To say that for destruction ice
Is also great
And would suffice." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14513-forgive-o-lord-my-little-jokes-on-thee-and-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:59:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14513-forgive-o-lord-my-little-jokes-on-thee-and-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgive, O Lord, my little jokes on Thee
And I'll forgive Thy great big one on me." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2207-a-poem-begins-as-a-lump-in-the-throat-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:59:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2207-a-poem-begins-as-a-lump-in-the-throat-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A poem begins as a lump in the throat, a sense of wrong, a homesickness, a lovesickness." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3722-summer-night---even-the-stars-are-whispering-to-each-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 11:59:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Kobayashi Issa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3722-summer-night---even-the-stars-are-whispering-to-each-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Summer night--
even the stars
are whispering to each other." -- Kobayashi Issa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70343-fighting-for-peace-is-like-screwing-for-virginity</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:03:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70343-fighting-for-peace-is-like-screwing-for-virginity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fighting for peace is like screwing for virginity." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6344-time-is-an-illusion-lunchtime-doubly-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:04:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6344-time-is-an-illusion-lunchtime-doubly-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is an illusion. Lunchtime doubly so." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7324-if-you-want-to-know-what-god-thinks-of-money</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:04:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7324-if-you-want-to-know-what-god-thinks-of-money]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you want to know what God thinks of money, just look at the people he gave it to." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5544-the-trouble-with-being-in-the-rat-race-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:04:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Lily Tomlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5544-the-trouble-with-being-in-the-rat-race-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with being in the rat race is that even if you win, you're still a rat." -- Lily Tomlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384312-i-want-to-grow-a-flower-for-every-time-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:05:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Jarod Kintz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/384312-i-want-to-grow-a-flower-for-every-time-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to grow a flower for every time someone tells me “F*** you.” Then I’ll go back to that person and pin the flower on their lapel in a gesture of friendship. And while they are looking down on it in astonishment, I’ll bunch up my knuckles and punch them in the face." -- Jarod Kintz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1012-we-have-to-dare-to-be-ourselves-however-frightening-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:07:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by May Sarton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1012-we-have-to-dare-to-be-ourselves-however-frightening-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to dare to be ourselves, however frightening or strange that self may prove to be." -- May Sarton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8634-may-you-live-every-day-of-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:07:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Jonathan Swift]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8634-may-you-live-every-day-of-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May you live every day of your life." -- Jonathan Swift]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10805-if-a-cluttered-desk-is-a-sign-of-a-cluttered</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:07:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10805-if-a-cluttered-desk-is-a-sign-of-a-cluttered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a cluttered desk is a sign of a cluttered mind, of what, then, is an empty desk a sign?" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31970-when-we-are-tired-we-are-attacked-by-ideas-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:07:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31970-when-we-are-tired-we-are-attacked-by-ideas-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we are tired, we are attacked by ideas we conquered long ago." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18344-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 12:08:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ruchi add a quote by Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18344-sometimes-i-lie-awake-at-night-and-i-ask-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I lie awake at night and I ask, &quot;Is life a multiple choice test or is it a true or false test?&quot; ...Then a voice comes to me out of the dark and says, &quot;We hate to tell you this but life is a thousand word essay." -- Charles M. Schulz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
