<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939305-kristen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939305-kristen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 16:42:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 16:42:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2499-there-are-two-motives-for-reading-a-book-one-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two motives for reading a book; one, that you enjoy it; the other, that you can boast about it." -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275296-happiness-doesn-t-lie-in-conspicuous-consumption-and-the-relentless-amassing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 07:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Dennis Lehane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275296-happiness-doesn-t-lie-in-conspicuous-consumption-and-the-relentless-amassing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness doesn't lie in conspicuous consumption and the relentless amassing of useless crap. Happiness lies in the person sitting beside you and your ability to talk to them. Happiness is clear-headed human interaction and empathy. Happiness is home. And home is not a house-home is a mythological conceit. It is a state of mind. A place of communion and unconditional love. It is where, when you cross its threshold, you finally feel at peace." -- Dennis Lehane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382952-home-wasn-t-a-set-house-or-a-single-town-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 07:28:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/382952-home-wasn-t-a-set-house-or-a-single-town-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Home wasn't a set house, or a single town on a map. It was wherever the people who loved you were, whenever you were together. Not a place, but a moment, and then another, building on each other like bricks to create a solid shelter that you take with you for your entire life, wherever you may go." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2012 20:53:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ever there is tomorrow when we're not together... there is something you must always remember. You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. But the most important thing is, even if we're apart... I'll always be with you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219728-well-it-seems-to-me-that-the-best-relationships--</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 06:27:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Gillian Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/219728-well-it-seems-to-me-that-the-best-relationships--]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Well, it seems to me that the best relationships - the ones that last - are frequently the ones that are rooted in friendship. You know, one day you look at the person and you see something more than you did the night before. Like a switch has been flicked somewhere. And the person who was just a friend is... suddenly the only person you can ever imagine yourself with." -- Gillian Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 16:27:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36501-perhaps-after-all-romance-did-not-come-into-one-s-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps, after all, romance did not come into one’s life with pomp and blare, like a gay knight riding down; perhaps it crept to one’s side like an old friend through quiet ways; perhaps it revealed itself in seeming prose, until some sudden shaft of illumination flung athwart its pages betrayed the rhythm and the music, perhaps . . . perhaps . . . love unfolded naturally out of a beautiful friendship, as a golden-hearted rose slipping from its green sheath." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350492-the-event-of-falling-in-love-is-of-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2014 16:33:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350492-the-event-of-falling-in-love-is-of-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The event of falling in love is of such a nature that we are right to reject as intolerable the idea that it should be transitory. In one high bound it has overleaped the massive of our selfhood; it has made appetite itself altruistic, tossed personal happiness aside as a triviality and planted the interests of another in the centre of our being. Spontaneously and without effort we have fulfilled the law (towards one person) by loving our neighbour as ourselves. It is an image, a foretaste, of what we must become to all if Love Himself rules in us without a rival. It is even (well used) a preparation for that." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
