<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939766-mitch]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939766-mitch" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 16:50:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68756-out-of-that-night-and-day-of-unconditional-wrath-folks</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 16:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mitch add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68756-out-of-that-night-and-day-of-unconditional-wrath-folks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of that night and day of unconditional wrath, folks would've expected to see any city, if it survived, all newly reborn, purified by flame, taken clear beyond greed, real-estate speculating, local politics--instead of which, here was this weeping widow, some one-woman grievance committee in black, who would go on and save up and lovlingly record and mercilessly begrudge every goddamn single tear she ever had to cry, and over the years to come would make up for them all by developing into the meanest, cruelest bitch of a city, even among cities not notable for their kindness.

To all appearance resolute, adventurous, manly, the city would not shake that terrible all-night rape, when &quot;he&quot; was forced to submit, surrending, inadmissably, blindly feminine, into the Hellfire embrace of &quot;her&quot; beloved. He spent the years afterward forgetting and fabulating and trying to get back some self-respect. But inwardly, deep inside, &quot;he&quot; remained the catamite of Hell, the punk at the disposal of all the denizens thereof, the bitch in men's clothing." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16469-they-re-in-love-fuck-the-war</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2009 21:41:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mitch add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16469-they-re-in-love-fuck-the-war]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They're in love.  Fuck the war." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
