<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939881-tara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/939881-tara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 07:32:52 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 07:32:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 07:33:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122020-the-truth-is-you-can-be-orphaned-again-and-again</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:27:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122020-the-truth-is-you-can-be-orphaned-again-and-again]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is you can be orphaned again and again and again. The truth is, you will be. And the secret is, this will hurt less and less each time until you can't feel a thing. Trust me on this." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122022-feminism-has-never-been-about-getting-a-job-for-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:28:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Gloria Steinem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122022-feminism-has-never-been-about-getting-a-job-for-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Feminism has never been about getting a job for one woman. It's about making life more fair for women everywhere. It's not about a piece of the existing pie; there are too many of us for that. It's about baking a new pie." -- Gloria Steinem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122023-it-pleased-him-to-imagine-god-as-someone-like-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:29:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Richard Russo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122023-it-pleased-him-to-imagine-god-as-someone-like-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It pleased him to imagine God as someone like his mother, someone beleagured by too many responsibilities, too dog-tired to monitor an energetic boy every minute of the day, but who, out of love and fear for his safety, checked in on him whenever she could. Was this so crazy? ...Miles liked the idea of a God who, when He at last had the oppotunity to return His attention to His children, might shake His head with wonder and mutter, &quot;Jesus. Look what they're up to now.&quot; A distractible God, perhaps, one who'd be startled to discover so many of His children way up in trees since the last time He looked. A God whose hand would go rushing to His mouth in fear in that instant of recognition that - good God! - that kid's going to hurt himself. A God who could be surprised by unanticipated pride - glory be, that boy is a climber!" -- Richard Russo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72290-we-ve-begun-to-raise-daughters-more-like-sons-but-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:34:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Gloria Steinem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72290-we-ve-begun-to-raise-daughters-more-like-sons-but-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We've begun to raise daughters more like sons... but few have the courage to raise our sons more like our daughters." -- Gloria Steinem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:36:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Douglas Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1398-i-love-deadlines-i-love-the-whooshing-noise-they-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love deadlines. I love the whooshing noise they make as they go by." -- Douglas Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 09:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:40:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2633-it-is-said-that-your-life-flashes-before-your-eyes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is said that your life flashes before your eyes just before you die. That is true, it's called Life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8667-it-takes-a-great-deal-of-bravery-to-stand-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 08:46:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8667-it-takes-a-great-deal-of-bravery-to-stand-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It takes a great deal of bravery to stand up to our enemies, but just as much to stand up to our friends." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61392-death-s-got-an-invisibility-cloak-harry-interrupted-again-so-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 10:26:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61392-death-s-got-an-invisibility-cloak-harry-interrupted-again-so-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death's got an Invisibility Cloak?&quot; Harry interrupted again.
&quot;So he can sneak up on people,&quot; said Ron. &quot;Sometimes he gets bored of running at them, flapping his arms and shrieking..." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96696-you-know-minister-i-disagree-with-dumbledore-on-many-counts-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2009 13:29:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96696-you-know-minister-i-disagree-with-dumbledore-on-many-counts-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, Minister, I disagree with Dumbledore on many counts...but you cannot deny he's got style..." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55271-focusing-your-life-solely-on-making-a-buck-shows-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 12:07:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55271-focusing-your-life-solely-on-making-a-buck-shows-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Focusing your life solely on making a buck shows a poverty of ambition. It asks too little of yourself. And it will leave you unfulfilled." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5603-we-have-to-continually-be-jumping-off-cliffs-and-developing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 12:53:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5603-we-have-to-continually-be-jumping-off-cliffs-and-developing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have to continually be jumping off cliffs and developing our wings on the way down." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 12:55:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14471-many-people-need-desperately-to-receive-this-message-i-feel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many people need desperately to receive this message: 'I feel and think much as you do, care about many of the things you care about, although most people do not care about them. You are not alone." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65481-falling-in-love-we-said-i-fell-for-him-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 12:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65481-falling-in-love-we-said-i-fell-for-him-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Falling in love, we said; I fell for him. We were falling women. We believed in it, this downward motion: so lovely, like flying, and yet at the same time so dire, so extreme, so unlikely. God is love, they once said, but we reversed that, and love, like heaven, was always just around the corner. The more difficult it was to love the particular man beside us, the more we believed in Love, abstract and total. We were waiting, always, for the incarnation. That word, made flesh.

And sometimes it happened, for a time. That kind of love comes and goes and is hard to remember afterwards, like pain. You would look at the man one day and you would think, I loved you, and the tense would be past, and you would be filled with a sense of wonder, because it was such an amazing and precarious and dumb thing to have done; and you would know too why your friends had been evasive about it, at the time.

There is a good deal of comfort, now, in remembering this." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37368-you-fit-into-me-like-a-hook-into-an-eye</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 12:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37368-you-fit-into-me-like-a-hook-into-an-eye]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You fit into me
like a hook into an eye

a fish hook
an open eye" -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12235-i-did-not-design-this-game-i-did-not-name</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 13:00:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by ani difranco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12235-i-did-not-design-this-game-i-did-not-name]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not design this game; I did not name the stakes. I just happen to like apples; and I am not afraid of snakes." -- ani difranco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74612-and-half-of-learning-to-play-is-learning-what-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2009 13:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Ani DiFranco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74612-and-half-of-learning-to-play-is-learning-what-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and half of learning to play is learning what not to play
and she's learning the spaces she leaves have their own things to say
and she's trying to sing just enough so that the air around her moves
and make music like mercy that gives what it is and has nothing to prove

she crawls out on a limb and begins to build her home
and it's enough just to look around and to know that she's not alone

up up up up up up up points the spire of the steeple
but god's work isn't done by god
it's done by people" -- Ani DiFranco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 11:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20404-i-meant-said-ipslore-bitterly-what-is-there-in-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 11:46:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20404-i-meant-said-ipslore-bitterly-what-is-there-in-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I meant,&quot; said Ipslore bitterly, &quot;what is there in this world that truly makes living worthwhile?&quot;
Death thought about it.
CATS, he said eventually. CATS ARE NICE." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55442-funny-for-all-surveillance-osama-bin-laden-is-still-free-151-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2009 15:51:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Cory Doctorow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55442-funny-for-all-surveillance-osama-bin-laden-is-still-free-151-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Funny, for all surveillance, Osama bin Laden is still free&amp;#151;and we're not. Guess who's winning the &quot;war on terror?" -- Cory Doctorow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213764-the-other-day-as-i-was-stepping-out-of-star</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 05:22:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/213764-the-other-day-as-i-was-stepping-out-of-star]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The other day as I was stepping out of Star Grocery on Claremont Avenue with some pork ribs under my arm, the Berkeley sky cloudless, a smell of jasmine in the air, a car driving by with its window rolled down, trailing a sweet ache of the Allman Brothers' &quot;Melissa,&quot; it struck me that in order to have reached only the midpoint of my life I will need to live to be 92. That's pretty old. If you live to be ninety-two, you've done well for yourself. I'd like to be optimistic, and I try to take care of my health, but none of my grandparents even made it past 76, three killed by cancer, one by Parkinson's disease. If I live no longer than any of them did, I have at most thirty years left, which puts me around sixty percent of the way through my time.

 

I am comfortable with the idea of mortality, or at least I always have been, up until now. I never felt the need to believe in heaven or an afterlife. It has been decades since I stopped believing-a belief that was never more than fitful and self-serving to begin with-in the possibility of reincarnation of the soul. I'm not totally certain where I stand on the whole &quot;soul&quot; question. Though I certainly feel as if I possess one, I'm inclined to disbelieve in its existence. I can live with that contradiction, as with the knowledge that my time is finite, and growing shorter by the day. It's just that lately, for the first time, that shortening has become perceptible. I can feel each tiny skyward lurch of the balloon as another bag of sand goes over the side of my basket." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 00:01:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76393-i-have-a-history-of-making-decisions-very-quickly-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have a history of making decisions very quickly about men.  I have always fallen in love fast and without measuring risks.  I have a tendency not only to see the best in everyone, but to assume that everyone is emotionally capable of reaching his highest potential.  I have fallen in love more times than I care to count with the highest potential of a man, rather than with the man himself, and I have hung on to the relationship for a long time (sometimes far too long) waiting for the man to ascend to his own greatness.  Many times in romance I have been a victim of my own optimism." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 14:26:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26963-if-you-can-t-fly-then-run-if-you-can-t-run</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2012 14:29:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26963-if-you-can-t-fly-then-run-if-you-can-t-run]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can't fly then run, if you can't run then walk, if you can't walk then crawl, but whatever you do you have to keep moving forward." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21910-do-your-bit-to-save-humanity-from-lapsing-back-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2012 16:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Richard Hughes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21910-do-your-bit-to-save-humanity-from-lapsing-back-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do your bit to save humanity from lapsing back into barbarity by reading all the novels you can." -- Richard Hughes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 19:00:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tara add a quote by Ann Patchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11268-it-makes-you-wonder-all-the-brilliant-things-we-might]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It makes you wonder. All the brilliant things we might have done with our lives if only we suspected we knew how." -- Ann Patchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
