<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/93981-kristen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/93981-kristen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:04:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150191-you-think-because-he-doesn-t-love-you-that-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:04:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150191-you-think-because-he-doesn-t-love-you-that-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think because he doesn't love you that you are worthless. You think that because he doesn't want you anymore that he is right -- that his judgement and opinion of you are correct. If he throws you out, then you are garbage. You think he belongs to you because you want to belong to him. Don't. It's a bad word, 'belong.' Especially when you put it with somebody you love. Love shouldn't be like that. Did you ever see the way the clouds love a mountain? They circle all around it; sometimes you can't even see the mountain for the clouds. But you know what? You go up top and what do you see? His head. The clouds never cover the head. His head pokes through, beacuse the clouds let him; they don't wrap him up. They let him keep his head up high, free, with nothing to hide him or bind him. You can't own a human being. You can't lose what you don't own. Suppose you did own him. Could you really love somebody who was absolutely nobody without you? You really want somebody like that? Somebody who falls apart when you walk out the door? You don't, do you? And neither does he. You're turning over your whole life to him. Your whole life, girl. And if it means so little to you that you can just give it away, hand it to him, then why should it mean any more to him? He can't value you more than you value yourself." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70058-i-am-simply-a-book-drunkard-books-have-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:10:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70058-i-am-simply-a-book-drunkard-books-have-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am simply a 'book drunkard.'  Books have the same irresistible temptation for me that liquor has for its devotee. I cannot withstand them." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95720-there-is-such-a-place-as-fairyland---but-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95720-there-is-such-a-place-as-fairyland---but-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is such a place as fairyland - but only children can find the way to it. And they do not know that it is fairyland until they have grown so old that they forget the way. One bitter day, when they seek it and cannot find it, they realize what they have lost; and that is the tragedy of life. On that day the gates of Eden are shut behind them and the age of gold is over. Henceforth they must dwell in the common light of common day. Only a few, who remain children at heart, can ever find that fair, lost path again; and blessed are they above mortals. They, and only they, can bring us tidings from that dear country where we once sojourned and from which we must evermore be exiles. The world calls them its singers and poets and artists and story-tellers; but they are just people who have never forgotten the way to fairyland." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150253-the-body-grows-slowly-and-steadily-but-the-soul-grows</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150253-the-body-grows-slowly-and-steadily-but-the-soul-grows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The body grows slowly and steadily but the soul grows by leaps and bounds.  It may come to its full stature in an hour." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103739-i-couldn-t-live-where-there-were-no-trees--something-vital-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:14:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/103739-i-couldn-t-live-where-there-were-no-trees--something-vital-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn't live where there were no trees--something vital in me would starve." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67011-don-t-be-led-away-by-those-howls-about-realism-remember-pine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:15:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67011-don-t-be-led-away-by-those-howls-about-realism-remember-pine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't be led away by those howls about realism. Remember-pine woods are just as real as pigsties and a darn sight pleasanter to be in." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119519-those-who-can-soar-to-the-highest-heights-can-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:15:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/119519-those-who-can-soar-to-the-highest-heights-can-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who can soar to the highest heights can also plunge to the deepest depths and the natures which enjoy most keenly are those which also suffer most sharply." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24044-there-s-no-use-trying-to-live-in-other-people-s-opinions</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:15:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24044-there-s-no-use-trying-to-live-in-other-people-s-opinions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["there's no use trying to live in other people's opinions. The only thing to do is live in your own." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39945-the-only-true-animal-is-a-cat-and-the-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:16:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maude Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39945-the-only-true-animal-is-a-cat-and-the-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only true animal is a cat, and the only true cat is a gray cat." -- Lucy Maude Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79372-without-shedding-of-blood-there-is-no-anything-everything-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79372-without-shedding-of-blood-there-is-no-anything-everything-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without shedding of blood there is no anything… Everything, it seems to me, has to be purchased by self-sacrifice. Our race has marked every step of its painful ascent with blood. And now torrents of it must flow again… I don’t think the war has been sent as a punishment for sin. I think it is the price humanity must pay for some blessing - some advance great enough to be worth the price which we may not live to see but which our children’s children will inherit." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68418-it-was-three-o-clock-in-the-morning-the-wisest</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68418-it-was-three-o-clock-in-the-morning-the-wisest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was three o'clock in the morning – the wisest and most accursed hour of the clock. But sometimes it sets us free." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152386-anne-always-remembered-the-silvery-peaceful-beauty-and-fragrant-calm</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:17:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152386-anne-always-remembered-the-silvery-peaceful-beauty-and-fragrant-calm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anne always remembered the silvery, peaceful beauty and fragrant calm of that night. It was the last night before sorrow touched her life; and no life is ever quite the same again when once that cold, sanctifying touch has been laid upon it." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42604-don-t-you-know-that-it-is-only-the-very-foolish</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:18:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42604-don-t-you-know-that-it-is-only-the-very-foolish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you know that it is only the very foolish folk who talk sense all the time? (Anne)" -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99776-as-she-walked-along-she-dramatized-the-night-there-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:19:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99776-as-she-walked-along-she-dramatized-the-night-there-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As she walked along she dramatized the night. There was about it a wild, lawless charm that appealed to a certain wild, lawless strain hidden deep in Emily’s nature—the strain of the gypsy and the poet, the genius and the fool." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17957-i-am-very-careful-to-be-shallow-and-conventional-where</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:20:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17957-i-am-very-careful-to-be-shallow-and-conventional-where]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am very careful to be shallow and conventional where depth and originality are wasted." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175714-i-am-quite-likely-to-re-act-to-the-opposite-extreme</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:20:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175714-i-am-quite-likely-to-re-act-to-the-opposite-extreme]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am quite likely to re-act to the opposite extreme - to feel rapturously that the world is beautiful and mere existence something to thank God for. I suppose our 'blues' are the price we have to pay for our temperament. 'The gods don't allow us to be in their debt.' They give us sensitiveness to beauty in all its forms but the shadow of the gift goes with it." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173252-i-feel-as-if-i-had-opened-a-book-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:22:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173252-i-feel-as-if-i-had-opened-a-book-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I feel as if I had opened a book and found roses of yesterday sweet and fragrant, between its leaves." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176260-if-it-s-in-you-to-climb-you-must----there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:25:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176260-if-it-s-in-you-to-climb-you-must----there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If it's IN you to climb you must -- there are those who MUST lift their eyes to the hills -- they can't breathe properly in the valleys." -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176261-i-ve-a-pocket-full-of-dreams-to-sell-said-teddy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 08:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176261-i-ve-a-pocket-full-of-dreams-to-sell-said-teddy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've a pocket full of dreams to sell,&quot; said Teddy, whimsically,...  &quot;What d'ye lack?  What d'ye lack?  A dream of success--a dream of adventure--a dream of the sea--a dream of the woodland--any kind of a dream you want at reasonable prices, including one or two unique little nightmares.  What will you give me for a dream?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 10:29:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristen add a quote by Rachel Cohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40902-i-mean-i-don-t-know-how-the-world-broke-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I mean, I don’t know how the world broke. And I don’t know if there’s a God who can help us fix it. But the fact that the world is broken - I absolutely believe that. Just look around us. Every minute - every single second - there are a million things you could be thinking about. A million things you could be worrying about. Our world - don’t you just feel we’re becoming more fragmented? I used to think that when I got older, the world would make so much more sense. But you know what? The older I get, the more confusing it is to me. The more complicated it is. Harder. You’d think we’d be getting better at it. But there’s just more and more chaos. The pieces - they’re everywhere. And nobody knows what to do about it. I find myself grasping, Nick. You know that feeling? That feeling when you just want the right thing to fall into the right place, not only because it’s right, but because it would mean that such a thing is still possible? I want to believe that." -- Rachel Cohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
