<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/940322-praneet-sandhu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/940322-praneet-sandhu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:11:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:11:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182796-out-of-my-thoughts-you-are-part-of-my-existence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out of my thoughts! You are part of my existence, part of myself. You have been in every line I have ever read, since I first came here, the rough common boy whose poor heart you wounded even then. You have been in every prospect I have ever seen since – on the river, on the sails of the ships, on the marshes, in the clouds, in the light, in the darkness, in the wind, in the woods, in the sea, in the streets. You have been the embodiment of every graceful fancy that my mind has ever become acquainted with. The stones of which the strongest London buildings are made, are not more real, or more impossible to displace with your hands, than your presence and influence have been to me, there and everywhere, and will be. Estella, to the last hour of my life, you cannot choose but remain part of my character, part of the little good in me, part of the evil. But, in this separation I associate you only with the good, and I will faithfully hold you to that always, for you must have done me far more good than harm, let me feel now what sharp distress I may. O God bless you, God forgive you!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8312-there-is-no-love-sincerer-than-the-love-of-food</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:17:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8312-there-is-no-love-sincerer-than-the-love-of-food]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no love sincerer than the love of food." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6371-those-who-cannot-change-their-minds-cannot-change-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:17:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6371-those-who-cannot-change-their-minds-cannot-change-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349491-higgins-i-find-that-the-moment-i-let-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/349491-higgins-i-find-that-the-moment-i-let-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Higgins: I find that the moment I let a woman make friends with me, she becomes jealous, exacting, suspicious, and a damned nuisance. I find that the moment I let myself make friends with a woman, I become selfish and tyrannical. Women upset everything. When you let them into your life, you find that the woman is driving at one thing and youre driving at another.
Pickering: At what, for example?
Higgins: Oh, Lord knows! I suppose the woman wants to live her own life; and the man wants to live his; and each tries to drag the other on to the wrong track. One wants to go north and the other south; and the result is that both have to go east, though they both hate the east wind." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55416-the-great-secret-eliza-is-not-having-bad-manners-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 03:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55416-the-great-secret-eliza-is-not-having-bad-manners-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great secret, Eliza, is not having bad manners or good manners or any other particular sort of manners, but having the same manner for all human souls: in short, behaving as if you were in Heaven, where there are no thirdclass carriages, and one soul is as good as another." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 04:02:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/942-two-things-are-infinite-the-universe-and-human-stupidity-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the universe." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 04:15:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2448-to-live-is-the-rarest-thing-in-the-world-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180993-the-unqualified-truth-is-that-when-i-loved-estella-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 19:08:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180993-the-unqualified-truth-is-that-when-i-loved-estella-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The unqualified truth is, that when I loved Estella with the love of a man, I loved her simply because I found her irresistible. Once for all; I knew to my sorrow, often and often, if not always, that I loved her against reason, against promise, against peace, against hope, against happiness, against all discouragement that could be. Once for all; I love her none the less because I knew it, and it had no more influence in restraining me, than if I had devoutly believed her to be human perfection." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37801-my-love-for-linton-is-like-the-foliage-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 19:10:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37801-my-love-for-linton-is-like-the-foliage-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My love for Linton is like the foliage in the woods: time will change it, I'm well aware, as winter changes the trees. My love for Heathcliff resembles the eternal rocks beneath: a source of little visible delight, but necessary. Nelly, I am Healthcliff! He's always, always in my mind: not as a pleasure, any more than I am always a pleasure to myself, but as my own being." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65838-it-was-not-the-thorn-bending-to-the-honeysuckles-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 19:11:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Emily Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65838-it-was-not-the-thorn-bending-to-the-honeysuckles-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was not the thorn bending to the honeysuckles, but the honeysuckles embracing the thorn." -- Emily Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173160-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2012 19:11:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Emily Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173160-you-teach-me-now-how-cruel-you-ve-been---cruel]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You teach me now how cruel you've been - cruel and false. Why did you despise me? Why did you betray your own heart, Cathy? I have not one word of comfort. You deserve this. You have killed yourself. Yes, you may kiss me, and cry; and wring out my kisses and tears: they'll blight you - they'll damn you. You loved me - what right had you to leave me? What right - answer me - for the poor fancy you felt for Linton? Because misery, and degradation, and death, and nothing that God or Satan could inflict would have parted us, you, of your own will did it. I have not broken your heart - you have broken it; and in breaking it, you have broken mine." -- Emily Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 15:05:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60492-and-yet-she-was-leaving-the-world-as-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:09:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by khaled hosseini (a thousand splendid suns)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60492-and-yet-she-was-leaving-the-world-as-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and yet she was leaving the world as a woman who had love and been loved back.  she was leaving it as a friend, a companion, a guardian.  a mother.  a person of consequence at last." -- khaled hosseini (a thousand splendid suns)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60172-if-you-expect-nothing-from-anybody-you-re-never-disappointed</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/60172-if-you-expect-nothing-from-anybody-you-re-never-disappointed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you expect nothing from anybody, you’re never disappointed." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98270-mad-girl-s-love-song-i-shut-my-eyes-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:11:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98270-mad-girl-s-love-song-i-shut-my-eyes-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mad Girl's Love Song

I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead;
I lift my lids and all is born again.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

The stars go waltzing out in blue and red,
And arbitrary blackness gallops in:
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.

I dreamed that you bewitched me into bed
And sung me moon-struck, kissed me quite insane.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

God topples from the sky, hell's fires fade:
Exit seraphim and Satan's men:
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.

I fancied you'd return the way you said,
But I grow old and I forget your name.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)

I should have loved a thunderbird instead;
At least when spring comes they roar back again.
I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.
(I think I made you up inside my head.)" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178991-god-but-life-is-loneliness-despite-all-the-opiates-despite</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:12:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178991-god-but-life-is-loneliness-despite-all-the-opiates-despite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God, but life is loneliness, despite all the opiates, despite the shrill tinsel gaiety of &quot;parties&quot; with no purpose, despite the false grinning faces we all wear.  And when at last you find someone to whom you feel you can pour out your soul, you stop in shock at the words you utter - they are so rusty, so ugly, so meaningless and feeble from being kept in the small cramped dark inside you so long.  Yes, there is joy, fulfillment and companionship - but the loneliness of the soul in its appalling self-consciousness is horrible and overpowering." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4757-the-trouble-was-i-had-been-inadequate-all-along-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:13:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4757-the-trouble-was-i-had-been-inadequate-all-along-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble was, I had been inadequate all along, I simply hadn't thought about it." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10942-to-the-person-in-the-bell-jar-blank-and-stopped</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:13:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10942-to-the-person-in-the-bell-jar-blank-and-stopped]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the person in the bell jar, blank and stopped as a dead baby, the world itself is a bad dream." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:15:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29213-life-is-like-riding-a-bicycle-to-keep-your-balance</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:15:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29213-life-is-like-riding-a-bicycle-to-keep-your-balance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 06:17:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6812-life-can-only-be-understood-backwards-but-it-must-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life can only be understood backwards; but it must be lived forwards." -- Søren Kierkegaard]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2013 15:52:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151476-only-once-in-your-life-i-truly-believe-you-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only once in your life, I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, you can’t wait to tell them about it, knowing they will share in your excitement. They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a fool of yourself. Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think of you because they love you for who you are. The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again. Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always brings a smile to your face. In their presence, there’s no need for continuous conversation, but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby. Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end. Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is in knowing that they are a part of your life." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182410-the-world-somebody-wrote-is-the-place-we-prove-real</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182410-the-world-somebody-wrote-is-the-place-we-prove-real]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world, somebody wrote, is the place we prove real by dying in it." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182173-you-can-t-judge-an-internal-injury-by-the-size-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:55:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182173-you-can-t-judge-an-internal-injury-by-the-size-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't judge an internal injury by the size of the hole." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39303-question-what-is-the-opposite-of-faith-not-disbelief-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:56:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39303-question-what-is-the-opposite-of-faith-not-disbelief-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: What is the opposite of faith? 

Not disbelief. Too final, certain, closed. Itself is a kind of belief. 

Doubt. 

The human condition, but what of the angelic? Halfway between Allahgod and homosap, did they ever doubt? They did: challenging God's will one day they hid muttering beneath the Throne, daring to ask forbidden things: antiquestions. Is it right that. Could it not be argued. Freedom, the old antiquest. He calmed them down, naturally, employing management skills a la god. Flattered them: you will be the instruments of my will on earth, the salvationdamnation of man, all the usual etcetera. And hey presto, the end of protest, on with the haloes, back to work. Angels are easily pacified; turn them into instruments and they'll play your harpy tune. Human beings are tougher nuts, can doubt anything, even the evidence of their own eyes. Of behing-their-own-eyes. Of what, as they sink heavy-lidded, transpires behind closed peepers ... angels, they don't have much in the way of a will. To will is to disagree; not to submit; to dissent." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234312-everest-silences-you-when-you-come-down-nothing-seems-worth-saying</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:57:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/234312-everest-silences-you-when-you-come-down-nothing-seems-worth-saying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everest silences you...when you come down, nothing seems worth saying, nothing at all.  You find the nothingness wrapping you up, like a sound.  Non-being.  You can't keep it up, of course.  the world rushes in soon enough.  What shuts you up is, I think, the sight you've had of perfection: why speak if you can't manage perfect thoughts, perfect sentences?  It feels like a betrayal of what you've been through.  But it fades; you accept that certain compromises, closures, are required if you're to continue." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182177-if-love-is-a-yearning-to-be-like-even-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 07:57:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Salman Rushdie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182177-if-love-is-a-yearning-to-be-like-even-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If love is a yearning to be like (even to become) the beloved, then hatred, it must be said, can be engendered by the same ambition, when it cannot be fulfilled." -- Salman Rushdie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25165-is-there-no-way-out-of-the-mind</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2014 12:14:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Praneet add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25165-is-there-no-way-out-of-the-mind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is there no way out of the mind?" -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
