<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/940530-amy-drew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/940530-amy-drew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295537-from-the-night-into-his-high-walled-room-there-came-persistently</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295537-from-the-night-into-his-high-walled-room-there-came-persistently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the night into his high-walled room there came, persistently, that evanescent and dissolving sound - something the city was tossing up and calling back again, like a child playing with a ball.  In Harlem, the Bronx, Gramercy Park, and along the water-fronts, in little parlors or on pebble-strewn, moon-flooded roofs, a thousand lovers were making this sound, crying little fragments of it into the air. All the city was playing with this sound out there in the blue summer dark, throwing it up and calling it back, promising that, in a little while, life would be beautiful as a story, promising happiness - and by that promise giving it.  It gave love hope in its own survival.  It could do no more." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295546-she-looked-down-again-and-i-was-stymied-i-sat</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295546-she-looked-down-again-and-i-was-stymied-i-sat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She looked down again and I was stymied. I sat. Oh, this was enough to make me love her, because I was right with her, understanding every second and longing to step in. I didn’t even need to know the specific that was troubling her, because to me her halting voice easily stood for the general woe that hangs in the air, even on life’s happiest days." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140422-isn-t-it-time-that-these-most-ancient-sorrows-of-ours</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140422-isn-t-it-time-that-these-most-ancient-sorrows-of-ours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it time that these most ancient 
                      sorrows of ours
grew fruitful? Time that we tenderly
               loosed ourselves
from the loved one, and, unsteadily,
               survived:
the way the arrow, suddenly all vector,
               survives the string
to be more than itself. For abiding is
                nowhere." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141038-by-then-i-knew-that-everything-good-and-bad-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By then I knew that everything good and bad left an emptiness when it stopped.  But if it was bad, the emptiness filled up by itself.  If it was good you could only fill it by finding something better." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295528-after-slipping-on-a-negligee-and-making-herself-comfortable-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:09:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295528-after-slipping-on-a-negligee-and-making-herself-comfortable-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After slipping on a negligee and making herself comfortable on the lounge, she became conscious that she was miserable and that the tears were rolling down her cheeks.  She wondered if they were the tears of self-pity, and tried resolutely not to cry, but this existence without hope, without happiness, oppressed her, and she kept shaking her head from side to side, her mouth drawn down tremulously in the corners, as though she were denying the assertion made by some one, somewhere.  She did not know that this gesture of hers was years older than history, that, for a hundred generations of men, intolerable and persistent grief has offered that gesture, of denial, of protest, of bewilderment, to something more profound, more powerful than the God made in the image of man, and before which that God, did he exist, would be equally impotent.  It is a truth set at the heart of tragedy that this force never explains, never answers - this force intangible as air, more definite than death." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64155-we-do-not-grow-absolutely-chronologically-we-grow-sometimes-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64155-we-do-not-grow-absolutely-chronologically-we-grow-sometimes-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We do not grow absolutely, chronologically. We grow sometimes in one dimension, and not in another; unevenly. We grow partially. We are relative. We are mature in one realm, childish in another. The past, present, and future mingle and pull us backward, forward, or fix us in the present. We are made up of layers, cells, constellations." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8089-don-t-let-us-forget-that-the-causes-of-human-actions</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8089-don-t-let-us-forget-that-the-causes-of-human-actions]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don’t let us forget that the causes of human actions are usually immeasurably more complex and varied than our subsequent explanations of them." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7915-each-friend-represents-a-world-in-us-a-world-possibly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295533-idiot-he-cried-that-from-you-here-i-sit-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:20:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295533-idiot-he-cried-that-from-you-here-i-sit-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Idiot!&quot; he cried, &quot;that from you! Here I sit, young Anthony, as I'll sit for a generation or more and watch such gay souls as you and Dick and Gloria Gilbery go past me, dancing and singing and loving and hating one another and being moved, being eternally moved.  And I am moved only by my lack of emotion.  I shall sit and the snow will come--oh, for a Caramel to take notes--and another winter and I shall be thirty and you and Dick and Gloria will go on being eternally moved and dancing by me and singing.  But after you've all gone I'll be saying things for new Dicks to write down, and listening to the disillusions and cynicisms and emotions of new Anthonys--yes, and talking to new Glorias about the tans of summers yet to come.&quot;
	The firelight flurried up on the hearth.  Maury left the window, stirred the blaze with a poker, and dropped a log upon the andirons.  Then he sat back in his chair and the remnants of his voice faded in the new fire that spit red and yellow along the bark.
	&quot;After all, Anthony, it's you who are very romantic and young. It's you who are infinitely more susceptible and afraid of your calm being broken.  It's me who tries again and again to be moved--let myself go a thousand times and I'm always me.  Nothing--quite--stirs me.
	&quot;Yet,&quot; he murmured after another long pause, &quot;there was something about that little girl with her absurd tan that was eternally old--like me." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295535-happiness-remarked-maury-noble-one-day-is-only-the-first</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:21:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295535-happiness-remarked-maury-noble-one-day-is-only-the-first]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness, remarked Maury Noble one day, is only the first hour after the alleviation of some especially intense misery." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148374-and-why-are-you-so-firmly-so-triumphantly-convinced-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148374-and-why-are-you-so-firmly-so-triumphantly-convinced-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And why are you so firmly, so triumphantly, convinced that only the normal and the positive--in other words, only what is conducive to welfare--is for the advantage of man? Is not reason in error as regards advantage? Does not man, perhaps, love something besides well-being? Perhaps he is just as fond of suffering? Perhaps suffering is just as great a benefit to him as well-being? Man is sometimes extraordinarily, passionately, in love with suffering, and that is a fact." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20699-remember-that-the-best-relationship-is-one-in-which-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Dali Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20699-remember-that-the-best-relationship-is-one-in-which-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember that the best relationship is one in which your love for each other exceeds your need for each other." -- Dali Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152634-i-have-amazing-news-for-you-man-is-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Daniel Quinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152634-i-have-amazing-news-for-you-man-is-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have amazing news for you. Man is not alone on this planet. He is part of a community, upon which he depends absolutely." -- Daniel Quinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295536-he-was-handsome-then-if-never-before-bound-for-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:21:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295536-he-was-handsome-then-if-never-before-bound-for-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was handsome then if never before, bound for one of those immortal moments which come so radiantly that their remembered light is enough to see by for years." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29007-every-day-think-as-you-wake-up-today-i-am</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by The Dalai Lama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29007-every-day-think-as-you-wake-up-today-i-am]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day, think as you wake up, today I am fortunate to be alive, I have a precious human life, I am not going to waste it. I am going to use all my energies to develop myself, to expand my heart out to others; to achieve enlightenment for the benefit of all beings. I am going to have kind thoughts towards others, I am not going to get angry or think badly about others. I am going to benefit others as much as I can." -- The Dalai Lama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63569-i-am-circling-around-god-around-the-ancient-tower-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63569-i-am-circling-around-god-around-the-ancient-tower-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am circling around God, around the ancient tower, and I have been circling for a thousand years, and I still don't know if I am a falcon, or a storm, or a great song." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104290-loafe-with-me-on-the-grass-loose-the-stop-from-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/104290-loafe-with-me-on-the-grass-loose-the-stop-from-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Loafe with me on the grass—loose the stop from your throat;   
Not words, not music or rhyme I want—not custom or lecture, not even the best;   
Only the lull I like, the hum of your valved voice. 
" -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50793-and-if-there-were-a-god-i-think-it-very</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50793-and-if-there-were-a-god-i-think-it-very]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And if there were a God, I think it very unlikely that He would have such an uneasy vanity as to be offended by those who doubt His existence" -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130989-people-who-talk-about-their-dreams-are-actually-trying-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130989-people-who-talk-about-their-dreams-are-actually-trying-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who talk about their dreams are actually trying to tell you things about themselves they’d never admit in normal conversation." -- Chuck Klosterman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243858-it-is-our-inward-journey-that-leads-us-through-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Eudora Welty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243858-it-is-our-inward-journey-that-leads-us-through-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our inward journey that leads us through time – forward or back, seldom in a straight line, most often spiraling. Each of us is moving, changing, with respect to others. As we discover, we remember; remembering, we discover; and most intensely do we experience this when our separate journeys converge. Our living experience at those meeting points is one of the charged dramatic fields of fiction.	" -- Eudora Welty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126795-once-or-twice-a-day-i-am-enveloped-inside-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Sarah Vowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126795-once-or-twice-a-day-i-am-enveloped-inside-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once or twice a day, I am enveloped inside what I like to call the Impenetrable Shield of Melancholy.  This shield, it is impenetrable.  Hence the name.  I cannot speak.  And while I can feel myself freeze up, I can't do anything about it." -- Sarah Vowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90569-don-t-you-think-i-have-sense-enough-to-worry-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90569-don-t-you-think-i-have-sense-enough-to-worry-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you think I have sense enough to worry about my motives for saying the prayer? That's exactly what's bothering me so. Just because I'm choosy about what I want - in this case, enlightenment or peace, instead or money or prestige or game or any of those things, doesn't mean I'm not as egotistical and self-seeking as everybody else. If anything, I'm more so!" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:38:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19791-to-him-she-seemed-so-beautiful-so-seductive-so-different]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To him she seemed so beautiful, so seductive, so different from ordinary people, that he could not understand why no one was as disturbed as he by the clicking of her heels on the paving stones, why no one else's heart was wild with the breeze stirred by the sighs of her veils, why everyone did not go mad with the movements of her braid, the flight of her hands, the gold of her laughter. He had not missed a single one of her gestures, not one of the indications of her character, but he did not dare approach her for fear of destroying the spell." -- Gabriel García Márquez]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9629-her-mind-blackens-the-blackness-is-not-a-thought-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9629-her-mind-blackens-the-blackness-is-not-a-thought-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[her] mind blackens. The blackness is not a thought, but if it could be pressed into a thought, if a chemical from a dropper could be dripped onto it causing its color and essence to become visible, it would take the shape of this sentence: Why does no one want me?" -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206725-some-nights-alone-he-thinks-of-her-and-some-nights</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:26:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/206725-some-nights-alone-he-thinks-of-her-and-some-nights]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some nights, alone, he thinks of her, and some nights, alone, she thinks of him. Some night these thoughts, separated by miles and time zones, occur at the same objective moment, and Ray and Mirabelle are connected without ever knowing it." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 12:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17521-it-s-so-hard-to-forget-pain-but-it-s-even-harder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness.  We have no scar to show for happiness. We learn so little from peace." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135277-it-is-not-the-big-events-that-hurt-the-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:27:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135277-it-is-not-the-big-events-that-hurt-the-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...it is not the big events that hurt the most but rather the smallest questionable shift in tone at the end of a spoken word that can plow most deeply into the heart." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13564-i-understood-that-as-much-as-i-had-resisted-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 10:28:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13564-i-understood-that-as-much-as-i-had-resisted-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I understood that as much as I had resisted the outside, as much as I had constricted my life, as much as I had closed and narrowed the channels into me, there were still many takers for the quiet heart." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91044-it-often-occurs-to-me-that-if-against-all-odds</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amy add a quote by E.O. Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91044-it-often-occurs-to-me-that-if-against-all-odds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It often occurs to me that if, against all odds, there is a judgmental God and heaven, it will come to pass that when the pearly gates open, those who had the valor to think for themselves will be escorted to the head of the line, garlanded, and given their own personal audience." -- E.O. Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
