<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/941451-dave-norwood]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/941451-dave-norwood" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 15:22:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 15:22:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6363-when-despair-for-the-world-grows-in-me-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When despair for the world grows in me and I wake in the night at the least sound in fear of what my life and my children's lives may be, I go and lie down where the wood drake rests in his beauty on the water, and the great heron feeds. I come into the peace of wild things who do not tax their lives with forethought of grief. I come into the presence of still water. And I feel above me the day-blind stars waiting with their light. For a time I rest in the grace of the world, and am free." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29023-of-all-the-passers-through-the-species-that-means-most-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 15:27:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by John Graves]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29023-of-all-the-passers-through-the-species-that-means-most-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Of all the passers-through, the species that means most to me, even more than geese and cranes, is the upland plover, the drab plump grassland bird that used to remind my gentle hunting uncle of the way things once had been, as it still reminds me. It flies from the far Northern prairies to the pampas of Argentina and then back again in spring, a miracle of navigation and a tremendous journey for six or eight ounces of flesh and feathers and entrails and hollow bones, fueled with bug meat. I see them sometimes in our pastures, standing still or dashing after prey in the grass, but mainly I know their presence through the mournful yet eager quavering whistles they cast down from the night sky in passing, and it makes me think of what the whistling must have been like when the American plains were virgin and their plover came through in millions. To grow up among tradition-minded people leads one often into backward yearnings and regrets, unprofitable feelings of which I was granted my share in youth-not having been born in time to get killed fighting Yankees, for one, or not having ridden up the cattle trails. But the only such regret that has strongly endured is not to have known the land when when it was whole and sprawling and rich and fresh, and the plover that whet one's edge every spring and every fall. In recent decades it has become customary- and right, I guess, and easy enough with hindsight- to damn the ancestral frame of mind that ravaged the world so fully and so soon. What I myself seem to damn mainly, though, is just not having seen it. Without any virtuous hindsight, I would likely have helped in the ravaging as did even most of those who loved it best. But God, to have viewed it entire, the soul and guts of what we had and gone forever now, except in books and such poignant remnants as small swift birds that journey to and from the distant Argentine and call at night in the sky." -- John Graves]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11245-instead-of-adapting-as-we-began-to-do-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 15:29:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dave add a quote by Wallace Stegner, &quot;Where the Bluebird Sings to the Lemonade Springs&quot;]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11245-instead-of-adapting-as-we-began-to-do-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instead of adapting, as we began to do, we have tried to make country and climate over to fit our existing habits and desires. Instead of listening to the silence, we have shouted into the void." -- Wallace Stegner, &quot;Where the Bluebird Sings to the Lemonade Springs&quot;]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
