<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/941601-kendra]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/941601-kendra" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 09:53:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 09:53:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18310-i-was-dead-until-you-found-me-though-i-breathed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 09:54:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by J.R. Ward]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18310-i-was-dead-until-you-found-me-though-i-breathed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was dead until you found me, though I breathed. I was sightless, though I could see. And then you came...and I was awakened." -- J.R. Ward]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6056-maybe-they-know-what-i-know-that-the-true-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2008 00:12:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6056-maybe-they-know-what-i-know-that-the-true-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe they know what I know, that the true way to a man's heart is six inches of metal between his ribs. Sometimes four inches will do the job, but to be really sure, I like to have six." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57477-eric-moved-the-broom-experimentally-and-made-an-attempt-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 10:09:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Charlaine Harris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57477-eric-moved-the-broom-experimentally-and-made-an-attempt-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eric moved the broom experimentally and made an attempt to sweep the glass into the pan while it lay in the middle of the floor. Of course, the pan slid away. Eric scowled.
I'd finally found something Eric did poorly." -- Charlaine Harris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 12:00:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15251-so-please-oh-please-we-beg-we-pray-go-throw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So, please, oh please, we beg, we pray, go throw your TV set away, and in its place you can install, a lovely bookcase on the wall." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 12:00:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7032-and-above-all-watch-with-glittering-eyes-the-whole-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And above all, watch with glittering eyes the whole world around you because the greatest secrets are always hidden in the most unlikely places. Those who don't believe in magic will never find it." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2008 12:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6051-if-ever-there-is-tomorrow-when-we-re-not-together-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ever there is tomorrow when we're not together... there is something you must always remember. You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. But the most important thing is, even if we're apart... I'll always be with you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62931-before-i-knew-you-i-thought-brave-was-not-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2008 11:12:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62931-before-i-knew-you-i-thought-brave-was-not-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Before I knew you, I thought brave was not being afraid. You've taught me that bravery is being terrified and doing it anyway." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 17:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57237-one-of-the-good-things-about-being-a-woman-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 07:59:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57237-one-of-the-good-things-about-being-a-woman-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["one of the good things about being a woman is that my level of testosterone poisoning is lower than most men's." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44587-he-had-this-old-southern-idea-of-what-a-lady</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 07:59:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44587-he-had-this-old-southern-idea-of-what-a-lady]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had this old southern idea of what a lady should be. A lady should not carry a gun and spend most of her time covered in blood and corpses. I had two words for that attitude. 
Yeah, those are the words." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67779-if-i-let-you-get-killed-the-other-body-guards</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2008 08:00:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67779-if-i-let-you-get-killed-the-other-body-guards]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I let you get killed, the other body guards will make fun of me." -- Laurell K. Hamilton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:01:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:02:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:09:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:10:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 22:11:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28571-if-i-had-a-flower-for-every-time-i-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I had a flower for every time I thought of you...I could walk through my garden forever." -- Alfred Lord Tennyson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 23:04:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 23:07:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 23:22:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48507-i-crave-your-mouth-your-voice-your-hair-silent-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I crave your mouth, your voice, your hair.
Silent and starving, I prowl through the streets. 
Bread does not nourish me, dawn disrupts me, all day 
I hunt for the liquid measure of your steps. 

I hunger for your sleek laugh, 
your hands the color of a savage harvest, 
hunger for the pale stones of your fingernails, 
I want to eat your skin like a whole almond. 

I want to eat the sunbeam flaring in your lovely body, 
the sovereign nose of your arrogant face, 
I want to eat the fleeting shade of your lashes, 

and I pace around hungry, sniffing the twilight, 
hunting for you, for your hot heart, 
Like a puma in the barrens of Quitratue." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2008 23:28:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1173-don-t-cry-because-it-s-over-smile-because-it-happened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened." -- Dr. Seuss ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36338-just-because-you-love-someone-doesn-t-mean-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 15:53:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Hugh  Elliott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36338-just-because-you-love-someone-doesn-t-mean-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you love someone, doesn't mean you have to be involved with them.  Love is not a bandage to cover wounds." -- Hugh  Elliott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48274-i-thought-we-were-a-real-love-relationship-i-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 15:53:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48274-i-thought-we-were-a-real-love-relationship-i-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought we were a real love relationship. I did. I was very invested in love, but it was just this long long sex thing that could end at any moment because after all, it's just about getting off. Almost all the time, you tell yourself you're loving somebody when you're just using them. This only looks like love." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46516-when-we-meet-someone-and-fall-in-love-we-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 16:04:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46516-when-we-meet-someone-and-fall-in-love-we-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we meet someone and fall in love, we have a sense that the whole universe is on our side. And yet if something goes wrong, there is nothing left! How is it possible for the beauty that was there only minutes before to vanish so quickly? Life moves very fast. It rushes from heaven to hell in a matter of seconds." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5520-a-life-spent-making-mistakes-is-not-only-more-honorable</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 07:28:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5520-a-life-spent-making-mistakes-is-not-only-more-honorable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 07:28:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Alan Moore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1981-my-experience-of-life-is-that-it-is-not-divided]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My experience of life is that it is not divided up into genres; it’s a horrifying, romantic, tragic, comical, science-fiction cowboy detective novel. You know, with a bit of pornography if you're lucky." -- Alan Moore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 13:23:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9675-i-m-the-one-that-s-got-to-die-when-it-s-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 13:23:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9675-i-m-the-one-that-s-got-to-die-when-it-s-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the one that's got to die when it's time for me to die, so let me live my life the way I want to." -- Jimi Hendrix]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 13:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/924-here-s-to-the-crazy-ones-the-misfits-the-rebels-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here's to the crazy ones. The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers. The round pegs in the square holes. The ones who see things differently. They're not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo. You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them. About the only thing you can't do is ignore them. Because they change things. They push the human race forward. And while some may see them as the crazy ones, we see genius. Because the people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world, are the ones who do." -- Apple Computer Inc.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2009 13:36:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kendra add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876-to-be-yourself-in-a-world-that-is-constantly-trying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be yourself in a world that is constantly trying to make you something else is the greatest accomplishment." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
