<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/942137-casey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/942137-casey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 15:11:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42343-the-syntactical-nature-of-reality-the-real-secret-of-magic</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 15:11:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Casey add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42343-the-syntactical-nature-of-reality-the-real-secret-of-magic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The syntactical nature of reality, the real secret of magic, is that the world is made of words. And if you know the words that the world is made of, you can make of it whatever you wish." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42350-what-is-honor-i-suspect-that-if-after-reading-this-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 16:02:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Casey add a quote by Jack Whyte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42350-what-is-honor-i-suspect-that-if-after-reading-this-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[What is honor]—I suspect that if, after reading this book, you were to go and ask the question of your friends and acquaintances, you might experience some difficultly finding someone who could give you, off the cuff, an accurate and adequate definition of honor. Those who do respond will probably offer synonyms, digging into their memories for other words that are seldom used in today's world, like integrity, probity, morality, and self-sufficiency based upon an ethical and moral code. Some might even refine that further to include a conscience, but no one has ever really succeeded in defining honor absolutely, because it is a very personal phenomenon, resonating differently in everyone who is aware of it. We seldom speak of it today, in our post-modern, post-everything society. It is an anachronism, a quaint, mildly amusing concept from a bygone time, and those of us who do speak of it and think of it are regarded benevolently, and condescendingly, as eccentrics. But honor, in every age except, perhaps, our own, has been highly regarded and greatly respected, and it has always been one of those intangible attributes that everyone assumes they possess naturally and in abundance. The standards established for it have always been high, and often artificially so, and throughout history battle standards have been waved as symbols of the honor and prowess of their owners. But for men and women of goodwill, the standard of honor has always been individual, jealously guarded, intensely personal, and uncaring of what others may think, say, or do." -- Jack Whyte]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
