<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943-h-ctor]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943-h-ctor" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 23:14:05 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215624-this-world-is-a-bridge-do-not-build-your-house</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 23:14:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Jesus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215624-this-world-is-a-bridge-do-not-build-your-house]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This world is a bridge. Do not build your house on it. Be a traveler passing through." -- Jesus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8851-your-weak-side-my-diabolic-friend-is-that-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 22:59:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8851-your-weak-side-my-diabolic-friend-is-that-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your weak side, my diabolic friend, is that you have always been a gull: you take Man at his own valuation. Nothing would flatter him more than your opinion of him. He loves to think of himself as bold and bad. He is neither one nor the other: he is only a coward. Call him tyrant, murderer, pirate, bully; and he will adore you, and swagger about with the consciousness of having the blood of the old sea kings in his veins. Call him liar and thief; and he will only take an action against you for libel. But call him coward; and he will go mad with rage: he will face death to outface that stinging truth. Man gives every reason for his conduct save one, every excuse for his crimes save one, every plea for his safety save one: and that one is his cowardice. Yet all his civilization is founded on his cowardice, on his abject tameness, which he calls his respectability. There are limits to what a mule or an ass will stand; but Man will suffer himself to be degraded until his vileness becomes so loathsome to his oppressors that they themselves are forced to reform it." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8857-although-most-people-never-overcome-the-habit-of-berating-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2007 23:20:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Max Horkheimer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8857-although-most-people-never-overcome-the-habit-of-berating-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although most people never overcome the habit of berating the world for their difficulties, those who are too weak to make a stand against reality have no choice but to obliterate themselves by identifying with it. They are never rationally reconciled to civilization. Instead, they bow to it, secretly accepting the identity of reason and domination, of civilization and the ideal, however much they may shrug their shoulders. Well-informed cynicism is only another mode of conformity. These people willingly embrace or force themselves to accept the rule of the stronger as the eternal norm. Their whole life is a continuous effort to suppress and abase nature, inwardly or outwardly, and to identify themselves with its more powerful surrogates—the race, fatherland, leader, cliques, and tradition. For them, all these words mean the same thing—the irresistible reality that must be honored and obeyed. However, their own natural impulses, those antagonistic to the various demands of civilization, lead a devious undercover life within them." -- Max Horkheimer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10294-that-the-sadian-fantasy-situates-itself-better-in-the-bearers</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2008 01:00:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Jacques Lacan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10294-that-the-sadian-fantasy-situates-itself-better-in-the-bearers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That the Sadian fantasy situates itself better in the bearers of Christian ethics than elsewhere is what our structural landmarks allow us to grasp easily. But that Sade, himself, refuses to be my neighbor, is what needs to be recalled, not in order to refuse it to him in return, but in order to recognize the meaning of this refusal. We believe that Sade is not close enough to his own wickedness to recognize his neighbor in it. A trait which he shares with many, and notably with Freud. For such is indeed the sole motive of the recoil of beings, sometimes forewarned, before the Christian commandment. For Sade, we see the test of this, crucial in our eyes, in his refusal of the death penalty, which history, if not logic, would suffice to show is one of the corollaries of Charity." -- Jacques Lacan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19151-i-can-tell-by-my-own-reaction-to-it-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 19:47:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19151-i-can-tell-by-my-own-reaction-to-it-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can tell by my own reaction to it that this book is harmful.&quot; But let him only wait and perhaps one day he will admit to himself that this same book has done him a great service by bringing out the hidden sickness of his heart and making it visible.— Altered opinions do not alter a man’s character (or do so very little); but they do illuminate individual aspects of the constellation of his personality which with a different constellation of opinions had hitherto remained dark and unrecognizable." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157719-por-qu-tan-lejos-de-los-dioses-quiz-por-preguntarlo</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 23:50:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Julio Cortázar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157719-por-qu-tan-lejos-de-los-dioses-quiz-por-preguntarlo]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["¿Por qué tan lejos de los dioses? Quizá por preguntarlo. ¿Y qué? El hombre es el animal que pregunta. El día en que verdaderamente sepamos preguntar, habrá diálogo. Por ahora las preguntas nos alejan vertiginosamente de las respuestas. ¿Qué &lt;i&gt;epifanía&lt;/i&gt; podemos esperar si nos estamos ahogando en la más falsa de las libertades, la dialéctica judeocristiana? Nos hace falta un &lt;i&gt;Novum Organum&lt;/i&gt; de verdad, hay que abrir de par en par todas las ventanas y tirar todo a la calle, pero sobre todo hay que tirar también la ventana, y nosotros con ella. Es la muerte, o salir volando. Hay que hacerlo, de alguna manera hay que hacerlo." -- Julio Cortázar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157723-heidegger-sostiene-que-el-hombre-es-un-ser-para-la</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 00:40:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by José Lezama Lima]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157723-heidegger-sostiene-que-el-hombre-es-un-ser-para-la]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heidegger sostiene que el hombre es un ser para la muerte; todo poeta, sin embargo, crea la resurrección, entona ante la muerte un hurra victorioso. Y si alguno piensa que exagero, quedará preso de los desastres, del demonio y de los círculos infernales." -- José Lezama Lima]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307915-yo-no-quiero-alcanzar-la-inmortalidad-por-mi-obra-quiero</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 16:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Héctor add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307915-yo-no-quiero-alcanzar-la-inmortalidad-por-mi-obra-quiero]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yo no quiero alcanzar la inmortalidad por mi obra. Quiero conseguirla por no morir. No quiero vivir en la memoria de mis compatriotas. Preferiría vivir en mi apartamento." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
