<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943420-lina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943420-lina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:21:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3596-without-words-without-writing-and-without-books-there-would-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:21:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3596-without-words-without-writing-and-without-books-there-would-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without words, without writing and without books there would be no history, there could be no concept of humanity." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34056-whoever-wants-music-instead-of-noise-joy-instead-of-pleasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2010 00:21:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34056-whoever-wants-music-instead-of-noise-joy-instead-of-pleasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever wants music instead of noise, joy instead of pleasure, soul instead of gold, creative work instead of business, passion instead of foolery, finds no home in this trivial world of ours." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9776-to-the-question-how-do-the-authors-of-sketches-stories</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 20:51:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9776-to-the-question-how-do-the-authors-of-sketches-stories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To the question: How do the authors of sketches, stories and novels get along in life, the following answer can or must be given: They are stragglers and they are down at heel." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172251-houses-gardens-and-people-were-transfigured-into-musical-sounds-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2010 20:51:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Robert Walser]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/172251-houses-gardens-and-people-were-transfigured-into-musical-sounds-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Houses, gardens, and people were transfigured into musical sounds, all that was solid seemed to be transfigured into soul and into gentleness. Sweet veils of silver and soul-haze swam through all things and lay over all things. The soul of the world had opened, and all grief, all human disappointment, all evil, all pain seemed to vanish, from now on never to appear again. Earlier walks came before my eyes; but the wonderful image of the humble present became a feeling which overpowered all others. The future paled, and the past dissolved. I glowed and flowered myself in the glowing, flowering present. From near and far, great things and small things emerged bright silver with marvelous gestures, joys, and enrichments, and in the midst of this beautiful place I dreamed of nothing but this place itself. All other fantasies sank and vanished in meaninglessness. I had the whole rich earth immediately before me, and I still looked only at what was most small and most humble. With gestures of love the heavens rose and fell. I had become an inward being, and walked as in an inward world; everything outside me became a dream; what I had understood till now became unintelligible. I fell away from the surface, down into the fabulous depths, which I recognized then to be all that was good. What we understand and love understands and loves us also. I was no longer myself, was another, and yet it was on this account that I became properly myself. In the sweet light of love I realized, or believe I realized, that perhaps the inward self is the only self which really exists." -- Robert Walser]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83663-an-organism-at-war-with-itself-is-doomed</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 15:30:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83663-an-organism-at-war-with-itself-is-doomed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An organism at war with itself is doomed." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205762-please-a-little-less-love-and-a-little-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 10:44:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205762-please-a-little-less-love-and-a-little-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Please — a little less love, and a little more common decency." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 16:44:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2798-i-like-too-many-things-and-get-all-confused-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like too many things and get all confused and hung-up running from one falling star to another till i drop. This is the night, what it does to you. I had nothing to offer anybody except my own confusion." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413672-i-sleep-i-inhabit-sleep-firmly-willing-it-wielding-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 16:44:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413672-i-sleep-i-inhabit-sleep-firmly-willing-it-wielding-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sleep. I inhabit sleep firmly, willing it, wielding it, pushing away dreams, refusing, refusing. Sleep is my lover now, my forgetting, my opiate, my oblivion." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7575-i-thought-how-unpleasant-it-is-to-be-locked-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 16:54:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7575-i-thought-how-unpleasant-it-is-to-be-locked-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought how unpleasant it is to be locked out; and I thought how it is worse, perhaps, to be locked in." -- Virginia Woolf ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 12:04:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110964-i-love-mankind-he-said-but-i-find-to-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love mankind, he said, &quot;but I find to my amazement that the more I love mankind as a whole, the less I love man in particular." -- Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39009-read-read-read-read-everything----trash-classics-good-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 12:04:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39009-read-read-read-read-everything----trash-classics-good-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Read, read, read. Read everything -- trash, classics, good and bad, and see how they do it. Just like a carpenter who works as an apprentice and studies the master. Read! You'll absorb it.
Then write. If it's good, you'll find out. If it's not, throw it out of the window." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136464-so-everything-lets-us-down-including-curiosity-and-honesty-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 00:03:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136464-so-everything-lets-us-down-including-curiosity-and-honesty-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So everything lets us down, including curiosity and honesty and what we love best. Yes, said the voice, but cheer up, it's fun in the end." -- Roberto Bolaño]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175845-i-have-grown-weary-of-literature-silence-alone-comforts-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2011 19:04:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Clarice Lispector]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175845-i-have-grown-weary-of-literature-silence-alone-comforts-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have grown weary of literature: silence alone comforts me. If I continue to write, it’s because I have nothing more to accomplish in this world except to wait for death. Searching for the word in darkness. Any little success invades me and puts me in full view of everyone. I long to wallow in the mud. I can scarcely control my need for self-abasement, my craving for licentiousness and debauchery. Sin tempts me, forbidden pleasures lure me. I want to be both pig and hen, then kill them and drink their blood." -- Clarice Lispector]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76651-don-t-feel-sorry-for-yourself-only-assholes-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 13:20:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76651-don-t-feel-sorry-for-yourself-only-assholes-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't feel sorry for yourself. Only assholes do that." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11258-she-was-gone-and-all-that-was-left-was-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 22:54:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11258-she-was-gone-and-all-that-was-left-was-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She was gone, and all that was left was the space you'd grown around her, like a tree that grows around a fence.  For a long time, it remained hollow.  Years, maybe.  And when at last it was filled again, you knew that the new love you felt for a woman would have been impossible without Alma.  If it weren't for her, there would never have been an empty space, or the need to fill it." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33881-the-truth-is-the-thing-i-invented-so-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2012 22:56:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33881-the-truth-is-the-thing-i-invented-so-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is the thing I invented so I could live." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269823-my-own-brain-is-to-me-the-most-unaccountable-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 00:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269823-my-own-brain-is-to-me-the-most-unaccountable-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My own brain is to me the most unaccountable of machinery - always buzzing, humming, soaring roaring diving, and then buried in mud. And why? What's this passion for?" -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 00:57:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Frank Herbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2-i-must-not-fear-fear-is-the-mind-killer-fear-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration. I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me. And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path. Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain." -- Frank Herbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78234-one-resolution-i-have-made-and-try-always-to-keep</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2012 12:56:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by John Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78234-one-resolution-i-have-made-and-try-always-to-keep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One resolution I have made, and try always to keep, is this: ‘To rise above little things’." -- John Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313718-someone-i-loved-once-gave-me-a-box-full-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2012 21:26:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313718-someone-i-loved-once-gave-me-a-box-full-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone I loved once gave me a box full of darkness. It took me years to understand that this too, was a gift." -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112975-she-didn-t-care-anymore-and-she-got-no-pleasure-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 21:38:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Louise Fitzhugh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112975-she-didn-t-care-anymore-and-she-got-no-pleasure-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She didn't care anymore... and she got no pleasure from the work she did, but she did it.  Everything bored her.  She found that when she didn't have a notebook it was hard for her to think.  The thoughts came slowly, as though they had to squeeze through a tiny door to get to her, whereas when she wrote, they flowed out faster than she could put them down.  She sat very stupidly with a blank mind until finall 'I feel different' came slowly to her mind.

Yes, she thought, after a long pause.  And then, after more time, 'Mean, I feel mean." -- Louise Fitzhugh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 23:28:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14033-question-i-am-interested-in-so-many-things-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Question: I am interested in so many things, and I have a terrible fear because my mother keeps telling me that I'm just going to be exploring the rest of my life and never get anything done. But I find it really hard to set my ways and say, &quot;Well, do I want to do this, or should I try to exploit that, or should I escape and completely do one thing?&quot;

Anaïs Nin: One word I would banish from the dictionary is 'escape.' Just banish that and you'll be fine. Because that word has been misused regarding anybody who wanted to move away from a certain spot and wanted to grow. He was an escapist. You know if you forget that word you will have a much easier time. Also you're in the prime, the beginning of your life; you should experiment with everything, try everything.... We are taught all these dichotomies, and I only learned later that they could work in harmony. We have created false dichotomies; we create false ambivalences, and very painful one's sometimes -the feeling that we have to choose. But I think at one point we finally realize, sometimes subconsciously, whether or not we are really fitted for what we try and if it's what we want to do.

You have a right to experiment with your life. You will make mistakes. And they are right too. No, I think there was too rigid a pattern. You came out of an education and are supposed to know your vocation. Your vocation is fixed, and maybe ten years later you find you are not a teacher anymore or you're not a painter anymore. It may happen. It has happened. I mean Gauguin decided at a certain point he wasn't a banker anymore; he was a painter. And so he walked away from banking. I think we have a right to change course. But society is the one that keeps demanding that we fit in and not disturb things. They would like you to fit in right away so that things work now." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 14:37:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140777-therefore-dear-sir-love-your-solitude-and-try-to-sing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Therefore, dear Sir, love your solitude and try to sing out with the pain it causes you. For those who are near you are far away... and this shows that the space around you is beginning to grow vast.... be happy about your growth, in which of course you can't take anyone with you, and be gentle with those who stay behind; be confident and calm in front of them and don't torment them with your doubts and don't frighten them with your faith or joy, which they wouldn't be able to comprehend. Seek out some simple and true feeling of what you have in common with them, which doesn't necessarily have to alter when you yourself change again and again; when you see them, love life in a form that is not your own and be indulgent toward those who are growing old, who are afraid of the aloneness that you trust.... and don't expect any understanding; but believe in a love that is being stored up for you like an inheritance, and have faith that in this love there is a strength and a blessing so large that you can travel as far as you wish without having to step outside it." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 09:56:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11193-love-after-love-the-time-will-come-when-with-elation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love After Love

The time will come 
when, with elation 
you will greet yourself arriving 
at your own door, in your own mirror 
and each will smile at the other's welcome, 

and say, sit here. Eat. 
You will love again the stranger who was your self.
Give wine. Give bread. Give back your heart 
to itself, to the stranger who has loved you 

all your life, whom you ignored 
for another, who knows you by heart. 
Take down the love letters from the bookshelf, 

the photographs, the desperate notes, 
peel your own image from the mirror. 
Sit. Feast on your life." -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78472-i-read-i-travel-i-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 09:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78472-i-read-i-travel-i-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read; I travel; I become" -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70473-break-a-vase-and-the-love-that-reassembles-the-fragments</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 09:56:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70473-break-a-vase-and-the-love-that-reassembles-the-fragments]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Break a vase, and the love that reassembles the fragments is stronger than that love which took its symmetry for granted when it was whole." -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/800943-slowly-my-body-grows-a-single-sound-slowly-i-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 09:57:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Derek Walcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/800943-slowly-my-body-grows-a-single-sound-slowly-i-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Slowly my body grows a single sound, slowly I become a bell, an oval, disembodied vowel, I grow, an owl, an aureole, white fire

poesia &quot;Metamorfosi, I. Luna" -- Derek Walcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 10:50:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178306-life-has-no-meaning-each-of-us-has-meaning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life has no meaning. Each of us has meaning and we bring it to life. It is a waste to be asking the question when you are the answer." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192665-the-cave-you-fear-to-enter-holds-the-treasure-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 10:50:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192665-the-cave-you-fear-to-enter-holds-the-treasure-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cave you fear to enter holds the treasure you seek." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115975-if-you-are-falling-dive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 10:49:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lina add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115975-if-you-are-falling-dive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are falling....dive." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
