<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943477-alyona]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/943477-alyona" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:28:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192370-the-rosy-hearth-the-lamplight-s-narrow-beam-the-meditation-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:28:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Verlaine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192370-the-rosy-hearth-the-lamplight-s-narrow-beam-the-meditation-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rosy hearth, the lamplight's narrow beam,
     The meditation that is rather dream,
     With looks that lose themselves in cherished looks;
     The hour of steaming tea and banished books;
     The sweetness of the evening at an end,
     The dear fatigue, and right to rest attained,
     And worshipped expectation of the night,—
     Oh, all these things, in unrelenting flight,
     My dream pursues through all the vain delays,
     Impatient of the weeks, mad at the days!" -- Verlaine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192371-an-infinite-resignedness-rains-where-the-white-mists-opalesce-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2009 12:29:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Verlaine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192371-an-infinite-resignedness-rains-where-the-white-mists-opalesce-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An infinite
        Resignedness
     Rains where the white
        Mists opalesce
     In the moon-shower..." -- Verlaine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:00:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208546-the-truth-is-everyone-is-going-to-hurt-you-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth is, everyone is going to hurt you. You just got to find the ones worth suffering for." -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Jon Katz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65817-i-think-if-i-ve-learned-anything-about-friendship-it-s-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think if I've learned anything about friendship, it's to hang in, stay connected, fight for them, and let them fight for you. Don't walk away, don't be distracted, don't be too busy or tired, don't take them for granted. Friends are part of the glue that holds life and faith together. Powerful stuff." -- Jon Katz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23446-this-is-how-it-works-i-love-the-people-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:01:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by James Lecesne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23446-this-is-how-it-works-i-love-the-people-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is how it works.  I love the people in my life, and I do for my friends whatever they need me to do for them, again and again, as many times as is necessary.  For example, in your case you always forgot who you are and how much you're loved.  So what I do for you as your friend is remind you who you are and tell you how much I love you.  And this isn't any kind of burden for me, because I love who you are very much.  Every time I remind you, I get to remember with you, which is my pleasure." -- James Lecesne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13272-sometimes-being-a-friend-means-mastering-the-art-of-timing</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:03:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Gloria Naylor ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13272-sometimes-being-a-friend-means-mastering-the-art-of-timing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes being a friend means mastering the art of timing. There is a time for silence. A time to let go and allow people to hurl themselves into their own destiny. And a time to prepare to pick up the pieces when it's all over." -- Gloria Naylor ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:06:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/939-if-the-world-were-merely-seductive-that-would-be-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the world were merely seductive, that would be easy. If it were merely challenging, that would be no problem. But I arise in the morning torn between a desire to improve the world and a desire to enjoy the world. This makes it hard to plan the day." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:13:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7992-don-t-say-you-don-t-have-enough-time-you-have-exactly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:15:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7992-don-t-say-you-don-t-have-enough-time-you-have-exactly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't say you don't have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were given to Helen Keller, Pasteur, Michaelangelo, Mother Teresa, Leonardo da Vinci, Thomas Jefferson, and Albert Einstein." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 13:15:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8706-life-will-break-you-nobody-can-protect-you-from-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life will break you. Nobody can protect you from that, and living alone won't either, for solitude will also break you with its yearning. You have to love. You have to feel. It is the reason you are here on earth. You are here to risk your heart. You are here to be swallowed up. And when it happens that you are broken, or betrayed, or left, or hurt, or death brushes near, let yourself sit by an apple tree and listen to the apples falling all around you in heaps, wasting their sweetness. Tell yourself you tasted as many as you could." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194550-leave-the-dishes-let-the-celery-rot-in-the-bottom</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 14:20:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194550-leave-the-dishes-let-the-celery-rot-in-the-bottom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave the dishes.
Let the celery rot in the bottom drawer of the refrigerator
and an earthen scum harden on the kitchen floor.
Leave the black crumbs in the bottom of the toaster.
Throw the cracked bowl out and don't patch the cup.
Don't patch anything. Don't mend. Buy safety pins.
Don't even sew on a button.
Let the wind have its way, then the earth
that invades as dust and then the dead
foaming up in gray rolls underneath the couch.
Talk to them. Tell them they are welcome.
Don't keep all the pieces of the puzzles
or the doll's tiny shoes in pairs, don't worry
who uses whose toothbrush or if anything
matches, at all.
Except one word to another. Or a thought.
Pursue the authentic-decide first
what is authentic,
then go after it with all your heart.
Your heart, that place
you don't even think of cleaning out.
That closet stuffed with savage mementos.
Don't sort the paper clips from screws from saved baby teeth
or worry if we're all eating cereal for dinner
again. Don't answer the telephone, ever,
or weep over anything at all that breaks.
Pink molds will grow within those sealed cartons
in the refrigerator. Accept new forms of life
and talk to the dead
who drift in though the screened windows, who collect
patiently on the tops of food jars and books.
Recycle the mail, don't read it, don't read anything
except what destroys
the insulation between yourself and your experience
or what pulls down or what strikes at or what shatters
this ruse you call necessity." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377067-the-music-was-more-than-music--at-least-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 14:22:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/377067-the-music-was-more-than-music--at-least-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The music was more than music- at least what we are used to hearing.  The music was feeling itself.  The sound connected instantly with something deep and joyous.  Those powerful moments of true knowledge that we have to paper over with daily life.  The music tapped the back of our terrors, too.  Things we'd lived through and didn't want to ever repeat.  Shredded imaginings, unadmitted longings, fear and also surprisingly pleasures.  No, we can't live at that pitch.  But every so often something shatters like ice and we are in the river of our existence.  We are aware.  And this realization was in the music, somehow, or in the way Shamengwa played it." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82918-with-friends-if-you-keep-making-an-effort-to-reach</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2011 14:59:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Tori Spelling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82918-with-friends-if-you-keep-making-an-effort-to-reach]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With friends, if you keep making an effort to reach out and you keep getting hurt, you eventually stop trying. But it's much harder to give up on family. Somewhere deep down you want it to work so badly that you keep making the same mistake over and over again." -- Tori Spelling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159302-the-mark-of-the-immature-man-is-that-he-wants</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 13:34:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159302-the-mark-of-the-immature-man-is-that-he-wants]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mark of the immature man is that he wants to die nobly for a cause, while the mark of the mature man is that he wants to live humbly for one." -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:02:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12357-i-wish-it-need-not-have-happened-in-my-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wish it need not have happened in my time,&quot; said Frodo.
&quot;So do I,&quot; said Gandalf, &quot;and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215-it-s-not-worth-doing-something-unless-someone-somewhere-would-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:09:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215-it-s-not-worth-doing-something-unless-someone-somewhere-would-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not worth doing something unless someone, somewhere, would much rather you weren't doing it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:11:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11871-that-s-the-problem-with-drinking-i-thought-as-i-poured]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the problem with drinking, I thought, as I poured myself a drink. If something bad happens you drink in an attempt to forget; if something good happens you drink in order to celebrate; and if nothing happens you drink to make something happen." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39207-if-you-re-going-to-try-go-all-the-way-otherwise</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39207-if-you-re-going-to-try-go-all-the-way-otherwise]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're going to try, go all the way. Otherwise, don't even start. This could mean losing girlfriends, wives, relatives and maybe even your mind. It could mean not eating for three or four days. It could mean freezing on a park bench. It could mean jail. It could mean derision. It could mean mockery--isolation. Isolation is the gift. All the others are a test of your endurance, of how much you really want to do it. And, you'll do it, despite rejection and the worst odds. And it will be better than anything else you can imagine. If you're going to try, go all the way. There is no other feeling like that. You will be alone with the gods, and the nights will flame with fire. You will ride life straight to perfect laughter. It's the only good fight there is." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154643-sometimes-you-climb-out-of-bed-in-the-morning-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:11:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154643-sometimes-you-climb-out-of-bed-in-the-morning-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you climb out of bed in the morning and you think, I'm not going to make it, but you laugh inside — remembering all the times you've felt that way." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123110-we-are-born-like-this-into-this-into-these-carefully</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:13:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123110-we-are-born-like-this-into-this-into-these-carefully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are
Born like this
Into this
Into these carefully mad wars
Into the sight of broken factory windows of emptiness
Into bars where people no longer speak to each other
Into fist fights that end as shootings and knifings
Born into this
Into hospitals which are so expensive that it’s cheaper to die
Into lawyers who charge so much it’s cheaper to plead guilty
Into a country where the jails are full and the madhouses closed
Into a place where the masses elevate fools into rich heroes" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10805-if-a-cluttered-desk-is-a-sign-of-a-cluttered</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:21:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10805-if-a-cluttered-desk-is-a-sign-of-a-cluttered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If a cluttered desk is a sign of a cluttered mind, of what, then, is an empty desk a sign?" -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:23:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11225-nothing-was-ever-in-tune-people-just-blindly-grabbed-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing was ever in tune. People just blindly grabbed at whatever there was: communism, health foods, zen, surfing, ballet, hypnotism, group encounters, orgies, biking, herbs, Catholicism, weight-lifting, travel, withdrawal, vegetarianism, India, painting, writing, sculpting, composing, conducting, backpacking, yoga, copulating, gambling, drinking, hanging around, frozen yogurt, Beethoven, Back, Buddha, Christ, TM, H, carrot juice, suicide, handmade suits, jet travel, New York City, and then it all evaporated and fell apart. People had to find things to do while waiting to die. I guess it was nice to have a choice." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188191-when-someone-cries-so-hard-that-it-hurts-their-throat</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 08:24:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Chase Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/188191-when-someone-cries-so-hard-that-it-hurts-their-throat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When someone cries so hard that it hurts their throat, it is out of frustration or knowing that no matter what you can do or attempt to do can change the situation. When you feel like you need to cry, when you want to just get it out, relieve some of the pressure from the inside - that is true pain. Because no matter how hard you try or how bad you want to, you can't. That pain just stays in place. Then, if you are lucky, one small tear may escape from those eyes that water constantly. That one tear, that tiny, salty, droplet of moisture is a means of escape. Although it's just a small tear, it is the heaviest thing in the world. And it doesn't do a damn thing to fix anything." -- Chase Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300760-if-you-wake-up-tired-you-ve-been-chasing-dreams-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 13:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Benny Bellamacina]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/300760-if-you-wake-up-tired-you-ve-been-chasing-dreams-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you wake up tired, you’ve been chasing dreams. If you go to bed tired, your making your dreams happen." -- Benny Bellamacina]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411539-to-be-a-man-is-precisely-to-be-responsible-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2011 13:31:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alyona add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411539-to-be-a-man-is-precisely-to-be-responsible-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be a man is, precisely, to be responsible. It is to feel shame at the sight of what seems to be unmerited misery. It is to take pride in a victory won by one's comrades. It is to feel, when setting one's stone, that one is contributing to the building of the world." -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
