<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/944567-rob-livingston]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/944567-rob-livingston" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 19:49:17 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33116-why-procrastinate-when-you-can-precognitate</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 19:49:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33116-why-procrastinate-when-you-can-precognitate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why procrastinate when you can precognitate?" -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33119-with-the-superciliousness-of-extreme-youth-i-put-thirty-five-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 19:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33119-with-the-superciliousness-of-extreme-youth-i-put-thirty-five-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With the superciliousness of extreme youth, I put thirty-five as the utmost limit at which a man might fall in love without making a fool of himself." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39061-her-tears-were-partly-tears-of-happiness-for-she-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 19:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39061-her-tears-were-partly-tears-of-happiness-for-she-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her tears were partly tears of happiness, for she felt that the strangeness between them was gone. She loved him now with a new love because he had made her suffer." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39063-he-had-been-taught-by-his-uncle-that-his-prayers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 19:16:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39063-he-had-been-taught-by-his-uncle-that-his-prayers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had been taught by his uncle that his prayers were more acceptable to God if he said them in his nightshirt than if he waited till he was dressed. This did not surprise him, for he was beginning to realize that he was the creature of a God who appreciated the discomfort of his worshipers." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39069-the-new-born-child-does-not-realize-that-his-body-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 19:45:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39069-the-new-born-child-does-not-realize-that-his-body-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The new-born child does not realize that his body is more a part of himself than surrounding objects, and will play with his toes without any feeling that they belong to him more than the rattle by his side; and it is only by degrees, through pain, that he understands the fact of the body. And experiences of the same kind are necessary for the individual to become conscious of himself; but here there is the difference that, although everyone becomes equally conscious of his body as a separate and complete organism, everyone does not become equally conscious of himself as a complete and separate personality.... It is such that he, as little conscious of himself as the bee in a hive, who are lucky in life, for they have the best chance of happiness: their activities are shared by all, and their pleasures are only pleasures because they are enjoyed in common.... It is because of them that man has been called a social animal." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31165-i-have-an-idea-that-some-men-are-born-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2008 19:50:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Rob add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31165-i-have-an-idea-that-some-men-are-born-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have an idea that some men are born out of their due place.  Accident has cast them amid certain surroundings, but they have always a nostalgia for a home they know not.  They are strangers in their birthplace, and the leafy lanes they have known from childhood or the populous streets in which they have played, remain but a place of passage.  They may spend their whole lives aliens among their kindred and remain aloof among the only scenes they have ever known.  Perhaps it is this sense of strangeness that sends men far and wide in the search for something permanent, to which they may attach themselves.  Perhaps some deep-rooted atavism urges the wanderer back to lands which his ancestors left in the dim beginnings of history.  Sometimes a man hits upon a place to which he mysteriously feels that he belongs.  Here is the home he sought, and he will settle amid scenes that he has never seen before, among men he has never known, as though they were familiar to him from his birth.  Here at last he finds rest." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
