<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/945419-maria]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/945419-maria" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 22:28:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36510-how-can-i-make-him-understand-that-he-did-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 22:28:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Daniel Keyes]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36510-how-can-i-make-him-understand-that-he-did-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How can I make him understand that he did not create me?
He makes the same mistake as the others when they look at a feeble-minded person and laugh because they don't understand there are human feelings involved." -- Daniel Keyes]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111155-one-of-the-principal-functions-of-a-friend-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 14:42:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111155-one-of-the-principal-functions-of-a-friend-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the principal functions of a friend is to suffer (in a milder and symbolic form) the punishments that we should like, but are unable, to inflict upon our enemies." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54845-although-he-had-used-it-very-sparingly-the-perfume-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 11:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Patrick Süskind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54845-although-he-had-used-it-very-sparingly-the-perfume-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although he had used it very sparingly, the perfume that he had mixed in Montpellier was slowly was slowly running out. He created a new one. But this time he was not content simply to imitate basic human odor by hastily tossing together some ingredients; he made it a matter of pride to acquire a personal odor, or better yet, a number of personal odors...
Protected by these various odors, which he changed like clothes as the situation demanded and which permitted him to move undisturbed in the world of men and to keep his true nature from them, Grenouille devoted himself to his real passion: the subtle pursuit of scent." -- Patrick Süskind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63013-religion-is-a-tool-to-bind-people-together-to-strengthen</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 11:47:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Deepak Chopra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63013-religion-is-a-tool-to-bind-people-together-to-strengthen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...religion is a tool to bind people together, to strengthen their unity, but like every tool, it can be mismanaged, even used in opposition to the way it should." -- Deepak Chopra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71265-by-the-time-you-ve-finished-naming-a-thing-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2008 22:48:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Joann Sfar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71265-by-the-time-you-ve-finished-naming-a-thing-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...by the time you've finished naming a thing, it has already changed and the name you gave it no longer defines it exactly..." -- Joann Sfar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101106-my-teacher-said-once-that-every-man-faces-seven-enemies</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 09:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Osamu Tezuka]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101106-my-teacher-said-once-that-every-man-faces-seven-enemies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My teacher said once that every man faces seven enemies in his lifetime. Sickness, hunger, betrayal, envy, greed, old age, and then death..." -- Osamu Tezuka]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164038-often-we-may-feel-a-wave-of-inspiration-come-over</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2009 15:24:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Cynthia M. Bulik]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164038-often-we-may-feel-a-wave-of-inspiration-come-over]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Often, we may feel a wave of inspiration come over us, but then it passes, sometimes too quickly for us to act on it. Waiting for inspiration is like waiting for a bus that has stopped running on a particular route; you've got to find the new route if you want to catch a bus and get to where you want to go." -- Cynthia M. Bulik]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171413-a-humble-person-never-believes-he-knows-everything-or-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 21:32:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Ryan D'Agostino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171413-a-humble-person-never-believes-he-knows-everything-or-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A humble person never believes he knows everything or has done everything, and that's what keeps him working hard. He believes there is always more he can learn, that he can always do a better job next time, and that hard work is just part of getting better." -- Ryan D'Agostino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252069-it-s-always-better-to-know-more-rather-than-less-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 10:53:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Pollan, Michael]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252069-it-s-always-better-to-know-more-rather-than-less-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's always better to know more rather than less, even when that knowledge complicates your life." -- Pollan, Michael]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568266-there-is-in-fact-not-much-point-in-writing-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2012 20:31:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Anthony Burgess]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/568266-there-is-in-fact-not-much-point-in-writing-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is, in fact, not much point in writing a novel unless you can show the possibility of moral transformation, or an increase in wisdom, operating in your chief character or characters. Even trashy bestsellers show people changing. When a fictional work fails to show change, when it merely indicates that human character is set, stony, unregenerable, then you are out of field of the novel and into that of the fable or the allegory. 

- from the introduction of the 1986 Norton edition" -- Anthony Burgess]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084485-but-the-important-thing-is-that-i-don-t-do-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 16:07:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084485-but-the-important-thing-is-that-i-don-t-do-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the important thing is that I don't do anything else. I avoid social life normally associated with publishing. I don't go to the cocktail parties, I don't give or go to dinner parties. I need that time in the evening because I can do a tremendous amount of work then. And I can concentrate. When I sit down to write I never brood. I have so many other things to do, with my children and teaching, that I can't afford it..." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084514-the-russian-born-novelist-s-writing-habits-were-famously-peculiar-beginning-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 16:13:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maria add a quote by Mason Currey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1084514-the-russian-born-novelist-s-writing-habits-were-famously-peculiar-beginning-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Russian-born novelist's writing habits were famously peculiar. Beginning in 1950, he composed first drafts in pencil on ruled index cards, which he stored in long file boxes. Since Nabokov claimed, he pictured an entire novel in complete form before he began writing it, this method allowed him to compose passages out of sequence, in whatever order he pleased..." -- Mason Currey]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
