<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946643-april]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946643-april" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 11:38:42 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151215-long-experience-has-taught-me-this-about-the-status-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 11:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Galileo Galilei]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151215-long-experience-has-taught-me-this-about-the-status-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Long experience has taught me this about the status of mankind with regard to matters requiring thought: the less people know and understand about them, the more positively they attempt to argue concerning them, while on the other hand to know and understand a multitude of things renders men cautious in passing judgment upon anything new." -- Galileo Galilei]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291409-i-esteem-myself-happy-to-have-as-great-an-ally</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 11:38:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Galileo Galilei]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291409-i-esteem-myself-happy-to-have-as-great-an-ally]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I esteem myself happy to have as great an ally as [author:you|79396] in my search for truth. I will read [author:your|79396] work ... all the more willingly because I have for many years been a partisan of the [author:Copernican|3072638] view because it reveals to me the causes of many natural phenomena that are entirely incomprehensible in the light of the generally accepted hypothesis. To refute the latter I have collected many proofs, but I do not publish them, because I am deterred by the fate of our teacher [author:Copernicus|3072638] who, although he had won immortal fame with a few, was ridiculed and condemned by countless people (for very great is the number of the stupid).

{&lt;i&gt;Letter to fellow revolutionary astronomer [author:Johannes Kepelr|79396]&lt;/i&gt;}" -- Galileo Galilei]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365531-fear-not-for-they-that-be-with-us-are-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 19:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365531-fear-not-for-they-that-be-with-us-are-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fear not: for they that be with us are more than they that be with them. And Elisha prayed, and said, Lord, I pray thee, open his eyes, that he may see. And the Lord opened the eyes of the young man; and he saw: and, behold, the mountain was full of horses and chariots of fire round about Elisha&quot; (2 Kings 6:16-17).

In the gospel of Jesus Christ you have help from both sides of the veil, and you must never forget that. When disappointment and discouragement strike--and they will--you remember and never forget that if our eyes could be opened we would see horses and chariots of fire as far as the eye can see riding at reckless speed to come to our protection. They will always be there, these armies of heaven, in defense of Abraham's seed." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:11:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2285-in-each-of-us-lie-good-and-bad-light-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In each of us lie good and bad, light and dark, art and pain, choice and regret, cruelty and sacrifice. We’re each of us our own chiaroscuro, our own bit of illusion fighting to emerge into something solid, something real. We’ve got to forgive ourselves that. I must remember to forgive myself. Because there is a lot of grey to work with. No one can live in the light all the time." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35863-i-know-because-i-read-your-mind-is-not-a-cage</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35863-i-know-because-i-read-your-mind-is-not-a-cage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know because I read...Your mind is not a cage. It's a garden. And it requires cultivating." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20117-i-am-a-jumble-of-passions-misgivings-and-wants-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:13:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20117-i-am-a-jumble-of-passions-misgivings-and-wants-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a jumble of passions, misgivings, and wants. It seems that I am always in a state of wishing and rarely in a state of contentment." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207621-these-are-hard-times-the-world-hurts-we-live-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:14:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207621-these-are-hard-times-the-world-hurts-we-live-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["These are hard times.  The world hurts.  We live in fear and forget to walk with hope.  But hope has not forgotten you.  So ask it to dinner.  It's probably hungry and would appreciate the invitation." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96914-there-is-much-asked-and-only-so-much-i-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:16:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96914-there-is-much-asked-and-only-so-much-i-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is much asked and only so much I think I can or should answer, and so, in this post I would like to give a few thoughts on what seemed to be the overwhelming question: “WHY?”
And here is the best answer I can give: Because.
Because sometimes, life is damned unfair.
Because sometimes, we lose people we love and it hurts deeply.
Because sometimes, as the writer, you have to put your characters in harm’s way and be willing to go there if it is the right thing for your book, even if it grieves you to do it.
Because sometimes there aren’t really answers to our questions except for what we discover, the meaning we assign them over time.
Because acceptance is yet another of life’s “here’s a side of hurt” lessons and it is never truly acceptance unless it has cost us something to arrive there.
Why, you ask? Because, I answer.
Inadequate yet true." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276397-she-never-utters-a-sound-even-when-she-s-crying-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:16:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276397-she-never-utters-a-sound-even-when-she-s-crying-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She never utters a sound even when she's crying, and that makes me a little sad. Doesn't seem right. When you cry, people should hear you. The world should stop." -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195558-you-ve-been-assigned-an-identity-since-birth-then-you-spend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2013 18:19:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Libba Bray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195558-you-ve-been-assigned-an-identity-since-birth-then-you-spend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You’ve been assigned an identity since birth. Then you spend the rest of your life walking around in it to see if it really fits. You try on all these different selves and abandon just as many. But really it’s about dismantling all that false armor, getting down to what’s real.
	-Going Bovine
" -- Libba Bray]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
