<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946619-gilly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946619-gilly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 04:59:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 04:59:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152338-one-of-the-gunmen-in-the-room-ending-his-call</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2014 21:36:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gilly add a quote by Raoul Pantin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1152338-one-of-the-gunmen-in-the-room-ending-his-call]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the gunmen in the room, ending his call to his wife, and seeing me typing, came across and shook my hand. “You going to make a lot of money off this story!” the gunman with the Rastafarian hairstyle said. His pump-action shotgun was slung in the crook of his arm. He was smiling. “Yeah”, I said. “If I get out of here alive.” “You all right, you going to be all right”, he said, laughing. But you see me? I don’t know too much about my future right now.” “Everybody’s going to be all right,” I said. He laughed again. And reached into his back pocket and came out with a little white slip of paper in his hand. “I don’t know about me,” he said, smiling. “But if you write the story and make a lot of money, maybe you could get these things for the wife for me.” He handed me the slip of paper. On it, in block letters, was an itemized list: TV SET VIDEO SET WASHING MACHINE FRIDGE For a moment I shook my head in bewilderment, looking at that list. But he was laughing again and saying: “So if you make a lot of money off your book, get those things for the wife for me, nuh.” I said: “Sure.” I pocketed the note and walked away, flooded by nausea, thinking: so this is what he’s in it for, this young Trinidadian with the Rasta hairdo, the fake army camouflage shirt and pants tucked into his big soldier-looking black boots, with the wicked-looking shotgun crooked in his arm. A free television set. A video set. A washing machine. A fridge." -- Raoul Pantin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
