<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946715-kevin-quinley]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/946715-kevin-quinley" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 07:29:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1822-is-it-life-he-answered-i-would-rather-be-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 07:29:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Flann O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1822-is-it-life-he-answered-i-would-rather-be-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Is it life?&quot; he answered, &quot;I would rather be without it,&quot; he said, &quot;for there is queer small utility in it. You cannot eat it or drink it or smoke it in your pipe, it does not keep the rain out and it is a poor armful in the dark if you strip it and take it to bed with you after a night of porter when you are shivering with the red passion. It is a great mistake and a thing better done without, like bed-jars and foreign bacon." -- Flann O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11536-after-a-time-said-old-mathers-disregarding-me-i-mercifully</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 07:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Flann O'Brien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11536-after-a-time-said-old-mathers-disregarding-me-i-mercifully]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["After a time,&quot; said old Mathers disregarding me, &quot;I mercifully perceived the errors of my ways and the unhappy destination I would reach unless I mended them. I retired from the world in order to try to comprehend it and to find out why it becomes more unsavoury as the years accumulate on a man's body. What do you think I discovered at the end of my meditations?&quot;

I felt pleased again. He was now questioning me.

&quot;What?&quot;

&quot;That No is a better word than Yes,&quot; he replied." -- Flann O'Brien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 21:08:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84678-the-family-is-the-cradle-of-the-world-s-misinformation-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The family is the cradle of the world’s misinformation. There must be something in family life that generates factual error. Over-closeness, the noise and heat of being. Perhaps even something deeper like the need to survive. Murray says we are fragile creatures surrounded by a world of hostile facts. Facts threaten our happiness and security. The deeper we delve into things, the looser our structure may seem to become. The family process works towards sealing off the world. Small errors grow heads, fictions proliferate. I tell Murray that ignorance and confusion can’t possibly be the driving forces behind family solidarity. What an idea, what a subversion. He asks me why the strongest family units exist in the least developed societies. Not to know is a weapon of survival, he says. Magic and superstition become entrenched as the powerful orthodoxy of the clan. The family is strongest where objective reality is most likely to be misinterpreted. What a heartless theory, I say. But Murray insists it’s true." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305853-it-was-important-for-him-to-believe-that-he-d-spent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 21:08:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kevin add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/305853-it-was-important-for-him-to-believe-that-he-d-spent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was important for him to believe that he'd spent his life among people who kept missing the point." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
