<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947244-oscar]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947244-oscar" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 06:56:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43627-a-general-principle-concerning-the-gender-of-bears-has-been</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 06:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Wolfgang Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43627-a-general-principle-concerning-the-gender-of-bears-has-been]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A general principle concerning the gender of bears has been established years ago by  bear supervisor König from Bern, after over thirty years of observation. It allows for predictions and states, in short, that when a female bear bears three cubs, and they aren't all male or female, it will invariably be either two males and a female, or two females and a male." -- Wolfgang Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4419-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 06:59:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4419-science-is-not-only-compatible-with-spirituality-it-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is not only compatible with spirituality; it is a profound source of spirituality." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 13:43:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fantasy is escapist, and that is its glory. If a soldier is imprisioned by the enemy, don't we consider it his duty to escape?. . .If we value the freedom of mind and soul, if we're partisans of liberty, then it's our plain duty to escape, and to take as many people with us as we can!" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45999-the-inner-fire-is-the-most-important-thing-mankind-possesses</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 13:51:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Edith Södergran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45999-the-inner-fire-is-the-most-important-thing-mankind-possesses]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inner fire is the most important thing mankind possesses." -- Edith Södergran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12588-death-therefore-the-most-awful-of-evils-is-nothing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 13:52:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Epicurus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12588-death-therefore-the-most-awful-of-evils-is-nothing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Death, therefore, the most awful of evils, is nothing to us, seeing that, when we are, death is not come, and, when death is come, we are not." -- Epicurus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110506-hope-and-memory-have-one-daughter-and-her-name-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 23:52:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by William Butler Yeats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110506-hope-and-memory-have-one-daughter-and-her-name-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope and Memory have one daughter and her name is Art, and she has built her dwelling far from the desperate field where men hang out their garments upon forked boughs to be banners of battle. O beloved daughter of Hope and Memory, be with me for a while." -- William Butler Yeats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128255-when-i-look-up-at-the-starry-heavens-at-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 12:00:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by John Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128255-when-i-look-up-at-the-starry-heavens-at-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I look up at the starry heavens at night and reflect upon what it is that I really see there, I am constrained to say, 'There is no God.' The mind staggers in its attempt to grasp the idea of a being that could do that. It is futile to attempt it. It is not the works of some God that I see there. I am face to face with a power that baffles speech. I see no lineaments of personality, no human traits, but an energy upon whose currents solar systems are but bubbles. In the presence of it man and the race of man are less than motes in the air. I doubt if any mind can expand its conception of God sufficiently to meet the astounding disclosures of modern science. It is easier to say there is no God. The universe is so &lt;i&gt;un&lt;/i&gt;human, that is, it goes its way with so little thought of man. He is but an incident, not an end. We must adjust our notions to the discovery that things are not shaped to him, but that he is shaped to them. The air was not made for his lungs, but he has lungs because there is air; the light was not created for his eye, but he has eyes because there is light. All the forces of nature are going their own way; man avails himself of them, or catches a ride as best he can. If he keeps his seat he prospers; if he misses his hold and falls he is crushed. Mankind used to think that the dews and rains were sent for their benefit, and the church still encourages this idea by praying for rain in times of drought, but the notion is nearly dissipated." -- John Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138689-if-you-know-that-i-am-an-unbeliever-then-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 01:56:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Pier Paolo Pasolini]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138689-if-you-know-that-i-am-an-unbeliever-then-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you know that I am an unbeliever, then you know me better than I do myself. I may be an unbeliever, but I am an unbeliever who has a nostalgia for a belief." -- Pier Paolo Pasolini]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131300-you-could-just-as-well-say-that-an-agnostic-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 00:31:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131300-you-could-just-as-well-say-that-an-agnostic-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You could just as well say that an agnostic is a deeply religious person with at least a rudimentary knowledge of human fallibility." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193005-it-does-not-follow-because-our-ancestors-made-so-many</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 02:15:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193005-it-does-not-follow-because-our-ancestors-made-so-many]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does not follow, because our ancestors made so many errors of fact and mixed them with their religion, that we should  therefore leave off being religious at all. By being religious we establish ourselves in possession of ultimate reality at the only points at which reality is given us to guard. Our responsible concern is with our private destiny, after all." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15140-i-d-like-to-go-by-climbing-a-birch-tree-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2010 13:56:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15140-i-d-like-to-go-by-climbing-a-birch-tree-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd like to go by climbing a birch tree~
And climb black branches up a snow-white trunk
Toward heaven, till the tree could bear no more,
But dipped its top and set me down again.
That would be good both going and coming back.
One could do worse than be a swinger of birches." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379502-our-intelligence-cannot-wall-itself-up-alive-like-a-pupa</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 01:18:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by William James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/379502-our-intelligence-cannot-wall-itself-up-alive-like-a-pupa]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our intelligence cannot wall itself up alive, like a pupa in a chrysalis. It must at any cost keep on speaking terms with the universe that engendered it." -- William James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429506-the-propensity-to-excessive-simplification-is-indeed-natural-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 01:17:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by James George Frazer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/429506-the-propensity-to-excessive-simplification-is-indeed-natural-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The propensity to excessive simplification is indeed natural to the mind of man, since it is only by abstraction and generalisation, which necessarily imply the neglect of a multitude of particulars, that he can stretch his puny faculties so as to embrace a minute portion of the illimitable vastness of the universe. But if the propensity is natural and even inevitable, it is nevertheless fraught with peril, since it is apt to narrow and falsify our conception of any subject under investigation. To correct it partially - for to correct it wholly would require an infinite intelligence - we must endeavour to broaden our views by taking account of a wide range of facts and possibilities; and when we have done so to the utmost of our power, we must still remember that from the very nature of things our ideas fall immeasurably short of the reality." -- James George Frazer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51664-the-intelligence-of-that-creature-known-as-a-crowd-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 05:26:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Oscar add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51664-the-intelligence-of-that-creature-known-as-a-crowd-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The intelligence of that creature known as a crowd is the square root of the number of people in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
