<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947528-vikki]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947528-vikki" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:26:11 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211000-i-like-people-too-much-or-not-at-all-i-ve</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:26:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/211000-i-like-people-too-much-or-not-at-all-i-ve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like people too much or not at all. I've got to go down deep, to fall into people, to really know them." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154775-if-you-care-about-what-others-think-of-you-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:59:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by James Frey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/154775-if-you-care-about-what-others-think-of-you-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you care about what others think of you, then you will always be their slave." -- James Frey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2945-accept-who-you-are-and-revel-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:59:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2945-accept-who-you-are-and-revel-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Accept who you are; and revel in it." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43519-things-don-t-go-wrong-and-break-your-heart-so-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:59:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Charles Jones]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43519-things-don-t-go-wrong-and-break-your-heart-so-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things don't go wrong and break your heart so you can become bitter and give up. They happen to break you down and build you up so you can be all that you were intended to be." -- Charles Jones]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9221-that-as-long-as-we-are-being-remembered-we-remain</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 13:39:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9221-that-as-long-as-we-are-being-remembered-we-remain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["that as long as we are being remembered, we remain alive." -- Carlos Ruiz Zafon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367497-it-s-easy-to-take-off-your-clothes-and-have-sex</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 10:45:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Rob Bell ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/367497-it-s-easy-to-take-off-your-clothes-and-have-sex]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s easy to take off your clothes and have sex. People do it all the time. But opening up your soul to someone, letting them into your spirit, thoughts, fears, future, hopes, dreams… that is being naked." -- Rob Bell ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66606-sure-we-d-faced-some-things-as-children-that-a-lot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 10:55:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66606-sure-we-d-faced-some-things-as-children-that-a-lot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure, we'd faced some things as children that a lot of kids don't. Sure, Justin had qualified for his Junior de Sade Badge in his teaching methods for dealing with pain. We still hadn't learned, though, that growing up is all about getting hurt. And then getting over it. You hurt. You recover. You move on. Odds are pretty good you're just going to get hurt again. But each time, you learn something.

Each time, you come out of it a little stronger, and at some point you realize that there are more flavors of pain than coffee. There's the little empty pain of leaving something behind - gradutaing, taking the next step forward, walking out of something familiar and safe into the unknown. There's the big, whirling pain of life upending all of your plans and expecations. There's the sharp little pains of failure, and the more obscure aches of successes that didn't give you what you thought they would. There are the vicious, stabbing pains of hopes being torn up. The sweet little pains of finding others, giving them your love, and taking joy in their life they grow and learn. There's the steady pain of empathy that you shrug off so you can stand beside a wounded friend and help them bear their burdens. 

And if you're very, very lucky, there are a very few blazing hot little pains you feel when you realized that you are standing in a moment of utter perfection, an instant of triumph, or happiness, or mirth which at the same time cannot possibly last - and yet will remain with you for life.

Everyone is down on pain, because they forget something important about it: Pain is for the living. Only the dead don't feel it.

Pain is a part of life. Sometimes it's a big part, and sometimes it isn't, but either way, it's a part of the big puzzle, the deep music, the great game. Pain does two things: It teaches you, tells you that you're alive. Then it passes away and leaves you changed. It leaves you wiser, sometimes. Sometimes it leaves you stronger. Either way, pain leaves its mark, and everything important that will ever happen to you in life is going to involve it in one degree or another." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175566-this-is-what-you-do-if-you-feel-low-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 11:54:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Hobson Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175566-this-is-what-you-do-if-you-feel-low-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what you do. If you feel low, you stand tall. You mess up, you move on. You want to try something, try it, and if it was a stupid thing to try, you look it in the eye. There's no turning back. You apologize if you're sorry, but know that the nimblest, strongest hands can't rebuild a bridge out of embers, so cut new wood. Start from scratch. You love with your whole heart. If you're jealous, talk yourself from the ledge. If you can't talk yourself down from the ledge, have a good time up there, looking down on the world. If you have to lie to make everything true again, lie like you mean it. If you find yourself in a cage, reach out through the bars for the key, unlock the door, and run away. If running away gets dangerous, run home. If home doesn't mean what it used to mean, decide what home will be in the future. If your best friend says she doesn't trust you, hold her jaw in your hand until it hurts, and make her face you. Thats all it takes. If you think you love a guy, see how his hand looks in yours, thats all it takes. If you get exiled into a new land, then go discover it. And if you feel like you're drowning, go swimming." -- Hobson Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 12:21:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/182896-i-no-longer-believed-in-the-idea-of-soul-mates]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I no longer believed in the idea of soul mates, or love at first sight.  But I was beginning to believe that a very few times in your life, if you were lucky, you might meet someone who was exactly right for you.  Not because he was perfect, or because you were, but because your combined flaws were arranged in a way that allowed two separate beings to hinge together." -- Lisa Kleypas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218503-i-think-i-made-you-up-inside-my-head</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 12:25:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218503-i-think-i-made-you-up-inside-my-head]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I made you up inside my head." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48274-i-thought-we-were-a-real-love-relationship-i-did</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 13:43:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48274-i-thought-we-were-a-real-love-relationship-i-did]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought we were a real love relationship. I did. I was very invested in love, but it was just this long long sex thing that could end at any moment because after all, it's just about getting off. Almost all the time, you tell yourself you're loving somebody when you're just using them. This only looks like love." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128439-some-friends-don-t-understand-this-they-don-t-understand-how-desperate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 13:45:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128439-some-friends-don-t-understand-this-they-don-t-understand-how-desperate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some friends don't understand this. They don't understand how desperate I am to have someone say, I love you and I support you just the way you are because you're wonderful just the way you are. They don't understand that I can't remember anyone ever saying that to me. I am so demanding and difficult for my friends because I want to crumble and fall apart before them so that they will love me even though I am no fun, lying in bed, crying all the time, not moving. Depression is all about If you loved me you would." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150492-be-strong-live-honorably-and-with-dignity-when-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 14:17:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by James Frey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150492-be-strong-live-honorably-and-with-dignity-when-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be strong. Live honorably and with dignity. When you don't think you can, hold on." -- James Frey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163847-when-i-see-you-the-world-stops-it-stops-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 14:17:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by James Frey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163847-when-i-see-you-the-world-stops-it-stops-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I see you, the World stops. It stops and all that exists for me is you and my eyes staring at you. There's nothing else. No noise, no other people, no thoughts or worries, no yesterday, no tomorrow. The World just stops, and it is a beautiful place, and there is only you." -- James Frey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142274-people-are-afraid-of-themselves-of-their-own-reality-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 11:57:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Jim Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142274-people-are-afraid-of-themselves-of-their-own-reality-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People are afraid of themselves, of their own reality; their feelings most of all. People talk about how great love is, but that’s bullshit. Love hurts. Feelings are disturbing. People are taught that pain is evil and dangerous. How can they deal with love if they’re afraid to feel? Pain is meant to wake us up. People try to hide their pain. But they’re wrong. Pain is something to carry, like a radio. You feel your strength in the experience of pain. It’s all in how you carry it. That’s what matters. Pain is a feeling. Your feelings are a part of you. Your own reality. If you feel ashamed of them, and hide them, you’re letting society destroy your reality. You should stand up for your right to feel your pain." -- Jim Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14121-people-with-courage-and-character-always-seem-sinister-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 11:15:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14121-people-with-courage-and-character-always-seem-sinister-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People with courage and character always seem sinister to the rest." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54666-if-i-know-what-love-is-it-is-because-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 11:15:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54666-if-i-know-what-love-is-it-is-because-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I know what love is, it is because of you." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123339-when-you-like-someone-you-like-them-in-spite-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 11:16:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Hermann Hesse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123339-when-you-like-someone-you-like-them-in-spite-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you like someone, you like them in spite of their faults. When you love someone, you love them with their faults." -- Hermann Hesse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225108-while-i-can-t-have-you-i-long-for-you-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 12:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225108-while-i-can-t-have-you-i-long-for-you-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["While I can’t have you, I long for you. I am the kind of person who would miss a train or a plane to meet you for coffee. I’d take a taxi across town to see you for ten minutes. I’d wait outside all night if I thought you would open the door in the morning. If you call me and say ‘Will you…’ my answer is ‘Yes’, before your sentence is out. I spin worlds where we could be together. I dream you. For me, imagination and desire are very close." -- Jeanette Winterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25930-style-is-knowing-who-you-are-what-you-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 12:38:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Gore Vidal]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25930-style-is-knowing-who-you-are-what-you-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn." -- Gore Vidal]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40187-if-all-the-world-s-a-stage-i-want-to-operate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 14:35:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Vikki add a quote by Paul Beatty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40187-if-all-the-world-s-a-stage-i-want-to-operate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all the world's a stage, I want to operate the trap door." -- Paul Beatty]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
