<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947944-snwleop]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/947944-snwleop" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:50:42 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:50:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5251-sometimes-you-wake-up-sometimes-the-fall-kills-you-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes you wake up. Sometimes the fall kills you. And sometimes, when you fall, you fly." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:50:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1344-only-the-phoenix-rises-and-does-not-descend-and-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the phoenix rises and does not descend. And everything changes. And nothing is truly lost." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:50:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7391-most-books-on-witchcraft-will-tell-you-that-witches-work</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:50:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7391-most-books-on-witchcraft-will-tell-you-that-witches-work]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most books on witchcraft will tell you that witches work naked.  This is because most books on witchcraft were written by men." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:51:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17764-fairy-tales-are-more-than-true-not-because-they-tell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tales are more than true: not because they tell us that dragons exist, but because they tell us that dragons can be beaten." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:51:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16261-life-is-a-disease-sexually-transmitted-and-invariably-fatal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a disease: sexually transmitted, and invariably fatal." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8298-so-what-i-want-to-know-is-why-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:52:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8298-so-what-i-want-to-know-is-why-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So what I want to know is why it is that I can no longer find you, in my mind. You are still there, just, but you are there like a ghost, a will o' the wisp. Not long ago you burned--your heart burned--in my mind like silver fire. But after that night in the inn it became patchy and dim, and now it is not there at all.&quot;

&quot;Could it be that the heart that you seek is no longer my own? I have given my heart to another.&quot;

&quot;The boy? The one in the inn? With the unicorn?&quot;

&quot;Yes.&quot;

&quot;You should have let me take it back then, for my sisters and me. We could have been young again, well into the next age of the world. Your boy will break it, or waste it, or lose it. They all do.&quot;

&quot;Nonetheless, he has my heart. I hope your sisters will not be too hard on you, when you return to them without it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7394-he-couldn-t-see-why-people-made-such-a-fuss-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:53:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7394-he-couldn-t-see-why-people-made-such-a-fuss-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He couldn’t see why people made such a fuss about people eating their silly old fruit anyway, but life would be a lot less fun if they didn’t.  And there was never an apple, in Adam’s opinion, that wasn’t worth the trouble you got into for eating it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:06:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7393-nothin-wrong-with-witchfinding-i-d-like-to-be-a-witchfinder</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:55:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7393-nothin-wrong-with-witchfinding-i-d-like-to-be-a-witchfinder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothin’ wrong with witchfinding.  I’d like to be a witchfinder.  It’s just, well, you’ve got to take it in turns.  Today we’ll go out witchfinding, an’ tomorrow we could hide, an’ it’d be the witches’ turn to find US.  " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27954-you-re-hell-s-angels-then-what-chapter-are-you-from-revelations</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:57:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27954-you-re-hell-s-angels-then-what-chapter-are-you-from-revelations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're Hell's Angels, then? What chapter are you from?'

'REVELATIONS. CHAPTER SIX." -- Neil Gaiman &amp; Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28658-beware-of-doors</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2008 12:57:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28658-beware-of-doors]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beware of Doors." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:18:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:19:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2580-never-put-off-till-tomorrow-what-may-be-done-day]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never put off till tomorrow what may be done day after tomorrow just as well&quot;. 

From: &quot;More Maxims of Mark" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:19:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Paul   Terry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1958-whenever-i-feel-the-need-to-exercise-i-lie-down]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away." -- Paul   Terry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:20:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4123-go-to-heaven-for-the-climate-and-hell-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Go to heaven for the climate and hell for the company." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5787-reader-suppose-you-were-an-idiot-and-suppose-you-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:20:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by mark twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5787-reader-suppose-you-were-an-idiot-and-suppose-you-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reader, suppose you were an idiot. And suppose you were a member of Congress. But I repeat myself." -- mark twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5740-you-believe-in-a-book-that-has-talking-animals-wizards</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 12:22:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5740-you-believe-in-a-book-that-has-talking-animals-wizards]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You believe in a book that has talking animals, wizards, witches, demons, sticks turning into snakes, burning bushes, food falling from the sky, people walking on water, and all sorts of magical, absurd and primitive stories, and you say that we are the ones that need help?" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14896-on-bad-days-i-talk-to-death-constantly-not-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:43:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Tori Amos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14896-on-bad-days-i-talk-to-death-constantly-not-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On bad days I talk to Death constantly, not about suicide because honestly that's not dramatic enough. Most of us love the stage and suicide is definitely your last performance and being addicted to the stage, suicide was never an option - plus people get to look you over and stare at your fatty bits and you can't cross your legs to give that flattering thigh angle and that's depressing. So we talk. She says things no one else seems to come up with, like let's have a hotdog and then it's like nothing's impossible.

She told me once there is a part of her in everyone, though Neil believes I'm more Delirium than Tori, and Death taught me to accept that, you know, wear your butterflies with pride. And when I do accept that, I know Death is somewhere inside of me. She was the kind of girl all the girls wanted to be, I believe, because of her acceptance of &quot;what is.&quot; She keeps reminding me there is change in the &quot;what is&quot; but change cannot be made till you accept the &quot;what is." -- Tori Amos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14137-get-off-the-cross-we-need-the-wood</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:43:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Tori Amos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14137-get-off-the-cross-we-need-the-wood]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Get off the cross, we need the wood." -- Tori Amos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27677-i-don-t-see-myself-as-weird-i-just-see-myself</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:43:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Tori Amos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27677-i-don-t-see-myself-as-weird-i-just-see-myself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't see myself as weird, I just see myself as honest." -- Tori Amos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14897-and-if-there-is-a-way-to-find-you-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:43:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Tori Amos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14897-and-if-there-is-a-way-to-find-you-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["and if there is a way to find you, I will find you. but will you find me if Neil makes me a tree" -- Tori Amos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8094-there-must-be-quite-a-few-things-that-a-hot</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 05:36:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8094-there-must-be-quite-a-few-things-that-a-hot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There must be quite a few things that a hot bath won't cure, but I don't know many of them." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/907-when-i-was-a-child-adults-would-tell-me-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was a child, adults would tell me not to make things up, warning me of what would happen if I did. As far as I can tell so far, it seems to involve lots of foreign travel and not having to get up too early in the morning." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21831-tomorrow-may-be-hell-but-today-was-a-good-writing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21831-tomorrow-may-be-hell-but-today-was-a-good-writing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tomorrow may be hell, but today was a good writing day, and on the good writing days nothing else matters." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14442-things-need-not-have-happened-to-be-true-tales-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Things need not have happened to be true. Tales and dreams are the shadow-truths that will endure when mere facts are dust and ashes, and forgot." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53787-what-i-say-is-a-town-isn-t-a-town-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I say is, a town isn't a town without a bookstore. It may call itself a town, but unless it's got a bookstore it knows it's not fooling a soul." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:14:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64407-may-your-coming-year-be-filled-with-magic-and-dreams]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["May your coming year be filled with magic and dreams and good madness. I hope you read some fine books and kiss someone who thinks you're wonderful, and don't forget to make some art -- write or draw or build or sing or live as only you can. And I hope, somewhere in the next year, you surprise yourself." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2009 21:15:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Snwleop add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45842-people-think-dreams-aren-t-real-just-because-they-aren-t-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think dreams aren't real just because they aren't made of matter, of particles. Dreams are real. But they are made of viewpoints, of images, of memories and puns and lost hopes." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
