<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948042-mary]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948042-mary" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:15:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:15:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:15:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66625-when-i-get-lonely-these-days-i-think-so-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I get lonely these days, I think: So BE lonely, Liz. Learn your way around loneliness. Make a map of it. Sit with it, for once in your life. Welcome to the human experience. But never again use another person's body or emotions as a scratching post for your own unfulfilled yearnings." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55141-i-hated-labels-anyway-people-didn-t-fit-in-slots--prostitute-housewife</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:16:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55141-i-hated-labels-anyway-people-didn-t-fit-in-slots--prostitute-housewife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hated labels anyway. People didn't fit in slots--prostitute, housewife, saint--like sorting the mail. We were so mutable, fluid with fear and desire, ideals and angles, changeable as water." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29305-dr-armonson-stitched-up-her-wrist-wounds-within-five-minutes</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:17:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29305-dr-armonson-stitched-up-her-wrist-wounds-within-five-minutes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dr. Armonson stitched up her wrist wounds. Within five minutes of the transfusion he declared her out of danger. Chucking her under the chin, he said, &quot;What are you doing here, honey? You're not even old enough to know how bad life gets.&quot;

And it was then Cecilia gave orally what was to be her only form of suicide note, and a useless one at that, because she was going to live: &quot;Obviously, Doctor,&quot; she said, &quot;you've never been a thirteen-year-old girl." -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 09:17:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5797-the-person-be-it-gentleman-or-lady-who-has-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The person, be it gentleman or lady, who has not pleasure in a good novel, must be intolerably stupid." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11469-that-s-the-thing-about-depression-a-human-being-can-survive</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 19:34:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11469-that-s-the-thing-about-depression-a-human-being-can-survive]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's the thing about depression: A human being can survive almost anything, as long as she sees the end in sight.  But depression is so insidious, and it compounds daily, that it's impossible to ever see the end." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152646-i-m-the-girl-who-is-lost-in-space-the-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2012 19:34:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152646-i-m-the-girl-who-is-lost-in-space-the-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm the girl who is lost in space, the girl who is disappearing always, forever fading away and receding farther and farther into the background. Just like the Cheshire cat, someday I will suddenly leave, but the artificial warmth of my smile, that phony, clownish curve, the kind you see on miserably sad people and villains in Disney movies, will remain behind as an ironic remnant. I am the girl you see in the photograph from some party someplace or some picnic in the park, the one who is in fact soon to be gone. When you look at the picture again, I want to assure you, I will no longer be there. I will be erased from history, like a traitor in the Soviet Union. Because with every day that goes by, I feel myself becoming more and more invisible..." -- Elizabeth Wurtzel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 09:44:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78158-i-can-never-read-all-the-books-i-want-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can never read all the books I want; I can never be all the people I want and live all the lives I want. I can never train myself in all the skills I want. And why do I want? I want to live and feel all the shades, tones and variations of mental and physical experience possible in life. And I am horribly limited." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:38:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2058-there-is-no-friend-as-loyal-as-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no friend as loyal as a book." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252045-it-was-not-the-feeling-of-completeness-i-so-needed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 06:48:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mary add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252045-it-was-not-the-feeling-of-completeness-i-so-needed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was not the feeling of completeness I so needed, but the feeling of not being empty." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
