<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948651-aishe]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948651-aishe" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 12:36:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 12:36:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aishe add a quote by Ira Glass]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/309485-nobody-tells-this-to-people-who-are-beginners-i-wish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody tells this to people who are beginners, I wish someone told me. All of us who do creative work, we get into it because we have good taste. But there is this gap. For the first couple years you make stuff, it’s just not that good. It’s trying to be good, it has potential, but it’s not. But your taste, the thing that got you into the game, is still killer. And your taste is why your work disappoints you. A lot of people never get past this phase, they quit. Most people I know who do interesting, creative work went through years of this. We know our work doesn’t have this special thing that we want it to have. We all go through this. And if you are just starting out or you are still in this phase, you gotta know its normal and the most important thing you can do is do a lot of work. Put yourself on a deadline so that every week you will finish one story. It is only by going through a volume of work that you will close that gap, and your work will be as good as your ambitions. And I took longer to figure out how to do this than anyone I’ve ever met. It’s gonna take awhile. It’s normal to take awhile. You’ve just gotta fight your way through." -- Ira Glass]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36952-there-are-books-full-of-great-writing-that-don-t-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 13:18:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aishe add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36952-there-are-books-full-of-great-writing-that-don-t-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are books full of great writing that don't have very good stories. Read sometimes for the story... don't be like the book-snobs who won't do that. Read sometimes for the words--the language. Don't be like the play-it-safers who won't do that. But when you find a book that has both a good story and good words, treasure that book." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191394-to-sew-is-to-pray-men-don-t-understand-this-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:53:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aishe add a quote by Louise Erdrich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191394-to-sew-is-to-pray-men-don-t-understand-this-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To sew is to pray. Men don't understand this. They see the whole but they don't see the stitches. They don't see the speech of the creator in the work of the needle. We mend. We women turn things inside out and set things right. We salvage what we can of human garments and piece the rest into blankets. Sometimes our stitches stutter and slow. Only a woman's eyes can tell. Other times, the tension in the stitches might be too tight because of tears, but only we know what emotion went into the making. Only women can hear the prayer." -- Louise Erdrich]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
