<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948616-aileen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/948616-aileen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 10:01:29 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beet is the most intense of vegetables. The radish, admittedly, is more feverish, but the fire of the radish is a cold fire, the fire of discontent not of passion. Tomatoes are lusty enough, yet there runs through tomatoes an undercurrent of frivolity. Beets are deadly serious.

Slavic peoples get their physical characteristics from potatoes, their smoldering inquietude from radishes, their seriousness from beets.

The beet is the melancholy vegetable, the one most willing to suffer. You can't squeeze blood out of a turnip...

The beet is the murderer returned to the scene of the crime. The beet is what happens when the cherry finishes with the carrot. The beet is the ancient ancestor of the autumn moon, bearded, buried, all but fossilized; the dark green sails of the grounded moon-boat stitched with veins of primordial plasma; the kite string that once connected the moon to the Earth now a muddy whisker drilling desperately for rubies.

The beet was Rasputin's favorite vegetable. You could see it in his eyes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472923-strong-minds-discuss-ideas-average-minds-discuss-events-weak-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 10:54:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Socrates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472923-strong-minds-discuss-ideas-average-minds-discuss-events-weak-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Strong minds discuss ideas, average minds discuss events, weak minds discuss people." -- Socrates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276642-people-always-did-like-to-talk-didn-t-they-that-s-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2013 20:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aileen add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276642-people-always-did-like-to-talk-didn-t-they-that-s-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People always did like to talk, didn't they? That's why I call myself a witch now: the Wicked Witch of the West, if you want the full glory of it. As long as people are going to call you a lunatic anyway, why not get the benefit of it? It liberates you from convention." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
