<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949159-linda-b]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949159-linda-b" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:43:12 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218698-why-do-men-want-to-kill-the-bodies-of-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:43:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218698-why-do-men-want-to-kill-the-bodies-of-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why do men want to kill the bodies of other men? Women don't want to kill the bodies of other women, by and large. As far as we know.

Here are some traditional reasons: Loot. Territory. Lust for power. Hormones. Adrenaline high. Rage. God. Flag. Honor. Righteous anger. Revenge. Oppression. Slavery. Starvation. Defense of one's life. Love; or, a desire to protect the women and children. From what? From the bodies of other men.

What men are most afraid of is not lions, not snakes, not the dark, not women. Not any more. What men are most afraid of is the body of another man.

Men's bodies are the most dangerous thing on earth." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218699-but-we-still-find-the-world-astounding-we-can-t-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:43:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218699-but-we-still-find-the-world-astounding-we-can-t-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But we still find the world astounding, we can't get enough of it; even as it shrivels, even as its many lights flicker and are extinguished (the tigers, the leopard frogs, the plunging dolphin flukes), flicker and are extinguished, by us, by us, we gaze and gaze. Where do you draw the line, between love and greed? We never did know, we always wanted more. We want to take it all in, for one last time, we want to eat the world with our eyes." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74559-we-still-think-of-a-powerful-man-as-a-born</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2010 07:43:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Margaret Atwood]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74559-we-still-think-of-a-powerful-man-as-a-born]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We still think of a powerful man as a born leader and a powerful woman as an anomaly." -- Margaret Atwood]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4850-a-human-being-is-primarily-a-bag-for-putting-food</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 23:01:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4850-a-human-being-is-primarily-a-bag-for-putting-food]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A human being is primarily a bag for putting food into; the other functions and faculties may be more godlike, but in point of time they come afterwards. A man dies and is buried, and all his words and actions are forgotten, but the food he has eaten lives after him in the sound or rotten bones of his children. I think it could be plausibly argued that changes of diet are more important than changes of dynasty or even of religion....Yet it is curious how seldom the all-importance of food is recognized. You see statues everywhere to politicians, poets, bishops, but none to cooks or bacon-curers or market gardeners." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150686-it-is-worth-saying-something-about-the-social-position-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 23:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150686-it-is-worth-saying-something-about-the-social-position-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is worth saying something about the social position of beggars, for when one has consorted with them, and found that they are ordinary human beings, one cannot help being struck by the curious attitude that society takes towards them. People seem to feel that there is some essential difference between beggars and ordinary 'working' men. They are a race apart--outcasts, like criminals and prostitutes. Working men 'work', beggars do not 'work'; they are parasites, worthless in their very nature. It is taken for granted that a beggar does not 'earn' his living, as a bricklayer or a literary critic 'earns' his. He is a mere social excrescence, tolerated because we live in a humane age, but essentially despicable.

Yet if one looks closely one sees that there is no ESSENTIAL difference between a beggar's livelihood and that of numberless respectable people. Beggars do not work, it is said; but, then, what is WORK? A navvy works by swinging a pick. An accountant works by adding up figures. A beggar works by standing out of doors in all weathers and getting varicose veins, chronic bronchitis, etc. It is a trade like any other; quite useless, of course--but, then, many reputable trades are quite useless. And as a social type a beggar compares well with scores of others. He is honest compared with the sellers of most patent medicines, high-minded compared with a Sunday newspaper proprietor, amiable compared with a hire-purchase tout--in short, a parasite, but a fairly harmless parasite. He seldom extracts more than a bare living from the community, and, what should justify him according to our ethical ideas, he pays for it over and over in suffering. I do not think there is anything about a beggar that sets him in a different class from other people, or gives most modern men the right to despise him.

Then the question arises, Why are beggars despised?--for they are despised, universally. I believe it is for the simple reason that they fail to earn a decent living. In practice nobody cares whether work is useful or useless, productive or parasitic; the sole thing demanded is that it shall be profitable. In all the modem talk about energy, efficiency, social service and the rest of it, what meaning is there except 'Get money, get it legally, and get a lot of it'? Money has become the grand test of virtue. By this test beggars fail, and for this they are despised. If one could earn even ten pounds a week at begging, it would become a respectable profession immediately. A beggar, looked at realistically, is simply a businessman, getting his living, like other businessmen, in the way that comes to hand. He has not, more than most modem people, sold his honour; he has merely made the mistake of choosing a trade at which it is impossible to grow rich." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138123-like-all-stories-of-creators-who-bring-life-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2011 20:26:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Salvador Plascencia]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138123-like-all-stories-of-creators-who-bring-life-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like all stories of creators who bring life from the dead, his story began with a struggling butcher, who chased a gray cat, caught it, took off its studded collar, and slit its throat." -- Salvador Plascencia]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35455-so-long-as-i-remain-alive-and-well-i-shall</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 18:09:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35455-so-long-as-i-remain-alive-and-well-i-shall]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So long as I remain alive and well I shall continue to feel strongly about prose style, to love the surface of the earth, and to take a pleasure in solid objects and scraps of useless information." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205987-just-how-destructive-does-a-culinary-preference-have-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2014 20:40:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205987-just-how-destructive-does-a-culinary-preference-have-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just how destructive does a culinary preference have to be before we decide to eat something else? If contributing to the suffering of billions of animals that live miserable lives and (quite often) die in horrific ways isn't motivating, what would be? If being the number one contributor to the most serious threat facing the planet (global warming) isn't enough, what is? And if you are tempted to put off these questions of conscience, to say not now, then when?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
