<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949295-emily]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949295-emily" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 09:00:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 09:00:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248986-a-compassion-swirled-form-nowhere-in-the-high-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 12:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kim Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248986-a-compassion-swirled-form-nowhere-in-the-high-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A compassion swirled form nowhere in the high I was lost in. She needed me. She needed me to accept her for what she was. And when I realized that I had it within myself to give her at least this small part of me, the last of my fear melted away. " -- Kim Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248987-i-tried-to-breathe-failing-i-clutched-her-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 12:21:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kim Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248987-i-tried-to-breathe-failing-i-clutched-her-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tried to breathe, failing. I clutched her to me, tears slipping from under my closed eyes. It was as if her soul was liquid fire and I could feel her aura, swirling about mine. She was taking my aura. But I wanted to give it to her, to cat her in a small part of me and protect her. Her needs made her so fragile. " -- Kim Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95158-fate-does-not-seek-our-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 16:49:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95158-fate-does-not-seek-our-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fate does not seek our consent." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97279-the-wizard-s-first-rule-people-are-stupid-given-proper-motivation</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2011 06:57:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97279-the-wizard-s-first-rule-people-are-stupid-given-proper-motivation]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Wizard's First Rule: People are stupid; given proper motivation almost anyone will believe almost anything." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76667-nothing-is-ever-easy</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 16:50:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76667-nothing-is-ever-easy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing is ever easy" -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96132-i-am-who-i-am-no-more-no-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2009 16:51:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96132-i-am-who-i-am-no-more-no-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am who I am; no more, no less." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136155-by-my-love-for-you-i-realized-i-loved-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 06:40:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136155-by-my-love-for-you-i-realized-i-loved-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By my love for you. I realized I loved you more than life itself, and I would rather give myself into your power than live without you. Nothing the magic could do to me could be worse than living without you. I was willing to give it all over to you. I offered the power everything I have. All of my love for you. Once I realized how much I loved you, I was willing to be yours on any terms. I understood that there could be nothing for the magic to harm. I’m already devoted to you; it didn’t need to change me. I was protected, because I have already been untouched by your love. I had utter faith that you felt the same, and had no fear of what would happen. Had I had any doubt, the magic would have latched on to that crack and taken me, but I had no doubt. My love for you is smooth and seamless. My love for you protected me from the magic." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95132-love-is-a-passion-for-life-shared-with-another-person</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2011 06:40:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95132-love-is-a-passion-for-life-shared-with-another-person]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a passion for life shared with another person. You fall in love with a person who you think is wonderful. It's your deepest appreciation of the value of that individual, and that individual is a reflection of what you value most in life. Love, for sound reasons, can be one of life's greatest rewards." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151390-she-understood-his-eyes-colder-than-winter-s-heart-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 20:39:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Robert Jordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151390-she-understood-his-eyes-colder-than-winter-s-heart-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She understood his eyes, colder than winter's heart. A man who knew he was dead and couldn't make himself care; you are spared that. Mashiara. His lost love." -- Robert Jordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151391-he-pushed-a-hand-inside-the-blankets-to-feel-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 20:42:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Robert Jordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/151391-he-pushed-a-hand-inside-the-blankets-to-feel-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He pushed a hand inside the blankets to feel her cheek, her shoulder. Trickles of water ran across her face as her hair melted. He was cold, but she was ice. She needed every scrap of warmth he could find for her...His sense of touch, enhanced by the Void and saidin, soaked in the feel of her. Her skin made silt feel rough." -- Robert Jordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152208-alone-he-must-bear-the-weight-of-a-sin-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2009 21:50:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Terry Goodkind]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152208-alone-he-must-bear-the-weight-of-a-sin-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Alone, he must bear the weight of a sin he dare not confess to the one person he loves…and has lost." -- Terry Goodkind]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:02:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1776-remember-if-the-time-should-come-when-you-have-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember, if the time should come when you have to make a choice between what is right and what is easy, remember what happened to a boy who was good, and kind, and brave, because he strayed across the path of Lord Voldemort.  Remember Cedric Diggory." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:02:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12415-it-is-our-choices-harry-that-show-what-we-truly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is our choices, Harry, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:02:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54339-i-solemnly-swear-that-i-am-up-to-no-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I solemnly swear that I am up to no good." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100169-yeah-ear-ear-said-george-with-half-a-glance-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100169-yeah-ear-ear-said-george-with-half-a-glance-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yeah 'ear 'ear,&quot; said George, with half a glance at Fred, the corner of whose mouth twitched." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147274-i-love-you-he-whispered-and-that-was-the-moment</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147274-i-love-you-he-whispered-and-that-was-the-moment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,&quot; he whispered, and that was the moment he knew what he was going to do. When you loved someone, you put their needs before your own. No matter how inconceivable those needs were; no matter how fucked up; no matter how much it made you feel like you were ripping yourself into pieces." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147238-no-matter-who-you-are-there-is-always-some-part</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2009 16:03:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147238-no-matter-who-you-are-there-is-always-some-part]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter who you are, there is always some part of you that wishes you were someone else, and when, for a millisecond, you get that wish, it's a miracle." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159170-but-in-the-night-he-woke-and-held-her-tight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 17:10:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159170-but-in-the-night-he-woke-and-held-her-tight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But in the night he woke and held her tight as though she were all of life and it was being taken from him. He held her feeling she was all of life there was and it was true." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160197-we-move-out-over-the-ocean-and-i-am-looking</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2009 19:18:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Shawn Klomparens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160197-we-move-out-over-the-ocean-and-i-am-looking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We move out over the ocean, and …I am looking straight down at the waves underneath me. The mid-morning sun is low and each crest flashes silver, silver, until it crashed into the rocky beach….and turns to foam. The rocks are broken into sand, and each grain …eventually…is broken down further.
And as each grief crashes into us, we are broken too. We are rendered down and broken apart. Maybe some scientist could determine our ages by the size and number of pieces into which we’ve been broken? Maybe she could look at our pieces and measure the weight in impact of every grief and joy and agony. Maybe.
" -- Shawn Klomparens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125312-there-is-no-greater-joy-than-to-have-an-endlessly</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Christopher McCandless]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125312-there-is-no-greater-joy-than-to-have-an-endlessly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun." -- Christopher McCandless]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19678-you-are-wrong-if-you-think-joy-emanates-only-from-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:11:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19678-you-are-wrong-if-you-think-joy-emanates-only-from-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are wrong if you think Joy emanates only...from human relationships.  God has placed it all around us...and all you have to do is reach for it." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11814-when-a-young-person-is-moved-by-a-passion-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:11:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11814-when-a-young-person-is-moved-by-a-passion-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a young person is moved by a passion and feels compelled to go on this sort of quest, I think you have to let him. You can't stop him. In our culture we don't have formal rights of passage like in some ancient cultures. Subjecting yourself to risk... may be something you have to go through to be a man or a woman." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105596-i-read-somewhere-how-important-it-is-in-life-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:11:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105596-i-read-somewhere-how-important-it-is-in-life-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read somewhere... how important it is in life not necessarily to be strong, but to feel strong... to measure yourself at least once." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145974-i-d-like-to-repeat-the-advice-that-i-gave-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:11:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Jon Krakauer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145974-i-d-like-to-repeat-the-advice-that-i-gave-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'd like to repeat the advice that I gave you before, in that I think you really should make a radical change in your lifestyle and begin to boldly do things which you may previously never have thought of doing, or been too hesitant to attempt.  So many people live within unhappy circumstances and yet will not take the initiative to change their situation because they are conditioned to a life of security, conformity, and conservatism, all of which may appear to give one peace of mind, but in reality nothing is more damaging to the adventurous spirit within a man than a secure future.  The very basic core of a man's living spirit is his passion for adventure.  The joy of life comes from our encounters with new experiences, and hence there is no greater joy than to have an endlessly changing horizon, for each day to have a new and different sun.  

If you want to get more out of life, Ron, you must lose your inclination for monotonous security and adopt a helter-skelter style of life that will at first appear to you to be crazy.  But once you become accustomed to such a life you will see its full meaning and its incredible beauty.  And so, Ron, in short, get out of Salton City and hit the Road.  I guarantee you will be very glad you did.  But I fear that you will ignore my advice.  You think that I am stubborn, but you are even more stubborn than me.  You had a wonderful chance on your drive back to see one of the greatest sights on earth, the Grand Canyon, something every American should see at least once in his life.  But for some reason incomprehensible to me you wanted nothing but to bolt for home as quickly as possible, right back to the same situation which you see day after day after day.  I fear you will follow this same inclination in the future and thus fail to discover all the wonderful things that God has placed around us to discover.  

Don't settle down and sit in one place.  Move around, be nomadic, make each day a new horizon.  You are still going to live a long time, Ron, and it would be a shame if you did not take the opportunity to revolutionize your life and move into an entirely new realm of experience.

You are wrong if you think Joy emanates only or principally from human relationships.  God has placed it all around us.  It is in everything and anything we might experience.  We just have to have the courage to turn against our habitual lifestyle and engage in unconventional living.

My point is that you do not need me or anyone else around to bring this new kind of light in your life.  It is simply waiting out there for you to grasp it, and all you have to do is reach for it.  The only person you are fighting is yourself and your stubbornness to engage in new circumstances." -- Jon Krakauer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16281-stop-wearing-your-wishbone-where-your-backbone-ought-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:16:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16281-stop-wearing-your-wishbone-where-your-backbone-ought-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop wearing your wishbone where your backbone ought to be." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2009 20:16:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10837-happiness-is-the-consequence-of-personal-effort-you-fight-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Happiness is the consequence of personal effort.  You fight for it, strive for it, insist upon it, and sometimes even travel around the world looking for it.  You have to participate relentlessly in the manifestations of your own blessings.  And once you have achieved a state of happiness, you must never become lax about maintaining it.  You must make a mighty effort to keep swimming upward into that happiness forever, to stay afloat on top of it." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214789-there-s-got-to-be-something-wrong-with-us-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 19:52:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Truman Capote]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/214789-there-s-got-to-be-something-wrong-with-us-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s got to be something wrong with us. To do what we did. " -- Truman Capote]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142998-bran-thought-about-it-can-a-man-still-be-brave</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 10:43:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/142998-bran-thought-about-it-can-a-man-still-be-brave]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Bran thought about it. 'Can a man still be brave if he's afraid?'
'That is the only time a man can be brave,' his father told him." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248985-hovering-near-panic-trying-to-focus-but-finding-it-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 12:21:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Emily add a quote by Kim Harrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/248985-hovering-near-panic-trying-to-focus-but-finding-it-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hovering near panic, trying to focus but finding it hard to open my eyes. My heart was pounding. I couldn’t get enough air, and I couldn’t find the desire to push her away" -- Kim Harrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
