<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949797-mark]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/949797-mark" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 06:00:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40552-i-am-a-sick-man-i-am-a-spiteful-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 06:00:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40552-i-am-a-sick-man-i-am-a-spiteful-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a sick man... I am a spiteful man.  I am an unpleasant man.  I think my liver is diseased.  However, I don't know beans about my disease, and I am not sure what is bothering me.  I don't treat it and never have, though I respect medicine and doctors.  Besides, I am extremely superstitious, let's say sufficiently so to respect medicine.  (I am educated enough not to be superstitious, but I am.)  No, I refuse to treat it out of spite.  You probably will not understand that.  Well, but I understand it.  Of course I can't explain to you just whom I am annoying in this case by my spite.  I am perfectly well aware that I cannot &quot;get even&quot; with the doctors by not consulting them.  I know better than anyone that I thereby injure only myself and no one else.  But still, if I don't treat it, its is out of spite.  My liver is bad, well then-- let it get even worse!" -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 10:24:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13733-for-those-who-believe-in-god-most-of-the-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For those who believe in God, most of the big questions are answered. But for those of us who can't readily accept the God formula, the big answers don't remain stone-written. We adjust to new conditions and discoveries. We are pliable. Love need not be a command nor faith a dictum. I am my own god. We are here to unlearn the teachings of the church, state, and our educational system. We are here to drink beer. We are here to kill war. We are here to laugh at the odds and live our lives so well that Death will tremble to take us." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 10:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Albert Camus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8178-nobody-realizes-that-some-people-expend-tremendous-energy-merely-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody realizes that some people expend tremendous energy merely to be normal." -- Albert Camus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 10:38:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6145-he-who-controls-the-past-controls-the-future-he-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He who controls the past controls the future. He who controls the present controls the past." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4416-we-are-all-atheists-about-most-of-the-gods-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 07:27:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mark add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4416-we-are-all-atheists-about-most-of-the-gods-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all atheists about most of the gods that humanity has ever believed in. Some of us just go one god further." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
