<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/95007-krissy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/95007-krissy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 02:49:24 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162323-from-the-pleasure-podium-of-ali-qapu-beyond-the-enhanced</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 02:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Christopher Kremmer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162323-from-the-pleasure-podium-of-ali-qapu-beyond-the-enhanced]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the pleasure podium of Ali Qapu, beyond the enhanced enclosure, the city spread itself towards the horizon. Ugly buildings are prohibited in Esfahan. They go to Tehran or stay in Mashhad. Planters vie with planners to outnumber buildings with trees. Attracting nightingales, blackbirds and orioles is considered as important as attracting people. Maples line the canals, reaching towards each other with branches linked. Beneath them, people meander, stroll and promenade. The Safavids' high standards generated a kind of architectural pole-vaulting competition in which beauty is the bar, and ever since the Persians have been imbuing the most mundane objects with design. Turquoise tiles ennoble even power stations.
In the meadow in the middle of Naghshe Jahan, as lovers strolled  or rode in horse-drawn traps, I lay on my back picking four-leafed clovers and looking at the sky. There was an intimacy about its grandeur, like having someone famous in your family. The life of centuries past was more alive here than anywhere else, its physical dimensions unchanged. Even the brutal mountains, folded in light and shadows beyond the square, stood back in awe of it. At three o'clock, the tiled domes soaked up the sunshine, transforming its invisible colours to their own hue, and the gushing fountains ventilated the breeze and passed it on to grateful Esfahanis. But above all was the soaring sky, captured by this snare of arches.(p378)" -- Christopher Kremmer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162325-how-did-these-organs-of-plant-sex-manage-to-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 02:59:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162325-how-did-these-organs-of-plant-sex-manage-to-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How did these organs of plant sex manage to get themselves cross-wired with human ideas of value and status and Eros? And what might our ancient attraction for flowers have to teach us about the deeper mysteries of beauty - what one poet has called &quot;this grace wholly gratuitous&quot;? Is that what it is? Or does beauty have a purpose? (64)" -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162326-witches-and-sorcerers-cultivated-plants-with-the-power-to-cast</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 03:07:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162326-witches-and-sorcerers-cultivated-plants-with-the-power-to-cast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Witches and sorcerers cultivated plants with the power to &quot;cast spells&quot; -- in our vocabulary, &quot;psychoactive&quot; plants. Their potion recipes called for such things as datura, opium poppies, belladona, hashish, fly-agaric mushrooms (Amanita muscaria), and the skin of toads (which can contain DMT, a powerful hallucinogen). These ingredients would be combined in a hempseed-oil-based &quot;flying ointment&quot; that the witches would then administer vaginally using a special dildo. This was the &quot;broomstick&quot; by which these women were said to travel. (119)" -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162327-consider-the-cattle-grazing-as-they-pass-you-by-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 03:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Friedrich Wilhelm Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162327-consider-the-cattle-grazing-as-they-pass-you-by-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider the cattle, grazing as they pass you by. They do not know what is meant by yesterday or today, they leap about, eat, rest, digest, leap about again, and so from morn till night and from day to day, fettered to the moment and its pleasure or displeasure, and thus neither melancholy nor bored. [...] A human being may well ask an animal: 'Why do you not speak to me of your happiness but only stand and gaze at me?' The animal would like to answer, and say, 'The reason is I always forget what I was going to say' - but then he forgot this answer too, and stayed silent." -- Friedrich Wilhelm Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162328-immersed-this-spring-in-research-for-this-chapter-i-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 03:27:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162328-immersed-this-spring-in-research-for-this-chapter-i-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Immersed this spring in research for this chapter, I was sorely tempted to plant one of the hybrid cannabis seeds I'd seen for sale in Amsterdam. I immediately thought better of it, however. So I planted lots of opium poppies instead. I hasten to add that I've no plans to do anything with my poppies except admire them - first their fleeting tissue-paper blooms, then their swelling blue-green seedpods, fat with milky alkaloid. (Unless, of course, simply walking among the poppies is enough to have an effect, as it was for Dorothy in Oz.)" -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162329-sooner-or-later-your-fingers-close-on-that-one-moist-cold</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 03:31:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162329-sooner-or-later-your-fingers-close-on-that-one-moist-cold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sooner or later your fingers close on that one moist-cold spud that the spade has accidentally sliced clean through, shining wetly white and giving off the most unearthly of earthly aromas. It's the smell of fresh soil in the spring, but fresh soil somehow distilled or improved upon, as if that wild, primordial scene has been refined and bottled: &lt;i&gt;eau de pomme de terre&lt;/i&gt;. You can smell the cold inhuman earth in it, but there's the cozy kitchen to, for the smell of potatoes is, at least by now, to us, the smell of comfort itself, a smell as blankly welcoming as spud flesh, a whiteness that takes up memories and sentiments as easily as flavors. To smell a raw potato is to stand on the very threshold of the domestic and the wild. (241)" -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33501-he-showed-the-words-chocolate-cake-to-a-group-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2009 03:35:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Michael Pollan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33501-he-showed-the-words-chocolate-cake-to-a-group-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He showed the words “chocolate cake” to a group of Americans and recorded their word associations. “Guilt” was the top response. If that strikes you as unexceptional, consider the response of French eaters to the same prompt: “celebration." -- Michael Pollan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26093-jealousy-is-a-disease-love-is-a-healthy-condition-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 12:40:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26093-jealousy-is-a-disease-love-is-a-healthy-condition-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jealousy is a disease, love is a healthy condition. The immature mind often mistakes one for the other, or assumes that the greater the love, the greater the jealousy - in fact, they are almost incompatible; one emotion hardly leaves room for the other." -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194604-foster-had-in-common-with-every-great-religious-leader-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 12:45:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194604-foster-had-in-common-with-every-great-religious-leader-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Foster had in common with every great religious leader of that planet two traits: he had an extremely magnetic personality, and sexually he did not fall near the human norm. On Earth great religious leaders were always either celibate or the antithesis. Foster was not celibate. (p.289)" -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194605-i-see-the-beauty-of-mike-s-attempt-to-devise-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 12:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/194605-i-see-the-beauty-of-mike-s-attempt-to-devise-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I see the beauty of Mike's attempt to devise an ideal ethic and applaud his recognition that such must start by junking the present sexual code and starting fresh. Most philosophers haven't the courage for this; they swallow the basics of the present code--monogamy, family pattern, continence, body taboos, conventional restrictions on intercourse, and so forth--then fiddle with details...even such piffle as discussing whether the female breast is an obscene sight! (p.365)" -- Robert A. Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237800-this-is-what-intimacy-does-to-us-over-time-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2010 12:43:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krissy add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237800-this-is-what-intimacy-does-to-us-over-time-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is what intimacy does to us over time. That's what a long marriage can do: It causes us to inherit and trade each other's stories. (p.237)" -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
