<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/950284-jennifer-hughes]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/950284-jennifer-hughes" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 21:23:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2008 21:23:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43584-the-submission-of-one-s-will-is-really-the-only-uniquely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2009 19:14:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43584-the-submission-of-one-s-will-is-really-the-only-uniquely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The submission of one's will is really the only uniquely personal thing we have to place on God's altar.  The many other things we 'give' are actually the things He has already given or loaned to us." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36605-jesus-said-several-times-come-follow-me-his-was-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 18:57:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36605-jesus-said-several-times-come-follow-me-his-was-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus said several times, “Come, follow me.” His was a program of “do what I do,” rather than “do what I say.” His innate brilliance would have permitted him to put on a dazzling display, but that would have left his followers far behind. He walked and worked with those he was to serve. His was not a long-distance leadership. He was not afraid of close friendships; he was not afraid that proximity to him would disappoint his followers. The leaven of true leadership cannot lift others unless we are with and serve those to be led." -- Spencer W. Kimball]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56665-coming-unto-the-lord-is-not-a-negotiation-but-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2009 18:59:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56665-coming-unto-the-lord-is-not-a-negotiation-but-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Coming unto the Lord is not a negotiation, but a surrender." -- Neal A. Maxwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359241-for-children-love-is-a-feeling-for-adults-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011 08:47:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/359241-for-children-love-is-a-feeling-for-adults-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For children love is a feeling; for adults, it is a decision. Children wait to learn if their love is true by seeing how long it lasts; adults make their love true by never wavering from their commitment." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42442-i-can-t-sit-still-and-see-another-man-slaving-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 08:13:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42442-i-can-t-sit-still-and-see-another-man-slaving-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't sit still and see another man slaving and working. I want to get up and superintend, and walk round with my hands in my pockets, and tell him what to do. It is my energetic nature. I can't help it." -- Jerome K. Jerome]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10471-wilderness-is-not-a-luxury-but-a-necessity-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 11:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10471-wilderness-is-not-a-luxury-but-a-necessity-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wilderness is not a luxury but a necessity of the human spirit, and as vital to our lives as water and good bread. A civilization which destroys what little remains of the wild, the spare, the original, is cutting itself off from its origins and betraying the principle of civilization itself." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10780-try-a-little-harder-to-be-a-little-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 11:39:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10780-try-a-little-harder-to-be-a-little-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try a little harder to be a little better." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41544-but-until-a-person-can-say-deeply-and-honestly-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2013 11:27:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41544-but-until-a-person-can-say-deeply-and-honestly-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But until a person can say deeply and honestly, &quot;I am what I am today because of the choices I made yesterday,&quot; that person cannot say, &quot;I choose otherwise." -- Stephen R. Covey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27861-i-read-so-i-can-live-more-than-one-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 07:52:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Anne Tyler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27861-i-read-so-i-can-live-more-than-one-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read so I can live more than one life in more than one place." -- Anne Tyler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15515-when-obedience-ceases-to-be-an-irritant-and-becomes-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2013 10:32:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15515-when-obedience-ceases-to-be-an-irritant-and-becomes-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When obedience ceases to be an irritant and becomes our quest, in that moment God will endow us with power." -- Ezra Taft Benson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6430-failing-to-fetch-me-at-first-keep-encouraged-missing-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2013 20:10:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Walt Whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6430-failing-to-fetch-me-at-first-keep-encouraged-missing-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Failing to fetch me at first, keep encouraged. Missing me one place, search another. I stop somewhere waiting for you." -- Walt Whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282593-it-is-a-serious-thing-to-live-in-a-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 22:51:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/282593-it-is-a-serious-thing-to-live-in-a-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a serious thing to live in a society of possible gods and goddesses, to remember that the dullest most uninteresting person you talk to may one day be a creature which,if you say it now, you would be strongly tempted to worship, or else a horror and a corruption such as you now meet, if at all, only in a nightmare. All day long we are, in some degree helping each other to one or the other of these destinations. It is in the light of these overwhelming possibilites, it is with the awe and the circumspection proper to them, that we should conduct all of our dealings with one another, all friendships, all loves, all play, all politics. There are no ordinary people. You have never  talked to a mere mortal. nations, cultures, arts, civilizations - These are mortal, and their life is to ours as the life of a gnat. But it is immortals whom we joke with, work with, marry, snub, and exploit - immortal horrors or everlasting splendors." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432849-it-may-be-possible-for-each-to-think-too-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 22:55:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/432849-it-may-be-possible-for-each-to-think-too-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may be possible for each to think too much of his own potential glory hereafter; it is hardly possible for him to think too often or too deeply about that of his neighbor. The load, or weight, or burden of my neighbor's glory should be laid daily on my back, a load so heavy that only humility can carry it, and the backs of the proud will be broken. ...  

&quot;It is in light of these overwhelming possibilities, it is with the awe and the circumspection proper to them, that we should conduct all our dealings with one another, all friendships, all loves, all play, all politics. There are no ordinary people. You have never talked to a mere mortal. Nations, cultures, arts, civilizations -- these are mortal, and their life is to ours as the life of a gnat. But it is immortals whom we joke with, work with, marry, snub and exploit. ... Next to the Blessed Sacrament itself, your neighbor is the holiest object presented to your senses." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9060-mother-always-said-she-was-a-size-7-woman-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 08:17:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Haven Kimmel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9060-mother-always-said-she-was-a-size-7-woman-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mother always said she was a size 7 woman she kept wrapped in fat to prevent bruising." -- Haven Kimmel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
