<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/951422-summre]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/951422-summre" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:30:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29218-above-all-don-t-lie-to-yourself-the-man-who-lies</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2008 10:30:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29218-above-all-don-t-lie-to-yourself-the-man-who-lies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Above all, don't lie to yourself. The man who lies to himself and listens to his own lie comes to a point that he cannot distinguish the truth within him, or around him, and so loses all respect for himself and for others. And having no respect he ceases to love." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63019-he-knew-only-that-his-child-was-his-warrant-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2010 18:49:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63019-he-knew-only-that-his-child-was-his-warrant-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He knew only that his child was his warrant. He said: If he is not the word of God God never spoke." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96600-the-earth-has-music-for-those-who-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2011 12:13:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by George Santayana]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96600-the-earth-has-music-for-those-who-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The earth has music for those who listen." -- George Santayana]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33408-i-believe-a-strong-woman-may-be-stronger-than-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 07:53:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33408-i-believe-a-strong-woman-may-be-stronger-than-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe a strong woman may be stronger than a man, particularly if she happens to have love in her heart. I guess a loving woman is indestructible." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5253-try-to-understand-men-if-you-understand-each-other-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 07:53:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5253-try-to-understand-men-if-you-understand-each-other-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Try to understand men. If you understand each other you will be kind to each other. Knowing a man well never leads to hate and almost always leads to love." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33327-it-s-so-much-darker-when-a-light-goes-out-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 07:55:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33327-it-s-so-much-darker-when-a-light-goes-out-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's so much darker when a light goes out than it would have been if it had never shone." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505483-the-people-came-out-of-their-houses-and-smelled-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/505483-the-people-came-out-of-their-houses-and-smelled-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The people came out of their houses and smelled the hot stinging air and covered their noses from it.  And the children came out of the houses, but they did not run or shout as they would have done after a rain.  Men stood by their fences and looked at the ruined corn, drying fast now, only a little green showing through the film of dust.  The men were silent and they did not move often.  And the women came out of the houses to stand beside their men - to feel whether this time the men would break.  The women studied the men's faces secretly, for the corn could go, as long as something else remained.  The children stood near by drawing figures in the dust with bare toes, and the children sent exploring senses out to see whether men and women would break.  The children peeked at the faces of the men and women, and then drew careful lines in the dust with their toes.  Horses came to the watering troughs and nuzzled the water to clear the surface dust.  After a while the faces of the watching men lost their bemused perplexity and became hard and angry and resistant.  Then the women knew that they were safe and that there was no break.  Then they asked, Whta'll we do?  And the men replied, I don't know.  but it was all right.  The women knew it was all right, and the watching children knew it was all right.  Women and children knew deep in themselves that no misfortune was too great to bear if their men were whole.  The women went into the houses to their work, and the children began to play, but cautiously at first.  As the day went forward the sun became less red.  It flared down on the dust-blanketed land.  The men sat in the doorways of their houses; their hands were busy with sticks and little rocks.  The men sat still - thinking - figuring." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529477-ma-was-heavy-but-not-fat-thick-with-child-bearing-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:10:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/529477-ma-was-heavy-but-not-fat-thick-with-child-bearing-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ma was heavy, but not fat; thick with child-bearing and work. She wore a loose Mother Hubbard of gray cloth in which there had once been colored flowers, but the color was washed out now, so that the small flowered pattern was only a little lighter gray than the background. The dress came down to her ankles, and he strong, broad, bare feet moved quickly and deftly over the floor. Her thin, steel-gray hair was gathered in a sparse wispy knot at the back of her head. Strong, freckled arms were bare to the elbow, and her hands were chubby and delicate, like those of a plump little girl. She looked out into the sunshine. Her full face was not soft; it was controlled, kindly. Her hazel eyes seemed to have experienced all possible tragedy and to have mounted pain and suffering like steps into a high calm and a superhuman understanding. She seemed to know, to accept, to welcome her position, the citadel of the family, the strong place that could not be taken. And since old Tom and the children could not know hurt or fear unless she acknowledged hurt and fear, she had practiced denying them in herself. And since, when a joyful thing happened, they looked to see whether joy was on her, it was her habit to build up laughter out of inadequate materials. But better than joy was calm. Imperturbability could be depended upon. And from her great and humble position in the family she had taken dignity and a clean calm beauty. From her position as healer, her hands had grown sure and cool and quiet; from her position as arbiter she had become as remote and faultless in judgment as a goddess. She seemed to know that if she swayed the family shook, and if she ever really deeply wavered or despaired the family would fall, the family will to function would be gone." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354-live-in-the-sunshine-swim-the-sea-drink-the-wild</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:15:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/354-live-in-the-sunshine-swim-the-sea-drink-the-wild]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live in the sunshine, swim the sea, drink the wild air." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52675-let-us-be-silent-that-we-may-hear-the-whisper</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:17:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52675-let-us-be-silent-that-we-may-hear-the-whisper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us be silent, that we may hear the whisper of God." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58485-few-people-know-how-to-take-a-walk-the-qualifications</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:18:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58485-few-people-know-how-to-take-a-walk-the-qualifications]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Few people know how to take a walk. The qualifications are endurance, plain clothes, old shoes, an eye for nature, good humor, vast curiosity, good speech, good silence and nothing too much." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29780-scatter-joy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 08:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29780-scatter-joy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scatter joy!" -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138924-all-men-have-stars-but-they-are-not-the-same</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 13:05:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138924-all-men-have-stars-but-they-are-not-the-same]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All men have stars, but they are not the same things for different people. For some, who are travelers, the stars are guides. For others they are no more than little lights in the sky. For others, who are scholars, they are problems... But all these stars are silent. You-You alone will have stars as no one else has them... In one of the stars I shall be living. In one of them I shall be laughing. And so it will be as if all the stars will be laughing when you look at the sky at night..You, only you, will have stars that can laugh! And when your sorrow is comforted (time soothes all sorrows) you will be content that you have known me... You will always be my friend. You will want to laugh with me. And you will sometimes open your window, so, for that pleasure... It will be as if, in place of the stars, I had given you a great number of little bells that knew how to laugh" -- Antoine de Saint-Exupéry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705520-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-ones-who-spill</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:42:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/705520-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-ones-who-spill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only people for me are the ones who spill things, the ones who drop their cups sometimes, the ones who get dirty hands and messy hair, the ones who can go barefoot if they feel like it, the people who forget things, and can laugh at themselves every day..." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:47:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:48:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15935-if-you-are-a-dreamer-come-in-if-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are a dreamer come in
If you are a dreamer a wisher a liar
A hoper a pray-er a magic-bean-buyer
If youre a pretender com sit by my fire
For we have some flax golden tales to spin
Come in! 
Come in!" -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226358-it-s-opener-out-there-in-the-wide-open-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:50:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/226358-it-s-opener-out-there-in-the-wide-open-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's opener, out there, in the wide, open air." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16373-you-re-off-to-great-places-today-is-your-day-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:50:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16373-you-re-off-to-great-places-today-is-your-day-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're off to Great Places!
Today is your day!
Your mountain is waiting,
So... get on your way!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357283-you-only-need-one-man-to-love-you-but-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357283-you-only-need-one-man-to-love-you-but-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You only need one man to love you. But him to love you free like a wildfire, crazy like the moon, always like tomorrow, sudden like an inhale and overcoming like the tides. Only one man and all of this." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390870-a-star-falls-from-the-sky-and-into-your-hands</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:52:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/390870-a-star-falls-from-the-sky-and-into-your-hands]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A star falls from the sky and into your hands. Then it seeps through your veins and swims inside your blood and becomes every part of you. And then you have to put it back into the sky. And it's the most painful thing you'll ever have to do and that you've ever done. But what's yours is yours. Whether it’s up in the sky or here in your hands. And one day, it'll fall from the sky and hit you in the head real hard and that time, you won't have to put it back in the sky again." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357281-they-say-a-good-love-is-one-that-sits-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 17:53:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357281-they-say-a-good-love-is-one-that-sits-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They say a good love is one that sits you down, gives you a drink of water, and pats you on top of the head. But I say a good love is one that casts you into the wind, sets you ablaze, makes you burn through the skies and ignite the night like a phoenix; the kind that cuts you loose like a wildfire and you can't stop running simply because you keep on burning everything that you touch! I say that's a good love; one that burns and flies, and you run with it!" -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147041-with-mirth-and-laughter-let-old-wrinkles-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147041-with-mirth-and-laughter-let-old-wrinkles-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["With mirth and laughter let old wrinkles come." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38920-the-human-race-has-only-one-really-effective-weapon-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38920-the-human-race-has-only-one-really-effective-weapon-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The human race has only one really effective weapon and that is laughter." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65375-life-is-worth-living-as-long-as-there-s-a-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65375-life-is-worth-living-as-long-as-there-s-a-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is worth living as long as there's a laugh in it." -- Lucy Maud Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656804-she-laughs-an-honest-laugh-one-that-puts-the-fakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:02:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656804-she-laughs-an-honest-laugh-one-that-puts-the-fakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She laughs an honest laugh... one that puts the fakes on edge and makes them dream of being better." -- C. JoyBell C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605768-take-bread-away-from-me-if-you-wish-take-air</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 18:03:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summre add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/605768-take-bread-away-from-me-if-you-wish-take-air]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take bread away from me, if you wish,
take air away, but
do not take from me your laughter." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
