<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/95156-flint]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/95156-flint" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:43:32 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7076-the-most-effective-way-to-destroy-people-is-to-deny</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:43:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7076-the-most-effective-way-to-destroy-people-is-to-deny]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most effective way to destroy people is to deny and obliterate their own understanding of their history." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682-the-street-finds-its-own-uses-for-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:43:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/682-the-street-finds-its-own-uses-for-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The street finds its own uses for things." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19274-ozymandias-i-met-a-traveller-from-an-antique-land-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:43:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19274-ozymandias-i-met-a-traveller-from-an-antique-land-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Ozymandias&lt;/b&gt;

I met a traveller from an antique land
Who said: &quot;Two vast and trunkless legs of stone
Stand in the desert. Near them on the sand,
Half sunk, a shattered visage lies, whose frown
And wrinkled lip and sneer of cold command
Tell that its sculptor well those passions read
Which yet survive, stamped on these lifeless things,
The hand that mocked them and the heart that fed.
And on the pedestal these words appear:
'My name is Ozymandias, King of Kings:
Look on my works, ye mighty, and despair!'
Nothing beside remains. Round the decay
Of that colossal wreck, boundless and bare,
The lone and level sands stretch far away." -- Percy Bysshe Shelley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176879-how-wearisom-eternity-so-spent-in-worship-paid-to-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2009 09:42:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by John Milton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/176879-how-wearisom-eternity-so-spent-in-worship-paid-to-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["how wearisom
Eternity so spent in worship paid
To whom we hate. Let us not then pursue
By force impossible, by leave obtain'd 
Unacceptable, though in Heav'n, our state
Of splendid vassalage, but rather seek
Our own good from our selves, and from our own
Live to our selves, though in this vast recess,
Free, and to none accountable, preferring 
Hard liberty before the easie yoke
Of servile Pomp" -- John Milton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14652-every-type-of-political-power-presupposes-some-particular-form-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 09:35:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Rudolf Rocker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14652-every-type-of-political-power-presupposes-some-particular-form-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every type of political power presupposes some particular form of human slavery, for the maintenance of which it is called into being. Just as outwardly, that is, in relation to other states the state has to create certain artificial antagonisms in order to justify its existence, so also internally the cleavage of society into castes, ranks and classes is an essential condition of its continuance. The development of the Bolshevist bureaucracy in Russia under the alleged dictatorship of the proletariat (which has never been anything but the dictatorship of a small clique over the proletariat and the whole Russian people) is merely a new instance of an old historical experience which has repeated itself countless times. This new ruling class, which to-day is rapidly growing into a new aristocracy, is set apart from the great masses of the Russian peasants and workers just as clearly as are the privileged castes and classes in other countries from the mass of the people. And this situation becomes still more unbearable when a despotic state denies to the lower classes the right to complain of existing conditions, so that any protest is made at the risk of their lives.

But even a far greater degree of economic equality than that which exists in Russia would be no guarantee against political and social oppression. Economic equality alone is not social liberation. It is precisely this which all the schools of authoritarian Socialism have never understood. In the prison, in the cloister, or in the barracks one finds a fairly high degree of economic equality, as all the inmates are provided with the same dwelling, the same food, the same uniform, and the same tasks. The ancient Inca state in Peru and the Jesuit state in Paraguay had brought equal economic provision for every inhabitant to a fixed system, but in spite of this the vilest despotism prevailed there, and the human being was merely the automaton of a higher will on whose decisions he had not the slightest influence. It was not without reason that Proudhon saw in a &quot;Socialism&quot; without freedom the worst form of slavery. The urge for social justice can only develop properly and be effective when it grows out of man's sense of freedom and responsibility, and is based upon it. In other words, Socialism will be free or it will not be at all. In its recognition of this fact lies the genuine and profound justification of Anarchism. " -- Rudolf Rocker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14649-to-be-governed-is-to-be-watched-inspected-spied-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 09:37:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Pierre-Joseph Proudhon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14649-to-be-governed-is-to-be-watched-inspected-spied-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To be GOVERNED is to be watched, inspected, spied upon, directed, law-driven, numbered, regulated, enrolled, indoctrinated, preached at, controlled, checked, estimated, valued, censured, commanded, by creatures who have neither the right nor the wisdom nor the virtue to do so. To be GOVERNED is to be at every operation, at every transaction noted, registered, counted, taxed, stamped, measured, numbered, assessed, licensed, authorized, admonished, prevented, forbidden, reformed, corrected, punished. It is, under pretext of public utility, and in the name of the general interest, to be place under contribution, drilled, fleeced, exploited, monopolized, extorted from, squeezed, hoaxed, robbed; then, at the slightest resistance, the first word of complaint, to be repressed, fined, vilified, harassed, hunted down, abused, clubbed, disarmed, bound, choked, imprisoned, judged, condemned, shot, deported, sacrificed, sold, betrayed; and to crown all, mocked, ridiculed, derided, outraged, dishonored. That is government; that is its justice; that is its morality.&quot;
General Idea of the Revolution in the Nineteenth Century, translated by John Beverly Robinson (London: Freedom Press, 1923), pp. 293-294." -- Pierre-Joseph Proudhon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14656-their-policy-in-this-is-very-wise-and-has-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 09:46:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Reuben Gold Thwaites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14656-their-policy-in-this-is-very-wise-and-has-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Their Policy in this is very wise, and has nothing Barbarous in it. For, since their preservation depends upon their union, and since it is hardly possible that among peoples where license reigns with all impunity -- and, above all, among young people -- there should not happen some event capable of causing a rupture, and disuniting their minds, -- for these reasons, they hold every year a general assembly in Onnontaé. There all the Deputies from the different Nations are present, to make their complaints and receive the necessary satisfaction in mutual gifts, -- by means of which they maintain a good understanding with one another" -- Reuben Gold Thwaites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14658-they-still-possess-virtues-which-might-cause-shame-to-most</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 09:48:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Reuben Gold Thwaites]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14658-they-still-possess-virtues-which-might-cause-shame-to-most]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They still possess virtues which might cause shame to most Christians. No hospitals are needed among them, because there are neither mendicants nor paupers as long as there are any rich people among them. Their kindness, humanity, and courtesy not only make them liberal with what they have, but cause them to possess hardly anything except in common. A whole village must be without corn before any individual can be obliged to endure privation. They divide the produce of their fisheries equally with all who come" -- Reuben Gold Thwaites]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14660-no-soldiers-no-gendarmes-or-police-no-nobles-kings-regents</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 09:50:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Frederick Engels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14660-no-soldiers-no-gendarmes-or-police-no-nobles-kings-regents]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No soldiers, no gendarmes or police, no nobles, kings, regents, prefects, or judges, no prisons, no lawsuits - and everything takes its orderly course. All quarrels and disputes are settled by the whole of the community affected, by the gens or the tribe, or by the gentes among themselves; only as an extreme and exceptional measure is blood revenge threatened-and our capital punishment is nothing but blood revenge in a civilized form, with all the advantages and drawbacks of civilization. Although there were many more matters to be settled in common than today - the household is maintained by a number of families in common, and is communistic, the land belongs to the tribe, only the small gardens are allotted provisionally to the households - yet there is no need for even a trace of our complicated administrative apparatus with all its ramifications. The decisions are taken by those concerned, and in most cases everything has been already settled by the custom of centuries. There cannot be any poor or needy - the communal household and the gens know their responsibilities towards the old, the sick, and those disabled in war. All are equal and free - the women included. There is no place yet for slaves, nor, as a rule, for the subjugation of other tribes." -- Frederick Engels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32134-anarchism-then-really-stands-for-the-liberation-of-the-human</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2008 13:18:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32134-anarchism-then-really-stands-for-the-liberation-of-the-human]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anarchism, then, really stands for the liberation of the human mind from the dominion of religion; the liberation of the human body from the dominion of property; liberation from the shackles and restraint of government." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27023-free-love-as-if-love-is-anything-but-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 08:46:53 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27023-free-love-as-if-love-is-anything-but-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Free love? As if love is anything but free! Man has bought brains, but all the millions in the world have failed to buy love. Man has subdued bodies, but all the power on earth has been unable to subdue love. Man has conquered whole nations, but all his armies could not conquer love. Man has chained and fettered the spirit, but he has been utterly helpless before love. High on a throne, with all the splendor and pomp his gold can command, man is yet poor and desolate, if love passes him by. And if it stays, the poorest hovel is radiant with warmth, with life and color. Thus love has the magic power to make of a beggar a king. Yes, love is free; it can dwell in no other atmosphere. In freedom it gives itself unreservedly, abundantly, completely. All the laws on the statutes, all the courts in the universe, cannot tear it from the soil, once love has taken root." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5723-now-i-will-tell-you-the-answer-to-my-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 08:50:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5723-now-i-will-tell-you-the-answer-to-my-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I will tell you the answer to my question. It is this. The Party seeks power entirely for its own sake. We are not interested in the good of others; we are interested solely in power, pure power. What pure power means you will understand presently. We are different from the oligarchies of the past in that we know what we are doing. All the others, even those who resembled ourselves, were cowards and hypocrites. The German Nazis and the Russian Communists came very close to us in their methods, but they never had the courage to recognize their own motives. They pretended, perhaps they even believed, that they had seized power unwillingly and for a limited time, and that just around the corner there lay a paradise where human beings would be free and equal. We are not like that. We know what no one ever seizes power with the intention of relinquishing it. Power is not a means; it is an end. One does not establish a dictatorship in order to safeguard a revolution; one makes the revolution in order to establish the dictatorship. The object of persecution is persecution. The object of torture is torture. The object of power is power. Now you begin to understand me." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 08:53:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by William Gibson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/889-the-sky-above-the-port-was-the-color-of-television]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sky above the port was the color of television, tuned to a dead channel." -- William Gibson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49867-even-galaxy-spanning-anarchist-utopias-of-stupefying-full-spectrum-civilisational-power-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 07:57:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Iain M. Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49867-even-galaxy-spanning-anarchist-utopias-of-stupefying-full-spectrum-civilisational-power-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even galaxy-spanning anarchist utopias of stupefying full-spectrum civilisational power have turf wars within their unacknowledged militaries." -- Iain M. Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146888-but-what-about-human-nature-can-it-be-changed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 11:51:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Emma Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146888-but-what-about-human-nature-can-it-be-changed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But what about human nature? Can it be changed? And if not, will it endure under Anarchism?

Poor human nature, what horrible crimes have been committed in thy name! Every fool, from king to policeman, from the flatheaded parson to the visionless dabbler in science, presumes to speak authoritatively of human nature. The greater the mental charlatan, the more definite his insistence on the wickedness and weaknesses of human nature. Yet, how can any one speak of it today, with every soul in a prison, with every heart fettered, wounded, and maimed?

John Burroughs has stated that experimental study of animals in captivity is absolutely useless. Their character, their habits, their appetites undergo a complete transformation when torn from their soil in field and forest. With human nature caged in a narrow space, whipped daily into submission, how can we speak of its potentialities?

Freedom, expansion, opportunity, and, above all, peace and repose, alone can teach us the real dominant factors of human nature and all its wonderful possibilities.

Anarchism, then, really stands for the liberation of the human mind from the dominion of religion; the liberation of the human body from the dominion of property; liberation from the shackles and restraint of government. Anarchism stands for a social order based on the free grouping of individuals for the purpose of producing real social wealth; an order that will guarantee to every human being free access to the earth and full enjoyment of the necessities of life, according to individual desires, tastes, and inclinations.

This is not a wild fancy or an aberration of the mind. It is the conclusion arrived at by hosts of intellectual men and women the world over; a conclusion resulting from the close and studious observation of the tendencies of modern society: individual liberty and economic equality, the twin forces for the birth of what is fine and true in man." -- Emma Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204739-fuck-every-cause-that-ends-in-murder-and-children-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 14:42:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Flint add a quote by Iain M. Banks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204739-fuck-every-cause-that-ends-in-murder-and-children-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fuck every cause that ends in murder and children crying." -- Iain M. Banks]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
