<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/953181-mike]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/953181-mike" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:01:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417462-it-is-not-for-nothing-that-you-are-named-ransom</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417462-it-is-not-for-nothing-that-you-are-named-ransom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not for nothing that you are named Ransom,” said the Voice...

The whole distinction between things accidental and things designed, like the distinction between fact and myth, was purely terrestrial. The pattern is so large that within the little frame of earthly experience there appear pieces of it between which we can see no connection, and other pieces between which we can. Hence we rightly, for our sue, distinguish the accidental from the essential. But step outside that frame and the distinction drops down into the void, fluttering useless wings. He had been forced out of the frame, caught up into the larger pattern… “My name also is Ransom,” said the Voice." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381536-the-whole-struggle-was-over-and-yet-there-seemed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/381536-the-whole-struggle-was-over-and-yet-there-seemed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whole struggle was over, and yet there seemed to have been no moment of victory. You might say, if you liked, that the power of choice had been simply set aside and an inflexible destiny substituted for it. On the other hand, you might say he had delivered from the rhetoric of his passions and had emerged in unassailable freedom. Ransom could not for the life of him, see any difference between these two statements. Predestination and freedom were apparently identical. He could no longer see any meaning in the many arguments he had heart on the subject." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656594-i-saw-what-andrew-did-in-our-family-i-saw</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/656594-i-saw-what-andrew-did-in-our-family-i-saw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw what Andrew did in our family. I saw that he came in and listened and watched and understood who we were, each individual one of us. He tried to discover our need and then supply it. He took responsibility for other people and it didn't seem to matter to him how much it cost him. And in the end, while he could never make the Ribeira family normal, he gave us peace and pride and identity. Stability. He married Mother and was kind to her. He loved us all. He was always there when we wanted him, and seemed unhurt by it when we didn't. He was firm with us about expecting civilized behavior, but never indulged his whims at our expense. And I thought: This is so much more important than science. Or politics, either. Or any particular profession or accomplishment or thing you can make. I thought: If I could just make a good family, if I could just learn to be to other children, their whole lives, what Andrew was, coming so late into ours, then that would mean more in the long run, it would be a finer accomplishment than anything I could ever do with my mind or hands.&quot;

&quot;So you're a career father,&quot; said Valentine.

&quot;Who works at a brick factory to feed and clothe the family. Not a brick-maker who also has kids. Lini also feels the same way... She followed her own road to the same place. We do what we must to earn our place in the community, but we live for the hours at home. For each other, for the children." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637536-there-is-always-the-danger-that-those-who-think-alike</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/637536-there-is-always-the-danger-that-those-who-think-alike]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is always the danger that those who think alike should gravitate together into ‘coteries’ where they will henceforth encounter opposition only in the emasculated form of rumor that the outsiders say thus and thus. The absent are easily refuted, complacent dogmatism thrives, and differences of opinion are embittered by group hostility. Each group hears not the best, but the worst, that the other groups can say." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620837-he-splashed-into-the-water-his-whole-body-not-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620837-he-splashed-into-the-water-his-whole-body-not-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He splashed into the water, his whole body, not with the reverent attitude of prayer, but with a desperate thirst; he buried his head under the water and drank deep, with his cheek against the cold stone of the riverbed, the water tumbling over his back, his calves. He drank and drank, lifted his head and shoulders above the water to gasp in the evening air, and then collapsed into the water again, to drink as greedily as before.

It was a kind of prayer, though, he realized as he emerged, freezing cold as the water evaporated from his skin in the breeze of the dark morning.

I am with you, he said to the Oversoul. I'll do whatever you ask, because I long for you to accomplish your purpose here." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502826-those-who-are-enjoying-something-or-suffering-something-together-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:02:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/502826-those-who-are-enjoying-something-or-suffering-something-together-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who are enjoying something, or suffering something, together, are companions. Those who enjoy or suffer one another, are not." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620840-that-s-what-father-and-mother-are-thought-nafai-they-stay</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620840-that-s-what-father-and-mother-are-thought-nafai-they-stay]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's what Father and Mother are, thought Nafai. They stay together, not because of any gain, but because of the gift. Father doesn't stay with Mother because she is good for him, but rather because together they can do good for us, and for many others." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620848-if-the-followers-of-the-oversoul-are-kept-blind-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620848-if-the-followers-of-the-oversoul-are-kept-blind-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the followers of the Oversoul are kept blind, if they can't judge the Oversoul's purpose for themselves, then they aren't freely choosing between good and evil, or between wise and foolish, but are only choosing to subsume themselves in the purposes of the Oversoul How can the Oversoul's plans be well-served, if all its followers are the kind of weak-souled people who are willing to obey the Oversoul without understanding? 

I will serve you, Oversoul, with my whole heart I'll serve you, if I understand what you're trying to do, what it means. And if your purpose is a good one... I will not be tamed, only persuaded. I will not be coerced or led blindly or tricked or bullied -- I am willing only to be convinced. If you don't trust your own basic goodness enough to tell me what you're trying to do, Oversoul, then you're confessing your own moral weakness and I'll never serve you." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620847-once-these-two-had-been-joined-together-in-love-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/620847-once-these-two-had-been-joined-together-in-love-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once these two had been joined together in love, or something like love; they had made two babies, and yet, only fifteen years later, the last tie between them was broken now. All lost, all gone. Nothing lasted, nothing. Even this forty-million-year world that the Oversoul had preserved as if in ice, even it would melt before the fire. Permanence was always an illusion, and love was just the disguise that lovers wore to hide the death of their union from each other for a while." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431114-many-references-have-been-made-in-this-book-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by E.B. White]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431114-many-references-have-been-made-in-this-book-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Many references have been made in this book to 'the reader,' who has been much in the news.  It is now necessary to warn you that your concern for the reader must be pure: you must sympathize with the reader's plight (most readers are in trouble about half the time) but never seek to know the reader's wants.  Your whole duty as a writer is to please and satisfy yourself, and the true writer always plays to an audience of one.  Start sniffing the air, or glancing at the Trend Machine, and you are as good as dead, although you may make a nice living." -- E.B. White]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606177-when-a-sentence-is-made-stronger-it-usually-becomes-shorter</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by William Strunk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606177-when-a-sentence-is-made-stronger-it-usually-becomes-shorter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a sentence is made stronger, it usually becomes shorter. Thus, brevity is a by-product of vigor." -- William Strunk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606688-consciously-or-unconsciously-the-reader-is-dissatisfied-with-being-told</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by William Strunk, Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/606688-consciously-or-unconsciously-the-reader-is-dissatisfied-with-being-told]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consciously or unconsciously, the reader is dissatisfied with being told only what is not; the reader wishes to be told what is... If your every sentence admits a doubt, your writing will lack authority." -- William Strunk, Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2538-people-love-a-happy-ending-so-every-episode-i-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2538-people-love-a-happy-ending-so-every-episode-i-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People love a happy ending. So every episode, I will explain once again that I don't like people. And then Mal will shoot someone. Someone we like. And their puppy." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287182-welcome-to-the-human-race-nobody-controls-his-own-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:03:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Orson Scott Card]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287182-welcome-to-the-human-race-nobody-controls-his-own-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Welcome to the human race. Nobody controls his own life, Ender. The best you can do is choose to fill the roles given you by good people, by people who love you." -- Orson Scott Card]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67508-passion-it-lies-in-all-of-us-sleeping-waiting-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Passion. It lies in all of us. Sleeping... waiting... and though unwanted, unbidden, it will stir... open its jaws and howl. It speaks to us... guides us. Passion rules us all. And we obey. What other choice do we have? Passion is the source of our finest moments. The joy of love... the clarity of hatred... the ecstasy of grief. It hurts sometimes more than we can bear. If we could live without passion, maybe we'd know some kind of peace. But we would be hollow. Empty rooms, shuttered and dank. Without passion, we'd be truly dead." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9067-two-roads-diverged-in-a-wood-and-i-took-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:01:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9067-two-roads-diverged-in-a-wood-and-i-took-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Two roads diverged in a wood, and I took the road less traveled by and they CANCELLED MY FRIKKIN' SHOW. I totally shoulda took the road that had all those people on it. Damn." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3203-but-the-hebrew-word-the-word-timshel-thou-mayest-that-gives</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 17:15:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3203-but-the-hebrew-word-the-word-timshel-thou-mayest-that-gives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the Hebrew word, the word timshel—‘Thou mayest’— that gives a choice. It might be the most important word in the world. That says the way is open. That throws it right back on a man. For if ‘Thou mayest’—it is also true that ‘Thou mayest not." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776826-old-sam-hamilton-saw-this-coming-he-said-there-couldn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2013 07:48:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776826-old-sam-hamilton-saw-this-coming-he-said-there-couldn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Old Sam Hamilton saw this coming. He said there couldn’t be any more universal philosophers. The weight of knowledge is too great for one mind to absorb. He saw a time when one man would know only one little fragment, but he would know it well.”

“Yes,” Lee said from the doorway, “and he deplored it. He hated it.”

“Did he, now?” Adam asked...

“Now you question it, I don’t know,” he said. “I don’t know whether he hated it or I hate it for him... Maybe the knowledge is too great and maybe men are growing too small... Maybe kneeling down to atoms, they’re becoming atom-sized in their souls. Maybe a specialist is only a coward, afraid to look out of his little cage. And think what any specialist misses! The whole world over his fence!”

“We’re only talking about making a living.”

“A living? Or money?” Lee said excitedly. “Money’s easy to make if it’s money you want. But with a few exceptions people don’t want money. They want luxury, and they want love, and they want admiration." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/771141-if-to-know-is-to-work-then-knowledge-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 06:12:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/771141-if-to-know-is-to-work-then-knowledge-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If to know is to work, then knowledge is the fruit of our own unaided effort and activity; then knowledge includes nothing which is not due to the effort of man, and there is nothing gratuitous about it, nothing &quot;inspired&quot;, nothing &quot;given&quot; about it." -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:01:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10554-friendship-is-born-at-that-moment-when-one-man-says]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is born at that moment when one man says to another: &quot;What! You too? I thought that no one but myself . . .&amp;#34;" -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/782349-the-inmost-significance-of-the-exaggerated-value-which-is-set</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2013 17:06:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/782349-the-inmost-significance-of-the-exaggerated-value-which-is-set]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The inmost significance of the exaggerated value which is set upon hard work appears to be this: man seems to mistrust everything that is effortless; he can only enjoy, with a good conscience, what he has acquired with toil and trouble; he refused to have anything as a gift." -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/782714-only-those-are-called-liberal-or-free-which-are-concerned</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 06:14:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/782714-only-those-are-called-liberal-or-free-which-are-concerned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only those are called liberal or free which are concerned with knowledge; those which are concerned with utilitarian ends... are called servile...

The question is... can man develop to the full as a functionary and a &quot;worker&quot; and nothing else; can a full human existence be contained within an exclusively workaday existence? Stated differently and translated back into our terms: is there such a thing as a liberal art?" -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793036-divine-worship-means-the-same-thing-where-time-is-concerned</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 06:19:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793036-divine-worship-means-the-same-thing-where-time-is-concerned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Divine worship means the same thing where time is concerned, as the temple where space is concerned. &quot;Temple&quot; means... that a particular piece of ground is specially reserved, and marked off from the remainder of the land which is used either for agriculture or habitation... Similarly in divine worship a certain definite space of time is set aside from working hours and days... and like the space allotted to the temple, is not used, is withdrawn from all merely utilitarian ends." -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793689-the-vacancy-left-by-absence-of-worship-is-filled-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 06:27:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/793689-the-vacancy-left-by-absence-of-worship-is-filled-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The vacancy left by absence of worship is filled by mere killing of time and by boredom, which is directly related to inability to enjoy leisure; for one can only be bored if the spiritual power to be leisurely has been lost. There is an entry in Baudelaire... &quot;One must work, if not from taste then at least from despair. For, to reduce everything to a single truth: work is less boring than pleasure." -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798158-in-2010-the-priesthood-quorums-and-relief-society-used-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 20:34:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Matthew Bowman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798158-in-2010-the-priesthood-quorums-and-relief-society-used-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In 2010, the Priesthood quorums and Relief Society used the same manual (Gospel Principles)… Most lessons consist of a few pages of exposition on various themes… studded with scriptural citations and quotations from leaders of the church. These are followed by points of discussion like “Think about what you can do to keep the purpose of the Sabbath in mind as you prepare for the day each week.” Gospel Principles instructs teachers not to substitute outside materials, however interesting they may be.  In practice this ensures that a common set of ideas are taught in all Mormon chapels every Sunday. That these ideas are the basic principles of the faith mean that Mormon Sunday schools and other church lessons function quite intentionally as devotional exercises rather than instruction in new concepts. The curriculum encourages teachers to ask questions that encourage catechistic reaffirmation of core beliefs. Further, lessons focus to a great extent on the importance of basic practices like prayer, paying tithing, and reading scripture rather than on doctrinal content… Correlated materials are designed not to promote theological reflection, but to produce Mormons dedicated to living the tenants of their faith." -- Matthew Bowman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/821607-it-is-possible-to-pray-in-such-a-way-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 19:16:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Josef Pieper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/821607-it-is-possible-to-pray-in-such-a-way-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is possible to pray in such a way that one does not transcend the world, in such a way that the divine is degraded to a functional part of the workaday world... then it is no longer devotion to the divine, but an attempt to master it." -- Josef Pieper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906919-next-to-theology-i-give-music-the-highest-place-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 07:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Roland Bainton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/906919-next-to-theology-i-give-music-the-highest-place-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Next to theology I give music the highest place of honor." -- Roland Bainton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955885-whereas-the-property-owning-middle-class-could-win-freedom-for-themselves</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 10:30:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Peter Singer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955885-whereas-the-property-owning-middle-class-could-win-freedom-for-themselves]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whereas the property-owning middle class could win freedom for themselves on the basis of rights to property--thus excluding others from the freedom they gain--the property-less working class possess nothing but their title as human beings. Thus they can liberate themselves only by liberating all humanity." -- Peter Singer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955891-money-is-the-universal-self-constituted-value-of-all-things-hence</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 10:34:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/955891-money-is-the-universal-self-constituted-value-of-all-things-hence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Money is the universal, self-constituted value of all things. Hence it has robbed the whole world... of its proper value. Money is the alienated essence of man's labour and life, and this alien essence dominates him as he worships it." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/968034-egoism-is-not-eliminated-by-economic-reorganization-or-by-material</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2013 17:00:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mike add a quote by Peter Singer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/968034-egoism-is-not-eliminated-by-economic-reorganization-or-by-material]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Egoism... is not eliminated by economic reorganization or by material abundance. When basic needs are satisfied, new 'needs' emerge. In our society, people want no simply clothes, but fashionable clothes; not shelter, but a house to display their wealth and taste." -- Peter Singer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
