<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/954066-sina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/954066-sina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 10:52:40 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12407-you-re-on-earth-there-s-no-cure-for-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 10:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sina add a quote by Samuel Beckett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12407-you-re-on-earth-there-s-no-cure-for-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're on Earth. There's no cure for that." -- Samuel Beckett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20710-g-reat-progress-was-evident-in-the-last-congress-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:48:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sina add a quote by Karl Marx ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20710-g-reat-progress-was-evident-in-the-last-congress-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...[G]reat progress was evident in the last Congress of the American 'Labour Union' in that among other things, it treated working women with complete equality. While in this respect the English, and still more the gallant French, are burdened with a spirit of narrow-mindedness. Anybody who knows anything of history knows that great social changes are impossible without the feminine ferment. Social progress can be measured exactly by the social position of the fair sex (the ugly ones included)." -- Karl Marx ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2008 23:49:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sina add a quote by Karl Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55036-the-foundation-of-irreligious-criticism-is-man-makes-religion-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The foundation of irreligious criticism is: Man makes religion, religion does not make man. Religion is, indeed, the self-consciousness and self-esteem of man who has either not yet won through to himself, or has already lost himself again. But man is no abstract being squatting outside the world. Man is the world of man – state, society. This state and this society produce religion, which is an inverted consciousness of the world, because they are an inverted world...

Religious suffering is, at one and the same time, the expression of real suffering and a protest against real suffering. Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people.

The abolition of religion as the illusory happiness of the people is the demand for their real happiness. To call on them to give up their illusions about their condition is to call on them to give up a condition that requires illusions. The criticism of religion is, therefore, in embryo, the criticism of that vale of tears of which religion is the halo.

Criticism has plucked the imaginary flowers on the chain not in order that man shall continue to bear that chain without fantasy or consolation, but so that he shall throw off the chain and pluck the living flower. The criticism of religion disillusions man, so that he will think, act, and fashion his reality like a man who has discarded his illusions and regained his senses, so that he will move around himself as his own true Sun. Religion is only the illusory Sun which revolves around man as long as he does not revolve around himself." -- Karl Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268877-nowadays-you-can-do-anything-that-you-want-anal-oral-fisting-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 03:18:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sina add a quote by Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/268877-nowadays-you-can-do-anything-that-you-want-anal-oral-fisting-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nowadays, you can do anything that you want—anal, oral, fisting—but you need to be wearing gloves, condoms, protection." -- Slavoj Žižek]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
