<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/954028-deborah-markus]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/954028-deborah-markus" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 21:37:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18525-one-half-of-the-world-cannot-understand-the-pleasures-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 21:37:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18525-one-half-of-the-world-cannot-understand-the-pleasures-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One half of the world cannot understand the pleasures of the other." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49597-but-there-certainly-are-not-so-many-men-of-large</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 21:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49597-but-there-certainly-are-not-so-many-men-of-large]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But there certainly are not so many men of large fortune in the world as there are pretty women to deserve them." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867082-when-she-was-older-after-ten-or-so-she-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 15:05:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867082-when-she-was-older-after-ten-or-so-she-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When she was older, after ten or so, she could tell she was being useful, but as a small child she was tolerated (only just, she knew) by this whirlwind of efficiency that was her mother organizing a party. Still she insisted on arranging fruit on a dish, or disposing ashtrays around the house, while her mother reduced her pace to Alice's. At least while &quot;helping,&quot; Alice did not feel quite so much as if she were a tiny creature on top of a great wave, frantically and hopelessly signalling to her mother, who stood indifferently on the shore, not noticing her." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867084-oh-no-i-m-not-saying-she-isn-t-a-nut---</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 15:08:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867084-oh-no-i-m-not-saying-she-isn-t-a-nut---]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, no, I'm not saying she isn't a nut -- she is -- but I've noticed before that sometimes someone like that behaves quite ordinarily with everybody, manages everything, you'd never think she was a nut, but there's just one person, with that person, she's out of control. It makes you wonder,' said Alice." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867086-it-was-not-a-question-of-philip-s-having-lost-hold</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 15:10:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867086-it-was-not-a-question-of-philip-s-having-lost-hold]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was not a question of Philip's having &quot;lost hold.&quot; He had never grasped hold. Something had not happened that should have happened: a teacher, or someone, should have said: This one, Philip Fowler, he must be a craftsman, do something small, and delicate and intricate; we must get him trained for that. Look how perfectly he does things! He can't fold a shirt or arrange some chips and a piece of fish on a plate without making a picture of it.

It had not happened." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867087-this-world-is-run-by-people-who-know-how-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 15:12:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867087-this-world-is-run-by-people-who-know-how-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This world is run by people who know how to do things. They know how things work. They are *equipped.* Up there, there's a layer of people who run everything. But we -- we're just peasants. We don't understand what's going on, and we can't do anything. ...You, running about playing at revolutions, playing little games, thinking you're important. You're just peasants, you'll never *do* anything." -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867090-oh-yes-alice-did-know-that-she-forgot-things-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 15:15:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Doris Lessing]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867090-oh-yes-alice-did-know-that-she-forgot-things-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh, yes, Alice did know that she forgot things, but not how badly, or how often. When her mind started to dazzle and to puzzle, frantically trying to lay hold of something stable, then she always at once allowed herself -- as she did now -- to slide back into her childhood, where she dwelt pleasurably on some scene or other that she had smoothed and polished and painted over and over again with fresh colour until it was like walking into a story that began, 'Once upon a time there was a little girl called Alice, with her mother, Dorothy. One morning Alice was in the kitchen with Dorothy, who was making her favourite pudding, apple with cinnamon and brown sugar and sour cream, and little Alice said, 'Mummy, I am a good girl, aren't I?" -- Doris Lessing]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867821-having-a-chronic-illness-molly-thought-was-like-being-invaded</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 14:20:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Alison Lurie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867821-having-a-chronic-illness-molly-thought-was-like-being-invaded]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Having a chronic illness, Molly thought, was like being invaded. Her grandmother back in Michigan used to tell about the day one of their cows got loose and wandered into the parlor, and the awful time they had getting her out. That was exactly what Molly's arthritis was like: as if some big old cow had got into her house and wouldn't go away. It just sat there, taking up space in her life and making everything more difficult, mooing loudly from time to time and making cow pies, and all she could do really was edge around it and put up with it.

When other people first became aware of the cow, they expressed concern and anxiety. They suggested strategies for getting the animal out of Molly's parlor: remedies and doctors and procedures, some mainstream and some New Age. They related anecdotes of friends who had removed their own cows in one way or another. But after a while they had exhausted their suggestions. Then they usually began to pretend that the cow wasn't there, and they preferred for Molly to go along with the pretense." -- Alison Lurie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867822-though-most-tourists-accepted-the-occasional-comic-misadventure-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2013 14:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Alison Lurie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/867822-though-most-tourists-accepted-the-occasional-comic-misadventure-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Though most tourists accepted the occasional comic misadventure, it was important to them that overall their vacation should be pleasant. When you spend money on a holiday you are essentially purchasing happiness: if you don't enjoy yourself you will feel defrauded." -- Alison Lurie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/872300-but-really-that-is-kind-of-silly-abigail-tried-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2013 14:22:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by William Sleator]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/872300-but-really-that-is-kind-of-silly-abigail-tried-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But really, that is kind of silly,' Abigail tried to explain. 'I mean, a book is much less personal than a programmed screen that can respond to you according to your needs, and concentrate on what's hard for you, and go fast on what's easy. A book stays the same no matter *who's* reading it. And anyway, I don't see how anyone could read a whole long book, it must be so boring!'

'But...but it wasn't,' Peter said faintly. 'I...almost forgot I was reading it. The...the whole story was going on in my head.'

'I still don't understand,' said Oliver. 'I mean, watching a real-life hologram right before your eyes is better than anything you could *imagine.*" -- William Sleator]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873070-what-would-it-mean-in-practice-to-eliminate-all-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 15:18:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873070-what-would-it-mean-in-practice-to-eliminate-all-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What would it mean in practice to eliminate all the 'negative people' from one's life? It might be a good move to separate from a chronically carping spouse, but it is not so easy to abandon the whiny toddler, the colicky infant, or the sullen teenager. And at the workplace, while it's probably advisable to detect and terminate those who show signs of becoming mass killers, there are other annoying people who might actually have something useful to say: the financial officer who keeps worrying about the bank's subprime mortgage exposure or the auto executive who questions the company's overinvestment in SUVs and trucks. Purge everyone who 'brings you down,' and you risk being very lonely, or, what is worse, cut off from reality." -- Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873072-at-issue-is-not-only-knowledge-of-the-world-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 15:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873072-at-issue-is-not-only-knowledge-of-the-world-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At issue is not only knowledge of the world but our survival as individuals and as a species. All the basic technologies ever invented by humans to feed and protect themselves depend on a relentless commitment to hard-nosed empiricism: you cannot assume that your arrowheads will pierce the hide of a bison or that your raft will float just because the omens are propitious and you have been given supernatural reassurance that they will. You have to be sure." -- Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873074-human-intellectual-progress-such-as-it-has-been-results-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 15:27:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873074-human-intellectual-progress-such-as-it-has-been-results-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human intellectual progress, such as it has been, results from our long struggle to see things 'as they are,' or in the most universally comprehensible way, and not as projections of our own emotions. Thunder is not a tantrum in the sky, disease is not a divine punishment, and not every death or accident results from witchcraft. What we call the Enlightenment and hold on to only tenuously, by our fingernails, is the slow-dawning understanding that the world is unfolding according to its own inner algorithms of cause and effect, probability and chance, without any regard for human feelings." -- Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873077-when-our-children-are-old-enough-and-if-we-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 15:31:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873077-when-our-children-are-old-enough-and-if-we-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When our children are old enough, and if we can afford to, we send them to college, where despite the recent proliferation of courses on 'happiness' and 'positive psychology,' the point is to acquire the skills not of positive thinking but of *critical* thinking, and critical thinking is inherently skeptical. The best students -- and in good colleges, also the most successful -- are the ones who raise sharp questions, even at the risk of making a professor momentarily uncomfortable. Whether the subject is literature or engineering, graduates should be capable of challenging authority figures, going against the views of their classmates, and defending novel points of view." -- Barbara Ehrenreich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873314-we-had-nothing-to-say-to-each-other-and-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 21:04:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873314-we-had-nothing-to-say-to-each-other-and-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We had nothing to say to each other; and I was conscious that not only my remarks but my presence was criticized. They wished for the truth, and doubted whether a woman could speak it or be it. I thought this courageous of them; but unsympathetic. I had to remember that one is not full grown at 21." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873315-she-seemed-determined-to-be-human-also-to-like-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 21:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873315-she-seemed-determined-to-be-human-also-to-like-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She seemed determined to be human also; to like people, even though they were stupid." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873318-she-lacks-mystery-and-the-charm-people-have-who-withdraw</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2013 21:06:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/873318-she-lacks-mystery-and-the-charm-people-have-who-withdraw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She lacks mystery; and the charm people have who withdraw, and don't care to coin their views. One figures her always in flight; so much determined to embrace everything that she fails." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876636-the-mountains-of-madness-have-many-little-plateaux-of-sanity</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 22:43:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876636-the-mountains-of-madness-have-many-little-plateaux-of-sanity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mountains of madness have many little plateaux of sanity." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876638-a-screaming-vampire-is-always-the-centre-of-attention</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 22:47:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876638-a-screaming-vampire-is-always-the-centre-of-attention]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A screaming vampire is always the centre of attention." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876639-william-wondered-why-he-always-disliked-people-who-said-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 22:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/876639-william-wondered-why-he-always-disliked-people-who-said-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["William wondered why he always disliked people who said 'no offence meant.' Maybe it was because they found it easier to say 'no offence meant' than actually refrain from giving offence." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879562-the-worst-part-the-worst-part-was-that-lord-de</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2013 14:32:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/879562-the-worst-part-the-worst-part-was-that-lord-de]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The worst part, the &lt;i&gt;worst&lt;/i&gt; part, was that Lord de Worde was never wrong. It was not a position he understood in relation to his personal geography. People who took an opposing view were insane, or dangerous, or possibly even not really people. You couldn't have an argument with Lord de Worde. Not a proper argument. An argument, from &lt;i&gt;arguer&lt;/i&gt;, meant to debate and discuss and persuade by reason. What you could have with William's father was a flaming row." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882582-just-at-that-moment-lucilla-happened-to-cross-the-lawn</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 18:06:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Hannah More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882582-just-at-that-moment-lucilla-happened-to-cross-the-lawn]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just at that moment, Lucilla happened to cross the lawn at a distance. At sight of her, I could not, as I pointed to her, forbear exclaiming in the words of Sir John's favorite poet,

There doth beauty dwell,
There most conspicuous, e'en in outward shape,
Where dawns the high expression of a mind.

&quot;This is very fine,&quot; said Sir John, sarcastically. &quot;I admire all you young enthusiastic philosophers, with your intellectual refinement. You pretend to be captivated only with _mind_. I observe, however, that previous to your raptures, you always take care to get this mind lodged in a fair and youthful form. This mental beauty is always prudently enshrined in some elegant corporeal frame, before it is worshiped. I should be glad to see some of these intellectual adorers in love with the mind of an old or ugly woman. I never heard any of you fall into ecstasies in descanting on the mind of your grandmother." -- Hannah More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882592-i-did-not-intend-making-a-philippic-against-covetousness-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 18:23:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Hannah More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882592-i-did-not-intend-making-a-philippic-against-covetousness-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not intend making a philippic against covetousness, a sin to which I believe no one here is addicted. Let us not, however, plume ourselves in not being guilty of a vice to which, as we have no natural bias so in not committing it, we resist no temptation. What I meant to insist on was, that exchanging a turbulent for a quiet sin, or a scandalous for an orderly one, is not reformation." -- Hannah More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882595-he-seemed-evidently-more-fond-of-controversy-than-of-truth</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 18:26:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Hannah More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882595-he-seemed-evidently-more-fond-of-controversy-than-of-truth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He seemed evidently more fond of controversy than of truth, and the whole turn of his conversation indicated that he derived his religious security rather from the adoption of a party, than from the implantation of a new principle." -- Hannah More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882597-if-the-almighty-chose-to-establish-his-religion-by-miracles</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 18:31:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Hannah More]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882597-if-the-almighty-chose-to-establish-his-religion-by-miracles]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If the Almighty chose to establish his religion by miracles, he chooses to carry it on by means." -- Hannah More]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882703-don-t-tell-me-from-genetics-what-ve-they-got-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 22:23:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882703-don-t-tell-me-from-genetics-what-ve-they-got-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't tell me from genetics. What've they got to do with it?&quot; said Crowley. &quot;Look at Satan. Created as an angel, grows up to be the Great Adversary. Hey, if you're going to go on about genetics, you might as well say the kid will grow up to be an angel. After all, his father was really big in Heaven in the old days. Saying he'll grow up to be a demon just because his dad _became_ one is like saying a mouse with its tail cut off will give birth to tailless mice. No. Upbringing is everything. Take it from me." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882705-evil-in-general-does-not-sleep-and-therefore-doesn-t-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2013 22:26:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882705-evil-in-general-does-not-sleep-and-therefore-doesn-t-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Evil in general does not sleep, and therefore doesn't see why anyone else should." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882959-i-rocked-in-silence-and-realized-for-the-first-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 09:35:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Jenny Lawson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882959-i-rocked-in-silence-and-realized-for-the-first-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I rocked in silence, and realized for the first time that 'home' wasn't this place anymore. It was wherever Victor was. It was both a terrifying and an enlightening realization, and I took a deep breath and thought carefully before I answered.

'Yes. I'm ready to go home.'

It was like saying hello and good-bye at the same time." -- Jenny Lawson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882960-i-sometimes-wonder-what-it-would-have-been-like-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 09:39:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Jenny Lawson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882960-i-sometimes-wonder-what-it-would-have-been-like-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sometimes wonder what it would have been like to have a childhood that was _not_ like mine. I have no real frame of reference, but when I question strangers I've found that their childhood generally had much less blood in it, and also that strangers seem uncomfortable when you question them about their childhood. But really, what else are you going to talk about in line at the liquor store? Childhood trauma seems like the natural choice, since it's the reason why most of us are in line there to begin with." -- Jenny Lawson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882963-i-ve-found-though-that-people-are-more-likely-to-share</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2013 09:43:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deborah add a quote by Jenny Lawson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/882963-i-ve-found-though-that-people-are-more-likely-to-share]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've found, though, that people are more likely to share their personal experiences if you go first, so that's why I always keep an eleven-point list of what went wrong in my childhood to share with them. Also I usually crack open a bottle of tequila to share with them, because alcohol makes me less nervous, and also because I'm from the South, and in Texas we offer drinks to strangers even when we're waiting in line at the liquor store. In Texas we call that '_southern hospitality_.' The people who own the liquor store call it 'shoplifting.' Probably because they're Yankees.

I'm not allowed to go back to that liquor store." -- Jenny Lawson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
