<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955080-pang]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955080-pang" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:52:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 10:52:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24499-be-the-change-that-you-wish-to-see-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be the change that you wish to see in the world." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132451-our-challenges-may-be-new-the-instruments-with-which-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2009 08:50:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132451-our-challenges-may-be-new-the-instruments-with-which-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our challenges may be new. The instruments with which we meet them may be new. But those values upon which our success depends - honesty and hard work, courage and fair play, tolerance and curiosity, loyalty and patriotism - these things are old. These things are true. They have been the quiet force of progress throughout our history. What is demanded then is a return to these truths. What is required of us now is a new era of responsibility - a recognition, on the part of every American, that we have duties to ourselves, our nation, and the world, duties that we do not grudgingly accept but rather seize gladly, firm in the knowledge that there is nothing so satisfying to the spirit, so defining of our character, than giving our all to a difficult task." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110129-forgiveness-is-not-about-forgetting-it-is-about-letting-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 17:46:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by William P. Young]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/110129-forgiveness-is-not-about-forgetting-it-is-about-letting-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgiveness is not about forgetting. It is about letting go of another person's throat......Forgiveness does not create a relationship. Unless people speak the truth about what they have done and change their mind and behavior, a relationship of trust is not possible. When you forgive someone you certainly release them from judgment, but without true change, no real relationship can be established.........Forgiveness in no way requires that you trust the one you forgive. But should they finally confess and repent, you will discover a miracle in your own heart that allows you to reach out and begin to build between you a bridge of reconciliation.........Forgiveness does not excuse anything.........You may have to declare your forgiveness a hundred times the first day and the second day, but the third day will be less and each day after, until one day you will realize that you have forgiven completely.  And then one day you will pray for his wholeness......" -- William P. Young]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179487-miss-ingram-was-a-mark-beneath-jealousy-she-was-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2013 09:10:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179487-miss-ingram-was-a-mark-beneath-jealousy-she-was-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Miss Ingram was a mark beneath jealousy: she was too inferior to excite feeling. Pardon the seeming paradox; I mean what I say. She was very showy, but she was not genuine; she had a fine person, many brilliant attainments, but her mind was poor, her heart barren by nature; nothing bloomed spontaneously on that soil; no unforced natural fruit delighted by its freshness. She was not good; she was not original; she used to repeat sounding phrases from books; she never offered, nor had, an opinion of her own. She advocated a high tone of sentiment, but she did not know the sensations of sympathy and pity; tenderness and truth were not in her" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22060-the-best-teacher-is-experience-and-not-through-someone-s-distorted</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 08:26:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22060-the-best-teacher-is-experience-and-not-through-someone-s-distorted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best teacher is experience and not through someone's distorted point of view" -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112822-there-s-lots-of-good-fish-in-the-sea-maybe-but-the-vast</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2013 19:57:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112822-there-s-lots-of-good-fish-in-the-sea-maybe-but-the-vast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's lots of good fish in the sea...maybe...but the vast masses seem to be mackerel or herring, and if you're not mackerel or herring yourself, you are likely to find very few good fish in the sea." -- D.H. Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510012-in-the-morning-a-new-man-was-behind-the-front</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:44:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/510012-in-the-morning-a-new-man-was-behind-the-front]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the morning a new man was behind the front desk. &quot;And how did you enjoy your stay, Sir?&quot; he asked smoothly.
&quot;It was singularly execrable,&quot; I replied.
&quot;Oh, excellent,&quot; he purred, taking my card
&quot;In fact, I would go so far as to say that the principal value of a stay in this establishment is that it is bound to make all subsequent service-related experiences seem, in comparison, refreshing.&quot;
He made a deeply appreciative expression as if to say, &quot;Praise indeed,&quot; and presnted my bill for signature. &quot;Well, we hope you'll come again.&quot;
&quot;I would sooner have bowel surgery in the woods with a a stick.&quot;
His expression wavered, then held there for a long moment. &quot;Excellent,&quot; he said again, but without a great show of conviction." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/774818-australia-is-mostly-empty-and-a-long-way-away-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:45:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/774818-australia-is-mostly-empty-and-a-long-way-away-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Australia is mostly empty and a long way away. Its population is small and its role in the world consequently peripheral. It doesn't have coups, recklessly overfish, arm disagreeable despots, grow coca in provocative quantities, or throw its weight around in a brash and unseemly manner. It is stable and peaceful and good. It doesn't need watching, and so we don't. But I will tell you this: the loss is entirely ours." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426669-a-waitress-came-out-and-plonked-in-front-of-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:45:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/426669-a-waitress-came-out-and-plonked-in-front-of-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…a waitress came out and plonked in front of each of us a small standard terra-cotta flowerpot in which had been baked a little loaf of bread.
&quot;What's this?&quot; I asked.
&quot;It's bread,&quot; she replied.
&quot;But it's in a flowerpot?&quot; She gave me a look that I was beginning to think of as the Darwin stare. It was a look that said, &quot;Yeah? So?&quot;
&quot;Well, isn't that kind of unusual?&quot;
She considered for a moment. &quot;Is a bit, I suppose.&quot; &quot;And will we be following a horticultural theme throughout the meal?&quot; Her expression contorted in a deeply pained look, as if she were trying to suck her face into the back of her head. &quot;What?&quot;
&quot;Will the main course arrive in a wheelbarrow?&quot; I elaborated helpfully. &quot;Will you be serving the salad with a pitchfork?&quot;
&quot;Oh, no. It's just the bread that's special.&quot;
&quot;I'm so pleased to hear it." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/898213-but-don-t-worry-she-continued-most-snakes-don-t-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 12:46:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Pang add a quote by Bill Bryson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/898213-but-don-t-worry-she-continued-most-snakes-don-t-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But don't worry,&quot; she continued. &quot;Most snakes don't want to hurt you. If you're out in the bush and a snake comes along, just stop dead and let it slide over your shoes.&quot;
This, I decided, was the least-likely-to-be-followed advice I have ever been given." -- Bill Bryson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
