<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955048-lisa-wuertz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955048-lisa-wuertz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:18:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29631-no-other-continent-has-endured-such-an-unspeakably-bizarre-combination</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:18:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29631-no-other-continent-has-endured-such-an-unspeakably-bizarre-combination]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No other continent has endured such an unspeakably bizarre combination of foreign thievery and foreign goodwill." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29636-for-my-entire-life-i-longed-for-love-i-knew</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:22:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lisa See]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29636-for-my-entire-life-i-longed-for-love-i-knew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For my entire life I longed for love. I knew it was not right for me — as a girl and later as a woman — to want or expect it, but I did, and this unjustified desire has been at the root of every problem I have experienced in my life." -- Lisa See]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29639-when-i-knew-i-couldn-t-suffer-another-moment-of-pain</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:24:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lisa See]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29639-when-i-knew-i-couldn-t-suffer-another-moment-of-pain]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I knew I couldn't suffer another moment of pain, and tears fell on my bloody bindings, my mother spoke softly into my ear, encouraging me to go one more hour, one more day, one more week, reminding me of the rewards I would have if I carried on a little longer. In this way, she taught me how to endure — not just the physical trials of footbinding and childbearing but the more torturous pain of the heart, mind, and soul." -- Lisa See]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:34:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434-he-s-like-a-drug-for-you-bella]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He's like a drug for you, Bella." -- Stephenie Meyer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:37:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3897-listen-to-live-is-to-be-marked-to-live-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen. To live is to be marked. To live is to change, to acquire the words of a story, and that is the only celebration we mortals really know. In perfect stillness, frankly, I've only found sorrow." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3896-every-betrayal-contains-a-perfect-moment-a-coin-stamped-heads</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:38:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3896-every-betrayal-contains-a-perfect-moment-a-coin-stamped-heads]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every betrayal contains a perfect moment, a coin stamped heads or tails with salvation on the other side." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11323-there-s-such-a-gulf-between-yourself-and-who-you-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 11:38:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11323-there-s-such-a-gulf-between-yourself-and-who-you-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's such a gulf between yourself and who you were then, but people speak to that other person and it answers; it's like having a stranger as a house guest in your skin." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:51:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:51:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22613-a-person-s-a-person-no-matter-how-small]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person's a person, no matter how small." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:51:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today you are You, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is Youer than You." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17411-think-left-and-think-right-and-think-low-and-think</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:52:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17411-think-left-and-think-right-and-think-low-and-think]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think left and think right and think low and think high. Oh, the thinks you can think up if only you try!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6575-the-soul-fortunately-has-an-interpreter---often-an-unconscious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 14:53:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6575-the-soul-fortunately-has-an-interpreter---often-an-unconscious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The soul, fortunately, has an interpreter - often an unconscious but still a faithful interpreter - in the eye." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 15:01:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in vain to say human beings ought to be satisfied with tranquillity: they must have action; and they will make it if they cannot find it. Millions are condemned to a stiller doom than mine, and millions are in silent revolt against their lot. Nobody knows how many rebellions besides political rebellions ferment in the masses of life which people earth. Women are supposed to be very calm generally: but women feel just as men feel; they need exercise for their faculties, and a field for their efforts, as much as their brothers do; they suffer from too rigid a restraint, to absolute a stagnation, precisely as men would suffer; and it is narrow-minded in their more privileged fellow-creatures to say that they ought to confine themselves to making puddings and knitting stockings, to playing on the piano and embroidering bags. It is thoughtless to condemn them, or laugh at them, if they seek to do more or learn more than custom has pronounced necessary for their sex." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99290-anybody-may-blame-me-who-likes-when-i-add-further</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 15:07:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99290-anybody-may-blame-me-who-likes-when-i-add-further]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anybody may blame me who likes, when I add further, that, now and then, when I took a walk by myself in the grounds; when I went down to the gates and looked through them along the road; or when, while Adele played with her nurse, and Mrs. Fairfax made jellies in the storeroom, I climbed the three staircases, raised the trap-door of the attic, and having reached the leads, looked out afar over sequestered field and hill, and along dim sky-line - that then I longed for a power of vision which might overpass that limit; which might reach the busy world, towns, regions full of life I had heard of but never seen - that then I desired more of practical experience than I possessed; more of intercourse with my kind, of acquaintance with variety of character, than was here within my reach." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44450-the-second-reason-caregivers-may-be-silent-about-the-dark</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2008 19:41:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Henci Goer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44450-the-second-reason-caregivers-may-be-silent-about-the-dark]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The second reason caregivers may be silent about the dark side of epidurals is that they generate big bucks for anesthesiologists and hospitals. Epidural charges range from $500 to $2500. A hospital consultant explained to me that hospitals have to maintain staff anesthesiologists around the clock to handle obstetric emergencies. In order for these doctors to make what they consider an adequate income, the hospital has to maintain something like an 80 percent epidural rate. Given this, how strongly do you think medical staff would resist the notion that epidurals are not always a good thing and most women can cope without them?" -- Henci Goer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2008 15:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49016-remember-this-for-it-is-as-true-and-true-gets]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember this, for it is as true and true gets: Your body is not a lemon. You are not a machine. The Creator is not a careless mechanic. Human female bodies have the same potential to give birth well as aardvarks, lions, rhinoceri, elephants, moose, and water buffalo. Even if it has not been your habit throughout your life so far, I recommend that you learn to think positively about your body." -- Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52350-the-techno-medical-model-of-maternity-care-unlike-the-midwifery-model</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2008 11:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52350-the-techno-medical-model-of-maternity-care-unlike-the-midwifery-model]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The techno-medical model of maternity care, unlike the midwifery model, is comparatively new on the world scene, having existed for barely two centuries. This male-derived framework for care is a product of the industrial revolution. As anthropologist Robbie Davis-Floyd has described in detail, underlying the technocratic mode of care of our own time is an assumption that the human body is a machine and that the female body in particular is a machine full of shortcomings and defects. Pregnancy and labor are seen as illnesses, which, in order not to be harmful to mother or baby, must be treated with drugs and medical equipment. Within the techno-medical model of birth, some medical intervention is considered necessary for every birth, and birth is safe only in retrospect." -- Ina May Gaskin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 22:47:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14485-but-i-don-t-want-to-go-among-mad-people-alice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I don’t want to go among mad people,&quot; Alice remarked.
&quot;Oh, you can’t help that,&quot; said the Cat: &quot;we’re all mad here. I’m mad. You’re mad.&quot;
&quot;How do you know I’m mad?&quot; said Alice.
&quot;You must be,&quot; said the Cat, or you wouldn’t have come here." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6028-the-time-has-come-the-walrus-said-to-talk-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 22:48:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6028-the-time-has-come-the-walrus-said-to-talk-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time has come,&quot; the walrus said, &quot;to talk of many things: Of shoes and ships - and sealing wax - of cabbages and kings" -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12608-when-i-use-a-word-humpty-dumpty-said-in-rather</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 07:09:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12608-when-i-use-a-word-humpty-dumpty-said-in-rather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I use a word,’ Humpty Dumpty said in rather a scornful tone, ‘it means just what I choose it to mean — neither more nor less.’

’The question is,’ said Alice, ‘whether you can make words mean so many different things.’

’The question is,’ said Humpty Dumpty, ‘which is to be master — that’s all." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80919-you-are-old-father-william-the-young-man-said-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 22:53:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80919-you-are-old-father-william-the-young-man-said-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are old Father William,' the young man said, 'and your hair has become very white; and yet you incessantly stand on your head-do you think, at your age, it is right?" -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47608-one-of-the-deep-secrets-of-life-is-that-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 13:25:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47608-one-of-the-deep-secrets-of-life-is-that-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One of the deep secrets of life is that all that is really worth the doing is what we do for others." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128238-most-anti-vaccine-books-claim-that-all-shots-are-bad-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 11:05:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Robert Sears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128238-most-anti-vaccine-books-claim-that-all-shots-are-bad-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most anti-vaccine books claim that all shots are bad, the diseases aren't really anything to fear, and as long as you live a natural and healthy lifestyle, you don't have to worry. I think this is a very irresponsible approach to the vaccine issue. Vaccines are beneficial in ridding our population of both serious and nonserious diseases." -- Robert Sears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128957-obviously-the-more-kids-who-are-vaccinated-the-better-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 19:33:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Robert Sears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128957-obviously-the-more-kids-who-are-vaccinated-the-better-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Obviously, the more kids who are vaccinated, the better our country is protected and the less likely it is that any child will die from a disease. Some parents, however, aren't willing to risk the very rare side effects of vaccines, so they choose to skip the shots. Their children benefit from herd immunity (the protection of all the vaccinated kids around them) without risking the vaccines themselves. Is this selfish? Perhaps. But as parents you have to decide. Are you supposed to make decisions that are good for the country as a whole? Or do you base your decision on what's best for your own child as an individual? Can we fault parents for putting their own child's health ahead of the other kids' around him?" -- Robert Sears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128958-what-i-really-don-t-understand-is-why-many-doctors-kick</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 19:37:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Robert Sears]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128958-what-i-really-don-t-understand-is-why-many-doctors-kick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What I really don't understand is why many doctors kick patients our of their practice over this issue. What's wrong with simply disagreeing with parents but still providing medical care to their child? That's what the American Academy of Pediatrics tells us we should do. Read them the riot act once then move on and be their doctor. A family that chooses not to vaccinate still needs medical care. Sure, their child may catch a vaccine-preventable disease, and yes, their unvaccinated child decreases the local herd immunity and puts other kids at risk, but that is still their choice. Parents of patients refuse to follow my medical advice every day. " -- Robert Sears]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129580-all-of-that-is-true-responded-don-quixote-but-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 20:08:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129580-all-of-that-is-true-responded-don-quixote-but-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All of that is true,’ responded Don Quixote, ‘but we cannot all be friars, and God brings His children to heaven by many paths: chivalry is a religion, and there are sainted knights in Glory.’

Yes,’ responded Sancho, ‘but I’ve heard that there are more friars in heaven than knights errant.’

That is true,’ responded Don Quixote, ‘because the number of religious is greater than the number of knights.’

There are many who are errant,’ said Sancho.

Many,’ responded Don Quixote, ‘but few who deserve to be called knights." -- Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 12:40:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9770-i-cannot-live-without-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I cannot live without books." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17386-the-man-who-reads-nothing-at-all-is-better-educated</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 12:41:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Thomas Jefferson ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17386-the-man-who-reads-nothing-at-all-is-better-educated]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who reads nothing at all is better educated than the man who reads nothing but newspapers." -- Thomas Jefferson ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26192-i-had-rather-be-shut-up-in-a-very-modest</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 12:42:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26192-i-had-rather-be-shut-up-in-a-very-modest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had rather be shut up in a very modest cottage with my books, my family and a few old friends, dining on simple bacon, and letting the world roll on as it liked, than to occupy the most splendid post, which any human power can give." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137015-accepting-the-reality-of-our-broken-flawed-lives-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 22:52:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Michael Yaconelli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137015-accepting-the-reality-of-our-broken-flawed-lives-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Accepting the reality of our broken, flawed lives is the beginning of spirituality not because the spiritual life will remove our flaws but because we let go of seeking perfection and, instead, seek God, the one who is present in the tangledness of our lives. " -- Michael Yaconelli]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
