<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955514-juliette-williams]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955514-juliette-williams" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 13:18:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 13:18:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4703-the-aim-of-life-is-to-live-and-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The aim of life is to live, and to live means to be aware, joyously, drunkenly, serenely, divinely aware." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/962-develop-an-interest-in-life-as-you-see-it-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 13:18:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/962-develop-an-interest-in-life-as-you-see-it-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Develop an interest in life as you see it; the people, things, literature, music - the world is so rich, simply throbbing with rich treasures, beautiful souls and interesting people. Forget yourself." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 13:18:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Henry Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4786-every-day-we-slaughter-our-finest-impulses-that-is-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every day we slaughter our finest impulses. That is why we get a heartache when we read those lines written by the hand of a master and recognize them as our own, as the tender shoots which we stifled because we lacked the faith to believe in our own powers, our own criterion of truth and beauty. Every man, when he gets quiet, when he becomes desperately honest with himself, is capable of uttering profound truths. We all derive from the same source. there is no mystery about the origin of things. We are all part of creation, all kings, all poets, all musicians; we have only to open up, only to discover what is already there." -- Henry Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Feb 2008 13:47:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Philip Pullman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10111-we-don-t-need-a-list-of-rights-and-wrongs-tables]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don’t need a list of rights and wrongs, tables of dos and don’ts: we need books, time, and silence. &lt;I&gt;Thou shalt not&lt;/I&gt; is soon forgotten, but &lt;I&gt;Once upon a time&lt;/I&gt; lasts forever." -- Philip Pullman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4167-if-you-do-follow-your-bliss-you-put-yourself-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 14:10:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Joseph Campbell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4167-if-you-do-follow-your-bliss-you-put-yourself-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you do follow your bliss you put yourself on a kind of track that has been there all the while, waiting for you, and the life that you ought to be living is the one you are living. Follow your bliss and don't be afraid, and doors will open where you didn't know they were going to be." -- Joseph Campbell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 11:30:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2627-the-trouble-with-having-an-open-mind-of-course-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble with having an open mind, of course, is that people will insist on coming along and trying to put things in it." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2008 11:30:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2634-give-a-man-a-fire-and-he-s-warm-for-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Give a man a fire and he's warm for a day, but set fire to him and he's warm for the rest of his life." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 16:43:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 16:44:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by William W. Purkey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10123-you-ve-gotta-dance-like-there-s-nobody-watching-love-like-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You've gotta dance like there's nobody watching,
Love like you'll never be hurt,
Sing like there's nobody listening,
And live like it's heaven on earth." -- William W. Purkey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 16:44:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 16:45:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2011 16:13:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14648-we-come-spinning-out-of-nothingness-scattering-stars-like-dust</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2012 11:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14648-we-come-spinning-out-of-nothingness-scattering-stars-like-dust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We come spinning out of nothingness, scattering stars like dust." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12885-i-am-certain-of-nothing-but-the-holiness-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 14:30:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by John Keats]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12885-i-am-certain-of-nothing-but-the-holiness-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am certain of nothing but the holiness of the Heart's affections and the truth of the Imagination." -- John Keats]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:40:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228647-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up. You build up all these defenses, you build up a whole suit of armor, so that nothing can hurt you, then one stupid person, no different from any other stupid person, wanders into your stupid life...You give them a piece of you. They didn't ask for it. They did something dumb one day, like kiss you or smile at you, and then your life isn't your own anymore. Love takes hostages. It gets inside you. It eats you out and leaves you crying in the darkness, so simple a phrase like 'maybe we should be just friends' turns into a glass splinter working its way into your heart. It hurts. Not just in the imagination. Not just in the mind. It's a soul-hurt, a real gets-inside-you-and-rips-you-apart pain. I hate love." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:40:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132670-i-hope-you-will-have-a-wonderful-year-that-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope you will have a wonderful year, that you'll dream dangerously and outrageously, that you'll make something that didn't exist before you made it, that you will be loved and that you will be liked, and that you will have people to love and to like in return. And, most importantly (because I think there should be more kindness and more wisdom in the world right now), that you will, when you need to be, be wise, and that you will always be kind." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/81428-d-on-t-ever-apologize-to-an-author-for-buying-something-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[D]on't ever apologize to an author for buying something in paperback, or taking it out from a library (that's what they're there for. Use your library). Don't apologize to this author for buying books second hand, or getting them from bookcrossing or borrowing a friend's copy. What's important to me is that people read the books and enjoy them, and that, at some point in there, the book was bought by someone. And that people who like things, tell other people. The most important thing is that people read... " -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115834-i-think-i-fell-in-love-with-her-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 20:41:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Juliette add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/115834-i-think-i-fell-in-love-with-her-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think I fell in love with her, a little bit. Isn't that dumb? But it was like I knew her. Like she was my oldest, dearest friend. The kind of person you can tell anything to, no matter how bad, and they'll still love you, because they know you. I wanted to go with her. I wanted her to notice me. And then she stopped walking. Under the moon, she stopped. And looked at us. She looked at me. Maybe she was trying to tell me something; I don't know. She probably didn't even know I was there. But I'll always love her. All my life." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
