<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955689-geoffery]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/955689-geoffery" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 10:42:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1954-we-believe-that-we-invent-symbols-the-truth-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 10:42:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffery add a quote by Gene Wolfe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1954-we-believe-that-we-invent-symbols-the-truth-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We believe that we invent symbols. The truth is that they invent us; we are their creatures, shaped by their hard, defining edges. When soldiers take their oath they are given a coin, an asimi stamped with the profile of the Autarch. Their acceptance of that coin is their acceptance of the special duties and burdens of military life&amp;mdash;they are soldiers from that moment, though they may know nothing of the management of arms. I did not know that then, but it is a profound mistake to believe that we must know of such things to be influenced by them, and in fact to believe so is to believe in the most debased and superstitious kind of magic. The would-be sorcerer alone has faith in the efficacy of pure knowledge; rational people know that things act of themselves or not at all." -- Gene Wolfe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48841-it-seems-to-me-i-am-trying-to-tell-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 13:23:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Geoffery add a quote by Joseph Conrad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48841-it-seems-to-me-i-am-trying-to-tell-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me I am trying to tell you a dream--making a vain attempt, because no relation of a dream can convey the dream-sensation, that commingling of absurdity, surprise, and bewilderment in a tremor of struggling revolt, that notion of being captured by the incredible which is of the very essence of dreams...No, it is impossible; it is impossible to convey the life-sensation of any given epoch of one's existence--that which makes its truth, its meaning--its subtle and penetrating essence. It is impossible. We live, as we dream-alone..." -- Joseph Conrad]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
