<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/957353-ditha-ayu]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/957353-ditha-ayu" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:13:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189754-stop-fighting-me-he-said-trying-to-pull-on-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:13:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189754-stop-fighting-me-he-said-trying-to-pull-on-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stop fighting me!&quot; he said, trying to pull on the arm he held.

He was in a precarious position himself, straddling the rail as he tried to lean over far enough to get me and actually hold onto me.

“Let go of me!” I yelled back.

But he was too strong and managed to haul most of me over the rail, enough so that I wasn’t in total danger of falling again.

See, here’s the thing. In that moment before I let go, I really had been contemplating my death. I’d come to terms with it and accepted it. I also, however, had known Dimitri might do something exactly like this. He was just that fast and that good. That was why I was holding my stake in the hand that was dangling free.

I looked him in the eye. &quot;I will always love you.&quot;

Then I plunged the stake into his chest.

It wasn’t as precise a blow as I would have liked, not with the skilled way he was dodging. I struggled to get the stake in deep enough to his heart, unsure if I could do it from this angle. Then, his struggles stopped. His eyes stared at me, stunned, and his lips parted, almost into a smile, albeit a grisly and pained one.

&quot;That’s what I was supposed to say. . .” he gasped out.

Those were his last words." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189200-no-dimitri-interrupted-gently-he-moved-his-face-toward-mine</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:14:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189200-no-dimitri-interrupted-gently-he-moved-his-face-toward-mine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No,&quot; Dimitri interrupted gently. He moved his face toward mine, our foreheads nearly touching. &quot;It won't happen to you. You're too strong. You'll fight it, just like you did this
time.&quot;
&quot;I only did because you were here.&quot; He wrapped his arms around me, and I buried my face in his chest. &quot;I can't do it by myself,&quot; I whispered.
&quot;You can,&quot; he said. There was a tremulous note in his voice. &quot;You're strong—you're so, so strong. It's why I love you." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189198-we-can-t-he-told-me-i-know-i-agreed-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:14:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/189198-we-can-t-he-told-me-i-know-i-agreed-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can't...&quot; he told me.
&quot;I know,&quot; I agreed.

Then his mouth was on mine again, and this time, I knew there would be no turning back. There were no walls this time. Our bodies wrapped together as he tried to get my coat off, then his shirt, then my shirt. ... It really was a lot like when we'd fought out on the quad earlier-that same passion and heat. I think at the end of the day, the instincts that power fighting and sex aren't so different. They all come from an animal side of us. 

Yet, as more and more clothes came off, it went beyond just animal passion. It was sweet and wonderful at the same time. When I looked into his eyes, I could see without a doubt that he loved me more than anyone else in the world, that I was his salvation, the same way that he was mine. I'd never expected my first time to be in a cabin in the woods, but I realized the place didn't matter. The person did. With someone you loved, you could be anywhere, and it would be incredible. Being in the most luxurious bed in the world wouldn't matter if you were with someone you didn't love." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184606-i-love-you-roza-he-kissed-me-again-i-ll-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:15:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184606-i-love-you-roza-he-kissed-me-again-i-ll-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you, Roza.&quot; He kissed me again. &quot;I'll always be here for you. I'm not going to let anything happen to you.&quot;
   The words were wonderful and dangerous. He shouldn't have said anything like that to me. He shouldn't have been promising he'd protect me, not when he was supposed to dedicate his life to protecting Moroi like Lissa. I couldn't be first in his heart, just like he couldn't be first in mine. That was why I shouldn't have said what I said next-but I did anyway.
   &quot;And I won't let anything happen to you,&quot; I promised. &quot;I love you.&quot; He kissed me again, swallowing off any other words I might have added." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157629-do-you-think-i-m-pretty-i-think-you-re-beautiful-beautiful</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:22:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157629-do-you-think-i-m-pretty-i-think-you-re-beautiful-beautiful]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you think I'm pretty?
I think you're beautiful
Beautiful?
You are so beautiful, it hurts sometimes." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79196-the-spell-victor-said-you-had-to-want-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 22:22:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Richelle Mead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/79196-the-spell-victor-said-you-had-to-want-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The spell. Victor said you had to want me... to care about me... for it to work.&quot; When he didn't say anything, I tried to grip his shirt, but my fingers were too weak. &quot;Did you? Did you want me?&quot;
His words came out thickly. &quot;Yes, Roza. I did want you. I still do. I wish... we could be together.&quot;
&quot;Then why did you lie to me?&quot;
We reached the clinic, and he managed to open the door while still holding me. As soon as he stepped inside, he began yelling for help. 
&quot;Why did you lie?&quot; I murmured again.
Still holding me in his arms, he looked down at me. I could hear voices and footsteps getting closer.
&quot;Because we can't be together.&quot;
&quot;Because of the age thing, right?&quot; I asked. &quot;Because you're my mentor?&quot;
His fingertip gently wiped away a tear that had escaped down my cheek. &quot;That's part of it,&quot; he said. &quot;But also... well, you and I will both be Lissa's gaurdians someday. I need to protect her at all cost. If a pack of Strogoi come, I need to throw my body between them and her.&quot;
I know that. Of course that's what you have to do.&quot; The black sparkles were dancing in front of my eyes again. I was fading out.
&quot;No. If I let myself love you, I won't throw myself in front of her. I'll throw myself in front of you." -- Richelle Mead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243505-aku-gak-mau-sepuluh-dua-puluh-tahun-dari-hari-ini</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 08:38:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Dee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/243505-aku-gak-mau-sepuluh-dua-puluh-tahun-dari-hari-ini]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["aku gak mau sepuluh, dua puluh tahun dari hari ini, aku masih terus-terusan memikirkan orang yg sama. bingung di antara penyesalan dan penerimaan." -- Dee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478659-karena-hati-tak-perlu-memilih-ia-selalu-tahu-kemana-harus</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 08:38:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Dee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/478659-karena-hati-tak-perlu-memilih-ia-selalu-tahu-kemana-harus]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Karena hati tak perlu memilih, ia selalu tahu kemana harus berlabuh" -- Dee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 06:49:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2534-we-accept-the-love-we-think-we-deserve]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We accept the love we think we deserve." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 06:50:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8716-and-in-that-moment-i-swear-we-were-infinite]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And in that moment, I swear we were infinite." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14397-i-am-very-interested-and-fascinated-how-everyone-loves-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 07:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14397-i-am-very-interested-and-fascinated-how-everyone-loves-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am very interested and fascinated how everyone loves each other, but no one really likes each other." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244677-this-moment-will-just-be-another-story-someday</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 10:04:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ditha add a quote by Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/244677-this-moment-will-just-be-another-story-someday]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This moment will just be another story someday." -- Stephen Chbosky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
