<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/957460-jeff-volkmann]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/957460-jeff-volkmann" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 18:43:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58095-lucius-art-thou-not-sorry-for-these-heinous-deeds-aaron</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2008 18:43:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58095-lucius-art-thou-not-sorry-for-these-heinous-deeds-aaron]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["LUCIUS. Art thou not sorry for these heinous deeds?

AARON. Ay, that I had not done a thousand more.
Even now I curse the day- and yet, I think,
Few come within the compass of my curse-
Wherein I did not some notorious ill;
As kill a man, or else devise his death;
Ravish a maid, or plot the way to do it;
Accuse some innocent, and forswear myself;
Set deadly enmity between two friends;
Make poor men's cattle break their necks;
Set fire on barns and hay-stacks in the night,
And bid the owners quench them with their tears.
Oft have I digg'd up dead men from their graves,
And set them upright at their dear friends' door
Even when their sorrows almost was forgot,
And on their skins, as on the bark of trees,
Have with my knife carved in Roman letters
'Let not your sorrow die, though I am dead.'
Tut, I have done a thousand dreadful things
As willingly as one would kill a fly;
And nothing grieves me heartily indeed
But that I cannot do ten thousand more." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6173-we-re-always-thinking-of-eternity-as-an-idea-that-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 16:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6173-we-re-always-thinking-of-eternity-as-an-idea-that-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're always thinking of eternity as an idea that cannot be understood, something immense. But why must it be? What if, instead of all this, you suddenly find just a little room there, something like a village bath-house, grimy, and spiders in every corner, and that's all eternity is.  Sometimes, you know, I can't help feeling that that's what it is." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 16:49:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12841-everyone-thinks-of-changing-the-world-but-no-one-thinks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone thinks of changing the world, but no one thinks of changing himself." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 16:49:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All happy families are alike; each unhappy family is unhappy in its own way." -- Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23336-he-suddenly-recalled-from-plato-s-symposium-people-were-hermaphrodites-until</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 16:58:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23336-he-suddenly-recalled-from-plato-s-symposium-people-were-hermaphrodites-until]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He suddenly recalled from Plato's Symposium: People were hermaphrodites until God split then in two, and now all the halves wander the world over seeking one another. Love is the longing for the half of ourselves we have lost." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5723-now-i-will-tell-you-the-answer-to-my-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 17:01:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5723-now-i-will-tell-you-the-answer-to-my-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I will tell you the answer to my question. It is this. The Party seeks power entirely for its own sake. We are not interested in the good of others; we are interested solely in power, pure power. What pure power means you will understand presently. We are different from the oligarchies of the past in that we know what we are doing. All the others, even those who resembled ourselves, were cowards and hypocrites. The German Nazis and the Russian Communists came very close to us in their methods, but they never had the courage to recognize their own motives. They pretended, perhaps they even believed, that they had seized power unwillingly and for a limited time, and that just around the corner there lay a paradise where human beings would be free and equal. We are not like that. We know what no one ever seizes power with the intention of relinquishing it. Power is not a means; it is an end. One does not establish a dictatorship in order to safeguard a revolution; one makes the revolution in order to establish the dictatorship. The object of persecution is persecution. The object of torture is torture. The object of power is power. Now you begin to understand me." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1730-always-do-sober-what-you-said-you-d-do-drunk-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 17:05:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1730-always-do-sober-what-you-said-you-d-do-drunk-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always do sober what you said you'd do drunk. That will teach you to keep your mouth shut." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21937-inside-myself-is-a-place-where-i-live-all-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 17:08:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21937-inside-myself-is-a-place-where-i-live-all-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Inside myself is a place where I live all alone and that's where you renew your springs that never dry up. " -- Pearl S. Buck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 09:22:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7570-if-you-have-a-garden-and-a-library-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need." -- Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46762-nescire-autem-quid-antequam-natus-sis-acciderit-id-est-semper</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 09:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46762-nescire-autem-quid-antequam-natus-sis-acciderit-id-est-semper]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nescire autem quid antequam natus sis acciderit, id est semper esse puerum. (To be ignorant of what occurred before you were born is to remain always a child.)" -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2008 09:22:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150864-no-single-man-makes-history-history-cannot-be-seen-just</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2009 17:28:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Boris Pasternak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/150864-no-single-man-makes-history-history-cannot-be-seen-just]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No single man makes history.  History cannot be seen, just as one cannot see grass growing.  Wars and revolutions, kings and Robespierres, are history's organic agents, its yeast.  But revolutions are made by fanatical men of action with one-track mind, geniuses in their ability to confine themselves to a limited field.  They overturn the old order in a few hours or days, the whole upheaval takes a few weeks or at most years, but the fanatical spirit that inspired the upheavals is worshiped for decades thereafter, for centuries.  " -- Boris Pasternak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111084-i-know-you-are-here-to-kill-me-shoot-coward</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2009 10:22:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jeff add a quote by Ernesto &quot;Che&quot; Guevara]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111084-i-know-you-are-here-to-kill-me-shoot-coward]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know you are here to kill me. Shoot, coward, you are only going to kill a man." -- Ernesto &quot;Che&quot; Guevara]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
