<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/958157-abby]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/958157-abby" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 06:20:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178237-i-love-books-by-the-way-way-more-than-movies</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 06:20:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178237-i-love-books-by-the-way-way-more-than-movies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love books, by the way, way more than movies. Movies tell you what to think. A good book lets you choose a few thoughts for yourself. Movies show you the pink house. A good book tells you there's a pink house and lets you paint some of the finishing touches, maybe choose the roof style,park your own car out front. My imagination has always topped anything a movie could come up with. Case in point, those darned Harry Potter movies. That was so not what that part-Veela-chick, Fleur Delacour, looked like." -- Karen Marie Moning]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350491-there-was-another-life-that-i-might-have-had-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 09:47:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350491-there-was-another-life-that-i-might-have-had-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There was another life that I might have had, but I am having this one." -- Kazuo Ishiguro]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84940-but-it-s-the-truth-even-if-it-didn-t-happen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2014 13:56:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Ken Kesey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84940-but-it-s-the-truth-even-if-it-didn-t-happen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But it's the truth even if it didn't happen." -- Ken Kesey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974178-so-do-we-pass-the-ghosts-that-haunt-us-later</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 20:15:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974178-so-do-we-pass-the-ghosts-that-haunt-us-later]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So do we pass the ghosts that haunt us later in our lives; they sit undramatically by the roadside like poor beggars, and we see them only from the corners of our eyes, if we see them at all. The idea that they have been waiting there for us rarely if ever crosses our minds. Yet they do wait, and when we have passed, they gather up their bundles of memory and fall in behind, treading in our footsteps and catching up, little by little." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242590-behind-the-naive-vanities-the-daydreams-they-had-very-badly</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 20:42:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242590-behind-the-naive-vanities-the-daydreams-they-had-very-badly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Behind the naive vanities, the daydreams, they had very badly wanted to be writers. Had wanted it without knowing at all what it was they wanted, their fervor making up for their ignorance. His older self was cooler, more noncommittal, for he had learned that to publicize your goals means running the risk of falling short of them." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245081-you-spend-hours-wrestling-with-yourself-trying-to-keep-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 20:50:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1245081-you-spend-hours-wrestling-with-yourself-trying-to-keep-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You spend hours wrestling with yourself, trying to keep your vision intact, your intensity undiminished. Sometimes I have to stick my head under the tap to get my wits back. And for what? You know what publishing is like these days. Paper costs going up all the time. Nothing gets printed unless it can be made into a movie. Everything is media. Crooked politicians sell their unwritten memoirs for thousands. I’ve got a great idea for a novel. It’s about a giant shark who’s possessed by a demon while swimming in the Bermuda Triangle. And the demon talks in CB lingo, see? There’ll be recipes in the back." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1247949-the-artist-s-impressions-of-a-walk-in-the-woods-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 20:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1247949-the-artist-s-impressions-of-a-walk-in-the-woods-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Artist’s impressions of a walk in the woods. The Artist’s view on viewing. The Artist on Art. How do you get your ideas for stories, Mr. Valentine? Well, I simply exploit everything I come into contact with. One ended, of course, by losing all spontaneity. You saw people as characters, sunsets as an excuse for similes—" -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253257-it-was-the-furthest-thing-in-the-world-from-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 19:30:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1253257-it-was-the-furthest-thing-in-the-world-from-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was the furthest thing in the world from the rosy-fingered dawn of poetry and old Technicolor movies; this was an anti-dawn, damp and as pale as the cheek of a day-old corpse." -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259154-aomame-imagined-1926-czechoslovakia-the-first-world-war-had-ended</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 19:15:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1259154-aomame-imagined-1926-czechoslovakia-the-first-world-war-had-ended]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aomame imagined 1926 Czechoslovakia: The First World War had ended, and the country was freed from the long rule of the Hapsburg Dynasty. As they enjoyed the peaceful respite visiting central Europe, people drank Pilsner beer in cafés and manufactured handsome light machine guns. Two years earlier, in utter obscurity, Franz Kafka had left the world behind. Soon Hitler would come out of nowhere and gobble up this beautiful little country in the blink of an eye, but at the time no one knew what hardships lay in store for them. This may be the most important proposition revealed by history: “At the time, no one knew what was coming." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260477-tengo-did-not-know-for-certain-whether-he-wanted-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 20:33:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260477-tengo-did-not-know-for-certain-whether-he-wanted-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tengo did not know for certain whether he wanted to be a professional novelist, nor was he sure he had the talent to write fiction. What he did know was that he could not help spending a large part of every day writing fiction. To him, writing was like breathing." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260496-now-the-room-has-the-contours-and-atmosphere-of-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 20:53:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1260496-now-the-room-has-the-contours-and-atmosphere-of-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now the room has the contours and atmosphere of all rooms in which people stay awake talking. The fluorescent light is grainy, staring. The clutter on the kitchen table—ketchup bottle, sagging butter dish, tin of Nestlé Quik, the rowdy crudded ashtray—the world is narrowed into these, a little universe that the eyes return to again and again. Now it begins, the sorting and testing of words. Remember that words are not symbols of other words. There are words which, when tinkered with, become honest representatives of the cresting blood, the fine living net of nerves. Define rain. Or even joy. It can be done." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1265734-all-s-well-that-ends-well-assuming-there-s-an-end-somewhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 06:14:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1265734-all-s-well-that-ends-well-assuming-there-s-an-end-somewhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All’s well that ends well.” “Assuming there’s an end somewhere,” Aomame said. Tamaru formed some short creases near his mouth that were faintly reminiscent of a smile. “There has to be an end somewhere. It’s just that nothing’s labeled ‘This is the end.’ Is the top rung of a ladder labeled ‘This is the last rung. Please don’t step higher than this’?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1266422-everything-seemed-to-be-coated-with-rust-even-the-child-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 21:06:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1266422-everything-seemed-to-be-coated-with-rust-even-the-child-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything seemed to be coated with rust. Even the child’s red hair added to the impression that we had strayed into a strange, decaying land where oxidation was king. Oxidation, I never tire of reminding myself, is what happens when oxygen attacks. It was nibbling away at my own skin at this very moment and at the skin of the Gypsy seated beside me, although it was easy to see that she was much further gone than I was. From my own early chemical experiments in the laboratory at Buckshaw, I had verified that in some cases, such as when iron is combusted in an atmosphere of pure oxygen, oxidation is a wolf that tears hungrily at its food: so hungrily, in fact, that the iron bursts into flames. What we call fire is really no more than our old friend oxidation working at fever pitch. But when oxidation nibbles more slowly—more delicately, like a tortoise—at the world around us, without a flame, we call it rust and we sometimes scarcely notice as it goes about its business consuming everything from hairpins to whole civilizations. I have sometimes thought that if we could stop oxidation we could stop time, and perhaps be able to—" -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1267174-as-dangerous-as-komatsu-s-plan-might-be-he-could-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2014 11:45:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1267174-as-dangerous-as-komatsu-s-plan-might-be-he-could-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As dangerous as Komatsu’s plan might be, he could not possibly stop rewriting the novella at this point. He might have been able to give up on the idea before he started working on it, but that was out of the question now. He was up to his neck in it. He was breathing the air of its world, adapting to its gravity. The story’s essence had permeated every part of him, to the walls of his viscera. Now the story was begging him to rework it: he could feel it pleading with him for help. This was something that only Tengo could do. It was a job well worth doing, a job he simply had to do." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269205-what-you-call-your-personality-you-know-it-s-not-the-actual</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 03:11:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1269205-what-you-call-your-personality-you-know-it-s-not-the-actual]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What you call your personality, you know?—it’s not the actual bones, or teeth, something solid. It’s more like a flame. A flame can be upright, and a flame can flicker in the wind, a flame can be extinguished so there’s no sign of it, like it had never been." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274065-to-know-the-narrative-in-advance-is-to-turn-yourself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 06:12:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274065-to-know-the-narrative-in-advance-is-to-turn-yourself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To know the narrative in advance is to turn yourself into a machine,” the Manager continues. “What makes humans human is precisely that they do not know the future. That is why they do the fateful and amusing things they do: who can say how anything will turn out? Therein lies the only hope for redemption, discovery, and—let’s be frank—fun, fun, fun! There might be things people will get away with. And not just motel towels. There might be great illicit loves, enduring joy, faith-shaking accidents with farm machinery. But you have to not know in order to see what stories your life’s efforts bring you. The mystery is all." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274336-the-moon-had-been-observing-the-earth-close-up-longer-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 12:02:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1274336-the-moon-had-been-observing-the-earth-close-up-longer-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The moon had been observing the earth close-up longer than anyone. It must have witnessed all of the phenomena occurring—and all of the acts carried out—on this earth. But the moon remained silent; it told no stories. All it did was embrace the heavy past with cool, measured detachment. On the moon there was neither air nor wind. Its vacuum was perfect for preserving memories unscathed. No one could unlock the heart of the moon. Aomame raised her glass to the moon and asked, “Have you gone to bed with someone in your arms lately?” The moon did not answer. “Do you have any friends?” she asked. The moon did not answer. “Don’t you get tired of always playing it cool?” The moon did not answer." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460467-tengo-knew-that-time-could-become-deformed-as-it-moved</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 14:49:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/460467-tengo-knew-that-time-could-become-deformed-as-it-moved]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tengo knew that time could become deformed as it moved forward. Time itself was uniform in composition, but once consumed, it took on a deformed shape. One period of time might be terribly heavy and long, while another could be light and short. Occasionally the order of things could be reversed, and in the worst cases order itself could vanish entirely. Sometimes things that should not be there at all might be added onto time. By adjusting time this way to suit their own purposes, people probably adjusted the meaning of their existences. In other words, by adding such operations to time, they were able—but just barely—to preserve their own sanity. Surely, if a person had to accept the time through which he had just passed uniformly in the given order, his nerves could not bear the strain. Such a life, Tengo felt, would be sheer torture." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473503-according-to-chekhov-tamaru-said-rising-from-his-chair-once</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 09:51:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473503-according-to-chekhov-tamaru-said-rising-from-his-chair-once]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["According to Chekhov,&quot; Tamaru said, rising from his chair, &quot;once a gun appears in a story, it has to be fired.&quot;
&quot;Meaning what?&quot;
&quot;Meaning, don't bring unnecessary props into a story. If a pistol appears, it has to be fired at some point. Chekhov liked to write stories that did away with all useless ornamentation." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275921-in-this-world-there-is-no-absolute-good-no-absolute</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2014 17:16:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1275921-in-this-world-there-is-no-absolute-good-no-absolute]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In this world, there is no absolute good, no absolute evil,” the man said. “Good and evil are not fixed, stable entities but are continually trading places. A good may be transformed into an evil in the next second. And vice versa. Such was the way of the world that Dostoevsky depicted in The Brothers Karamazov. The most important thing is to maintain the balance between the constantly moving good and evil. If you lean too much in either direction, it becomes difficult to maintain actual morals. Indeed, balance itself is the good." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1282723-an-inscrutable-new-world-silently-surrounded-him-like-lapping-dark</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 06:23:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Abby add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1282723-an-inscrutable-new-world-silently-surrounded-him-like-lapping-dark]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An inscrutable new world silently surrounded him like lapping dark water. Perhaps a new trouble had chased out the old one. Perhaps the old, familiar riddle had been replaced by a fresh, new one. The thought came to Tengo without irony. Nor did he feel any need to complain about it. Whatever the composition of this new world might be, I surely have no choice but to accept it in silence. There’s no way to pick and choose. Even in the world that existed until now, there was no choice. It’s the same thing. And besides, he asked himself, even if I wanted to lodge a complaint, who is there for me to complain to?" -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
