<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/958204-greg]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/958204-greg" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 18:58:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46342-if-two-people-stare-at-each-other-for-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 18:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Robert Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46342-if-two-people-stare-at-each-other-for-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If two people stare at each other for more than a few seconds, it means they are about to either make love or fight. Something similar might be said about human societies. If two nearby societies are in contact for any length of time, they will either trade or fight. The first is non-zero-sum social integration, and the second ultimately brings it." -- Robert Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46343-commerce-with-all-nations-alliance-with-none-should-be-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 18:59:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46343-commerce-with-all-nations-alliance-with-none-should-be-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Commerce with all nations, alliance with none, should be our motto." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46344-i-predict-future-happiness-for-americans-if-they-can-prevent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 18:59:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46344-i-predict-future-happiness-for-americans-if-they-can-prevent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I predict future happiness for Americans, if they can prevent the government from wasting the labors of the people under the pretense of taking care of them." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26740-the-fact-that-a-believer-is-happier-than-a-skeptic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:01:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26740-the-fact-that-a-believer-is-happier-than-a-skeptic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The fact that a believer is happier than a skeptic is no more to the point than the fact that a drunken man is happier than a sober one. The happiness of credulity is a cheap and dangerous quality of happiness, and by no means a necessity of life." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:02:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6144-all-thinking-men-are-atheists]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All thinking men are atheists." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46345-i-was-born-a-heretic-i-always-distrusted-people-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Susan B. Anthony]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46345-i-was-born-a-heretic-i-always-distrusted-people-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was born a heretic. I always distrusted people who know so much about what God wants them to do to their fellows." -- Susan B. Anthony]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46346-religious-bondage-shackles-and-debilitates-the-mind-and-unfits-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:03:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46346-religious-bondage-shackles-and-debilitates-the-mind-and-unfits-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religious bondage shackles and debilitates the mind, and unfits it for every noble enterprise, every expanded prospect.

[&lt;i&gt;Letter to William Bradford Jr. April 1 1774&lt;/i&gt;]" -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44601-what-i-have-denied-and-what-my-reason-compels-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44601-what-i-have-denied-and-what-my-reason-compels-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...What I have denied and what my reason compels me to deny, is the existence of a Being throned above us as a god, directing our mundane affairs in detail, regarding us as individuals, punishing us, rewarding us as human judges might.

When the churches learn to take this rational view of things, when they become true schools of ethics and stop teaching fables, they will be more effective than they are to-day... If they would turn all that ability to teaching this one thing – the fact that honesty is best, that selfishness and lies of any sort must surely fail to produce happiness – they would accomplish actual things. Religious faiths and creeds have greatly hampered our development. They have absorbed and wasted some fine intellects. That creeds are getting to be less and less important to the average mind with every passing year is a good sign, I think, although I do not wish to talk about what is commonly called theology.

The criticisms which have been hurled at me have not worried me. A man cannot control his beliefs. If he is honest in his frank expression of them, that is all that can in justice be required of him. Professor Thomson and a thousand others do not in the least agree with me. His criticism of me, as I read it, charged that because I doubted the soul’s immortality, or ‘personality,’ as he called it, my mind must be abnormal, ‘pathological,’ in other, words, diseased... I try to say exactly what I honestly believe to be the truth, and more than that no man can do. I honestly believe that creedists have built up a mighty structure of inaccuracy, based, curiously, on those fundamental truths which I, with every honest man, must not alone admit but earnestly acclaim.

I have been working on the same lines for many years. I have tried to go as far as possible toward the bottom of each subject I have studied. I have not reached my conclusions through study of traditions; I have reached them through the study of hard fact. I cannot see that unproved theories or sentiment should be permitted to have influence in the building of conviction upon matters so important. Science proves its theories or it rejects them. I have never seen the slightest scientific proof of the religious theories of heaven and hell, of future life for individuals, or of a personal God. I earnestly believe that I am right; I cannot help believing as I do... I cannot accept as final any theory which is not provable. The theories of the theologians cannot be proved. Proof, proof! That is what I always have been after; that is what my mind requires before it can accept a theory as fact. Some things are provable, some things disprovable, some things are doubtful. All the problems which perplex us, now, will, soon or late, be solved, and solved beyond a question through scientific investigation. The thing which most impresses me about theology is that it does not seem to be investigating. It seems to be asserting, merely, without actual study.

...Moral teaching is the thing we need most in this world, and many of these men could be great moral teachers if they would but give their whole time to it, and to scientific search for the rock-bottom truth, instead of wasting it upon expounding theories of theology which are not in the first place firmly based. What we need is search for fundamentals, not reiteration of traditions born in days when men knew even less than we do now.

[&lt;i&gt;Columbian Magazine interview&lt;/i&gt;]" -- Thomas A. Edison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46348-difference-of-opinion-is-advantageous-in-religion-the-several-sects</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:04:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46348-difference-of-opinion-is-advantageous-in-religion-the-several-sects]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Difference of opinion is advantageous in religion. The several sects perform the office of a Censor morum over each other. Is uniformity attainable? &lt;b&gt;Millions of innocent men, women, and children, since the introduction of Christianity, have been burnt, tortured, fined, imprisoned; yet we have not advanced one inch towards uniformity. What has been the effect of coercion? To make one half the world fools, and the other half hypocrites. To support roguery and error all over the earth&lt;/b&gt;. Let us reflect that it is inhabited by a thousand millions of people. That these profess probably a thousand different systems of religion. That ours is but one of that thousand. That if there be but one right, and ours that one, we should wish to see the 999 wandering sects gathered into the fold of truth. But against such a majority we cannot effect this by force. Reason and persuasion are the only practicable instruments. To make way for these, free enquiry must be indulged; and how can we wish others to indulge it while we refuse it ourselves?" -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46350-faith-is-the-great-cop-out-the-great-excuse-to-evade</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:04:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46350-faith-is-the-great-cop-out-the-great-excuse-to-evade]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faith is the great cop-out, the great excuse to evade the need to think and evaluate evidence. Faith is the belief in spite of, even perhaps because of, the lack of evidence." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8816-i-am-against-religion-because-it-teaches-us-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:05:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8816-i-am-against-religion-because-it-teaches-us-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am against religion because it teaches us to be satisfied with not understanding the world." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46351-religion-is-excellent-stuff-for-keeping-common-people-quiet-religion</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:05:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Napoleon Bonaparte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46351-religion-is-excellent-stuff-for-keeping-common-people-quiet-religion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Religion is excellent stuff for keeping common people quiet. Religion is what keeps the poor from murdering the rich." -- Napoleon Bonaparte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46352-the-bible-and-the-church-have-been-the-greatest-stumbling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:06:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Elizabeth Stanton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46352-the-bible-and-the-church-have-been-the-greatest-stumbling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The bible and the church have been the greatest stumbling blocks in the way of women’s emancipation." -- Elizabeth Stanton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46353-my-view-is-that-if-there-is-no-evidence-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:07:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46353-my-view-is-that-if-there-is-no-evidence-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My view is that if there is no evidence for it, then forget about it. An agnostic is somebody who doesn’t believe in something until there is evidence for it, so I’m agnostic." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37037-we-must-question-the-story-logic-of-having-an-all-knowing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37037-we-must-question-the-story-logic-of-having-an-all-knowing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must question the story logic of having an all-knowing all-powerful God, who creates faulty Humans, and then blames them for his own mistakes." -- Gene Roddenberry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4664-the-various-modes-of-worship-which-prevailed-in-the-roman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:08:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Edward Gibbon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4664-the-various-modes-of-worship-which-prevailed-in-the-roman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The various modes of worship which prevailed in the Roman world were all considered by the people as equally true; by the philosopher as equally false; and by the magistrate as equally useful." -- Edward Gibbon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46354-the-time-appears-to-me-to-have-come-when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:08:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46354-the-time-appears-to-me-to-have-come-when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The time appears to me to have come when it is the duty of all to make their dissent from religion known." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15762-i-slept-and-dreamt-that-life-was-joy-i-awoke</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Tagore]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15762-i-slept-and-dreamt-that-life-was-joy-i-awoke]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I slept and dreamt that life was joy. I awoke and saw that life was service. I acted and behold, service was joy." -- Tagore]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46375-a-man-who-has-never-gone-to-school-may-steal</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:54:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46375-a-man-who-has-never-gone-to-school-may-steal]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who has never gone to school may steal a freight car; but if he has a university education, he may steal the whole railroad." -- Theodore Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46376-love-is-the-movement-within-life-that-carries-us-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Huston Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46376-love-is-the-movement-within-life-that-carries-us-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the movement within life that carries us, that enables us, that causes us to break out of what Alan Watts calls the “skin-encapsulated ego.” Without love, we are self-centered, but love enables us to move the center of our lives outside our ego. Therefore it expands our lives and, needless to say, enriches it. Any human being would give anything to love or be loved. When it really happens, it is like heaven on earth." -- Huston Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28865-time-is-the-coin-of-your-life-it-is-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:55:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Carl Sandburg ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28865-time-is-the-coin-of-your-life-it-is-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is the coin of your life. It is the only coin you have, and only you can determine how it will be spent. Be careful lest you let other people spend it for you." -- Carl Sandburg ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46378-when-you-blame-others-you-give-up-your-power-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Robert Anthony]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46378-when-you-blame-others-you-give-up-your-power-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you blame others, you give up your power to change." -- Robert Anthony]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46380-chase-after-the-truth-like-all-hell-and-you-ll-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:57:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Clarence Darrow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46380-chase-after-the-truth-like-all-hell-and-you-ll-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Chase after the truth like all hell and you’ll free yourself, even though you never touch its coat tails." -- Clarence Darrow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31315-education-is-a-progressive-discovery-of-our-own-ignorance</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:57:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Will Durant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31315-education-is-a-progressive-discovery-of-our-own-ignorance]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance." -- Will Durant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16909-only-a-life-lived-for-others-is-a-life-worthwhile</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:58:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16909-only-a-life-lived-for-others-is-a-life-worthwhile]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only a life lived for others is a life worthwhile." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183399-only-the-educated-are-free</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:59:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Epictetus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/183399-only-the-educated-are-free]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the educated are free." -- Epictetus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 19:59:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1502-facts-do-not-cease-to-exist-because-they-are-ignored]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Facts do not cease to exist because they are ignored." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46385-the-opinions-and-beliefs-of-men-follow-involuntarily-the-evidence</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 20:01:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46385-the-opinions-and-beliefs-of-men-follow-involuntarily-the-evidence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opinions and beliefs of men follow involuntarily the evidence proposed to their minds." -- Thomas Jefferson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69-folks-are-usually-about-as-happy-as-they-make-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 20:01:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Greg add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69-folks-are-usually-about-as-happy-as-they-make-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Folks are usually about as happy as they make their minds up to be." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
