<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/960454-g-li]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/960454-g-li" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 00:17:09 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8857-although-most-people-never-overcome-the-habit-of-berating-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 00:17:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Güli add a quote by Max Horkheimer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8857-although-most-people-never-overcome-the-habit-of-berating-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Although most people never overcome the habit of berating the world for their difficulties, those who are too weak to make a stand against reality have no choice but to obliterate themselves by identifying with it. They are never rationally reconciled to civilization. Instead, they bow to it, secretly accepting the identity of reason and domination, of civilization and the ideal, however much they may shrug their shoulders. Well-informed cynicism is only another mode of conformity. These people willingly embrace or force themselves to accept the rule of the stronger as the eternal norm. Their whole life is a continuous effort to suppress and abase nature, inwardly or outwardly, and to identify themselves with its more powerful surrogates—the race, fatherland, leader, cliques, and tradition. For them, all these words mean the same thing—the irresistible reality that must be honored and obeyed. However, their own natural impulses, those antagonistic to the various demands of civilization, lead a devious undercover life within them." -- Max Horkheimer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/838384-now-that-science-has-helped-us-to-overcome-the-awe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2013 00:28:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Güli add a quote by Max Horkheimer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/838384-now-that-science-has-helped-us-to-overcome-the-awe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now that science has helped us to overcome the awe of the unknown in nature, we are the slaves of social pressures of our own making. When called upon to act independently, we cry for patterns, systems, and authorities. If by enlightenment and intellectual progress we mean the freeing of man from superstitious belief in evil forces, in demons and fairies, in blind fate--in short, the emancipation from fear--then denunciation of what is currently called reason is the greatest service reason can render." -- Max Horkheimer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
