<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/961133-deanna]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/961133-deanna" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 19:46:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31057-those-who-have-been-too-long-at-their-labor-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 19:46:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Jean Anthelme Brillat-Savarin ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31057-those-who-have-been-too-long-at-their-labor-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Those who have been too long at their labor, who have drunk too long 
at the cup of voluptuousness, who feel they have become temporarily 
inhumane, who are tormented by their families, who find life sad and 
love ephemeral......they should all eat chocolate and they will be 
comforted." -- Jean Anthelme Brillat-Savarin ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2027-the-cure-for-boredom-is-curiosity-there-is-no-cure</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 19:47:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Dorothy Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2027-the-cure-for-boredom-is-curiosity-there-is-no-cure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The cure for boredom is curiosity.
There is no cure for curiosity." -- Dorothy Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31061-flowers-always-make-people-better-happier-and-more-helpful-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 19:48:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Luther Burbank ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31061-flowers-always-make-people-better-happier-and-more-helpful-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Flowers always make people better, happier, and more helpful; they are sunshine, food and medicine to the mind." -- Luther Burbank ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2008 19:49:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31063-never-be-afraid-to-raise-your-voice-for-honesty-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never be afraid to raise your voice for honesty and truth and compassion against injustice and lying and greed. If people all over the world...would do this, it would change the earth." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167324-i-really-should-come-with-a-warning-label</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 05:14:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Tom Upton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167324-i-really-should-come-with-a-warning-label]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I really should come with a warning label." -- Tom Upton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 18:34:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/161972-the-first-thing-you-notice-about-new-orleans-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first thing you notice about New Orleans are the burying grounds - the cemeteries - and they're a cold proposition, one of the best things there are here. Going by, you try to be as quiet as possible, better to let them sleep. Greek, Roman, sepulchres- palatial mausoleums made to order, phantomesque, signs and symbols of hidden decay - ghosts of women and men who have sinned and who've died and are now living in tombs. The past doesn't pass away so quickly here. You could be dead for a long time.

The ghosts race towards the light, you can almost hear the heavy breathing spirits, all determined to get somewhere. New Orleans, unlike a lot of those places you go back to and that don't have the magic anymore, still has got it. Night can swallow you up, yet none of it touches you. Around any corner, there's a promise of something daring and ideal and things are just getting going. There's something obscenely joyful behind every door, either that or somebody crying with their head in their hands. A lazy rhythm looms in the dreamy air and the atmosphere pulsates with bygone duels, past-life romance, comrades requesting comrades to aid them in some way. You can't see it, but you know it's here. Somebody is always sinking. Everyone seems to be from some very old Southern families. Either that or a foreigner. I like the way it is.

There are a lot of places I like, but I like New Orleans better. There's a thousand different angles at any moment. At any time you could run into a ritual honoring some vaguely known queen. Bluebloods, titled persons like crazy drunks, lean weakly against the walls and drag themselves through the gutter. Even they seem to have insights you might want to listen to. No action seems inappropriate here. The city is one very long poem. Gardens full of pansies, pink petunias, opiates. Flower-bedecked shrines, white myrtles, bougainvillea and purple oleander stimulate your senses, make you feel cool and clear inside.

Everything in New Orleans is a good idea. Bijou temple-type cottages and lyric cathedrals side by side. Houses and mansions, structures of wild grace. Italianate, Gothic, Romanesque, Greek Revival standing in a long line in the rain. Roman Catholic art. Sweeping front porches, turrets, cast-iron balconies, colonnades- 30-foot columns, gloriously beautiful- double pitched roofs, all the architecture of the whole wide world and it doesn't move. All that and a town square where public executions took place. In New Orleans you could almost see other dimensions. There's only one day at a time here, then it's tonight and then tomorrow will be today again. Chronic melancholia hanging from the trees. You never get tired of it. After a while you start to feel like a ghost from one of the tombs, like you're in a wax museum below crimson clouds. Spirit empire. Wealthy empire. One of Napoleon's generals, Lallemaud, was said to have come here to check it out, looking for a place for his commander to seek refuge after Waterloo. He scouted around and left, said that here the devil is damned, just like everybody else, only worse. The devil comes here and sighs. New Orleans. Exquisite, old-fashioned. A great place to live vicariously. Nothing makes any difference and you never feel hurt, a great place to really hit on things. Somebody puts something in front of you here and you might as well drink it. Great place to be intimate or do nothing. A place to come and hope you'll get smart - to feed pigeons looking for handouts" -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24207-and-heaven-have-mercy-on-us-all---presbyterians-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 06:15:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Herman Melville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24207-and-heaven-have-mercy-on-us-all---presbyterians-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...and Heaven have mercy on us all - Presbyterians and Pagans alike - for we are all somehow dreadfully cracked about the head, and sadly need mending." -- Herman Melville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32079-all-right-then-i-ll-go-to-hell</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 15:50:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32079-all-right-then-i-ll-go-to-hell]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All right, then, I'll go to hell." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187019-that-is-just-the-way-with-some-people-they-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 15:49:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187019-that-is-just-the-way-with-some-people-they-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is just the way with some people. They get down on a thing when they don’t know nothing about it." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600498-just-because-you-re-taught-that-something-s-right-and-everyone-believes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 15:51:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/600498-just-because-you-re-taught-that-something-s-right-and-everyone-believes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just because you’re taught that something’s right and everyone believes it’s right, it don’t make it right." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417960-it-made-me-shiver-and-i-about-made-up-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 15:52:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417960-it-made-me-shiver-and-i-about-made-up-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It made me shiver. And I about made up my mind to pray, and see if I couldn't try to quit being the kind of a boy I was and be better. So I kneeled down. But the words wouldn't come. Why wouldn't they? It warn't no use to try and hide it from Him. Nor from ME, neither. I knowed very well why they wouldn't come. It was because my heart warn't right; it was because I warn't square; it was because I was playing double. I was letting ON to give up sin, but away inside of me I was holding on to the biggest one of all. I was trying to make my mouth SAY I would do the right thing and the clean thing, and go and write to that nigger's owner and tell where he was; but deep down in me I knowed it was a lie, and He knowed it. You can't pray a lie--I found that out. 

So I was full of trouble, full as I could be; and didn't know what to do. At last I had an idea; and I says, I'll go and write the letter--and then see if I can pray. Why, it was astonishing, the way I felt as light as a feather right straight off, and my troubles all gone. So I got a piece of paper and a pencil, all glad and excited, and set down and wrote:

Miss Watson, your runaway nigger Jim is down here two mile below Pikesville, and Mr. Phelps has got him and he will give him up for the reward if you send.

HUCK FINN.

I felt good and all washed clean of sin for the first time I had ever felt so in my life, and I knowed I could pray now. But I didn't do it straight off, but laid the paper down and set there thinking--thinking how good it was all this happened so, and how near I come to being lost and going to hell. And went on thinking. And got to thinking over our trip down the river; and I see Jim before me all the time: in the day and in the night-time, sometimes moonlight, sometimes storms, and we a-floating along, talking and singing and laughing. But somehow I couldn't seem to strike no places to harden me against him, but only the other kind. I'd see him standing my watch on top of his'n, 'stead of calling me, so I could go on sleeping; and see him how glad he was when I come back out of the fog; and when I come to him again in the swamp, up there where the feud was; and such-like times; and would always call me honey, and pet me and do everything he could think of for me, and how good he always was; and at last I struck the time I saved him by telling the men we had small-pox aboard, and he was so grateful, and said I was the best friend old Jim ever had in the world, and the ONLY one he's got now; and then I happened to look around and see that paper.

It was a close place. I took it up, and held it in my hand. I was a-trembling, because I'd got to decide, forever, betwixt two things, and I knowed it. I studied a minute, sort of holding my breath, and then says to myself:

&quot;All right, then, I'll GO to hell&quot;--and tore it up." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:18:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764-a-room-without-books-is-like-a-body-without-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A room without books is like a body without a soul." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:18:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Frank Zappa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66-so-many-books-so-little-time]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So many books, so little time." -- Frank Zappa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4583-always-forgive-your-enemies-nothing-annoys-them-so-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:19:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4583-always-forgive-your-enemies-nothing-annoys-them-so-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:19:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/943-darkness-cannot-drive-out-darkness-only-light-can-do-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Darkness cannot drive out darkness: only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate: only love can do that." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:19:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4590-without-music-life-would-be-a-mistake]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Without music, life would be a mistake." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 22:21:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Deanna add a quote by H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2340-twenty-years-from-now-you-will-be-more-disappointed-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didn't do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover." -- H. Jackson Brown Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
