<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/961805-shayla]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/961805-shayla" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 13:12:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5453-to-conceal-anything-from-those-to-whom-i-am-attached</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 13:12:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shayla add a quote by charles dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5453-to-conceal-anything-from-those-to-whom-i-am-attached]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To conceal anything from those to whom I am attached, is not in my nature. I can never close my lips where I have opened my heart." -- charles dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62008-adults-are-just-obsolete-children-and-the-hell-with-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 13:33:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shayla add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62008-adults-are-just-obsolete-children-and-the-hell-with-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adults are just obsolete children and the hell with them." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5479-taking-one-s-chances-is-like-taking-a-bath-because-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 14:14:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shayla add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5479-taking-one-s-chances-is-like-taking-a-bath-because-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Taking one’s chances is like taking a bath, because sometimes you end up feeling comfortable and warm, and sometimes there is something terrible lurking around that you cannot see until it is too late and you can do nothing else but scream and cling to a plastic duck." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 14:26:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shayla add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34685-the-only-way-to-get-through-life-is-to-laugh]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The only way to get through life is to laugh your way through it. You either have to laugh or cry. I prefer to laugh. Crying gives me a headache." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208621-there-is-also-the-ceaseless-outpouring-of-books-on-toilet</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 20:42:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Shayla add a quote by Susan Douglas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/208621-there-is-also-the-ceaseless-outpouring-of-books-on-toilet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is also the ceaseless outpouring of books on toilet training, separating one sibling's fist from another sibling's eye socket, expressing breast milk while reading a legal brief, helping preschoolers to &quot;own&quot; their feelings, getting Joshua to do his homework, and raising teenage boys so they become Sensitive New Age Guys instead of rooftop snipers or Chippendale dancers. Over eight hundred books on motherhood were published between 1970 and 2000; only twenty-seven of these came out between 1970 and 1980, so the real avalanch happened in the past twenty years. We've learned about the perils of &quot;the hurried child&quot; and &quot;hyperparenting,&quot; in which we schedule our kids with so many enriching activities that they make the secretary of state look like a couch spud. But the unhurried child probably plays too much Nintendo and is out in the garage building pipe bombs, so you can't underschedule them either. Then there's the Martha Stewartization of America, in which we are meant to sculpt the carrots we put in our kids' lunches into the shape of peonies and build funhouses for them in the backyard; this has raised the bar to even more ridiculous levels than during the June Cleaver era. " -- Susan Douglas]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
