<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/962293-alisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/962293-alisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:50:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:50:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40152-he-smiled-understandingly-much-more-than-understandingly-it-was-one-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He smiled understandingly-much more than understandingly. It was one of those rare smiles with a quality of eternal reassurance in it, that you may come across four or five times in life. It faced--or seemed to face--the whole eternal world for an instant, and then concentrated on you with an irresistible prejudice in your favor. It understood you just as far as you wanted to be understood, believed in you as you would like to believe in yourself, and assured you that it had precisely the impression of you that, at your best, you hoped to convey." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132325-let-us-learn-to-show-our-friendship-for-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/132325-let-us-learn-to-show-our-friendship-for-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us learn to show our friendship for a man when he is alive and not after he is dead." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31090-reserving-judgements-is-a-matter-of-infinite-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:51:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31090-reserving-judgements-is-a-matter-of-infinite-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reserving judgements is a matter of infinite hope." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:51:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2481-there-must-have-been-moments-even-that-afternoon-when-daisy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There must have been moments even that afternoon when Daisy tumbled short of his dreams -- not through her own fault, but because of the colossal vitality of his illusion. It had gone beyond her, beyond everything. He had thrown himself into it with a creative passion, adding to it all the time, decking it out with every bright feather that drifted his way. No amount of fire or freshness can challenge what a man will store up in his ghostly heart." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28657-i-couldn-t-forgive-him-or-like-him-but-i-saw</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:51:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28657-i-couldn-t-forgive-him-or-like-him-but-i-saw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I couldn’t forgive him or like him, but I saw that what he had done was, to him, entirely justified. It was all very careless and confused. They were careless people, Tom and Daisy—they smashed up things and creatures and then retreated back into their money or their vast carelessness, or whatever it was that kept them together, and let other people clean up the mess they had made." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10866-it-s-a-great-advantage-not-to-drink-among-hard-drinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:51:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10866-it-s-a-great-advantage-not-to-drink-among-hard-drinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It’s a great advantage not to drink among hard drinking people." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251538-do-you-remember-what-you-said-to-me-once-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:52:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/251538-do-you-remember-what-you-said-to-me-once-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you remember what you said to me once?  That you could help me only by loving me?  Well-you did love me for a moment; and it helped me.  It has always helped me." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58937-there-is-someone-i-must-say-goodbye-to-oh-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:53:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58937-there-is-someone-i-must-say-goodbye-to-oh-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is someone I must say goodbye to. Oh, not you - we are sure to see each other again - but the Lily Bart you knew. I have kept her with me all this time, but now we are going to part, and I have brought her back to you - I am going to leave her here. When I go out presently she will not go with me. I shall like to think that she has stayed with you." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202812-she-had-been-bored-all-afternoon-by-percy-gryce-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:53:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/202812-she-had-been-bored-all-afternoon-by-percy-gryce-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had been bored all afternoon by Percy Gryce... but she could not ignore him on the morrow, she must follow up her success, must submit to more boredom, must be ready with fresh compliances and adaptibilities, and all on the bare chance that he might ultimately decide to do her the honour of boring her for life." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357431-it-is-less-mortifying-to-believe-one-s-self-unpopular-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:54:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/357431-it-is-less-mortifying-to-believe-one-s-self-unpopular-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is less mortifying to believe one's self unpopular than insignificant, and vanity prefers to assume that indifference is a latent form of unfriendliness." -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595015-it-is-so-easy-for-a-woman-to-become-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 12:55:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Edith Wharton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/595015-it-is-so-easy-for-a-woman-to-become-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is so easy for a woman to become what the man she loves believes her to be" -- Edith Wharton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313665-do-you-realize-that-all-great-literature-moby-dick</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:03:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313665-do-you-realize-that-all-great-literature-moby-dick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you realize that all great literature — &quot;Moby Dick,&quot; &quot;Huckleberry Finn,&quot; &quot;A Farewell to Arms,&quot; &quot;The Scarlet Letter,&quot; &quot;The Red Badge of Courage,&quot; &quot;The Iliad and The Odyssey,&quot; &quot;Crime and Punishment,&quot; the Bible, and &quot;The Charge of the Light Brigade&quot; — are all about what a bummer it is to be a ...human being?" -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504598-within-him-as-he-hurled-himself-forward-was-born-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:04:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Stephen Crane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/504598-within-him-as-he-hurled-himself-forward-was-born-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Within him, as he hurled himself forward, was born a love, a despairing fondness for this flag which was near him. It was a creation of beauty and invulnerability. It was a goddess, radiant, that bended its form with an imperious gesture to him. It was a woman, red and white, hating and loving, that called him with the voice of his hopes. Because no harm could come to it he endowed it with power. He kept near, as if it could be a saver of lives, and an imploring cry went from his mind." -- Stephen Crane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531188-he-vaguely-desired-to-walk-around-and-around-the-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:04:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Stephen Crane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/531188-he-vaguely-desired-to-walk-around-and-around-the-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He vaguely desired to walk around and around the body and stare; the impulse of the living to try to read in dead eyes the answer to the Question." -- Stephen Crane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7705-jim-said-that-bees-won-t-sting-idiots-but-i-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:10:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7705-jim-said-that-bees-won-t-sting-idiots-but-i-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jim said that bees won't sting idiots, but I didn't believe that, because I tried them lots of times myself and they wouldn't sting me." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4088-hain-t-we-got-all-the-fools-in-town-on-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:10:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4088-hain-t-we-got-all-the-fools-in-town-on-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hain't we got all the fools in town on our side? And hain't that a big enough majority in any town?" -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481193-human-beings-can-be-awful-cruel-to-one-another</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:10:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/481193-human-beings-can-be-awful-cruel-to-one-another]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human beings can be awful cruel to one another." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340303-if-you-are-with-the-quality-or-at-a-funeral</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:11:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/340303-if-you-are-with-the-quality-or-at-a-funeral]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are with the quality, or at a funeral, or trying to go to sleep when you ain't sleepy - if you are anywheres where it won't do for you to scratch, why you will itch all over in upwards of a thousand places." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413825-he-was-sunshine-most-always-i-mean-he-made-it-seem</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:11:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/413825-he-was-sunshine-most-always-i-mean-he-made-it-seem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was sunshine most always-I mean he made it seem like good weather." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417960-it-made-me-shiver-and-i-about-made-up-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:12:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/417960-it-made-me-shiver-and-i-about-made-up-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It made me shiver. And I about made up my mind to pray, and see if I couldn't try to quit being the kind of a boy I was and be better. So I kneeled down. But the words wouldn't come. Why wouldn't they? It warn't no use to try and hide it from Him. Nor from ME, neither. I knowed very well why they wouldn't come. It was because my heart warn't right; it was because I warn't square; it was because I was playing double. I was letting ON to give up sin, but away inside of me I was holding on to the biggest one of all. I was trying to make my mouth SAY I would do the right thing and the clean thing, and go and write to that nigger's owner and tell where he was; but deep down in me I knowed it was a lie, and He knowed it. You can't pray a lie--I found that out. 

So I was full of trouble, full as I could be; and didn't know what to do. At last I had an idea; and I says, I'll go and write the letter--and then see if I can pray. Why, it was astonishing, the way I felt as light as a feather right straight off, and my troubles all gone. So I got a piece of paper and a pencil, all glad and excited, and set down and wrote:

Miss Watson, your runaway nigger Jim is down here two mile below Pikesville, and Mr. Phelps has got him and he will give him up for the reward if you send.

HUCK FINN.

I felt good and all washed clean of sin for the first time I had ever felt so in my life, and I knowed I could pray now. But I didn't do it straight off, but laid the paper down and set there thinking--thinking how good it was all this happened so, and how near I come to being lost and going to hell. And went on thinking. And got to thinking over our trip down the river; and I see Jim before me all the time: in the day and in the night-time, sometimes moonlight, sometimes storms, and we a-floating along, talking and singing and laughing. But somehow I couldn't seem to strike no places to harden me against him, but only the other kind. I'd see him standing my watch on top of his'n, 'stead of calling me, so I could go on sleeping; and see him how glad he was when I come back out of the fog; and when I come to him again in the swamp, up there where the feud was; and such-like times; and would always call me honey, and pet me and do everything he could think of for me, and how good he always was; and at last I struck the time I saved him by telling the men we had small-pox aboard, and he was so grateful, and said I was the best friend old Jim ever had in the world, and the ONLY one he's got now; and then I happened to look around and see that paper.

It was a close place. I took it up, and held it in my hand. I was a-trembling, because I'd got to decide, forever, betwixt two things, and I knowed it. I studied a minute, sort of holding my breath, and then says to myself:

&quot;All right, then, I'll GO to hell&quot;--and tore it up." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32808-it-has-made-me-better-loving-you-it-has-made</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:18:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32808-it-has-made-me-better-loving-you-it-has-made]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has made me better loving you... it has made me wiser, and easier, and brighter. I used to want a great many things before, and to be angry that I did not have them. Theoretically, I was satisfied. I flattered myself that I had limited my wants. But I was subject to irritation; I used to have morbid sterile hateful fits of hunger, of desire. Now I really am satisfied, because I can’t think of anything better. It’s just as when one has been trying to spell out a book in the twilight, and suddenly the lamp comes in. I had been putting out my eyes over the book of life, and finding nothing to reward me for my pains; but now that I can read it properly I see that it’s a delightful story." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72412-i-m-yours-for-ever--for-ever-and-ever-here-i-stand</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:19:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72412-i-m-yours-for-ever--for-ever-and-ever-here-i-stand]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm yours for ever--for ever and ever.  Here I stand; I'm as firm as a rock. If you'll only trust me, how little you'll be disappointed. Be mine as I am yours." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3585-i-always-want-to-know-the-things-one-shouldn-t-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:19:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3585-i-always-want-to-know-the-things-one-shouldn-t-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I always want to know the things one shouldn't do.&quot;
&quot;So as to do them?&quot; asked her aunt.
&quot;So as to choose.&quot; said Isabel" -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280623-and-remember-this-that-if-you-ve-been-hated-you-ve-also</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:20:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280623-and-remember-this-that-if-you-ve-been-hated-you-ve-also]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And remember this, that if you've been hated, you've also been loved." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100138-whatever-life-you-lead-you-must-put-your-soul-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 13:21:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Henry James]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100138-whatever-life-you-lead-you-must-put-your-soul-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever life you lead you must put your soul in it--to make any sort of success in it; and from the moment you do that it ceases to be romance, I assure you: it becomes grim reality! And you can't always please yourself; you must sometimes please other people. That, I admit, you're very ready to do; but there's another thing that's still more important--you must often displease others. You must always be ready for that--you must never shrink from it. That doesn't suit you at all--you're too fond of admiration, you like to be thought well of. You think we can escape disagreeable duties by taking romantic views--that's your great illusion, my dear. But we can't. You must be prepared on many occasions in life to please no one at all--not even yourself." -- Henry James]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22342-men-can-starve-from-a-lack-of-self-realization-as-much</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 09:03:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22342-men-can-starve-from-a-lack-of-self-realization-as-much]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men can starve from a lack of self-realization  as much as they can from a lack of bread." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442644-they-hate-because-they-fear-and-they-fear-because-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 09:02:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/442644-they-hate-because-they-fear-and-they-fear-because-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They hate because they fear, and they fear because they feel that the deepest feelings of their lives are being assaulted and outraged. And they do not know why; they are powerless pawns in a blind play of social forces." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635695-i-didn-t-know-i-was-really-alive-in-this-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2013 09:03:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by Richard Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/635695-i-didn-t-know-i-was-really-alive-in-this-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't know I was really alive in this world until I felt things hard enough to kill for 'em..." -- Richard Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52089-to-me-history-ought-to-be-a-source-of-pleasure</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 16:58:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52089-to-me-history-ought-to-be-a-source-of-pleasure]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To me, history ought to be a source of pleasure. It isn't just part of our civic responsibility. To me, it's an enlargement of the experience of being alive, just the way literature or art or music is.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;The Title Always Comes Last&lt;/i&gt;; NEH 2003 Jefferson Lecturer interview profile]" -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314777-the-longer-i-live-the-more-i-read-the-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2013 17:00:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alisa add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314777-the-longer-i-live-the-more-i-read-the-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The longer I live, the more I read, the more patiently I think and the more anxiously I inquire, the less I seem to know...do justly.  Love mercy.  Walk humbly.  This is enough." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
