<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96338-carly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96338-carly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 05:59:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41058-he-is-the-half-part-of-a-blessed-man-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 05:59:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41058-he-is-the-half-part-of-a-blessed-man-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is the half part of a blessed man,
Left to be finished by such as she;
And she a fair divided excellence,
Whose fullness of perfection lies in him. " -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 13:54:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9120-if-we-listened-to-our-intellect-we-d-never-have-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we listened to our intellect we'd never have a love affair. We'd never have a friendship. We'd never go in business because we'd be cynical: &quot;It's gonna go wrong.&quot; Or &quot;She's going to hurt me.&quot; Or,&quot;I've had a couple of bad love affairs, so therefore . . .&quot; Well, that's nonsense. You're going to miss life. You've got to jump off the cliff all the time and build your wings on the way down." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24403-be-like-the-sun-for-grace-and-mercy-be-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:26:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24403-be-like-the-sun-for-grace-and-mercy-be-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be like the sun for grace and mercy. Be like the night to cover others' faults. Be like running water for generosity. Be like death for rage and anger. Be like the Earth for modesty. Appear as you are. Be as you appear." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145712-speak-quietly-to-yourself-promise-there-will-be-better</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:27:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by mary anne radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/145712-speak-quietly-to-yourself-promise-there-will-be-better]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["speak quietly to yourself &amp; promise there will be better days.  whisper gently to yourself and provide assurance that you really are extending your best effort.  console your bruised and tender spirit with reminders of many other successes.  offer comfort in practical and tangible ways - as if you were encouraging your dearest friend.  recognize that on certain days the greatest grace is that the day is over and you get to close your eyes.  tomorrow comes more brightly..." -- mary anne radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13864-so-you-think-that-you-re-a-failure-do-you-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:27:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13864-so-you-think-that-you-re-a-failure-do-you-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So you think that you're a failure, do you? Well, you probably are. What's wrong with that? In the first place, if you've any sense at all you must have learned by now that we pay just as dearly for our triumphs as we do for our defeats. Go ahead and fail. But fail with wit, fail with grace, fail with style. A mediocre failure is as insufferable as a mediocre success. Embrace failure! Seek it out. Learn to love it. That may be the only way any of us will ever be free." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36842-he-stared-up-at-the-stars-and-it-seemed-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:28:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36842-he-stared-up-at-the-stars-and-it-seemed-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He stared up at the stars: and it seemed to him then that they were dancers, stately and graceful, performing a dance almost infinite in its complexity. He imagined he could see the very faces of the stars; pale, they were, and smiling gently, as if they had spent so much time above the world, watching the scrambling and the joy and the pain of the people below them, that they could not help being amused every time another little human believed itself the center of its world, as each of us does." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85164-ordinary-life-does-not-interest-me-i-seek-only-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:28:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85164-ordinary-life-does-not-interest-me-i-seek-only-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ordinary life does not interest me. I seek only the high moments. I am in accord with the surrealists, searching for the marvelous. I want to be a writer who reminds others that these moments exist; I want to prove that there is infinite space, infinite meaning, infinite dimension. But I am not always in what I call a state of grace. I have days of illuminations and fevers. I have days when the music in my head stops. Then I mend socks, prune trees, can fruits, polish furniture. But while I am doing this I feel I am not living." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236036-you-can-have-the-other-words-chance-luck-coincidence-serendipity-i-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:29:30 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236036-you-can-have-the-other-words-chance-luck-coincidence-serendipity-i-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can have the other words-chance, luck, coincidence, serendipity. I'll take grace. I don't know what it is exactly, but I'll take it. " -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38657-courage-doesn-t-always-roar-sometimes-courage-is-the-little-voice</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 18:30:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38657-courage-doesn-t-always-roar-sometimes-courage-is-the-little-voice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Courage doesn't always roar.  Sometimes courage is the little voice at the end of the day that says I'll try again tomorrow." -- Mary Anne Radmacher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472091-words-don-t-change-their-shape-they-change-their-meaning-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:34:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472091-words-don-t-change-their-shape-they-change-their-meaning-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words don't change their shape, they change their meaning, their function...They don't have a meaning of their own any more, they refer to other words that you don't know, that you've never read or heard...you've never seen their shape, but you feel...you suspect...they correspond to...an empty space inside you...or in the universe..." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558379-women-must-find-their-own-answer-that-s-the-important-thing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:35:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558379-women-must-find-their-own-answer-that-s-the-important-thing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Women must find their own answer. That’s the important thing. I’m no longer interested in books about women written by men. Even if I could believe in their objectivity, I just can’t find their opinions relevant. Now I will only believe what a woman has to say about women, because even if it’s not entirely true, it’s her struggle and she’s on the way to the answer.

Many of you seek masculine approval. Even though you have inside you your way of talking and writing, you have mountains of it inside you, and even though it is enough to begin expressing yourselves so long as it is with your vocabulary, your abstractions, and your own conceptualization, I think you are still afraid of the master: men. Of their judgment. As long as you have this fear, you will not progress. I think the future belongs to women. Men have been completely dethroned. Their rhetoric is stale, used up. We must move on the rhetoric of women, one that is anchored in the organism, in the body." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559790-i-often-think-of-the-image-only-i-can-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:36:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/559790-i-often-think-of-the-image-only-i-can-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often think of the image only I can see now, and of which I’ve never spoken. It’s always there, in the same silence, amazing. It’s the only image of myself I like, the only one in which I recognize myself, in which I delight" -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22403-sometimes-she-said-i-think-i-must-have-invented-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:37:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22403-sometimes-she-said-i-think-i-must-have-invented-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes,’ she said, ‘I think I must have invented him.’
I know all I want to about your child,’ Chauvin said harshly.
Anne Desbaresdes moaned again, louder than before.  Again she put her hand on the table.  His eyes followed her movement and finally, painfully, he understood and lifted his own leaden hand and placed it on hers.  Their hands were so cold they were touching only in intention, an illusion, in order for this to be fulfilled, for the sole reason that it should be fulfilled, none other, it was no longer possible.  And yet, with their hands frozen in this funereal pose, Anne Desbaresdes stopped moaning.
One last time,’ she begged, ‘tell me about it one last time.’
Chauvin hesitated, his eyes somewhere else, still fixed on the back wall.  Then he decided to tell her about it as if it were a memory.
He had never dreamed, before meeting her, that he would one day want anything so badly.’
And she acquiesced completely?’
Wonderfully.’
Anne Desbaresdes looked at Chauvin absently.  Her voice became thin, almost childlike.
I'd like to understand why his desire to have it happen one day was so wonderful?’
Chauvin still avoided looking at her.  Her voice was steady, wooden, the voice of a deaf person.
There's no use trying to understand.  It's beyond understanding.’
You mean there are some things like that that can't be gone into?’
I think so.’
Anne Desbaresdes' expression became dull, almost stupid.  Her lips had turned pale, they were gray and trembled as though she were on the verge of tears.
She does nothing t try and stop him?’ she whispered.
No.  Have a little more wine.’
She sipped her wine.  He also drank, and his lips on the glass were also trembling.
Time,’ he said
Does it take a long time, a very long time?’
Yes, a very long time.  But I don't know anything.’  He lowered his voice.  ‘Like you, I don't know anything.  Nothing at all.’
Anne Desbaresdes forced back her tears.  Her voice was normal, momentarily awake.
She will never speak again,’ she said." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472092-their-voices-reach-out-into-the-empty-yard-plunge-deep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:37:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/472092-their-voices-reach-out-into-the-empty-yard-plunge-deep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Their voices reach out into the empty yard, plunge deep into the hills, go right through the heart." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783050-she-lavishes-pain-with-generosity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 14:37:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Marguerite Duras]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783050-she-lavishes-pain-with-generosity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She lavishes pain with generosity." -- Marguerite Duras]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404785-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 08:59:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Pema Chodron]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404785-compassion-is-not-a-relationship-between-the-healer-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Compassion is not a relationship between the healer and the wounded. It’s a relationship between equals. Only when we know our own darkness well can we be present with the darkness of others. Compassion becomes real when we recognize our shared humanity." -- Pema Chodron]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128742-if-you-don-t-like-how-things-are-change-it-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2014 18:53:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Jim Rohn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128742-if-you-don-t-like-how-things-are-change-it-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you don't like how things are, change it. You are not a tree.
" -- Jim Rohn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 10:44:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Carl Sagan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/230027-look-again-at-that-dot-that-s-here-that-s-home-that-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &quot;superstar,&quot; every &quot;supreme leader,&quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.

The Earth is a very small stage in a vast cosmic arena.  Think of the endless cruelties visited by the inhabitants of one corner of this pixel on the scarcely distinguishable inhabitants of some other corner, how frequent their misunderstandings, how eager they are to kill one another, how fervent their hatreds.  Think of the rivers of blood spilled by all those generals and emperors so that, in glory and triumph, they could become the momentary masters of a fraction of a dot.

Our posturings, our imagined self-importance, the delusion that we have some privileged position in the Universe, are challenged by this point of pale light. Our planet is a lonely speck in the great enveloping cosmic dark. In our obscurity, in all this vastness, there is no hint that help will come from elsewhere to save us from ourselves.

The Earth is the only world known so far to harbor life. There is nowhere else, at least in the near future, to which our species could migrate. Visit, yes. Settle, not yet.  Like it or not, for the moment the Earth is where we make our stand.

It has been said that astronomy is a humbling and character-building experience. There is perhaps no better demonstration of the folly of human conceits than this distant image of our tiny world. To me, it underscores our responsibility to deal more kindly with one another, and to preserve and cherish the pale blue dot, the only home we've ever known." -- Carl Sagan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297203-then-she-wished-more-rationally-that-she-could-love-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 10:53:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297203-then-she-wished-more-rationally-that-she-could-love-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then she wished, more rationally, that she could love him without needing him.  Need gave him power without his trying; need was the choicelessness she often felt around him." -- Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70717-we-are-all-strangers-in-a-strange-land-longing-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:27:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70717-we-are-all-strangers-in-a-strange-land-longing-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are all strangers in a strange land, longing for home, but not quite knowing what or where home is. We glimpse it sometimes in our dreams, or as we turn a corner, and suddenly there is a strange, sweet familiarity that vanishes almost as soon as it comes." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185033-and-so-my-prayer-is-that-your-story-will-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:27:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185033-and-so-my-prayer-is-that-your-story-will-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so my prayer is that your story will have involved some leaving and some coming home, some summer and some winter, some roses blooming out like children in a play.  My hope is your story will be about changing, about getting something beautiful born inside of you about learning to love a woman or a man, about learning to love a child, about moving yourself around water, around mountains, around friends, about learning to love others more than we love ourselves, about learning oneness as a way of understanding God.  We get one story, you and I, and one story alone.  God has established the elements, the setting and the climax and the resolution.  It would be a crime not to venture out, wouldn't it?

It might be time for you to go.  It might be time to change, to shine out.

I want to repeat one word for you:
&lt;i&gt;Leave&lt;/i&gt;.

Roll the word around on your tongue for a bit.  It is a beautiful word, isn't it?  So strong and forceful, the way you have always wanted to be.  And you will not be alone.  You have never been alone.  Don't worry.  Everything will still be here when you get back.  It is you who will have changed." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496335-stars-too-were-time-travelers-how-many-of-those-ancient</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:27:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Ransom Riggs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/496335-stars-too-were-time-travelers-how-many-of-those-ancient]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stars, too, were time travelers. How many of those ancient points of light were the last echoes of suns now dead? How many had been born but their light not yet come this far? If all the suns but ours collapsed tonight, how many lifetimes would it take us to realize we were alone? I had always known the sky was full of mysteries—but not until now had I realized how full of them the earth was." -- Ransom Riggs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434914-karou-wished-she-could-be-the-kind-of-girl-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:28:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Carly add a quote by Laini Taylor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434914-karou-wished-she-could-be-the-kind-of-girl-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Karou wished she could be the kind of girl who was complete unto herself, comfortable in solitude, serene.  But she wasn't. She was lonely, and she feared the missingness within her as if it might expand and... cancel her. She craved a presence beside her, solid. Fingertips light at the nape of her neck and a voice meeting hers in the dark. Someone who would wait with an umbrella to walk her home in the rain, and smile like sunshine when he saw her coming. Who would dance with her on her balcony, keep his promises and know her secrets, and make a tiny world wherever he was, with just her and his arms and his whisper and her trust." -- Laini Taylor]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
