<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/964823-mo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/964823-mo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 11:09:53 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549848-her-s-what-i-tell-myself-now-that-it-s-vital-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2012 11:09:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Katherine Center]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549848-her-s-what-i-tell-myself-now-that-it-s-vital-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her's what I tell myself now. That it's vital to learn how to make the best of things. That there is no tenderness without bravery. That if things hadn't been so bad they could never have gotten so good. And that it's always better to have what you have than to get what you wanted. Except for this: Every now and then, when you are impossibly lucky you rise above yourself-and get both." -- Katherine Center]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171502-and-here-after-all-that-is-what-i-have-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 07:17:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Katherine Center]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171502-and-here-after-all-that-is-what-i-have-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And here, after all that, is what I have come to believe about beauty:  Laughter is beautiful.  Kindness is beautiful.  Cellulite is beautiful.  Softness and plumpness and roundness are beautiful.  It’s more important to be interesting, to be vivid, and to be adventurous than to sit pretty for pictures.  The soft tummy of a woman is a miracle of nature.  Beauty comes from tenderness.  Beauty comes from variety, from specificity, from the fact that no person in the world looks exactly like anyone else.  Beauty comes from the tragedy that each person’s life is destined to be lost to time.  I believe women are too hard on themselves.  I believe that when you love someone, she becomes beautiful to you.  I believe the eyes see everything through the heart, that nothing in the world feels as good as resting them on someone you love.  I have trained my eyes to look for beauty, and I’ve gotten very good at finding it.  You can argue and tell me it’s not true, but I really don’t care what anyone says.  I have come at last to believe in the title of the book: Everyone Is Beautiful." -- Katherine Center]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193095-when-god-created-mothers-when-the-good-lord-was-creating</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 07:28:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Erma Bombeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/193095-when-god-created-mothers-when-the-good-lord-was-creating]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When God Created Mothers&quot;
  
When the Good Lord was creating mothers, He was into His sixth day of &quot;overtime&quot; when the angel appeared and said. &quot;You're doing a lot of fiddling around on this one.&quot; 

And God said, &quot;Have you read the specs on this order?&quot; She has to be completely washable, but not plastic. Have 180 moveable parts...all replaceable. Run on black coffee and leftovers. Have a lap that disappears when she stands up. A kiss that can cure anything from a broken leg to a disappointed love affair. And six pairs of hands.&quot; 

The angel shook her head slowly and said. &quot;Six pairs of hands.... no way.&quot; 

It's not the hands that are causing me problems,&quot; God remarked, &quot;it's the three pairs of eyes that mothers have to have.&quot; 

That's on the standard model?&quot; asked the angel. God nodded. 

One pair that sees through closed doors when she asks, 'What are you kids doing in there?' when she already knows. Another here in the back of her head that sees what she shouldn't but what she has to know, and of course the ones here in front that can look at a child when he goofs up and say. 'I understand and I love you' without so much as uttering a word.&quot; 

God,&quot; said the angel touching his sleeve gently, &quot;Get some rest tomorrow....&quot; 

I can't,&quot; said God, &quot;I'm so close to creating something so close to myself. Already I have one who heals herself when she is sick...can feed a family of six on one pound of hamburger...and can get a nine year old to stand under a shower.&quot; 

The angel circled the model of a mother very slowly. &quot;It's too soft,&quot; she sighed. 

But tough!&quot; said God excitedly. &quot;You can imagine what this mother can do or endure.&quot; 

Can it think?&quot; 

Not only can it think, but it can reason and compromise,&quot; said the Creator. 

Finally, the angel bent over and ran her finger across the cheek. 

There's a leak,&quot; she pronounced. &quot;I told You that You were trying to put too much into this model.&quot; 

It's not a leak,&quot; said the Lord, &quot;It's a tear.&quot; 

What's it for?&quot; 

It's for joy, sadness, disappointment, pain, loneliness, and pride.&quot; 

You are a genius, &quot; said the angel. 

Somberly, God said, &quot;I didn't put it there." -- Erma Bombeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396385-and-so-rock-bottom-became-the-solid-foundation-on-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 05:09:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by J.K. Rowling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/396385-and-so-rock-bottom-became-the-solid-foundation-on-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And so rock bottom became the solid foundation on which I rebuilt my life." -- J.K. Rowling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94042-she-had-always-wanted-words-she-loved-them-grew-up</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 09:07:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94042-she-had-always-wanted-words-she-loved-them-grew-up]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She had always wanted words, she loved them; grew up on them. Words gave her clarity, brought reason, shape." -- Michael Ondaatje]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271974-summertime-is-always-the-best-of-what-might-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 16:37:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Mo add a quote by Charles Bowden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271974-summertime-is-always-the-best-of-what-might-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Summertime is always the best of what might be." -- Charles Bowden]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
