<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/964869-elizabeth-olsen]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/964869-elizabeth-olsen" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 02:24:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22323-all-things-are-subject-to-interpretation-whichever-interpretation-prevails-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 02:24:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22323-all-things-are-subject-to-interpretation-whichever-interpretation-prevails-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All things are subject to interpretation. Whichever interpretation prevails at a given time is a function of power and not truth." -- Friedrich Nietzsche]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 10:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5853-you-think-your-pain-and-your-heartbreak-are-unprecedented-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You think your pain and your heartbreak are unprecedented in the history of the world, but then you read. It was books that taught me that the things that tormented me most were the very things that connected me with all the people who were alive, or who had ever been alive." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166793-the-very-beginning-of-genesis-tells-us-that-god-created</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 08:33:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/166793-the-very-beginning-of-genesis-tells-us-that-god-created]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very beginning of Genesis tells us that God created man in order to give him dominion over fish and fowl and all creatures. Of course, Genesis was written by a man, not a horse. There is no certainty that God actually did grant man dominion over other creatures. What seems more likely, in fact, is that man invented God to sanctify the dominion that he had usurped for himself over the cow and the horse." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129113-every-form-of-happiness-is-private-our-greatest-moments-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2010 04:21:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129113-every-form-of-happiness-is-private-our-greatest-moments-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every form of happiness is private. Our greatest moments are personal, self-motivated, not to be touched. The things which are sacred or precious to us are the things we withdraw from promiscuous sharing. But now we are taught to throw everything within us into public light and common pawing. To seek joy in meeting halls. We haven't even got a word for the quality I mean--for the self-sufficiency of man's spirit. It's difficult to call it selfishness or egotism, the words have been perverted, they've come to mean Peter Keating. Gail, I think the only cardinal evil on earth is that of placing your prime concern within other men. I've always demanded a certain quality in the people I liked. I've always recognized it at once--and it's the only quality I respect in men. I chose my friends by that. Now I know what it is. A self-sufficient ego. Nothing else matters." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20693-whoever-you-are-no-matter-how-lonely-the-world-offers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 21:11:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by ~Mary Oliver, &quot;Wild Geese&quot;]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20693-whoever-you-are-no-matter-how-lonely-the-world-offers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whoever you are, no matter how lonely, the world offers itself to your imagination, calls to you like the wild geese, harsh and exciting-over and over announcing your place in the family of things." -- ~Mary Oliver, &quot;Wild Geese&quot;]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2010 21:10:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by David McCullough]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19080-once-upon-a-time-in-the-dead-of-winter-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once upon a time in the dead of winter in the Dakota Territory, Theodore Roosevelt took off in a makeshift boat down the Little Missouri River in pursuit of a couple of thieves who had stolen his prized rowboat.  After several days on the river, he caught up and got the draw on them with his trusty Winchester, at which point they surrendered.  Then Roosevelt set off in a borrowed wagon to haul the thieves cross-country to justice.  They headed across the snow-covered wastes of the Badlands to the railhead at Dickinson, and Roosevelt walked the whole way, the entire 40 miles.  It was an astonishing feat, what might be called a defining moment in Roosevelt’s eventful life.  But what makes it especially memorable is that during that time, he managed to read all of &lt;i&gt;Anna Karenina&lt;/i&gt;.  I often think of that when I hear people say they haven’t time to read." -- David McCullough]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37510-dogs-are-our-link-to-paradise-they-don-t-know-evil</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 10:44:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37510-dogs-are-our-link-to-paradise-they-don-t-know-evil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dogs are our link to paradise. They don't know evil or jealousy or discontent. To sit with a dog on a hillside on a glorious afternoon is to be back in Eden, where doing nothing was not boring--it was peace." -- Milan Kundera ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1228-humanity-s-true-moral-test-its-fundamental-test-consists-of-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 10:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1228-humanity-s-true-moral-test-its-fundamental-test-consists-of-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humanity's true moral test, its fundamental test, consists of its attitude towards those who are at its mercy: animals.  And in this respect humankind has suffered a fundamental debacle, a debacle so fundamental that all others stem from it." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275714-we-have-a-soul-at-times-no-one-s-got-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 14:24:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Wisława Szymborska]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275714-we-have-a-soul-at-times-no-one-s-got-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have a soul at times.
No one’s got it non-stop,
for keeps.

Day after day,
year after year
may pass without it.

Sometimes
it will settle for awhile
only in childhood’s fears and raptures.
Sometimes only in astonishment
that we are old.

It rarely lends a hand
in uphill tasks,
like moving furniture,
or lifting luggage,
or going miles in shoes that pinch.

It usually steps out
whenever meat needs chopping
or forms have to be filled.

For every thousand conversations
it participates in one,
if even that,
since it prefers silence.

Just when our body goes from ache to pain,
it slips off-duty.

It’s picky:
it doesn’t like seeing us in crowds,
our hustling for a dubious advantage
and creaky machinations make it sick.

Joy and sorrow
aren’t two different feelings for it.
It attends us
only when the two are joined.

We can count on it
when we’re sure of nothing
and curious about everything.

Among the material objects
it favors clocks with pendulums
and mirrors, which keep on working
even when no one is looking.

It won’t say where it comes from
or when it’s taking off again,
though it’s clearly expecting such questions.

We need it
but apparently
it needs us
for some reason too." -- Wisława Szymborska]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48431-she-loved-to-walk-down-the-street-with-a-book</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 10:45:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48431-she-loved-to-walk-down-the-street-with-a-book]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["she loved to walk down the street with a book under her arm. It had the same significance for her as an elegant cane for the dandy a century ago. It differentiated her from others." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94098-he-had-always-wanted-to-write-music-and-he-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 16:26:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94098-he-had-always-wanted-to-write-music-and-he-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He had always wanted to write music, and he could give no other identity to the thing he sought. If you want to know what it is, he told himself, listen to the first phrases of Tchaikovsky’s First Concerto--or the last movement of Rachmaninoff’s Second. Men have not found the words for it, nor the deed nor the thought, but they have found the music. Let me see that in one single act of man on earth. Let me see it made real. Let me see the answer to the promise of that music. Not servants nor those served; not altars and immolations; but the final, the fulfilled, innocent of pain. Don’t help me or serve me, but let me see it once, because I need it. Don’t work for my happiness, my brothers--show me yours--show me that it is possible--show me your achievement--and the knowledge will give me courage for mine." -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129117-the-future-enters-into-us-in-order-to-transform-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 14:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129117-the-future-enters-into-us-in-order-to-transform-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future enters into us, in order to transform itself in us, long before it happens." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275709-be-helpless-dumbfounded-unable-to-say-yes-or-no-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2010 14:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275709-be-helpless-dumbfounded-unable-to-say-yes-or-no-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be helpless, dumbfounded,
Unable to say yes or no.
Then a stretcher will come from grace
    to gather us up.

We are too dull-eyed to see that beauty.
If we say we can, we’re lying.
If we say No, we don’t see it,
That No will behead us
And shut tight our window onto spirit.

So let us rather not be sure of anything,
Beside ourselves, and only that, so
Miraculous beings come running to help.
Crazed, lying in a zero circle, mute,
We shall be saying finally,
With tremendous eloquence, Lead us.
When we have totally surrendered to that beauty,
We shall be a mighty kindness." -- Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67769-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 11:59:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by W.H. Murray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/67769-until-one-is-committed-there-is-hesitancy-the-chance-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Until one is committed, there is hesitancy, the chance to draw back. Concerning all acts of initiative (and creation), there is one elementary truth, the ignorance of which kills countless ideas and splendid plans: that the moment one definitely commits oneself, then Providence moves too. All sorts of things occur to help one that would never otherwise have occurred. A whole stream of events issues from the decision, raising in one's favor all manner of unforeseen incidents and meetings and material assistance, which no man could have dreamed would have come his way. Whatever you can do, or dream you can do, begin it. Boldness has genius, power, and magic in it. Begin it now." -- W.H. Murray]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 07:09:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 07:09:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 07:10:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Miss Piggy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and it may be necessary from time to time to give a stupid or misinformed beholder a black eye." -- Miss Piggy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 07:12:05 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5030-we-don-t-see-things-as-they-are-we-see-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29455-thanks-to-art-instead-of-seeing-one-world-only-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 07:53:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29455-thanks-to-art-instead-of-seeing-one-world-only-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks to art, instead of seeing one world only, our own, we see that world multiply itself and we have at our disposal as many worlds as there are original artists, worlds more different one from the other than those which revolve in infinite space, worlds which, centuries after the extinction of the fire from which their light first emanated, whether it is called Rembrandt or Vermeer, send us still each one its special radiance." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14648-we-come-spinning-out-of-nothingness-scattering-stars-like-dust</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 09:51:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14648-we-come-spinning-out-of-nothingness-scattering-stars-like-dust]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We come spinning out of nothingness, scattering stars like dust." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58372-hard-people-are-weak-people-whom-nobody-wants-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 08:11:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58372-hard-people-are-weak-people-whom-nobody-wants-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Hard people are weak people whom nobody wants, and the strong, caring little whether they are wanted or not, have alone that meekness which the common herd mistake for weakness." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113175-everything-great-in-the-world-is-done-by-neurotics-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 08:12:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Marcel Proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113175-everything-great-in-the-world-is-done-by-neurotics-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything great in the world is done by neurotics; they alone founded our religions and created our masterpieces." -- Marcel Proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58146-forgetting-that-beauty-and-happiness-are-only-ever-incarnated-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2009 08:14:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by proust]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58146-forgetting-that-beauty-and-happiness-are-only-ever-incarnated-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forgetting that beauty and happiness are only ever incarnated in an individual person, we replace them in our minds by a conventional pattern, a sort of average of all the different faces we have ever admired, all the different pleasures we have ever enjoyed, and thus carry about with us abstract images, which are lifeless and uninspiring because they lack the very quality that something new, something different from what is familiar, always possesses, and which is the quality inseparable from real beauty and happiness. So we make our pessimistic pronouncements on life, which we think are valid, in the belief that we have taken account of beauty and happiness, whereas we have actually omitted them from consideration, substituting for them synthetic compounds that contain nothing of them." -- proust]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 14:32:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6806-the-more-that-you-read-the-more-things-you-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more that you read, the more things you will know. The more that you learn, the more places you'll go." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94878-you-ll-get-mixed-up-of-course-as-you-already-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2009 14:42:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94878-you-ll-get-mixed-up-of-course-as-you-already-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll get mixed up, of course, as you already know. You'll get mixed up with many strange birds as you go. So be sure when you step. Step with care and great tact and remember that Life's a Great Balancing Act. Just never forget to be dexterous and deft. And never mix up your right foot with your left." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27067-in-silence-there-is-eloquence-stop-weaving-and-see-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2010 09:52:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27067-in-silence-there-is-eloquence-stop-weaving-and-see-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Silence there is eloquence. Stop weaving and see how the pattern improves." -- Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187565-her-father-was-frightened-by-a-strange-bed-or-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2009 10:50:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/187565-her-father-was-frightened-by-a-strange-bed-or-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her father was frightened by a strange bed or a foreign language or a political party he didn't belong to.  Her father truly believed that the Democratic party was a subversive organization whose design would destroy the United States and put it in the hands of bearded communists." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 20:27:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Mary Oliver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1921-tell-me-what-is-it-you-plan-to-do-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me, what is it you plan to do 
with your one wild and precious life?" -- Mary Oliver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 20:30:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3823-you-gain-strength-courage-and-confidence-by-every-experience-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You are able to say to yourself, 'I have lived through this horror. I can take the next thing that comes along.' You must do the thing you think you cannot do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 20:30:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Elizabeth add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26110-you-wouldn-t-worry-so-much-about-what-others-think-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You wouldn't worry so much about what others think of you if you realized how seldom they do." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
