<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/965714-lisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/965714-lisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:38:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352299-i-have-decided-to-leave-clea-s-last-letter-un-answered-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 14:38:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352299-i-have-decided-to-leave-clea-s-last-letter-un-answered-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have decided to leave Clea’s last letter un-answered. I no longer wish to coerce anyone, to make promises, to think of life in terms of compacts, resolutions, covenants. It will be up to Clea to interpret my silence according to her own needs and desires, to come to me if she has need or not, as the case may be. Does not everything depend on our interpretation of the silence around us?" -- Lawrence Durrell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352297-lincoln-s-ability-to-retain-his-emotional-balance-in-such-difficult</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 03:17:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352297-lincoln-s-ability-to-retain-his-emotional-balance-in-such-difficult]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lincoln's ability to retain his emotional balance in such difficult situations was rooted in actute self-awareness and an enormous capacity to dispel anxiety in constructive ways." -- Doris Kearns Goodwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43943-we-re-here-to-get-each-other-through-this-thing-whatever</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2011 13:39:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43943-we-re-here-to-get-each-other-through-this-thing-whatever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We're here to get each other through this thing, whatever it is." -- Mark Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 08:40:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38225-if-you-are-careful-garp-wrote-if-you-use-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are careful,' Garp wrote, 'if you use good ingredients, and you don't take any shortcuts, then you can usually cook something very good. Sometimes it is the only worthwhile product you can salvage from a day; what you make to eat. With writing, I find, you can have all the right ingredients, give plenty of time and care, and still get nothing. Also true of love. Cooking, therefore, can keep a person who tries hard sane." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403932-you-have-been-reading-byron-you-have-been-marking-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 18:07:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Virgina Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403932-you-have-been-reading-byron-you-have-been-marking-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have been reading Byron. You have been marking the passages that seem to approve of your own character. I find marks against all those sentences which seem to express a sardonic yet passionate nature a moth-like impetuosity dashing itself against hard glass. You thought as you drew your pencil there 'I too throw off my cloak like that. I too snap my fingers in the face of destiny." -- Virgina Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404959-it-will-be-hard-james-but-you-come-from-sturdy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 08:56:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404959-it-will-be-hard-james-but-you-come-from-sturdy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It will be hard James but you come from sturdy peasant stock men who picked cotton and dammed rivers and built railroads and in the teeth of the most terrifying odds achieved an unassailable and monumental dignity You come from a long line of great poets some of the greatest poets since Homer. One of them said &quot;The very time I thought I was lost My dungeon shook and my chains fell off.&quot; You know and I know that the country is celebrating one hundred years of freedom one hundred years too soon. We cannot be free until they are free. God bless you James and Godspeed." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411085-it-s-corny-but-i-think-poems-are-echoes-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 09:32:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Paul Beatty]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411085-it-s-corny-but-i-think-poems-are-echoes-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's corny, but I think poems are echoes of the voices in your head and from your past. Your sisters, your father, your ancestors taking to you and through you. Some of it is primal, some of it is hallucinatory bullshit. That madness those boys rapping ain't nothing but urban folklore. They retelling stories passed down from chicken coop to apartment stoop to Ford coupe. Hear that rhyme, boy. Shit, I could get down and rap if I had to. MC Big Mama Osteoporosis in the house." -- Paul Beatty]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403441-how-do-you-know-your-peanut-butter-has-a-pill</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 07:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Joe Garden]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/403441-how-do-you-know-your-peanut-butter-has-a-pill]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How do you know your peanut butter has a pill inside of it? Take this simple test. Is your owner giving you peanut butter? If the answer is yes then the chances are are good that there is a pill in it." -- Joe Garden]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615101-ten-watercolors-were-made-from-that-star</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 15:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/615101-ten-watercolors-were-made-from-that-star]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ten watercolors were made from that star." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
