<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/965901-brittany]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/965901-brittany" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:21:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:21:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22087-this-much-i-m-certain-of-it-doesn-t-happen-immediately-you-ll]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This much I'm certain of: it doesn't happen immediately. You'll finish [the book] and that will be that, until a moment will come, maybe in a month, maybe a year, maybe even several years. You'll be sick or feeling troubled or deeply in love or quietly uncertain or even content for the first time in your life. It won't matter. Out of the blue, beyond any cause you can trace, you'll suddenly realize things are not how you perceived them to be at all. For some reason, you will no longer be the person you believed you once were. You'll detect slow and subtle shifts going on all around you, more importantly shifts in you. Worse, you'll realize it's always been shifting, like a shimmer of sorts, a vast shimmer, only dark like a room. But you won't understand why or how. You'll have forgotten what granted you this awareness in the first place&lt;br&gt;
...&lt;br&gt;
You might try then, as I did, to find a sky so full of stars it will blind you again. Only no sky can blind you now. Even with all that iridescent magic up there, your eye will no longer linger on the light, it will no longer trace constellations. You'll care only about the darkness and you'll watch it for hours, for days, maybe even for years, trying in vain to believe you're some kind of indispensable, universe-appointed sentinel, as if just by looking you could actually keep it all at bay. It will get so bad you'll be afraid to look away, you'll be afraid to sleep.&lt;br&gt;
Then no matter where you are, in a crowded restaurant or on some desolate street or even in the comforts of your own home, you'll watch yourself dismantle every assurance you ever lived by. You'll stand aside as a great complexity intrudes, tearing apart, piece by piece, all of your carefully conceived denials, whether deliberate or unconscious. And then for better or worse you'll turn, unable to resist, though try to resist you still will, fighting with everything you've got not to face the thing you most dread, what is now, what will be, what has always come before, the creature you truly are, the creature we all are, buried in the nameless black of a name.&lt;br&gt;
And then the nightmares will begin." -- Mark Z. Danielewski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:49:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:57:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44796-it-s-the-job-that-s-never-started-as-takes-longest-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44796-it-s-the-job-that-s-never-started-as-takes-longest-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's the job that's never started as takes longest to finish." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167791-a-single-dream-is-more-powerful-than-a-thousand-realities</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 09:58:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167791-a-single-dream-is-more-powerful-than-a-thousand-realities]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A single dream is more powerful than a thousand realities." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83729-an-intellectual-says-a-simple-thing-in-a-hard-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 08:56:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83729-an-intellectual-says-a-simple-thing-in-a-hard-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An intellectual says a simple thing in a hard way. An artist says a hard thing in a simple way." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54579-if-you-re-losing-your-soul-and-you-know-it-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 08:56:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by charles bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54579-if-you-re-losing-your-soul-and-you-know-it-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're losing your soul and you know it, then you've still got a soul left to lose" -- charles bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34532-poetry-is-what-happens-when-nothing-else-can</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 08:57:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Brittany add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34532-poetry-is-what-happens-when-nothing-else-can]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Poetry is what happens when nothing else can." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
