<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966154-kasey]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966154-kasey" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:41:34 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:41:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:42:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32810-i-will-hate-the-man-you-choose-because-he-isn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 08:13:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Robert Jordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32810-i-will-hate-the-man-you-choose-because-he-isn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will hate the man you choose because he isn't me, and love him if he makes you smile." -- Robert Jordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40031-you-have-made-flowers-grow-where-i-cultivated-dust-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2008 09:00:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Robert Jordon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40031-you-have-made-flowers-grow-where-i-cultivated-dust-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have made flowers grow where I cultivated dust and stones. Remember this, on this journey you insist on making. If you die, I will not survive you long." -- Robert Jordon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146209-sometimes-it-s-a-good-thing-we-don-t-remember-things-half</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 20:56:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146209-sometimes-it-s-a-good-thing-we-don-t-remember-things-half]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes it's a good thing we don't remember things half as well as books do." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24217-books-have-to-be-heavy-because-the-whole-world-s-inside</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 20:57:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24217-books-have-to-be-heavy-because-the-whole-world-s-inside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books have to be heavy because the whole world's inside them." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2009 20:57:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30181-if-you-take-a-book-with-you-on-a-journey]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you take a book with you on a journey,&quot; Mo had said when he put the first one in her box, &quot;an odd thing happens: The book begins collecting your memories. And forever after you have only to open that book to be back where you first read it. It will all come into your mind with the very first words: the sights you saw in that place, what it smelled like, the ice cream you ate while you were reading it... yes, books are like flypaper—memories cling to the printed page better than anything else." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 19:49:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18630-i-ve-been-making-a-list-of-the-things-they-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've been making a list of the things they don't teach you at school. They don't teach you how to love somebody. They don't teach you how to be famous. They don't teach you how to be rich or how to be poor. They don't teach you how to walk away from someone you don't love any longer. They don't teach you how to know what's going on in someone else's mind. They don't teach you what to say to someone who's dying. They don't teach you anything worth knowing." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54774-the-house-smelled-musty-and-damp-and-a-little-sweet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 19:52:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54774-the-house-smelled-musty-and-damp-and-a-little-sweet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The house smelled musty and damp, and a little sweet, as if it were haunted by the ghosts of long-dead cookies." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2009 19:57:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 14:54:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/352-outside-of-a-dog-a-book-is-man-s-best-friend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Outside of a dog, a book is man's best friend. Inside of a dog it's too dark to read." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2009 14:54:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222967-the-sea-always-filled-her-with-longing-though-for-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 12:14:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Cornelia Funke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222967-the-sea-always-filled-her-with-longing-though-for-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The sea always filled her with longing, though for what she was never sure." -- Cornelia Funke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222968-honestly-if-you-re-given-the-choice-between-armageddon-or-tea</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 10:57:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222968-honestly-if-you-re-given-the-choice-between-armageddon-or-tea]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Honestly, if you're given the choice between Armageddon or tea, you don't say 'what kind of tea?" -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228355-clare-seems-so-pleased-with-the-idea-of-me-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 12:15:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kasey add a quote by Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228355-clare-seems-so-pleased-with-the-idea-of-me-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Clare seems so pleased with the idea of me as a pirate that she forgets that I am Stranger Danger." -- Audrey Niffenegger]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
