<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966139-sara-mcnamara]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966139-sara-mcnamara" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 02:53:18 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41662-a-true-revolution-of-values-will-soon-cause-us-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 02:53:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41662-a-true-revolution-of-values-will-soon-cause-us-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A true revolution of values will soon cause us to question the fairness and justice of many of our past and present policies. ... A true revolution of values will soon look uneasily on the glaring contrast of poverty and wealth. With righteous indignation, it will look across the seas and see individual capitalists of the West investing huge sums of money in Asia, Africa, and South America, only to take the profits out with no concern for the social betterment of the countries, and say, &quot;This is not just.&quot; It will look at our alliance with the landed gentry of South America and say, &quot;This is not just.&quot; The Western arrogance of feeling that it has everything to teach others and nothing to learn from them is not just." -- Martin Luther King Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17501-if-ye-love-wealth-better-than-liberty-the-tranquility-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 04:08:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sara add a quote by Samuel Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17501-if-ye-love-wealth-better-than-liberty-the-tranquility-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If ye love wealth better than liberty, the tranquility of servitude better than the animating contest of freedom, go home from us in peace. We ask not your counsels or arms. Crouch down and lick the hands which feed you. May your chains set lightly upon you, and may posterity forget that ye were our countrymen." -- Samuel Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
