<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966316-tony-derricott]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/966316-tony-derricott" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 17:29:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 17:29:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tony add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2621-love-all-trust-a-few-do-wrong-to-none]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273478-think-of-the-purest-most-all-consuming-love-you-can-imagine</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 13:27:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tony add a quote by Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/273478-think-of-the-purest-most-all-consuming-love-you-can-imagine]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Think of the purest, most all-consuming love you can imagine. Now multiply that love by an infinite amount—that is the measure of God’s love for you. God does not look on the outward appearance. I believe that He doesn’t care one bit if we live in a castle or a cottage, if we are handsome or homely, if we are famous or forgotten. Though we are incomplete, God loves us completely. Though we are imperfect, He loves us perfectly. Though we may feel lost and without compass, God love encompasses us completely. He loves us because He is filled with an infinite measure of holy, pure, and indescribable love. We are important to God not because of our résumé but because we are His children. He loves every one of us, even those who are flawed, rejected, awkward, sorrowful, or broken. God’s love is so great that He loves even the proud, the selfish, the arrogant, and the wicked. What this means is that, regardless of our current state, there is hope for us. No matter our distress, no matter our sorrow, no matter our mistakes, our infinitely compassionate Heavenly Father desires that we draw near to Him so that He can draw near to us." -- Dieter F. Uchtdorf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116204-only-those-who-try-to-resist-temptation-know-how-strong</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2013 09:19:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tony add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116204-only-those-who-try-to-resist-temptation-know-how-strong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only those who try to resist temptation know how strong it is. ... We never find out the strength of the evil impulse inside us until we try to fight it: and Christ, because He was the only man who never yielded to temptation, is also the only man who knows to the full what temptation means—the only complete realist." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
