<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/967054-amanda-jacobs]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/967054-amanda-jacobs" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 20:37:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 20:37:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13878-whatever-i-do-however-i-find-a-way-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whatever I do, however I find a way to live, I will tell these stories.  I have spoken to every person I have encountered these last difficult days...I speak to these people, and I speak to you because I cannot help it.  It gives me strength, almost unbelievable strength, to know that you are there.  I covet your eyes, your ears, the collapsible space between us.  How blessed are we to have each other?  I am alive and you are alive and so we must fill the air with our words.  I will fill today, tomorrow, every day until I am taken back to God.  I will tell stories to people who will listen and to people who don't want to listen, to people who seek me out and to those who run.  All the while I will know that you are there.  How can I pretend that you do not exist?  It would be almost as impossible as you pretending that I do not exist." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 20:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 20:39:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Nicole Krauss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11332-at-the-end-all-that-s-left-of-you-are-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At the end, all that's left of you are your possessions.  Perhaps that's why I've never been able to throw anything away.  Perhaps that's why I hoarded the world:  with the hope that when I died, the sum total of my things would suggest a life larger than the one I lived." -- Nicole Krauss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 20:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16238-some-people-never-go-crazy-what-truly-horrible-lives-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people never go crazy. What truly horrible lives they must lead." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 21:32:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Joshua Ferris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet for all the depression no one ever quit.  When someone quit, we couldn't believe it. 'I'm becoming a rafting instructor on the Colorado River,' they said.  'I'm touring college towns with my garage band.'  We were dumbfounded. It was like they were from another planet.  Where had they found the derring-do?  What would they do about car payments?  We got together for going away drinks on their final day and tried to hide our envy while reminding ourselves that we still had the freedom and luxury to shop indiscriminately." -- Joshua Ferris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46243-when-i-see-a-couple-of-kids-and-guess-he-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2008 10:38:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Amanda add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46243-when-i-see-a-couple-of-kids-and-guess-he-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I see a couple of kids
And guess he's fucking her and she's
Taking pills or wearing a diaphragm,
I know this is paradise

Everyone old has dreamed of all their lives—
Bonds and gestures pushed to one side
Like an outdated combine harvester,
And everyone young going down the long slide" -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
