<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/967923-marie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/967923-marie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:22:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216149-no-space-of-regret-can-make-amends-for-one-life-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:22:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216149-no-space-of-regret-can-make-amends-for-one-life-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No space of regret can make amends for one life's opportunity misused" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216152-for-it-is-good-to-be-children-sometimes-and-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216152-for-it-is-good-to-be-children-sometimes-and-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For it is good to be children sometimes, and never better than at Christmas, when its mighty Founder was a child Himself." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122226-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-irresistibly-contagious-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:22:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122226-there-is-nothing-in-the-world-so-irresistibly-contagious-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing in the world so irresistibly contagious as laughter and good humor." -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494832-i-will-honour-christmas-in-my-heart-and-try-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 00:23:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Charles Dickens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494832-i-will-honour-christmas-in-my-heart-and-try-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will honour Christmas in my heart, and try to keep it all the year. I will live in the Past, the Present, and the Future. The Spirits of all Three shall strive within me. I will not shut out the lessons that they teach!" -- Charles Dickens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34012-if-you-re-trying-to-be-miserable-it-s-important-you-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 10:10:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by John Bytheway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34012-if-you-re-trying-to-be-miserable-it-s-important-you-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you're trying to be miserable, it's important you don't have any goals.  No school goals, personal goals, family goals.  Your only objective each day should be to inhale and exhale for sixteen hours before you go to bed again.  Don't read anything informative, don't listen to anything useful, don't do anything productive.  If you start achieving goals, you might start to feel a sense of excitement, then you might want to set another goal, and then your miserable mornings are through.  To maintain your misery, the idea of crossing off your goals should never cross your mind." -- John Bytheway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329837-cat-where-are-you-going-alice-which-way-should-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 10:11:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Lewis Carroll]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/329837-cat-where-are-you-going-alice-which-way-should-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cat: Where are you going?
Alice: Which way should I go?
Cat: That depends on where you are going.
Alice: I don’t know.
Cat: Then it doesn’t matter which way you go." -- Lewis Carroll]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55268-even-a-moment-s-reflection-will-help-you-see-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 10:15:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55268-even-a-moment-s-reflection-will-help-you-see-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even a moment's reflection will help you see that the problem of using your time well is not a problem of the mind but of the heart. It will only yield to a change in the very way we feel about time. The value of time must change for us. And then the way we think about it will change, naturally and wisely. 
That change in feeling and in thinking is combined in the words of a prophet of God in this dispensation. It was Brigham Young, and the year was 1877, and he was speaking at April general conference. He wasn't talking about time or schedules or frustrations with too many demands upon us. Rather, he was trying to teach the members of the Church how to unite themselves in what was called the united order. The Saints were grappling with the question of how property should be distributed if they were to live the celestial law. In his usual direct style, he taught the people that they were having trouble finding solutions because they misunderstood the problem. Particularly, he told them they didn't understand either property or the distribution of wealth. Here is what he said: 

With regard to our property, as I have told you many times, the property which we inherit from our Heavenly Father is our time, and the power to choose in the disposition of the same. This is the real capital that is bequeathed unto us by our Heavenly Father; all the rest is what he may be pleased to add unto us. To direct, to counsel and to advise in the disposition of our time, pertains to our calling as God's servants, according to the wisdom which he has given and will continue to give unto us as we seek it. [JD 18:354] 

Time is the property we inherit from God, along with the power to choose what we will do with it. President Young calls the gift of life, which is time and the power to dispose of it, so great an inheritance that we should feel it is our capital. The early Yankee families in America taught their children and grandchildren some rules about an inheritance. They were always to invest the capital they inherited and live only on part of the earnings. One rule was &quot;Never spend your capital.&quot; And those families had confidence the rule would be followed because of an attitude of responsibility toward those who would follow in later generations. It didn't always work, but the hope was that inherited wealth would be felt a trust so important that no descendent would put pleasure ahead of obligation to those who would follow. Now, I can see and hear Brigham Young, who was as flinty a New Englander as the Adams or the Cabots ever hoped to be, as if he were leaning over this pulpit tonight. He would say something like this, with a directness and power I wish I could approach: &quot;Your inheritance is time. It is capital far more precious than any lands or stocks or houses you will ever get. Spend it foolishly, and you will bankrupt yourself and cheapen the inheritance of those that follow you. Invest it wisely, and you will bless generations to come.
	“A Child of Promise”, BYU Speeches, 4 May 1986" -- Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336959-it-is-important-that-when-we-make-a-resolution-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2012 10:16:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Steve Maraboli]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/336959-it-is-important-that-when-we-make-a-resolution-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is important that when we make a resolution, or establish a goal, that we take the ACTION necessary to accomplish that goal." -- Steve Maraboli]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411386-i-m-bored-is-a-useless-thing-to-say-i-mean</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 20:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Marie add a quote by Louis C.K.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411386-i-m-bored-is-a-useless-thing-to-say-i-mean]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m bored’ is a useless thing to say. I mean, you live in a great, big, vast world that you’ve seen none percent of. Even the inside of your own mind is endless; it goes on forever, inwardly, do you understand? The fact that you’re alive is amazing, so you don’t get to say ‘I’m bored." -- Louis C.K.]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
