<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96812-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96812-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 23:09:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43120-from-the-place-by-the-railing-at-the-edge-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 23:09:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Sherwood Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43120-from-the-place-by-the-railing-at-the-edge-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From the place by the railing at the edge of the tracks on the summer evening I return across the city to my own room. I am vividly aware of my own life that escaped the winter on the boat. How many such lives I have lived. Then I only made a dollar and a half a day and now I sometimes make more than that in a few minutes. How wonderful to be able to write words. ... Again I begin the endless game of reconstructing my own life, jerking it out of the shell that dies, striving to breathe into it beauty and meaning. ... I wonder why my life, why all lives, are not more beautiful." -- Sherwood Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43122-because-some-days-the-world-holds-true-at-the-drop</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 23:21:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Gary Lutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43122-because-some-days-the-world-holds-true-at-the-drop]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because some days the world holds true at the drop of a hat, don't you find? Things favor themselves: whatever you reach for - a shimmered arm, or parts unknown - is ready, finally, to have itself be handled." -- Gary Lutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43123-then-came-nights-when-lying-awake-beside-my-final-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2008 23:23:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Gary Lutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43123-then-came-nights-when-lying-awake-beside-my-final-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then came nights when, lying awake beside my final wife, I would spend too much time putting my finger on what was wrong. I was wearing the finger out. 

What was wrong was very simple. 

Sometimes her life and mine fell on the same day." -- Gary Lutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38207-then-what-is-good-the-obsessive-interest-in-human-affairs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2008 21:40:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Tennessee Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38207-then-what-is-good-the-obsessive-interest-in-human-affairs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then what is good? The obsessive interest in human affairs, plus a certain amount of compassion and moral conviction, that first made the experience of living something that must be translated into pigment or music or bodily movement or poetry or prose or anything that's dynamic and expressivee--that's what's good for you if you're at all serious in your aims. William Saroyan wrote a great play on this theme, that purity of heart is the one success worth having. &quot;In the time of your life--live!&quot; That time is short and it doesn't return again. It is slipping away while I write this and while you read it, the monosyllable of the clock is Loss, loss, loss, unless you devote your heart to its opposition." -- Tennessee Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
