<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96892-jennifer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/96892-jennifer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 11:17:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201521-good-writing-does-not-succeed-or-fail-on-the-strength</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2010 11:17:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201521-good-writing-does-not-succeed-or-fail-on-the-strength]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good writing does not succeed or fail on the strength of its ability to persuade.  It succeeds or fails on the strength of its ability to engage you, to make you think, to give you a glimpse into someone else's head." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239633-nothing-momentous-comes-in-this-world-unless-it-comes-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2010 10:14:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/239633-nothing-momentous-comes-in-this-world-unless-it-comes-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...nothing momentous comes in this world unless it comes on the shoulders of kindness." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267653-this-is-me-he-handed-her-the-precious-scrap-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 06:45:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/267653-this-is-me-he-handed-her-the-precious-scrap-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This is me.’&quot; He handed her the precious scrap of paper. ‘Call me or I’ll call you, but one of us will call, yes? What I mean is it’s not a competition. You don’t lose if you phone first" -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312964-in-the-world-i-notice-persons-are-nearly-always-stressed</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 05:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Emma Donoghue]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312964-in-the-world-i-notice-persons-are-nearly-always-stressed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the world I notice persons are nearly always stressed and have no time...I don't know how persons with jobs do the jobs and all the living as well...I guess the time gets spread very thin like butter all over the world, the roads and houses and playgrounds and stores, so there's only a little smear of time on each place, then everyone has to hurry on to the next bit." -- Emma Donoghue]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184216-life-is-so-often-unfair-and-painful-and-love-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2012 07:36:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jenna Blum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/184216-life-is-so-often-unfair-and-painful-and-love-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is so often unfair and painful and love is hard to find and you have to take it whenever and wherever you can get it, no matter how brief it is or how it ends." -- Jenna Blum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575228-love-makes-you-want-to-be-a-better-man-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 17:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575228-love-makes-you-want-to-be-a-better-man-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love makes you want to be a better man. But maybe love, real love, also gives you permission to just be the man you are." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 05:01:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/584441-men-always-say-that-as-the-defining-compliment-don-t-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Men always say that as the defining compliment, don’t they? She’s a cool girl. Being the Cool Girl means I am a hot, brilliant, funny woman who adores football, poker, dirty jokes, and burping, who plays video games, drinks cheap beer, loves threesomes and anal sex, and jams hot dogs and hamburgers into her mouth like she’s hosting the world’s biggest culinary gang bang while somehow maintaining a size 2, because Cool Girls are above all hot. Hot and understanding. Cool Girls never get angry; they only smile in a chagrined, loving manner and let their men do whatever they want. Go ahead, shit on me, I don’t mind, I’m the Cool Girl.

Men actually think this girl exists. Maybe they’re fooled because so many women are willing to pretend to be this girl. For a long time Cool Girl offended me. I used to see men – friends, coworkers, strangers – giddy over these awful pretender women, and I’d want to sit these men down and calmly say: You are not dating a woman, you are dating a woman who has watched too many movies written by socially awkward men who’d like to believe that this kind of woman exists and might kiss them. I’d want to grab the poor guy by his lapels or messenger bag and say: The bitch doesn’t really love chili dogs that much – no one loves chili dogs that much! And the Cool Girls are even more pathetic: They’re not even pretending to be the woman they want to be, they’re pretending to be the woman a man wants them to be. Oh, and if you’re not a Cool Girl, I beg you not to believe that your man doesn’t want the Cool Girl. It may be a slightly different version – maybe he’s a vegetarian, so Cool Girl loves seitan and is great with dogs; or maybe he’s a hipster artist, so Cool Girl is a tattooed, bespectacled nerd who loves comics. There are variations to the window dressing, but believe me, he wants Cool Girl, who is basically the girl who likes every fucking thing he likes and doesn’t ever complain. (How do you know you’re not Cool Girl? Because he says things like: “I like strong women.” If he says that to you, he will at some point fuck someone else. Because “I like strong women” is code for “I hate strong women.”)" -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575063-the-ones-who-are-not-soul-mated-the-ones-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 05:12:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Gillian Flynn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/575063-the-ones-who-are-not-soul-mated-the-ones-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ones who are not soul-mated – the ones who have settled – are even more dismissive of my singleness: It’s not that hard to find someone to marry, they say. No relationship is perfect, they say – they, who make do with dutiful sex and gassy bedtime rituals, who settle for TV as conversation, who believe that husbandly capitulation – yes, honey, okay, honey – is the same as concord. &lt;i&gt;He’s doing what you tell him to do because he doesn’t care enough to argue&lt;/i&gt;, I think. &lt;i&gt;Your petty demands simply make him feel superior, or resentful, and someday he will fuck his pretty, young coworker who asks nothing of him, and you will actually be shocked&lt;/i&gt;. 

Give me a man with a little fight in him, a man who calls me on my bullshit. (But who also kind of likes my bullshit.) And yet: Don’t land me in one of those relationships where we’re always pecking at each other, disguising insults as jokes, rolling our eyes and ‘playfully’ scrapping in front of our friends, hoping to lure them to our side of an argument they could not care less about. Those awful &lt;i&gt;if only&lt;/i&gt; relationships: &lt;i&gt;This marriage would be great if only…&lt;/i&gt; and you sense the &lt;i&gt;if only&lt;/i&gt; list is a lot longer than either of them realizes.

So I know I am right not to settle, but it doesn’t make me feel better as my friends pair off and I stay home on Friday night with a bottle of wine and make myself an extravagant meal and tell myself, &lt;i&gt;This is perfect&lt;/i&gt;, as if I’m the one dating me. As I go to endless rounds of parties and bar nights, perfumed and sprayed and hopeful, rotating myself around the room like some dubious dessert. I go on dates with men who are nice and good-looking and smart – perfect-on-paper men who make me feel like I’m in a foreign land, trying to explain myself, trying to make myself known. Because isn’t that the point of every relationship: to be known by someone else, to be understood? He &lt;i&gt;gets&lt;/i&gt; me. She &lt;i&gt;gets&lt;/i&gt; me. Isn’t that the simple magic phrase?

So you suffer through the night with the perfect-on-paper man – the stutter of jokes misunderstood, the witty remarks lobbed and missed. Or maybe he understands that you’ve made a witty remark but, unsure of what to do with it, he holds it in his hand like some bit of conversational phlegm he will wipe away later. You spend another hour trying to find each other, to recognise each other, and you drink a little too much and try a little too hard. And you go home to a cold bed and think, &lt;i&gt;That was fine&lt;/i&gt;. And your life is a long line of fine." -- Gillian Flynn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10708-in-his-blue-gardens-men-and-girls-came-and-went</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 11:42:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10708-in-his-blue-gardens-men-and-girls-came-and-went]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his blue gardens men and girls came and went like moths among the whisperings and the champagne and the stars." -- F. Scott Fitzgerald]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827283-family-the-greatest-loyalty-after-god-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2013 17:23:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Sarah Dunant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827283-family-the-greatest-loyalty-after-god-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Family. The greatest loyalty after God in the world." -- Sarah Dunant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193961-when-i-am-an-old-woman-i-shall-wear-purple</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2014 05:21:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Jenny Joseph]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193961-when-i-am-an-old-woman-i-shall-wear-purple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I am an old woman I shall wear purple. With a red hat which doesn't go, and doesn't suit me." -- Jenny Joseph]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1191551-a-woman-without-a-man-is-like-a-fish-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 11:31:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jennifer add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1191551-a-woman-without-a-man-is-like-a-fish-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman without a man is like a fish without a bicycle, right?" -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
