<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/969308-michelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/969308-michelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 08:09:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29052-it-is-the-function-of-art-to-renew-our-perception</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 08:09:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29052-it-is-the-function-of-art-to-renew-our-perception]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is the function of art to renew our perception. What we are familiar with we cease to see. The writer shakes up the familiar scene, and, as if by magic, we see a new meaning in it." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38081-there-are-few-ways-in-which-good-people-do-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38081-there-are-few-ways-in-which-good-people-do-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are few ways in which good people do more harm to those who take them seriously than to defend the gospel with arguments that won't hold water. Many of the difficulties encountered by young people going to college would be avoided if parents and teachers were more careful to distinguish between what they know to be true and what they think may be true. Impetuous youth, upon finding the authority it trusts crumbling, even on unimportant details, is apt to lump everything together and throw the baby out with the bath." -- Henry B. Eyring]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:24:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Miss Piggy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder-and-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and it may be necessary from time to time to give a stupid or misinformed beholder a black eye." -- Miss Piggy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2008 22:34:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 07:47:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21075-love-is-a-temporary-madness-it-erupts-like-volcanoes-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a temporary madness, it erupts like volcanoes and then subsides.  And when it subsides, you have to make a decision.  You have to work out whether your roots have so entwined together that it is inconceivable that you should ever part.  Because this is what love is.  Love is not breathlessness, it is not excitement, it is not the promulgation of promises of eternal passion, it is not the desire to mate every second minute of the day, it is not lying awake at night imagining that he is kissing every cranny of your body.  No, don't blush, I am telling you some truths.  That is just being &quot;in love&quot;, which any fool can do.  Love itself is what is left over when being in love has burned away, and this is both an art and a fortunate accident." -- Louis de Bernieres]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
