<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/969400-michel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/969400-michel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:02:57 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31228-what-sphinx-of-cement-and-aluminium-bashed-open-their-skulls</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:02:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michel add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31228-what-sphinx-of-cement-and-aluminium-bashed-open-their-skulls]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["what sphinx of cement and aluminium bashed open their skulls and ate up their brains and imagination" -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 11:03:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michel add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 21:44:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michel add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is more complicated than you think. You only see a tenth of what is true. There are a million little strings attached to every choice you make; you can destroy your life every time you choose. But maybe you won't know for twenty years. And you'll never ever trace it to its source. And you only get one chance to play it out. Just try and figure out your own divorce. And they say there is no fate, but there is: it's what you create. Even though the world goes on for eons and eons, you are here for a fraction of a fraction of a second. Most of your time is spent being dead or not yet born. But while alive, you wait in vain, wasting years, for a phone call or a letter or a look from someone or something to make it all right. And it never comes or it seems to but doesn't really. And so you spend your time in vague regret or vaguer hope for something good to come along. Something to make you feel connected, to make you feel whole, to make you feel loved." -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
