<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/9694-robin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/9694-robin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 07:55:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65651-that-s-all-we-have-finally-the-words-and-they-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 07:55:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Raymond Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65651-that-s-all-we-have-finally-the-words-and-they-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That's all we have, finally, the words, and they had better be the right ones." -- Raymond Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 07:55:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10839-music-has-always-been-a-matter-of-energy-to-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Music has always been a matter of Energy to me, a question of Fuel.  Sentimental people call it Inspiration, but what they really mean is Fuel.  I have always needed Fuel. I am a serious consumer.  On some nights I still believe that a car with the gas needle on empty can run about fifty more miles if you have the right music very loud on the radio." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 04:05:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 04:05:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10722-i-love-you-as-certain-dark-things-are-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you as certain dark things are to be loved, 
in secret, between the shadow and the soul." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138724-the-more-i-make-love-the-more-i-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 05:25:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Ferlinghetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138724-the-more-i-make-love-the-more-i-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more I make love, the more I want to make revolution.  The more I make revolution, the more I want to make love." -- Ferlinghetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51416-smile-breathe-and-go-slowly</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 05:53:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51416-smile-breathe-and-go-slowly]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Smile, breathe and go slowly." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13666-if-there-is-any-secret-to-this-life-i-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 05:56:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by brian andreas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13666-if-there-is-any-secret-to-this-life-i-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["if there is any secret to this life i live, this is it: the sound of what cannot be seen sings within everything that can. and there is nothing more to it than that." -- brian andreas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47094-the-mind-was-dreaming-the-world-was-its-dream</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 14:02:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47094-the-mind-was-dreaming-the-world-was-its-dream]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The mind was dreaming. The world was its dream." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 15:15:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22892-it-s-only-after-we-ve-lost-everything-that-we-re-free-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's only after we've lost everything that we're free to do anything." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96553-love-is-the-mystery-of-water-and-a-star</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 21:07:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96553-love-is-the-mystery-of-water-and-a-star]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the mystery of water and a star." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4691-the-days-aren-t-discarded-or-collected-they-are-bees-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 21:08:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4691-the-days-aren-t-discarded-or-collected-they-are-bees-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The days aren't discarded or collected, they are bees
that burned with sweetness or maddened
the sting: the struggle continues,
the journeys go and come between honey and pain.
No, the net of years doesn't unweave: there is no net.
They don't fall drop by drop from a river: there is no river.
Sleep doesn't divide life into halves,
or action, or silence, or honor:
life is like a stone, a single motion,
a lonesome bonfire reflected on the leaves,
an arrow, only one, slow or swift, a metal
that climbs or descends burning in your bones." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 21:36:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102204-it-seems-to-me-that-almost-all-our-sadnesses-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It seems to me that almost all our sadnesses are moments of tension, which we feel as paralysis because we no longer hear our astonished emotions living. Because we are alone with the unfamiliar presence that has entered us; because everything we trust and are used to is for a moment taken away from us; because we stand in the midst of a transition where we cannot remain standing. That is why the sadness passes: the new presence inside us, the presence that has been added, has entered our heart, has gone into its innermost chamber and is no longer even there, - is already in our bloodstream. And we don't know what it was. We could easily be made to believe that nothing happened, and yet we have changed, as a house that a guest has entered changes. We can't say who has come, perhaps we will never know, but many signs indicate that the future enters us in this way in order to be transformed in us, long before it happens. And that is why it is so important to be solitary and attentive when one is sad: because the seemingly uneventful and motionless moment when our future steps into us is so much closer to life than that other loud and accidental point of time when it happens to us as if from outside. The quieter we are, the more patient and open we are in our sadnesses, the more deeply and serenely the new presence can enter us, and the more we can make it our own, the more it becomes our fate." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40728-this-sentence-is-made-of-lead-and-a-sentence-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 22:53:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40728-this-sentence-is-made-of-lead-and-a-sentence-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["This sentence is made of lead (and a sentence of lead gives a reader an entirely different sensation from one made of magnesium). This sentence is made of yak wool. This sentence is made of sunlight and plums. This sentence is made of ice. This sentence is made from the blood of the poet. This sentence was made in Japan. This sentence glows in the dark. This sentence was born with a caul. This sentence has a crush on Norman Mailer. This sentence is a wino and doesn't care who knows it. Like many italic sentences, this one has Mafia connections. This sentence is a double Cancer with a Pisces rising. This sentence lost its mind searching for the perfect paragraph. This sentence refuses to be diagrammed. This sentence ran off with an adverb clause. This sentence is 100 percent organic: it will not retain a facsimile of freshness like those sentences of Homer, Shakespeare, Goethe et al., which are loaded with preservatives. This sentence leaks. This sentence doesn't look Jewish... This sentence has accepted Jesus Christ as its personal savior. This sentence once spit in a book reviewer's eye. This sentence can do the funky chicken. This sentence has seen too much and forgotten too little. This sentence is called &quot;Speedoo&quot; but its real name is Mr. Earl. This sentence may be pregnant. This sentence suffered a split infinitive - and survived. If this sentence has been a snake you'd have bitten it. This sentence went to jail with Clifford Irving. This sentence went to Woodstock. And this little sentence went wee wee wee all the way home." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3035-you-can-t-measure-the-mutual-affection-of-two-human-beings</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 12:58:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Milan Kundera]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3035-you-can-t-measure-the-mutual-affection-of-two-human-beings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't measure the mutual affection of two human beings by the number of words they exchange." -- Milan Kundera]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1000-anyone-lived-in-a-pretty-how-town-with-up-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:00:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by E. E. Cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1000-anyone-lived-in-a-pretty-how-town-with-up-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["anyone lived in a pretty how town
(with up so floating many bells down)
spring summer autumn winter
he sang his didn't he danced his did

Women and men(both little and small)
cared for anyone not at all
they sowed their isn't they reaped their same
sun moon stars rain

children guessed(but only a few
and down they forgot as up they grew
autumn winter spring summer)
that noone loved him more by more

when by now and tree by leaf
she laughed his joy she cried his grief
bird by snow and stir by still
anyone's any was all to her

someones married their everyones
laughed their cryings and did their dance
(sleep wake hope and then)they
said their nevers they slept their dream

stars rain sun moon
(and only the snow can begin to explain
how children are apt to forget to remember
with up so floating many bells down)

one day anyone died i guess
(and noone stooped to kiss his face)
busy folk buried them side by side
little by little and was by was

all by all and deep by deep
and more by more they dream their sleep
noone and anyone earth by april
wish by spirit and if by yes.

Women and men (both dong and ding)
summer autumn winter spring
reaped their sowing and went their came
sun moon stars rain" -- E. E. Cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:01:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/999-oh-jake-brett-said-we-could-have-had-such-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oh Jake,&quot; Brett said, &quot;We could have had such a damned good time together.&quot;
Ahead was a mounted policeman in khaki directing traffic. He raised his baton. The car slowed suddenly, pressing Brett against me.
Yes,&quot; I said. &quot;Isn't it pretty to think so?" -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2306-ah-me-but-where-are-now-the-songs-i-sang</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Christina Rossetti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2306-ah-me-but-where-are-now-the-songs-i-sang]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ah me, but where are now the songs I sang
When life was sweet because you call’d them sweet?" -- Christina Rossetti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:03:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life. 
&quot; Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget, that until the day God will deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is contained in these two words, 'Wait and Hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7881-trees-are-poems-the-earth-writes-upon-the-sky-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:04:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7881-trees-are-poems-the-earth-writes-upon-the-sky-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trees are poems the earth writes upon the sky, We fell them down and turn them into paper,
That we may record our emptiness." -- Kahlil Gibran]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6052-sometimes-if-you-stand-on-the-bottom-rail-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:04:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6052-sometimes-if-you-stand-on-the-bottom-rail-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, if you stand on the bottom rail of a bridge and lean over to watch the river slipping slowly away beneath you, you will suddenly know everything there is to be known." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7830-take-it-moment-by-moment-and-you-will-find-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:05:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7830-take-it-moment-by-moment-and-you-will-find-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Take it moment by moment, and you will find that we are all, as I’ve said before, bugs in amber." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27777-love-of-music-of-sunsets-and-sea-a-liking-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:07:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27777-love-of-music-of-sunsets-and-sea-a-liking-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love of music, of sunsets and sea; a liking for the same kind of people; political opinions that are not radically divergent; a similar stance as we look at the stars and think of the marvelous strangeness of the universe - these are what build a marriage. And it is never to be taken for granted." -- Madeleine L'Engle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:13:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/988-sometimes-our-light-goes-out-but-is-blown-again-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes our light goes out, but is blown again into instant flame by an encounter with another human being." -- Albert Schweitzer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203210-she-is-like-all-the-rest-of-them-whether-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 15:15:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203210-she-is-like-all-the-rest-of-them-whether-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is like all the rest of them. Whether they are seventeen or fortyseven, when they finally come to surrender completely, it's going to be in words." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203212-at-first-it-had-been-a-torrent-now-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 15:15:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203212-at-first-it-had-been-a-torrent-now-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["At first it had been a torrent; now it was a tide, with a flow and ebb. During its flood she could almost fool them both. It was as if out of her knowledge that it was just a flow that must presently react was born a wilder fury, a fierce denial that could flag itself and him into physical experimentation that transcended imagining, carried them as though by momentum alone, bearing them without volition or plan. It was as if she knew somehow that time was short, that autumn was almost upon her, without knowing yet the exact significance of autumn. It seemed to be instinct alone: instinct physical and instinctive denial of the wasted years. Then the tide would ebb. Then they would be stranded as behind a dying mistral, upon a spent and satiate beach, looking at one another like strangers, with hopeless and reproachful (on his part with weary: on hers with despairing) eyes." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203207-the-whiskey-died-away-in-time-and-was-renewed-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 15:15:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203207-the-whiskey-died-away-in-time-and-was-renewed-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The whiskey died away in time and was renewed and died again, but the street ran on. From that night the thousand streets ran as one street, with imperceptible corners and changes of scene ..." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271547-like-a-fellow-running-from-or-toward-a-gun-ain-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 15:15:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271547-like-a-fellow-running-from-or-toward-a-gun-ain-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like a fellow running from or toward a gun ain't got time to worry whether the word for what he is doing is courage or cowardice." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117882-you-doctor-martin-walk-from-breakfast-to-madness-late-august</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 15:29:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117882-you-doctor-martin-walk-from-breakfast-to-madness-late-august]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You, Doctor Martin, walk
from breakfast to madness. Late August,
I speed through the antiseptic tunnel
where the moving dead still talk
of pushing their bones against the thrust
of cure. And I am queen of this summer hotel
or the laughing bee on a stalk

of death. We stand in broken
lines and wait while they unlock
the doors and count us at the frozen gates
of dinner. The shibboleth is spoken
and we move to gravy in our smock
of smiles. We chew in rows, our plates
scratch and whine like chalk

in school. There are no knives
for cutting your throat. I make
moccasins all morning. At first my hands
kept empty, unraveled for the lives
they used to work. Now I learn to take
them back, each angry finger that demands
I mend what another will break

tomorrow. Of course, I love you;
you lean above the plastic sky,
god of our block, prince of all the foxes.
The breaking crowns are new
that Jack wore. Your third eye
moves among us and lights the separate boxes
where we sleep or cry.

What large children we are
here. All over I grow most tall
in the best ward. Your business is people,
you call at the madhouse, an oracular
eye in our nest. Out in the hall
the intercom pages you. You twist in the pull
of the foxy children who fall

like floods of life in frost.
And we are magic talking to itself,
noisy and alone. I am queen of all my sins
forgotten. Am I still lost?
Once I was beautiful. Now I am myself,
counting this row and that row of moccasins
waiting on the silent shelf." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26883-the-four-agreements-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-2</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 00:21:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26883-the-four-agreements-1-be-impeccable-with-your-word-2]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Four Agreements
1. Be impeccable with your word.
2. Don’t take anything personally.
3. Don’t make assumptions.
4. Always do your best. " -- don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10314-be-impeccable-with-your-word-don-t-take-anything-personally-don-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2011 00:22:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[robin add a quote by Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10314-be-impeccable-with-your-word-don-t-take-anything-personally-don-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be impeccable with your word. Don't take anything personally. Don't make assumptions. Always do your best." -- Don Miguel Ruiz]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
