<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970677-ravic]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970677-ravic" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:54:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3645-we-have-become-by-the-power-of-a-glorious-evolutionary</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3645-we-have-become-by-the-power-of-a-glorious-evolutionary]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We have become, by the power of a glorious evolutionary accident called intelligence, the stewards of life's continuity on earth.  We did not ask for this role, but we cannot abjure it.  We may not be suited to it, but here we are." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83235-i-would-not-choose-to-live-in-any-age-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould (Dinosaur in a Haystack)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83235-i-would-not-choose-to-live-in-any-age-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would not choose to live in any age but my own; advances in medicine alone, and the consequent survival of children with access to these benefits, should preclude any temptation to trade for the past. But we cannot understand history if we saddle the past with pejorative categories based on our bad habits for dividing continua into compartments of increasing worth towards the present. These errors apply to the vast paleontological history of life, as much as to the temporally trivial chronicle of human beings. I cringe every time I read that this failed business, or that defeated team, has become a dinosaur is succumbing to progress. &lt;i&gt;Dinosaur&lt;/i&gt; should be a term of praise, not opprobrium. Dinosaurs reigned for more than 100 million years and died through no fault of their own; &lt;i&gt;Homo sapiens&lt;/i&gt; is nowhere near a million years old, and has limited prospects, entirely self-imposed, for extended geological longevity. " -- Stephen Jay Gould (Dinosaur in a Haystack)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84338-the-most-important-scientific-revolutions-all-include-as-their-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:56:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84338-the-most-important-scientific-revolutions-all-include-as-their-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most important scientific revolutions all include, as their only common feature, the dethronement of human arrogance from one pedestal after another of previous convictions about our centrality in the cosmos" -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434836-we-are-here-because-one-odd-group-of-fishes-had</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:57:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/434836-we-are-here-because-one-odd-group-of-fishes-had]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are here because one odd group of fishes had a peculiar fin anatomy that could transform into legs for terrestrial creatures; because the earth never froze entirely during an ice age; because a small and tenuous species, arising in Africa a quarter of a million years ago, has managed, so far, to survive by hook and by crook. We may yearn for a ‘higher answer’– but none exists" -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295465-science-is-not-a-heartless-pursuit-of-objective-information-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:57:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295465-science-is-not-a-heartless-pursuit-of-objective-information-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Science is not a heartless pursuit of objective information; it is a creative human activity." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333245-when-people-learn-no-tools-of-judgment-and-merely-follow</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/333245-when-people-learn-no-tools-of-judgment-and-merely-follow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When people learn no tools of judgment and merely follow their hopes, the seeds of political manipulation are sown." -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404247-the-dogmatist-within-is-always-worse-than-the-enemy-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 01:59:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/404247-the-dogmatist-within-is-always-worse-than-the-enemy-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The dogmatist within is always worse than the enemy without." -- Stephen Jay Gould ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570585-i-remember-when-we-found-the-first-population-of-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2012 02:08:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ravic add a quote by Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/570585-i-remember-when-we-found-the-first-population-of-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I remember when we found the first population of living Cerion agassizi in central Eleuthera. Our hypothesis of Cerion's general pattern required that two predictions be affirmed (or else we were in trouble): this population must disappear by hybridization with mottled shells toward bank-interior coasts and with ribby snails toward the bank-edge. We hiked west toward the bank-interior and easily found hybrids right on the verge of the airport road. We then moved east toward the bank-edge along a disused road with vegetation rising to five feet in the center between the tire paths. We should have found our hybrids but we did not. The Cerion agassizi simply stopped about two hundred yards north of our first ribby Cerion. Then we realized that a pond lay just to our east and that ribby forms, with their coastal preferences, might not favor the western side of the pond. We forded the pond and found a classic hybrid zone between Cerion agassizi and ribby Cerions. (Ribby Cerion had just managed to round the south end of the pond, but had not moved sufficiently north along the west side to establish contact with C. agassizi populations.) I wanted to shout for joy. Then I thought, &quot;But who can I tell; who cares?&quot; And I answered myself, &quot;I don't have to tell anyone. We have just seen and understood something that no one has ever seen and understood before. What more does a man need?" -- Stephen Jay Gould]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
