<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970714-sharon]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970714-sharon" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 19:54:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31420-helped-are-those-who-are-content-to-be-themselves-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 19:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31420-helped-are-those-who-are-content-to-be-themselves-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["HELPED are those who are content to be themselves; they will never lack mystery in their lives and the joys of self-discovery will be constant.
HELPED are those who love the entire cosmos rather than their own tiny country, city, or farm, for to them will be shown the unbroken web of life and the meaning of infinity.
HELPED are those who live in quietness, knowing neither brand name nor fad; they shall live every day as if in eternity, and each moment shall be as full as it is long.
HELPED are those who love others unsplit off from their faults; to them will be given clarity of vision.
HELPED are those who create anything at all, for they shall relive the thrill of their own conception, and realize an partnership in the creation of the Universe that keeps them responsible and cheerful.
HELPED are those who love the Earth, their mother, and who willingly suffer that she may not die; in their grief over her pain they will weep rivers of blood, and in their joy in her lively response to love, they will converse with the trees.
HELPED are those whose ever act is a prayer for harmony in the Universe, for they are the restorers of balance to our planet. To them will be given the insight that every good act done anywhere in the cosmos welcomes the life of an animal or a child.
HELPED are those who risk themselves for others' sakes; to them will be given increasing opportunities for ever greater risks. Theirs will be a vision of the word in which no one's gift is despised or lost.
HELPED are those who strive to give up their anger; their reward will be that in any confrontation their first thoughts will never be of violence or of war.
HELPED are those whose every act is a prayer for peace; on them depends the future of the world.
HELPED are those who forgive; their reward shall be forgiveness of every evil done to them. It will be in their power, therefore, to envision the new Earth.
HELPED are those who are shown the existence of the Creator's magic in the Universe; they shall experience delight and astonishment without ceasing.
HELPED are those who laugh with a pure heart; theirs will be the company of the jolly righteous.
HELPED are those who love all the colors of all the human beings, as they love all the colors of the animals and plants; none of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who love the lesbian, the gay, and the straight, as they love the sun, the moon, and the stars. None of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who love the broken and the whole; none of their children, nor any of their ancestors, nor any parts of themselves, shall be hidden from them.
HELPED are those who do not join mobs; theirs shall be the understanding that to attack in anger is to murder in confusion.
HELPED are those who find the courage to do at least one small thing each day to help the existence of another--plant, animal, river, or human being. They shall be joined by a multitude of the timid.
HELPED are those who lose their fear of death; theirs is the power to envision the future in a blade of grass.
HELPED are those who love and actively support the diversity of life; they shall be secure in their differences.
HELPED are those who KNOW." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47384-i-won-t-even-mention-the-swift-transitory-reward-of-lemon</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 17:59:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Carol Shields]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47384-i-won-t-even-mention-the-swift-transitory-reward-of-lemon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I won't even mention the swift, transitory reward of lemon spray wax. Danielle Westerman and I have discussed the matter of housework. Not surprisingly, she, always looking a little dérisoire, believes that women have been enslaved by their possessions. Acquiring and then tending--these eat up a woman's creativity, anyone's creativity. But I've been watching the ways she arranges articles on a shelf, and how carefully she sets a table, even with it is just me coming into Toronto to have lunch in her sunroom." -- Carol Shields]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162661-there-s-no-spirit-or-soul-i-will-be-dead-get</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 17:59:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Edwin Shneidman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162661-there-s-no-spirit-or-soul-i-will-be-dead-get]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There’s no spirit or soul. I will be dead. Get that through your thick head. I’ll be dead. And I live, in quotation marks, in my children, in my DNA, in my books, in my reputation. It’s as simple as that. (http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=104267986)" -- Edwin Shneidman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221960-people-should-never-think-that-you-have-to-be-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 19:39:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Miep Gies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221960-people-should-never-think-that-you-have-to-be-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People should never think that you have to be a very special person to help those who need you." -- Miep Gies]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916560-so-what-will-happen-to-your-consciousness-after-you-die</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 19:16:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Boris Pasternak]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/916560-so-what-will-happen-to-your-consciousness-after-you-die]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So what will happen to your consciousness [after you die]? *Your* consciousness, yours, not anyone else's. Well, what are *you*? There's the point. Let's try to find out. What is it about you that you have always known as yourself? What are you conscious of in yourself? Your kidneys? Your liver? Your blood vessels? No. However far back you go in your memory, it is always in some external, active manifestation of yourself that you come across your identity--in the work of your hands, in your family, in other people. And now listen carefully. You in others--this is your soul. This is what you are. This is what your consciousness has breathed and lived on and enjoyed throughout your life--your soul, your immortality, your life in others. And what now? You have always been in others and you will remain in others. And what does it matter to you if later on that is called your memory? This will be you--the you that enters the future and becomes part of it." -- Boris Pasternak]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1131333-her-ideas-were-expressions-of-her-inability-to-accept-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2014 12:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sharon add a quote by Jill Ker Conway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1131333-her-ideas-were-expressions-of-her-inability-to-accept-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Her ideas were expressions of her inability to accept her own personal tragedy and her quest for some certainty on which she could rest a troubled spirit. Her her lack of education was a real handicap, because she had no historical or philosophical perspective from which to analyze her own experience of grief and loss. Because we lived in a cultural wasteland of suburbia, there were no schools or evening classes she might have attended which could offer an intellectually disciplined approach to her quest. Nor were there any churches which might have offered comfort through the beauty of their liturgy." -- Jill Ker Conway]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
