<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970898-kathi]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/970898-kathi" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 09:42:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 09:42:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Derrick Jensen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122326-what-if-the-point-of-life-has-nothing-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if the point of life has nothing to do with the creation of an ever-expanding region of control? What if the point is not to keep at bay all those people, beings, objects and emotions that we so needlessly fear? What if the point instead is to let go of that control? What if the point of life, the primary reason for existence, is to lie naked with your lover in a shady grove of trees? What if the point is to taste each other's sweat and feel the delicate pressure of finger on chest, thigh on thigh, lip on cheek? What if the point is to stop, then, in your slow movements together, and listen to the birdsong, to watch the dragonflies hover, to look at your lover's face, then up at the undersides of leaves moving together in the breeze? What if the point is to invite these others into your movement, to bring trees, wind, grass, dragonflies into your family and in so doing abandon any attempt to control them? What if the point all along has been to get along, to relate, to experience things on their own terms? What if the point is to feel joy when joyous, love when loving, anger when angry, thoughtful when full of thought? What if the point from the beginning has been to simply be?" -- Derrick Jensen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57497-the-power-of-resistance-is-to-set-an-example-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 10:11:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Tim Wise]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/57497-the-power-of-resistance-is-to-set-an-example-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The power of resistance is to set an example: not necessarily to change the person with whom you disagree, but to empower the one who is watching and whose growth is not yet completed, whose path is not at all clear, whose direction is still very much up in the proverbial air." -- Tim Wise]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204034-i-know-you-think-you-understand-what-you-thought</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2013 16:24:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Alan Greenspan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204034-i-know-you-think-you-understand-what-you-thought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" I know you think you understand what you thought I said but I'm not sure you realize that what you heard is not what I meant" -- Alan Greenspan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141658-the-ship-was-sinking---and-sinking-fast-the-captain-told-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2013 14:05:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Daniel Quinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141658-the-ship-was-sinking---and-sinking-fast-the-captain-told-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The ship was sinking---and sinking fast. The captain told the passengers and crew, &quot;We've got to get the lifeboats in the water right away.&quot; 
But the crew said, &quot;First we have to end capitalist oppression of the working class. Then we'll take care of the lifeboats.&quot; 

Then the women said, &quot;First we want equal pay for equal work. The lifeboats can wait.&quot; 

The racial minorities said, &quot;First we need to end racial discrimination. Then seating in the lifeboats will be allotted fairly.&quot; 

The captain said, &quot;These are all important issues, but they won't matter a damn if we don't survive. We've got to lower the lifeboats right away!&quot; 

But the religionists said, &quot;First we need to bring prayer back into the classroom. This is more important than lifeboats.&quot; 

Then the pro-life contingent said, &quot;First we must outlaw abortion. Fetuses have just as much right to be in those lifeboats as anyone else.&quot; 

The right-to-choose contingent said, &quot;First acknowledge our right to abortion, then we'll help with the lifeboats.&quot; 

The socialists said, &quot;First we must redistribute the wealth. Once that's done everyone will work equally hard at lowering the lifeboats.&quot; 

The animal-rights activists said, &quot;First we must end the use of animals in medical experiments. We can't let this be subordinated to lowering the lifeboats.&quot; 

Finally the ship sank, and because none of the lifeboats had been lowered, everyone drowned. 

The last thought of more than one of them was, &quot;I never dreamed that solving humanity's problems would take so long---or that the ship would sink so SUDDENLY." -- Daniel Quinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461373-the-apocalypse-is-not-something-which-is-coming-the-apocalypse</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 15:07:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Terence McKenna]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/461373-the-apocalypse-is-not-something-which-is-coming-the-apocalypse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The apocalypse is not something which is coming. The apocalypse has arrived in major portions of the planet and it’s only because we live within a bubble of incredible privilege and social insulation that we still have the luxury of anticipating the apocalypse." -- Terence McKenna]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195963-we-are-buried-beneath-the-weight-of-information-which-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 08:08:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kathi add a quote by Tom Waits]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/195963-we-are-buried-beneath-the-weight-of-information-which-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are buried beneath the weight of information, which is being confused with knowledge; quantity is being confused with abundance and wealth with happiness.
We are monkeys with money and guns." -- Tom Waits]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
