<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971067-angie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971067-angie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:07:02 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:07:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/865-be-who-you-are-and-say-what-you-feel-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind." -- Bernard M. Baruch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29968-about-all-you-can-do-in-life-is-be-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2010 20:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29968-about-all-you-can-do-in-life-is-be-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["About all you can do in life is be who you are. Some people will love you for you. Most will love you for what you can do for them, and some won't like you at all." -- Rita Mae Brown]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223221-are-you-always-a-smartass-nope-sometimes-i-m-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 11:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223221-are-you-always-a-smartass-nope-sometimes-i-m-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Are you always a smartass?'

Nope.  Sometimes I'm asleep." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66606-sure-we-d-faced-some-things-as-children-that-a-lot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 12:14:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66606-sure-we-d-faced-some-things-as-children-that-a-lot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sure, we'd faced some things as children that a lot of kids don't. Sure, Justin had qualified for his Junior de Sade Badge in his teaching methods for dealing with pain. We still hadn't learned, though, that growing up is all about getting hurt. And then getting over it. You hurt. You recover. You move on. Odds are pretty good you're just going to get hurt again. But each time, you learn something.

Each time, you come out of it a little stronger, and at some point you realize that there are more flavors of pain than coffee. There's the little empty pain of leaving something behind - gradutaing, taking the next step forward, walking out of something familiar and safe into the unknown. There's the big, whirling pain of life upending all of your plans and expecations. There's the sharp little pains of failure, and the more obscure aches of successes that didn't give you what you thought they would. There are the vicious, stabbing pains of hopes being torn up. The sweet little pains of finding others, giving them your love, and taking joy in their life they grow and learn. There's the steady pain of empathy that you shrug off so you can stand beside a wounded friend and help them bear their burdens. 

And if you're very, very lucky, there are a very few blazing hot little pains you feel when you realized that you are standing in a moment of utter perfection, an instant of triumph, or happiness, or mirth which at the same time cannot possibly last - and yet will remain with you for life.

Everyone is down on pain, because they forget something important about it: Pain is for the living. Only the dead don't feel it.

Pain is a part of life. Sometimes it's a big part, and sometimes it isn't, but either way, it's a part of the big puzzle, the deep music, the great game. Pain does two things: It teaches you, tells you that you're alive. Then it passes away and leaves you changed. It leaves you wiser, sometimes. Sometimes it leaves you stronger. Either way, pain leaves its mark, and everything important that will ever happen to you in life is going to involve it in one degree or another." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83265-the-building-was-on-fire-and-it-wasn-t-my-fault</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 12:14:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83265-the-building-was-on-fire-and-it-wasn-t-my-fault]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The building was on fire, and it wasn’t my fault." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209972-we-are-not-going-to-die-butters-stared-up-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 12:14:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/209972-we-are-not-going-to-die-butters-stared-up-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are not going to die.&quot; 

Butters stared up at me, pale, his eyes terrified. &quot;We're not?&quot; 

No. And do you know why?&quot; He shook his head. &quot;Because Thomas is too pretty to die. And because I'm too stubborn to die.&quot; I hauled on the shirt even harder. &quot;And most of all because tomorrow is Oktoberfest, Butters, and polka will never die." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185444-son-everyone-dies-alone-that-s-what-it-is-it-s-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 12:15:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Jim Butcher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/185444-son-everyone-dies-alone-that-s-what-it-is-it-s-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Son.  Everyone dies alone.  That's what it is.  It's a door.  It's one person wide.  When you go through it, you do it alone.  But it doesn't mean you've got to be alone before you go through the door.  And believe me, you aren't alone on the other side." -- Jim Butcher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275150-jesus-man-why-do-people-want-to-be-paris-hilton</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2012 07:33:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Mark Millar]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/275150-jesus-man-why-do-people-want-to-be-paris-hilton]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jesus, man. Why do people want to be Paris Hilton and nobody wants to be Spider-Man?" -- Mark Millar]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284486-my-mother-once-told-me-that-no-woman-is-naked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2012 12:56:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Mira Grant]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/284486-my-mother-once-told-me-that-no-woman-is-naked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My mother once told me that no woman is naked when she comes equipped with a bad mood and a steady glare." -- Mira Grant]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45233-the-first-ten-lies-they-tell-you-in-high-school</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 05:12:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Angie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45233-the-first-ten-lies-they-tell-you-in-high-school]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["THE FIRST TEN LIES THEY TELL YOU IN HIGH SCHOOL 

1. We are here to help you. 
2. You will have time to get to your class before the bell rings. 
3. The dress code will be enforced. 
4. No smoking is allowed on school grounds. 
5. Our football team will win the championship this year. 
6. We expect more of you here. 
7. Guidance counselors are always available to listen. 
8. Your schedule was created with you in mind. 
9. Your locker combination is private. 
10. These will be the years you look back on fondly. 

TEN MORE LIES THEY TELL YOU IN HIGH SCHOOL 

1. You will use algebra in your adult lives. 
2. Driving to school is a privilege that can be taken away. 
3. Students must stay on campus during lunch. 
4. The new text books will arrive any day now. 
5. Colleges care more about you than your SAT scores. 
6. We are enforcing the dress code. 
7. We will figure out how to turn off the heat soon. 
8. Our bus drivers are highly trained professionals. 
9. There is nothing wrong with summer school. 
10. We want to hear what you have to say." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
