<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971634-maulida-raviola]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971634-maulida-raviola" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 02:16:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33188-generally-by-the-time-you-are-real-most-of-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 02:16:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33188-generally-by-the-time-you-are-real-most-of-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54183-kalian-boleh-maju-dalam-pelajaran-mungkin-mencapai-deretan-gelar-kesarjanaan</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 03:41:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Pramoedya Ananta Toer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54183-kalian-boleh-maju-dalam-pelajaran-mungkin-mencapai-deretan-gelar-kesarjanaan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kalian boleh maju dalam pelajaran, mungkin mencapai deretan gelar kesarjanaan apa saja, tapi tanpa mencintai sastra, kalian tinggal hanya hewan yang pandai." -- Pramoedya Ananta Toer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52828-maybe-the-truth-is-there-s-a-little-bit-of-loser</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2009 07:14:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52828-maybe-the-truth-is-there-s-a-little-bit-of-loser]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe the truth is, there's a little bit of loser in all of us. Being happy isn't having everything in your life be perfect. Maybe it's about stringing together all the little things." -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10286-if-i-have-seen-further-it-is-by-standing-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 03:50:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Isaac Newton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10286-if-i-have-seen-further-it-is-by-standing-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If I have seen further it is by standing on the shoulders of Giants." -- Isaac Newton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11741-the-weak-can-never-forgive-forgiveness-is-the-attribute-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 03:51:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11741-the-weak-can-never-forgive-forgiveness-is-the-attribute-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2008 03:51:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/739-when-i-despair-i-remember-that-all-through-history-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I despair, I remember that all through history the way of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants and murderers, and for a time, they can seem invincible, but in the end, they always fall. Think of it--always." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105020-when-you-remembered-to-forget-you-were-remembering-it-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 09:38:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Ann Brashares]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/105020-when-you-remembered-to-forget-you-were-remembering-it-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you remembered to forget, you were remembering. It was when you forgot to forget that you forgot. " -- Ann Brashares]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116914-dalam-diriku-mengalir-sungai-panjang-darah-namanya-dalam-diriku-menggenang</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 07:27:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Sapardi Djoko Damono]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116914-dalam-diriku-mengalir-sungai-panjang-darah-namanya-dalam-diriku-menggenang]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["dalam diriku mengalir sungai panjang,
darah namanya;
dalam diriku menggenang telaga darah,
sukma namanya;
dalam diriku meriak gelombang sukma,
hidup namanya;
dan karena hidup itu indah,
aku menangis sepuas-puasnya" -- Sapardi Djoko Damono]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138936-kemampuan-membaca-itu-sebuah-rahmat-kegemaran-membaca-sebuah-kebahagiaan</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 07:33:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Goenawan Mohamad]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138936-kemampuan-membaca-itu-sebuah-rahmat-kegemaran-membaca-sebuah-kebahagiaan]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Kemampuan membaca itu sebuah rahmat. Kegemaran membaca; sebuah kebahagiaan." -- Goenawan Mohamad]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23447-all-the-books-we-own-both-read-and-unread-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 03:58:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23447-all-the-books-we-own-both-read-and-unread-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All the books we own, both read and unread, are the fullest expression of self we have at our disposal. ... But with each passing year, and with each whimsical purchase, our libraries become more and more able to articulate who we are, whether we read the books or not." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112273-even-bad-times-have-good-things-in-them-to-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 04:01:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/112273-even-bad-times-have-good-things-in-them-to-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Even bad times have good things in them to make you feel alive." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 03:29:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19884-be-yourself-everyone-else-is-already-taken]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66735-i-never-tell-anyone-exactly-how-clever-i-am-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2011 01:49:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Eoin Colfer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66735-i-never-tell-anyone-exactly-how-clever-i-am-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never tell anyone exactly how clever I am. They would be too scared." -- Eoin Colfer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72283-follow-your-inner-moonlight-don-t-hide-the-madness</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 09:58:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72283-follow-your-inner-moonlight-don-t-hide-the-madness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Follow your inner moonlight; don't hide the madness." -- Allen Ginsberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317382-memory-is-the-space-in-which-a-thing-happens-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 00:27:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Paul Auster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/317382-memory-is-the-space-in-which-a-thing-happens-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory is the space in which a thing happens for a second time." -- Paul Auster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175499-you-have-to-believe-it-and-you-hate-it-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 05:37:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Katherine Paterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175499-you-have-to-believe-it-and-you-hate-it-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You have to believe it and you hate it. I don't have to and I think it's beautiful." -- Katherine Paterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376426-i-d-volunteer-to-go-to-prison-as-long-as-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 03:23:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Mohammad Hatta]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/376426-i-d-volunteer-to-go-to-prison-as-long-as-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’d volunteer to go to prison, as long as there are books. Because with books I am free." -- Mohammad Hatta]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 20:07:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437516-you-should-date-a-girl-who-reads-date-a-girl]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You should date a girl who reads.
Date a girl who reads. Date a girl who spends her money on books instead of clothes, who has problems with closet space because she has too many books. Date a girl who has a list of books she wants to read, who has had a library card since she was twelve.

Find a girl who reads. You’ll know that she does because she will always have an unread book in her bag. She’s the one lovingly looking over the shelves in the bookstore, the one who quietly cries out when she has found the book she wants. You see that weird chick sniffing the pages of an old book in a secondhand book shop? That’s the reader. They can never resist smelling the pages, especially when they are yellow and worn.

She’s the girl reading while waiting in that coffee shop down the street. If you take a peek at her mug, the non-dairy creamer is floating on top because she’s kind of engrossed already. Lost in a world of the author’s making. Sit down. She might give you a glare, as most girls who read do not like to be interrupted. Ask her if she likes the book.

Buy her another cup of coffee.

Let her know what you really think of Murakami. See if she got through the first chapter of Fellowship. Understand that if she says she understood James Joyce’s Ulysses she’s just saying that to sound intelligent.  Ask her if she loves Alice or she would like to be Alice.

It’s easy to date a girl who reads. Give her books for her birthday, for Christmas, for anniversaries. Give her the gift of words, in poetry and in song. Give her Neruda, Pound, Sexton, Cummings. Let her know that you understand that words are love. Understand that she knows the difference between books and reality but by god, she’s going to try to make her life a little like her favorite book. It will never be your fault if she does.

She has to give it a shot somehow.

Lie to her. If she understands syntax, she will understand your need to lie. Behind words are other things: motivation, value, nuance, dialogue. It will not be the end of the world.

Fail her. Because a girl who reads knows that failure always leads up to the climax. Because girls who read understand that all things must come to end, but that you can always write a sequel. That you can begin again and again and still be the hero. That life is meant to have a villain or two.

Why be frightened of everything that you are not? Girls who read understand that people, like characters, develop. Except in the Twilight series.

If you find a girl who reads, keep her close. When you find her up at 2 AM clutching a book to her chest and weeping, make her a cup of tea and hold her. You may lose her for a couple of hours but she will always come back to you. She’ll talk as if the characters in the book are real, because for a while, they always are.

You will propose on a hot air balloon. Or during a rock concert. Or very casually next time she’s sick. Over Skype.

You will smile so hard you will wonder why your heart hasn’t burst and bled out all over your chest yet. You will write the story of your lives, have kids with strange names and even stranger tastes. She will introduce your children to the Cat in the Hat and Aslan, maybe in the same day. You will walk the winters of your old age together and she will recite Keats under her breath while you shake the snow off your boots.

Date a girl who reads because you deserve it. You deserve a girl who can give you the most colorful life imaginable. If you can only give her monotony, and stale hours and half-baked proposals, then you’re better off alone. If you want the world and the worlds beyond it, date a girl who reads.

Or better yet, date a girl who writes." -- Rosemarie Urquico]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193963-o-ah-the-awareness-of-emptiness-brings-forth-a-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 02:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Maulida add a quote by Gary Snyder]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1193963-o-ah-the-awareness-of-emptiness-brings-forth-a-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O, ah! The awareness of emptiness brings forth a heart of compassion!" -- Gary Snyder]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
