<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971892-linda-quarne]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971892-linda-quarne" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:36:19 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27503-i-read-because-one-life-is-not-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:36:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Richard Peck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27503-i-read-because-one-life-is-not-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read.. because one life is not enough" -- Richard Peck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416-make-it-a-rule-never-to-give-a-child-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:55:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/416-make-it-a-rule-never-to-give-a-child-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Make it a rule never to give a child a book you would not read yourself." -- George Bernard Shaw]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:57:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Italo Calvino]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9766-in-the-shop-window-you-have-promptly-identified-the-cover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the shop window you have promptly identified the cover with the title you were looking for. Following this visual trail, you have forced your way through the shop past the thick barricade of Books You Haven't Read, which are frowning at you from the tables and shelves, trying to cow you...And thus you pass the outer girdle of ramparts, but then you are attacked by the infantry of Books That If You Had More Than One Life You Would Certainly Also Read But Unfortunately Your Days Are Numbered. With a rapid maneuver you bypass them and move into the phalanxes of the Books You Mean To Read But There Are Others You Must Read First, the Books Too Expensive Now And You'll Wait Till They're Remaindered, the Books ditto When They Come Out in Paperback, Books You Can Borrow From Somebody, Books That Everybody's Read So It's As If You Had Read Them, Too. " -- Italo Calvino]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14454-still-round-the-corner-there-may-wait-a-new-road</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:58:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14454-still-round-the-corner-there-may-wait-a-new-road]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Still round the corner there may wait
 A new road or a secret gate
And though I oft have passed them by
 A day will come at last when I
Shall take the hidden paths that run
 West of the Moon, East of the Sun." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17491-only-bad-books-have-good-endings-if-a-book-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:58:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by Pseudonymous Bosch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17491-only-bad-books-have-good-endings-if-a-book-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only bad books have good endings.
If a book is any good, it's ending is always bad - because you don't want the book to end." -- Pseudonymous Bosch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 14:59:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Linda add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a product [...of] endless books. My father bought all the books he read and never got rid of any of them. There were books in the study, books in the drawing room, books in the cloakroom, books (two deep) in the great bookcase on the landing, books in a bedroom, books piled as high as my shoulder in the cistern attic, books of all kinds reflecting every transient stage of my parents' interest, books readable and unreadable, books suitable for a child and books most emphatically not. Nothing was forbidden me. In the seemingly endless rainy afternoons I took volume after volume from the shelves. I had always the same certainty of finding a book that was new to me as a man who walks into a field has of finding a new blade of grass." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
