<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971869-steve]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/971869-steve" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:36:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:36:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/192819-no-matter-how-close-we-are-to-another-person-few]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how close we are to another person, few human relationships are as free from strife, disagreement, and frustration as is the relationship you have with a good dog. Few human beings give of themselves to another as a dog gives of itself. I also suspect that we cherish dogs because their unblemished souls make us wish - consciously or unconsciously - that we were as innocent as they are, and make us yearn for a place where innocence is universal and where the meanness, the betrayals, and the cruelties of this world are unknown." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64541-the-purpose-of-life-is-not-to-be-happy-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2008 11:18:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64541-the-purpose-of-life-is-not-to-be-happy-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The purpose of life is not to be happy. It is to be useful, to be honorable, to be compassionate, to have it make some difference that you have lived and lived well." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125195-whether-they-realized-it-or-not-they-were-doubting-possibility</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 11:02:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Shreve Stockton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/125195-whether-they-realized-it-or-not-they-were-doubting-possibility]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether they realized it or not, they were doubting possibility, and the unknown. They believed I would fail. And when we only believe what has been said before, what has been done before, we give our own power away. Possibility evaporates; potential melts and seeps away deep into the earth below us. We cut ourselves short by thinking this way. I have always felt that it is from what we believe that our lives are created, not the other way around." -- Shreve Stockton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65885-that-which-we-manifest-is-before-us-we-are-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 21:19:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65885-that-which-we-manifest-is-before-us-we-are-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That which we manifest is before us; we are the creators of our own destiny. Be it through intention or ignorance, our successes and our failures have been brought on by none other than ourselves." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2009 21:25:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11035-no-one-can-make-you-feel-inferior-without-your-consent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one can make you feel inferior without your consent." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140450-he-died-that-day-because-his-body-had-served-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 11:26:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140450-he-died-that-day-because-his-body-had-served-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He died that day because his body had served its purpose. His soul had done what it came to do, learned what it came to learn, and then was free to leave." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140451-there-is-no-dishonor-in-losing-the-race-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 11:27:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Garth Stein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/140451-there-is-no-dishonor-in-losing-the-race-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no dishonor in losing the race. There is only dishonor in not racing because you are afraid to lose." -- Garth Stein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196-when-you-have-eliminated-all-which-is-impossible-then-whatever</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 11:38:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1196-when-you-have-eliminated-all-which-is-impossible-then-whatever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you have eliminated all which is impossible, then whatever remains, however improbable, must be the truth." -- Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118639-because-god-is-never-cruel-there-is-a-reason-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:36:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Dean Koontz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118639-because-god-is-never-cruel-there-is-a-reason-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because God is never cruel, there is a reason for all things. We must know the pain of loss; because if we never knew it, we would have no compassion for others, and we would become monsters of self-regard, creatures of unalloyed self-interest. The terrible pain of loss teaches humility to our prideful kind, has the power to soften uncaring hearts, to make a better person of a good one." -- Dean Koontz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80489-a-dog-has-no-use-for-fancy-cars-or-big</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:44:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by John Grogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80489-a-dog-has-no-use-for-fancy-cars-or-big]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A dog has no use for fancy cars or big homes or designer clothes. Status symbol means nothing to him. A waterlogged stick will do just fine. A dog judges others not by their color or creed or class but by who they are inside. A dog doesn't care if you are rich or poor, educated or illiterate, clever or dull. Give him your heart and he will give you his. It was really quite simple, and yet we humans, so much wiser and more sophisticated, have always had trouble figuring out what really counts and what does not. As I wrote that farewell column to Marley, I realized it was all right there in front of us, if only we opened our eyes. Sometimes it took a dog with bad breath, worse manners, and pure intentions to help us see." -- John Grogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15054-the-average-dog-is-a-nicer-person-than-the-average</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Andy Rooney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15054-the-average-dog-is-a-nicer-person-than-the-average]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The average dog is a nicer person than the average person." -- Andy Rooney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95055-a-person-can-learn-a-lot-from-a-dog-even</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by John Grogan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95055-a-person-can-learn-a-lot-from-a-dog-even]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A person can learn a lot from a dog, even a loopy one like ours. Marley taught me about living each day with unbridled exuberance and joy, about seizing the moment and following your heart. He taught me to appreciate the simple things-a walk in the woods, a fresh snowfall, a nap in a shaft of winter sunlight. And as he grew old and achy, he taught me about optimism in the face of adversity. Mostly, he taught me about friendship and selflessness and, above all else, unwavering loyalty." -- John Grogan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691-heaven-goes-by-favor-if-it-went-by-merit-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:51:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/691-heaven-goes-by-favor-if-it-went-by-merit-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Heaven goes by favor. If it went by merit, you would stay out and your dog would go in." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18943-if-there-are-no-dogs-in-heaven-then-when-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2009 21:53:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Will Rogers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18943-if-there-are-no-dogs-in-heaven-then-when-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there are no dogs in Heaven, then when I die I want to go where they went." -- Will Rogers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224307-percy-lesser-beings-do-many-horrible-things-in-the-name</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 21:25:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Rick Riordan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224307-percy-lesser-beings-do-many-horrible-things-in-the-name]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Percy, lesser beings do many horrible things in the name of the gods. That does not mean we gods approve. The way our sons and daughters act in our names... well, it usually says more about THEM than it does about us." -- Rick Riordan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229729-mom-pop-stores-are-not-about-something-small-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 20:26:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Spector]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229729-mom-pop-stores-are-not-about-something-small-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mom &amp; pop stores are not about something small; they are about something big. Ninety percent of all U.S. businesses are family owned or controlled. They are important not only for the food, drink, clothing, and tools they sell us, but also for providing us with intellectual stimulation, social interaction, and connection to our communities. We must have mom &amp; pop stores because we are social animals. We crave to be part of the marketplace. " -- Robert Spector]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296104-and-yet-it-had-come-to-this-a-cult-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Terry Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296104-and-yet-it-had-come-to-this-a-cult-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And yet it had come to this: a cult that followed a dogmatic hard line of exclusion and repression, believed its teachings alone were the way that others must follow, and claimed special knowledge of something that had happened more than five centuries ago. It did nothing to soften its rigid stance, nothing to heal wounds that it had helped to create by deliberately shunning people of other Races, and nothing to explore the possibility of other beliefs. It held its ground even in the face of hard evidence that perhaps it had misjudged and refused to consider that it was courting a danger that might destroy everyone. p96" -- Terry Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296107-we-are-doomed-to-repeat-the-mistakes-of-the-past</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2010 16:38:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Terry Brooks]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/296107-we-are-doomed-to-repeat-the-mistakes-of-the-past]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are doomed to repeat the mistakes of the past, and no amount of education gleaned from our propensity for self-destruction and misguided thinking ever teaches us anything. Not anything that we remember for more than a generation or two.

I think maybe we learn a few things each time that we don't forget. A few things that stick with us. It's just hard to pass those things on to those who come after us because if they didn't live through it, they don't view it the same way we do. If you don't experience something firsthand, it's a lot harder to accept.  Terry Brooks, Bearers of the Black Staff, p 89" -- Terry Brooks]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372590-every-year-thousands-of-dogs-are-abandoned-to-shelters-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 21:56:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Martin Kihn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/372590-every-year-thousands-of-dogs-are-abandoned-to-shelters-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every year thousands of dogs are abandoned to shelters because of behavior problems. And these are things that can be corrected with just basic training. Dogs are being killed because of lack of training, and that's what the Canine Good Citizen program is all about. (Mary Burch, AKC)" -- Martin Kihn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424196-the-great-game-of-life-is-not-about-money-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 09:25:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Jack Bogle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/424196-the-great-game-of-life-is-not-about-money-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The great game of life is not about money; it is about doing your best to join the battle to build anew our communities, our nation, and our world." -- Jack Bogle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542636-i-read-parker-s-spenser-series-in-college-when-it-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 21:28:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Harlan Coben]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/542636-i-read-parker-s-spenser-series-in-college-when-it-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I read Parker's Spenser series in college. When it comes to detective novels, 90 percent of us admit he's an influence, and the rest of us lie about it." -- Harlan Coben]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750834-talk-to-her-goddamnit-she-ain-t-a-stick-of-furniture</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 17:33:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Crais]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750834-talk-to-her-goddamnit-she-ain-t-a-stick-of-furniture]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Talk to her, goddamnit. She ain't a stick of furniture. She is one of God's creatures, and she will hear you. I see these goddamned people walkin' dogs, yakking on their phones, makes me wanna kick their sissy asses. What they got a dog for, they want to talk on their phones? That dog there will understand you, Officer James. She will understand what's in your heart. Am I just shouting at the grass and dog shit out here, or are you reading what I am telling you?" -- Robert Crais]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750837-the-best-dog-training-was-based-on-the-reward-system</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 17:37:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Crais]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750837-the-best-dog-training-was-based-on-the-reward-system]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best dog training was based on the reward system. You did not punish a dog for doing wrong, you rewarded the dog for doing right. The dog did something you wanted, you reinforced the behavior with a reward - pet'm, tell'm they're a good dog, let'm play with a toy. The standard reward for a K-9 working dog was a hard plastic ball with a hole drilled through it where Leland liked to smear a little peanut butter." -- Robert Crais]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750839-scott-walked-away-and-did-not-look-back-they-knew</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2013 17:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert Crais]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/750839-scott-walked-away-and-did-not-look-back-they-knew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scott walked away and did not look back. They knew Maggie would try to follow him, and she did. In her world, they were a pack, and the pack stayed together.

Maggie whined and barked, and he heard her claws scrape the tarmac like files. Budress had cautioned him not to look back or wave bye-bye or any of the silly things people did. Dogs weren't people. Eye contact would make her struggle harder to reach him. A dog could see your heart in your eyes, Budress told him, and dogs were drawn to our hearts." -- Robert Crais]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741367-both-our-opinions-are-rooted-in-our-experience-i-said</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 22:55:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert B. Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741367-both-our-opinions-are-rooted-in-our-experience-i-said]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Both our opinions are rooted in our experience,&quot; I said. &quot;Both of them are true, it's just that we've had different experiences." -- Robert B. Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974672-i-try-to-be-honorable-i-know-that-s-embarrassing-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 23:04:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert B. Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974672-i-try-to-be-honorable-i-know-that-s-embarrassing-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I try to be honorable. I know that's embarrassing to hear. It's embarrassing to say. But I believe most of the nonsense that Thoreau was preaching. And I have spent a long time working on getting myself to where I could do it. Where I could live life largely on my own terms." -- Robert B. Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974681-the-urban-renewers-had-struck-again-they-d-evicted-me-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 23:22:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Steve add a quote by Robert B. Parker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/974681-the-urban-renewers-had-struck-again-they-d-evicted-me-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The urban renewers had struck again. They'd evicted me, a fortune-teller, and a bookie from the corner of Mass. Ave. and Boylston, moved in with sandblasters and bleached oak and plant hangers, and last I looked appeared to be turning the place into a Marin County whorehouse." -- Robert B. Parker]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
