<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/972065-jacie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/972065-jacie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:06:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:06:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacie add a quote by Janet Fitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10743-loneliness-is-the-human-condition-cultivate-it-the-way-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[" Loneliness is the human condition. Cultivate it. The way it tunnels into you allows your soul room to grow. Never expect to outgrow loneliness. Never hope to find people who will understand you, someone to fill that space. An intelligent, sensitive person is the exception, the very great exception. If you expect to find people who will understand you, you will grow murderous with disappointment. The best you'll ever do is to understand yourself, know what it is that you want, and not let the cattle stand in your way." -- Janet Fitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50997-the-most-terrible-poverty-is-loneliness-and-the-feeling-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:09:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacie add a quote by Mother Teresa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50997-the-most-terrible-poverty-is-loneliness-and-the-feeling-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most terrible poverty is loneliness, and the feeling of being unloved." -- Mother Teresa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430186-occasionally-very-occasionally-say-at-four-o-clock-in-the-afternoon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 22:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacie add a quote by David Nicholls]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430186-occasionally-very-occasionally-say-at-four-o-clock-in-the-afternoon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Occasionally, very occasionally, say at four o’clock in the afternoon on a wet Sunday, she feels panic-stricken and almost breathless with loneliness. Once or twice she has been known to pick up the phone to check that it isn’t broken. Sometimes she thinks how nice it would be to be woken by a call in the night: ‘get in a taxi now’ or ‘I need to see you, we need to talk’. But at the best of times she feels like a character in a Muriel Spark novel – independent, bookish, sharp-minded, secretly romantic." -- David Nicholls]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2014 19:16:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacie add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
