<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/97224-kristin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/97224-kristin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:43:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473341-it-was-a-fine-night-a-warm-night-a-wine-drinking</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:43:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473341-it-was-a-fine-night-a-warm-night-a-wine-drinking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was a fine night, a warm night, a wine-drinking night, a moony night, and a night to hug your girl and talk and spit and be heavengoing. This we did." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2011 11:51:40 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307194-sometimes-i-would-open-my-eyes-when-we-were-kissing</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:16:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/307194-sometimes-i-would-open-my-eyes-when-we-were-kissing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I would open my eyes when we were kissing, I would watch him and I could see it. I could actually see LOVE - not words, not an emotion, not an abstract concept or a subjective state of mind, but a living, breathing thing." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314438-eliza-has-the-sky-in-her-eyes-and-i-ve-always</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 10:16:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/314438-eliza-has-the-sky-in-her-eyes-and-i-ve-always]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eliza has the sky in her eyes and I’ve always wanted to touch
the goddamn sky." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744093-trying-to-describe-how-i-felt-watching-her-dance-around</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 19:44:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/744093-trying-to-describe-how-i-felt-watching-her-dance-around]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Trying to describe how I felt watching her dance around and sing would be like trying to build a skyscraper with my bare bands. It made me want to marry her. Made me want to buy her a magic airplane and fly her away to a place where nothing bad could ever happen. Made me want to pour rubber cement all over my chest and then lay down on top of her so that we'd be stuck together, and so it would hurt like ell if we eer tried to tear ourselves apart." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91480-i-m-one-of-those-people-who-other-people-like-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 12:34:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jill A. Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/91480-i-m-one-of-those-people-who-other-people-like-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm one of those people who other people like but never remember. I think most of the world is probably like me. Until recently nothing about me was outstanding, and then my mother got cancer. It's a disease people like to talk about, so I'm more popular now. And when I flip through magazines, I read the breast cancer articles first, even before the numerology column." -- Jill A. Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76138-ruth-smiles-which-rearranges-the-lines-on-her-face-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2012 12:24:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76138-ruth-smiles-which-rearranges-the-lines-on-her-face-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ruth smiles, which rearranges the lines on her face. She inverts her parentheses and transforms commas into apostrophes. The pattern is that of a woman who has no regrets." -- Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 07:18:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/485442-as-he-read-i-fell-in-love-the-way-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As he read, I fell in love the way you fall asleep: slowly, and then all at once." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741485-i-had-the-feeling-i-d-just-found-something-i-didn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 09:28:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/741485-i-had-the-feeling-i-d-just-found-something-i-didn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had the feeling I'd just found something I didn't even know I'd lost. We hovered above the moment like two rain clouds, until I said: &quot;Don't swear off all fruit just because you ate one bad apple." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65430-adulthood-isn-t-black-and-white---it-s-a-thousand-shades</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:41:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Elizabeth Noble]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65430-adulthood-isn-t-black-and-white---it-s-a-thousand-shades]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Adulthood isn't black and white - it's a thousand shades of grey. Or taupe. It's not who you are, it's where you are." -- Elizabeth Noble]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16621-we-re-all-searching-for-something-to-fill-up-what-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:37:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16621-we-re-all-searching-for-something-to-fill-up-what-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all searching for something to fill up what I like to call that big, God-shaped hole in our souls. Some people use alcohol, or sex, or their children, or food, or money, or music, or heroin. A lot of people even use the concept of God itself. I could go on and on. I used to know a girl who used shoes. She had over two-hundred pairs. But it’s all the same thing, really. People, for some stupid reason, think they can escape their sorrows." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593033-cussing-doesn-t-come-from-a-lack-of-vocabulary-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 05:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Anis Mojgani]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/593033-cussing-doesn-t-come-from-a-lack-of-vocabulary-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cussing doesn’t come from a lack of vocabulary – I know all the other words. None of them speak the same language that my fucking heart does." -- Anis Mojgani]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16616-i-wanted-a-boyfriend-who-was-a-christian-but-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:36:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Sarah Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16616-i-wanted-a-boyfriend-who-was-a-christian-but-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wanted a boyfriend who was a Christian but who wasn't uptight about it, who was good-looking and intelligent and had an interesting job and a sense of humor, who said &quot;fuck&quot; when the situation warranted it, who had attempted to but been unable to finish St. Augustine's City of God, who could argue politics with my mother and talk business with my father, who liked Indian food and had nice friends and knew how to dress and would like someday to live abroad." -- Sarah Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521521-that-was-what-i-feared-most-that-he-just-wasn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 19:03:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Laura Dave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/521521-that-was-what-i-feared-most-that-he-just-wasn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was what I feared most: that he just wasn’t excited about us anymore—that something between us had altered irreversibly. And afterward, I started seeing the evidence everywhere: in the way he didn’t sleep facing me anymore, or the way he’d stopped asking me the questions he used to need to know the answers to, the way he stopped needing to tell me things in order for them to count." -- Laura Dave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15883-when-i-was-twelve-a-fortune-teller-told-me-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:24:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15883-when-i-was-twelve-a-fortune-teller-told-me-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I was twelve, a fortune teller told me that my one true love would die young and leave me all alone.. Everyone said she was a fraud, that she was just making it up.. I’d really like to know why the hell a person would make up a thing like that." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15884-on-the-way-back-to-the-office--i-get-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:25:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jane Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15884-on-the-way-back-to-the-office--i-get-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the way back to the office- I get a cab, on expenses, naturally- I decide that I could quite like Ed. Maybe I could even fancy him, and maybe the fact that I'm not thinking about him that much when I'm not with him is a good thing, maybe it means this is a proper relationship, not just lust, or the equivalent to a teenage crush. Because quite frankly I'm sick of falling madly in love and spending twenty-four hours a day thinking about them and crying with misery when they don't phone. I'm sick of being the kind of girl who, when they say jump, says how high. I'm sick of always, always being the one to fall in love and get hurt. And maybe this is how it should be, getting on with my life and not putting all my energies into a relationship." -- Jane Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15882-he-isn-t-like-most-guys-you-know-i-know-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15882-he-isn-t-like-most-guys-you-know-i-know-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He isn’t like most guys, you know?'

I know.'

No, but do you really know? I mean here’s the deal, what do most guys want from a woman? I’ll tell you what we want. We want a warm body to sleep next to, preferably one with a nice pair of tits, maybe someone who’ll cook for us and fuck us on a regular basis. Pretty simple, huh? Now, what we don’t want is someone who’s going to come in and disrupt our lives and steal our souls. That’s what we fear most. We call it our freedom, but it’s our souls we’re talking about. You following me?'

I nodded.

Okay, good. Now forget it. Forget all that,' Pete said. 'Because Jacob’s not like that. He’s never been like that. He’s a damn fool and he wants the exact opposite of all that. He wants someone to obsess over, someone to possess his soul, and those are his corny words, by the way, not mine. It’s what he lives for. It’s what he thinks life’s all about. Do you get what I’m saying?'

I nodded again." -- Tiffanie DeBartolo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15886-yes-she-thought-laying-down-her-brush-in-extreme-fatigues</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:35:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15886-yes-she-thought-laying-down-her-brush-in-extreme-fatigues]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yes, she thought, laying down her brush in extreme fatigues, I have had my vision." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76571-a-year-later-we-were-in-a-coffee-shop-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2008 15:22:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76571-a-year-later-we-were-in-a-coffee-shop-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A year later we were in a coffee shop, the kind taking a last stand against Starbucks with its thrift-store chairs, vegan cookies, and over-promising teas with names like Serenity and Inner Peace. I was curled up with a stack of causes, trying to get in a few extra hours of work over the weekend, and Andrew sat with one hand gripping his mug, his nose in The New York Times; the two of us a parody of the yuppie couple of the new millennium. We sat silently that way, though there wasn't silence at all. On top of the typical coffee-shop sounds - the whir of an expresso machine, the click of the cash register, the bell above the door - Andrew was making his noises, an occasional snort at something he read in the paper, the jangle of his keys in his pocket, a sniffle since he was getting over a cold, a clearing of his throat. And as we sat there, all I could do was listen to those Andrew-specific noises, the rhythm of his breath, the in-out in-out, its low whistle. Snort. Jangle. Sniffle. Clear.

Hypnotized. I wanted to buy his soundtrack. 

This must be what love is, I thought. Not wanting his noises to ever stop." -- Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77433-i-miss-the-way-he-used-to-kiss-my-shoulder</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2008 11:03:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77433-i-miss-the-way-he-used-to-kiss-my-shoulder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I miss the way he used to kiss my shoulder whenever it was bare and he was nearby. I miss how he cleared his throat before he took a sip of water and scratched his left arm with his right hand when he was nervous. I miss how he tucked my hair behind my ear when it came loose and took my temperature when I was sick or when he was bored. I miss his glasses on my nightstand. I miss watching him take Sunday afternoon naps on my couch, with the newspaper resting on his stomach like a blanket. How his hands stayed clasped, fingers intertwined, while he slept. I miss the cadence of his speech and the stupidity of his puns. I miss playing doctor when we made love, and even when we didn't. I miss his smell, like fresh laundry and honey (because of his shampoo) at his place. Fresh laundry and coconut (because of my shampoo) at mine. I miss that he used to force me to listen to French rap and would sing along in a horrible accent. I miss that he always said &quot;I love you&quot; when he hung up the phone with his sister, never shy or embarassed, regardless of who else was around. I miss that his ideal Friday night included a DVD, eating Chinese food right out of the carton, and cuddling on top of my duvet cover. I miss that he reread books from his childhood and then from mine. I miss that he was the only man that I have ever farted on, and with, freely. I miss that he understood that the holidays were hard for me and that he wanted me to never feel lonely." -- Julie Buxbaum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15887-what-is-the-meaning-of-life-that-was-all--a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15887-what-is-the-meaning-of-life-that-was-all--a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is the meaning of life? That was all- a simple question; one that tended to close in on one with years, the great revelation had never come. The great revelation perhaps never did come. Instead, there were little daily miracles, illuminations, matches struck unexpectedly in the dark; here was one." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15889-you-can-have-the-best-message-in-the-world-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 13:35:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Frank Luntz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15889-you-can-have-the-best-message-in-the-world-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can have the best message in the world, but the person on the receiving end will always understand it through the prism of his or her own emotions, preconceptions, prejudices, and preexisting beliefs. It's not enough to be correct or reasonable or even brilliant. The key to successful communication is to take the imaginative leap of stuffing yourself into your listener's shoes to know what they are thinking and feeling in the deepest recesses of their mind and heart. How that person perceives what you say is even more real, at least in a practical sense, than how you perceive yourself." -- Frank Luntz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:38:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Donald Miller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15891-there-is-something-beautiful-about-a-billion-stars-held-steady]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is something beautiful about a billion stars held steady by a God who knows what He is doing. (They hang there, the stars, like notes on a page of music, free-form verse, silent mysteries swirling in the blue like jazz.) And as I lay there, it occurred to me that God is up there somewhere. Of course, I had always known He was, but this time I felt it, I realized it, the way a person realizes they are hungry or thirsty. The knowledge of God seeped out of my brain and into my heart. I imagined Him looking down on this earth, half angry because His beloved mankind had cheated on Him, had committed adultery, and yet hopelessly in love with her, drunk with love for her." -- Donald Miller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15893-i-don-t-think-you-get-to-be-mad-at-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:39:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Laura Dave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15893-i-don-t-think-you-get-to-be-mad-at-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't think you get to be mad at someone unless they come through for you. I don't think you have that luxury. I think you think you can be mad, but really you're just doing something else.&quot;

&quot;What's that?&quot; 

&quot;Waiting." -- Laura Dave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15894-do-you-know-how-sometimes---when-you-are-riding</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:39:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15894-do-you-know-how-sometimes---when-you-are-riding]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do you know how sometimes - when you are riding your bike and you start skidding across sand, or when you miss a step and start tumbling down the stairs - you have those long, long seconds to know that you are going to be hurt, and badly?" -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15895-it-s-about-a-girl-who-is-on-the-cusp-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:40:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jodi Picoult]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15895-it-s-about-a-girl-who-is-on-the-cusp-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's about a girl who is on the cusp of becoming someone.. A girl who may not know what she wants right now, and she may not know who she is right now, but who deserves the chance to find out." -- Jodi Picoult]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15896-love-came-in-so-many-forms-we-love-for-weakness</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:41:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Elizabeth Cox]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15896-love-came-in-so-many-forms-we-love-for-weakness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love came in so many forms. We love for weakness or strength, she thought, for security or wildness, for money, or beauty, or sometimes for sadness. Whatever reason, the brain turned giddy with self-worth, and self-worth became indelibly linked to the one who was loved." -- Elizabeth Cox]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15873-was-everyone-else-really-as-alive-as-she-was-if-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2008 10:42:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15873-was-everyone-else-really-as-alive-as-she-was-if-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Was everyone else really as alive as she was?...If the answer was yes, then the world, the social world, was unbearably complicated, with two billion voices, and everyone's thoughts striving in equal importance and everyone's claim on life as intense, and everyone thinking they were unique, when no one was." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16343-wasn-t-writing-a-kind-of-soaring-an-achievable-form-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 09:09:13 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16343-wasn-t-writing-a-kind-of-soaring-an-achievable-form-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wasn't writing a kind of soaring, an achievable form of flight, of fancy, of the imagination?" -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38294-nothing-that-can-be-can-come-between-me-and-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 09:10:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ian McEwan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38294-nothing-that-can-be-can-come-between-me-and-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nothing that can be, can come between me and the full prospect of my hopes." -- Ian McEwan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
