<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/972379-kelly]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/972379-kelly" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 22:28:50 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170846-on-the-day-of-the-dead-when-the-year-too</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 22:28:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170846-on-the-day-of-the-dead-when-the-year-too]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the day of the dead, when the year too dies,
Must the youngest open the oldest hills
Through the door of the birds, where the breeze breaks.
There fire shall fly from the raven boy,
And the silver eyes that see the wind,
And the light shall have the harp of gold.

By the pleasant lake the Sleepers lie,
On Cadfan’s Way where the kestrels call;
Though grim from the Grey King shadows fall,
Yet singing the golden harp shall guide
To break their sleep and bid them ride.

When light from the lost land shall return,
Six Sleepers shall ride, six Signs shall burn,
And where the midsummer tree grows tall
By Pendragon’s sword the Dark shall fall.

Y maent yr mynyddoedd yn canu,
ac y mae’r arglwyddes yn dod." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12988-for-ever-and-ever-we-say-when-we-are-young</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 22:28:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12988-for-ever-and-ever-we-say-when-we-are-young]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For ever and ever, we say when we are young, or in our prayers. Twice, we say it. Old One, do we not? For ever and ever ... so that a thing may be for ever, a life or a love or a quest, and yet begin again, and be for ever just as before. And any ending that may seem to come is not truly an ending, but an illusion. For Time does not die, Time has neither beginning nor end, and so nothing can end or die that has once had a place in Time." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212610-when-the-dark-comes-rising-six-shall-turn-it-back</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 22:29:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Susan Cooper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212610-when-the-dark-comes-rising-six-shall-turn-it-back]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the Dark comes rising six shall turn it back;
Three from the circle, three from the track;
Wood, bronze, iron; Water, fire, stone;
Five will return and one go alone.

Iron for the birthday; bronze carried long;
Wood from the burning; stone out of song;
Fire in the candle ring; water from the thaw;
Six signs the circle and the grail gone before.

Fire on the mountain shall find the harp of gold
Played to wake the sleepers, oldest of old.
Power from the Green Witch, lost beneath the sea.
All shall find the Light at last, silver on the tree." -- Susan Cooper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15839-it-s-not-time-to-worry-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 14:15:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by Harper Lee]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15839-it-s-not-time-to-worry-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not time to worry yet" -- Harper Lee]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449970-george-had-turned-at-the-sound-of-her-arrival-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2013 16:58:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kelly add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/449970-george-had-turned-at-the-sound-of-her-arrival-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["George had turned at the sound of her arrival. For a moment he contemplated her, as one who had fallen out of heaven. He saw radiant joy in her face, he saw the flowers beat against her dress in blue waves. The bushes above them closed. He stepped quickly forward and kissed her.
Before she could speak, almost before she could feel, a voice called 'Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!' The silence of life had been broken by Miss Bartlett, who stood brown against the view." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
