<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/973905-lisa]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/973905-lisa" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:20:54 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28-i-sent-the-club-a-wire-stating-please-accept-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:20:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Groucho Marx]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28-i-sent-the-club-a-wire-stating-please-accept-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I sent the club a wire stating, PLEASE ACCEPT MY RESIGNATION. I DON'T WANT TO BELONG TO ANY CLUB THAT WILL ACCEPT ME AS A MEMBER." -- Groucho Marx]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1968-i-used-to-be-snow-white-but-i-drifted</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:22:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1968-i-used-to-be-snow-white-but-i-drifted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I used to be Snow White, but I drifted." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21619-i-love-you-buttercup-said-i-know-this-must-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you,' Buttercup said. 'I know this must come as something of a surprise to you, since all I've ever done is scorn you and degrade you and taunt you, but I have loved you for several hours now, and every second, more. I thought an hour ago that I loved you more than any woman has ever loved a man, but a half hour after that I knew that what I felt before was nothing compared to what I felt then. But ten minutes after that, I understood that my previous love was a puddle compared to the high seas before a storm. Your eyes are like that, did you know? Well they are. How many minutes ago was I? Twenty? Had I brought my feelings up to then? It doesn't matter.' Buttercup still could not look at him. The sun was rising behind her now; she could feel the heat on her back, and it gave her courage. 'I love you so much more now than twenty minutes ago that there cannot be comparison. I love you so much more now then when you opened your hovel door, there cannot be comparison. There is no room in my body for anything but you. My arms love you, my ears adore you, my knees shake with blind affection. My mind begs you to ask it something so it can obey. Do you want me to follow you for the rest of your days? I will do that. Do you want me to crawl? I will crawl. I will be quiet for you or sing for you, or if you are hungry, let me bring you food, or if you have thirst and nothing will quench it but Arabian wine, I will go to Araby, even though it is across the world, and bring a bottle back for your lunch. Anything there is that I can do for you, I will do for you; anything there is that I cannot do, I will learn to do. I know I cannot compete with the Countess in skills or wisdom or appeal, and I saw the way she looked at you. And I saw the way you looked at her. But remember, please, that she is old and has other interests, while I am seventeen and for me there is only you. Dearest Westley--I've never called you that before, have I?--Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley, Westley,--darling Westley, adored Westley, sweet perfect Westley, whisper that I have a chance to win your love.' And with that, she dared the bravest thing she'd ever done; she looked right into his eyes." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31760-wait-we-can-not-break-bread-with-you-you-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:29:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Paul Rudnick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31760-wait-we-can-not-break-bread-with-you-you-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wait, we can not break bread with you. You have taken the land which is rightfully ours. Years from now my people will be forced to live in mobile homes on reservations. Your people will wear cardigans, and drink highballs. We will sell our bracelets by the road sides, and you will play golf, and eat hot h'ors d'ourves. My people will have pain and degradation. Your people will have stick shifts. The gods of my tribe have spoken. They said do not trust the pilgrims, especially Sarah Miller. And for all of these reasons I have decided to scalp you and burn your village to the ground." -- Paul Rudnick]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31762-gotta-protect-the-little-dudes-i-tried-an-ak-47-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 20:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Janet Evanovich]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31762-gotta-protect-the-little-dudes-i-tried-an-ak-47-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Gotta protect the little dudes. I tried an AK-47, but it wouldn't fit under my seat. I like the Uzi better, anyway. It looks better with the dress. The AK seems too casual to me" -- Janet Evanovich]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1599-i-generally-avoid-temptation-unless-i-can-t-resist-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:18:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1599-i-generally-avoid-temptation-unless-i-can-t-resist-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I generally avoid temptation unless I can't resist it." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8701-between-two-evils-i-always-pick-the-one-i-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:18:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8701-between-two-evils-i-always-pick-the-one-i-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Between two evils, I always pick the one I never tried before." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1600-i-wrote-the-story-myself-it-s-about-a-girl-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:18:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Mae West]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1600-i-wrote-the-story-myself-it-s-about-a-girl-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wrote the story myself. It's about a girl who lost her reputation and never missed it." -- Mae West]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:19:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8630-i-m-selfish-impatient-and-a-little-insecure-i-make-mistakes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm selfish, impatient and a little insecure. I make mistakes, I am out of control and at times hard to handle. But if you can't handle me at my worst, then you sure as hell don't deserve me at my best." -- Marilyn Monroe]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31774-fear-thou-not-for-i-am-with-thee-be-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:32:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31774-fear-thou-not-for-i-am-with-thee-be-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fear thou not; for I am with thee: be not dismayed; for I am thy God: I will strengthen thee; yea, I will help thee; yea, I will uphold thee with the right hand of my righteousness." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17498-if-we-shadows-have-offended-think-but-this-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2008 21:37:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by William Shakespeare ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17498-if-we-shadows-have-offended-think-but-this-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If we shadows have offended,
Think but this, and all is mended,
That you have but slumber'd here
While these visions did appear." -- William Shakespeare ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2008 18:43:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1944-a-woman-is-like-a-tea-bag-you-never-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman is like a tea bag; you never know how strong it is until it's in hot water." -- Eleanor Roosevelt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42439-it-s-not-the-length-of-the-word-it-s-how-well</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 20:56:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lisa add a quote by Rachel Vincent]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42439-it-s-not-the-length-of-the-word-it-s-how-well]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's not the length of the word; it's how well you use it!" -- Rachel Vincent]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
