<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/974798-lori]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/974798-lori" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 18:44:49 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141195-to-think-of-the-midwest-as-a-whole-as-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 18:44:49 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/141195-to-think-of-the-midwest-as-a-whole-as-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To think of the Midwest as a whole as anything other than beautiful is to ignore the extraordinary power of the land. The lushness of the grass and trees in August, the roll of the hills (far less of the Midwest is flat than outsiders seem to imagine), the rich smell of soil, the evening sunlight over a field of wheat, or the crickets chirping at dusk on a residential street: All of it, it has always made me feel at peace. There is room to breathe, there is a realness of place. The seasons are extreme, but they pass and return, pass and return, and the world seems far steadier than it does from the vantage point of a coastal city.

Certainly picturesque towns can be found in New England or California or the Pacific Northwest, but I can't shake the sense that they're too picturesque. On the East Coast, especially, these places seem to me aggressively quaint, unbecomingly smug, and even xenophobic, downright paranoid in their wariness of those who might somehow infringe upon the local charm. I suspect this wariness is tied to the high cost of real estate, the fear that there might not be enough space or money and what there is of both must be clung to and defended. The West Coast, I think, has a similar self-regard...and a beauty that I can't help seeing as show-offy. But the Midwest: It is quietly lovely, not preening with the need to have its attributes remarked on. It is the place I am calmest and most myself." -- Curtis Sittenfeld]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97012-love-is-the-voice-under-all-silences-the-hope-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 18:45:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by e.e cummings]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97012-love-is-the-voice-under-all-silences-the-hope-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is the voice under all silences, the hope which has no opposite in fear; the strength so strong mere force is feebleness: the truth more first than sun, more last than star..." -- e.e cummings]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31882-you-must-live-every-day-as-if-it-counts-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 13:12:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by C.A. Belmond]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31882-you-must-live-every-day-as-if-it-counts-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You must live every day as if it counts, which means to love all of it. Never let a single one go by without noting the color of the sky, the song of the bird, the face of the one you love best. And don't let yourself get talked out of the things you really care about, don't put off what you want to be." -- C.A. Belmond]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58600-maybe-that-s-what-it-all-comes-down-to-love-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 09:56:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Emily Giffin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58600-maybe-that-s-what-it-all-comes-down-to-love-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Maybe that's what it all comes down to. Love, not as a surge of passion, but as a choice to commit to something, someone, no matter what obstacles or temptations stand in the way. And maybe making that choice, again and again, day in and day out, year after year, says more about love than never having a choice to make at all." -- Emily Giffin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68258-life-s-under-no-obligation-to-give-us-what-we-expect</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2010 11:55:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68258-life-s-under-no-obligation-to-give-us-what-we-expect]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's under no obligation to give us what we expect." -- Margaret Mitchell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5550-let-me-not-to-the-marriage-of-true-minds-admit</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 18:43:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5550-let-me-not-to-the-marriage-of-true-minds-admit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let me not to the marriage of true minds 
Admit impediments. Love is not love 
Which alters when it alteration finds, 
Or bends with the remover to remove. 
O no, it is an ever-fixed mark 
That looks on tempests and is never shaken; 
It is the star to every wand'ring barque, 
Whose worth's unknown, although his height be taken. 
Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks 
Within his bending sickle's compass come; 
Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks, 
But bears it out even to the edge of doom. 
If this be error and upon me proved, 
I never writ, nor no man ever loved." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2012 18:49:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lori add a quote by George Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2801-but-the-effect-of-her-being-on-those-around-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the effect of her being on those around her was incalculably diffusive: for the growing good of the world is partly dependent on unhistoric acts; and that things are not so ill with you and me as they might have been, is half owing to the number who lived faithfully a hidden life, and rest in unvisited tombs." -- George Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
