<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/975308-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/975308-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 23:37:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 23:37:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Marianne Williamson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/928-our-deepest-fear-is-not-that-we-are-inadequate-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our light, not our darkness that most frightens us. We ask ourselves, 'Who am I to be brilliant, gorgeous, talented, fabulous?' Actually, who are you not to be? You are a child of God. Your playing small does not serve the world. There is nothing enlightened about shrinking so that other people won't feel insecure around you. We are all meant to shine, as children do. We were born to make manifest the glory of God that is within us. It's not just in some of us; it's in everyone. And as we let our own light shine, we unconsciously give other people permission to do the same. As we are liberated from our own fear, our presence automatically liberates others." -- Marianne Williamson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5832-argue-for-your-limitations-and-sure-enough-they-re-yours</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 12:54:45 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Richard Bach]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5832-argue-for-your-limitations-and-sure-enough-they-re-yours]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Argue for your limitations and, sure enough, they're yours." -- Richard Bach]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2009 08:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1718-the-very-least-you-can-do-in-your-life-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The very least you can do in your life is figure out what you hope for. And the most you can do is live inside that hope. Not admire it from a distance but live right in it, under its roof." -- Barbara Kingsolver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2012 15:15:23 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
