<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/975304-josephus-fromplacitas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/975304-josephus-fromplacitas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 08:26:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54957-there-has-never-been-a-just-war-never-an-honorable</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 08:26:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54957-there-has-never-been-a-just-war-never-an-honorable]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There has never been a just [war], never an honorable one--on the part of the instigator of the war. I can see a million years ahead, and this rule will never change in so many as half a dozen instances. The loud little handful--as usual--will shout for the war. The pulpit will--warily and cautiously--object--at first; the great, big, dull bulk of the nation will rub its sleepy eyes and try to make out why there should be a war, and will say, earnestly and indignantly, 'It is unjust and dishonorable, and there is no necessity for it.' Then the handful will shout louder. A few fair men on the other side will argue and reason against the war with speech and pen, and at first will have a hearing and be applauded; but it will not last long; those others will outshout them, and presently the anti-war audiences will thin out and lose popularity. Before long you will see this curious thing: the speakers stoned from the platform, and free speech strangled by hordes of furious men who in their secret hearts are still at one with those stoned speakers--as earlier--but do not dare say so. And now the whole nation--pulpit and all--will take up the war-cry, and shout itself hoarse, and mob any honest man who ventures to open his mouth; and presently such mouths will cease to open. Next the statesmen will invent cheap lies, putting the blame upon the nation that is attacked, and every man will be glad of those conscience-soothing falsities, and will diligently study them, and refuse to examine any refutations of them; and thus he will by and by convince himself the war is just, and will thank God for the better sleep he enjoys after this process of grotesque self-deception." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54928-when-the-pentagon-feels-free-and-even-gleeful-about-killing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 18:16:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54928-when-the-pentagon-feels-free-and-even-gleeful-about-killing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the Pentagon feels free and even gleeful about killing anybody and Everybody who gets in the way of their vicious crusade for oil, the public soul of this country has changed forever, and professional sports is only a serenade for the death of the American dream. &lt;i&gt;Mahalo&lt;/i&gt;." -- Hunter S. Thompson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54956-and-what-does-it-amount-to-said-satan-with-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 08:26:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54956-and-what-does-it-amount-to-said-satan-with-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And what does it amount to?&quot; said Satan, with his evil chuckle. &quot;Nothing at all. You gain nothing; you always come out where you went in. For a million years the race has gone on monotonously propagating itself and monotonously reperforming this dull nonsense--to what end? No wisdom can guess! Who gets a profit out of it?  Nobody but a parcel of usurping little monarchs and nobilities who despise you; would feel defiled if you touched them; would shut the door in your face if you proposed to call; whom you slave for, fight for, die for, and are not ashamed of it, but proud; whose existence is a perpetual insult to you and you are afraid to resent it; who are mendicants supported by your alms, yet assume toward you the airs of benefactor toward beggar; who address you in the language of master to slave, and are answered in in the language of slave to master; who are worshiped by you with your mouth, while in your heart--if you have one--you despise yourselves for it. The first man was hypocrite and a coward, qualities which have not yet failed in his line; it is the foundation upon which all civilizations have been built. Drink to their perpetuation! Drink to their augmentation! Drink to--&quot; Then he saw by our faces how much we were hurt, and he cut his sentence short and stopped chuckling..." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59146-orthodoxy-means-not-thinking--not-needing-to-think-orthodoxy-is-unconsciousness</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 10:53:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59146-orthodoxy-means-not-thinking--not-needing-to-think-orthodoxy-is-unconsciousness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Orthodoxy means not thinking--not needing to think. Orthodoxy is unconsciousness." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59141-to-speak-behind-others-backs-is-the-ventilator-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 10:53:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59141-to-speak-behind-others-backs-is-the-ventilator-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To speak behind others' backs is the ventilator of the heart." -- Marjane Satrapi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69923-journalists-are-notoriously-prone-to-exaggerate-the-beneficial-impact-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 07:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Patrick Cockburn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69923-journalists-are-notoriously-prone-to-exaggerate-the-beneficial-impact-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Journalists are notoriously prone to exaggerate the beneficial impact of elections and to ignore more complex developments." -- Patrick Cockburn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33322-i-know-of-no-american-who-starts-from-a-higher</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 17:44:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by H.L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33322-i-know-of-no-american-who-starts-from-a-higher]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know of no American who starts from a higher level of aspiration than the journalist. . . . He plans to be both an artist and a moralist -- a master of lovely words and merchant of sound ideas. He ends, commonly, as the most depressing jackass of his community -- that is, if his career goes on to what is called a success." -- H.L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70073-a-newspaper-is-a-device-for-making-the-ignorant-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2008 18:12:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by H.L. Mencken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70073-a-newspaper-is-a-device-for-making-the-ignorant-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A newspaper is a device for making the ignorant more ignorant and the crazy crazier." -- H.L. Mencken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82405-war-is-just-demographics-in-a-hurry</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 07:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Gary Brecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82405-war-is-just-demographics-in-a-hurry]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["War is just demographics in a hurry." -- Gary Brecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83045-it-s-always-the-same-story-it-s-not-violence-until-somebody</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 07:54:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Gary Brecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83045-it-s-always-the-same-story-it-s-not-violence-until-somebody]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's always the same story: It's not 'violence' until somebody hits you back.  Till then, you don't notice your guys hitting the other tribe.  That's just normal background noise.  It takes blood, buckets of it, to get a person's attention.  And not just anybody's blood--it's gotta be your own, or that of a close relative.  Otherwise it's just spots on the sidewalk." -- Gary Brecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111214-but-no-soldier-above-the-rank-of-sergeant-ever-served</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 09:51:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Philip Gourevitch]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111214-but-no-soldier-above-the-rank-of-sergeant-ever-served]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But no soldier above the rank of sergeant ever served jail time.  No civilian interrogators ever faced legal proceedings.  Nobody was ever charged with torture, or war crimes, or any violation of the Geneva Conventions.  Nobody ever faced charges for keeping prisoners naked,or shackled.  Nobody ever faced charges for holding prisoners as hostages.  Nobody ever faced charges for incarcerating children who were accused of no crime and posed no known security threat.  Nobody ever faced charges for holding thousands of prisoners in a combat zone in constant danger of their lives.  Nobody ever faced charges for arresting thousands of civilians without direct cause and holding them indefinitely, incommunicado, in concentration camp conditions.  Nobody ever faced charges for shooting and killing prisoners who were confined behind concertina wire.  And nobody has ever been held to account for murdering al-Jamadi in the Tier 1B shower, although Sabrina Harman initially faced several charges for having photographed him there." -- Philip Gourevitch]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21895-true-terror-is-to-wake-up-one-morning-and-discover</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 11:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21895-true-terror-is-to-wake-up-one-morning-and-discover]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["True terror is to wake up one morning and discover that your high school class is running the country." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40812-anarchism-is-founded-on-the-observation-that-since-few-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:35:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40812-anarchism-is-founded-on-the-observation-that-since-few-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anarchism is founded on the observation that since few men are wise enough to rule themselves, even fewer are wise enough to rule others." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76073-a-pretty-girl-can-do-no-wrong</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:37:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76073-a-pretty-girl-can-do-no-wrong]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A pretty girl can do no wrong." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80672-the-tragedy-of-modern-war-is-that-the-young-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:37:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80672-the-tragedy-of-modern-war-is-that-the-young-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The tragedy of modern war is that the young men die fighting each other - instead of their real enemies back home in the capitals. " -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99402-the-wilderness-should-be-preserved-for-political-reasons-we-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:38:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/99402-the-wilderness-should-be-preserved-for-political-reasons-we-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the wilderness should be preserved for political reasons. We may need it someday not only as a refuge from excessive industrialism but also as a refuge from authoritarian government, from political oppression. Grand Canyon, Big Bend, Yellowstone, and the High Sierras may be required to function as bases for guerrilla warfare against tyranny...The value of wilderness, on the other hand, as a base for resistance to centralized domination is demonstrated by recent history. In Budapest and Santo Domingo, for example, popular revolts were easily and quickly crushed because an urbanized environment gives the advantage to the power with technological equipment. But in Cuba, Algeria, and Vietnam the revolutionaries, operating in mountain, desert, and jungle hinterlands with the active or tacit support of a thinly dispersed population, have been able to overcome or at least fight to a draw official establishment forces equipped with all of the terrible weapons of twentieth century militarism." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61178-the-missionaries-go-forth-to-christianize-the-savages---as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2009 14:39:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61178-the-missionaries-go-forth-to-christianize-the-savages---as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The missionaries go forth to Christianize the savages - as if the savages weren't dangerous enough already." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203330-most-striking-about-the-traditional-societies-of-the-congo-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 10:49:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Adam Hochschild]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203330-most-striking-about-the-traditional-societies-of-the-congo-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most striking about the traditional societies of the Congo was their remarkable artwork: baskets, mats, pottery, copper and ironwork, and, above all, woodcarving.  It would be two decades before Europeans really noticed this art.  Its discovery then had a strong influence on  Braque, Matisse, and Picasso -- who subsequently kept African art objects in his studio until his death.  Cubism was new only for Europeans, for it was partly inspired by specific pieces of African art, some of them from the Pende and Songye peoples, who live in the basin of the Kasai River, one of the Congo's major tributaries.

It was easy to see the distinctive brilliance that so entranced Picasso and his colleagues at their first encounter with this art at an exhibit in Paris in 1907.  In these central African sculptures some body parts are exaggerated, some shrunken; eyes project, cheeks sink, mouths disappear, torsos become elongated; eye sockets expand to cover almost the entire face; the human face and figure are broken apart and formed again in new ways and proportions that had previously lain beyond sight of traditional European realism.

The art sprang from cultures that had, among other things, a looser sense than Islam or Christianity of the boundaries between our world and the next, as well as those between the world of humans and the world of beasts.  Among the Bolia people of the Congo, for example, a king was chosen by a council of elders; by ancestors, who appeared to him in a dream; and finally by wild animals, who signaled their assent by roaring during a night when the royal candidate was left at a particular spot in the rain forest.  Perhaps it was the fluidity of these boundaries that granted central Africa's artists a freedom those in Europe had not yet discovered. " -- Adam Hochschild]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203473-despotism-is-a-legitimate-mode-of-government-in-dealing-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 20:51:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by John Stuart Mill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203473-despotism-is-a-legitimate-mode-of-government-in-dealing-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Despotism is a legitimate mode of government in dealing with barbarians, provided the end be their improvement." -- John Stuart Mill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203475-when-leopold-wrote-that-the-precise-frontiers-of-the-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2009 20:58:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Adam Hochschild]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/203475-when-leopold-wrote-that-the-precise-frontiers-of-the-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When Leopold wrote that the precise frontiers of the new state or states would be defined later, [German Chancellor] Bismarck said to an aide, &quot;His Majesty displays the pretensions and naive selfishness of an Italian who considers that his charm and good looks will enable him to get away with anything." -- Adam Hochschild]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102341-monsters-exist-but-they-are-too-few-in-number-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2009 08:14:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Primo Levi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102341-monsters-exist-but-they-are-too-few-in-number-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Monsters exist, but they are too few in number to be truly dangerous. More dangerous are the common men, the functionaries ready to believe and to act without asking questions." -- Primo Levi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205067-plundered-wine-tastes-all-the-sweeter</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 22:05:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Linnus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/205067-plundered-wine-tastes-all-the-sweeter]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Plundered wine tastes all the sweeter." -- Linnus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216434-the-parties-with-the-most-gain-never-show-up-on</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 22:52:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216434-the-parties-with-the-most-gain-never-show-up-on]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The parties with the most gain never show up on the battlefield." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216436-extreme-violence-has-a-way-of-preventing-us-from-seeing</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 22:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/216436-extreme-violence-has-a-way-of-preventing-us-from-seeing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Extreme violence has a way of preventing us from seeing the interests it serves." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217006-like-russia-s-gangsterism-and-bush-s-cronyism-contemporary-iraq-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2009 22:48:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217006-like-russia-s-gangsterism-and-bush-s-cronyism-contemporary-iraq-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like Russia's gangsterism and Bush's cronyism, contemporary Iraq is a creation of the fifty-year crusade to privatize the world.  Rather than being disowned by its creators, it deserves to be seen as the purest incarnation yet of the ideology that gave it birth." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38442-the-religion-of-one-age-is-the-literary-entertainment-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 02:36:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38442-the-religion-of-one-age-is-the-literary-entertainment-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The religion of one age is the literary entertainment of the next." -- Ralph Waldo Emerson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222580-sloth-is-a-cancer-eating-up-that-time-princes-should</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2010 21:18:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Edmund Ken]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222580-sloth-is-a-cancer-eating-up-that-time-princes-should]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sloth is a Cancer, eating up that Time Princes should cultivate for Things sublime." -- Edmund Ken]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222904-a-large-part-of-the-popularity-and-persuasiveness-of-psychology</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2010 00:08:48 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/222904-a-large-part-of-the-popularity-and-persuasiveness-of-psychology]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A large part of the popularity and persuasiveness of psychology comes from its being a sublimated spiritualism: a secular, ostensibly scientific way of affirming the primacy of spirit over matter." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224795-el-amor-es-una-epidemia-que-se-acaba-con-el</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 19:49:52 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Joaquín Sabina]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/224795-el-amor-es-una-epidemia-que-se-acaba-con-el]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["El amor es una epidemia que se acaba con el tiempo." -- Joaquín Sabina]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225224-abuse-of-the-military-metaphor-may-be-inevitable-in-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2010 11:49:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Josephus add a quote by Susan Sontag]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/225224-abuse-of-the-military-metaphor-may-be-inevitable-in-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Abuse of the military metaphor may be inevitable in a capitalist society, a society that increasingly restricts the scope and credibility of appeals to ethical principle, in which it is thought foolish not to subject one's actions to the calculus of self-interest and profitability.  War-making is one of the few activities that people are not supposed to view 'realistically'; that is, with an eye to expense and practical outcome.  In all-out war, expenditure is all-out, unprudent--war being defined as as an emergency in which no sacrifice is excessive." -- Susan Sontag]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
