<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/976519-summer]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/976519-summer" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 23:14:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 23:14:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3078-the-man-who-believes-that-the-secrets-of-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The man who believes that the secrets of the world are forever hidden lives in mystery and fear. Superstitiion will drag him down. The rain will erode the deeds of his life. But that man who sets himself the task of singling out the thread of order from the tapestry will by the decision alone have taken charge of the world and it is only by such taking charge that he will effect a way to dictate the terms of his own fate. 

I dont see what that has to do with catchin birds. 

The freedom of birds is an insult to me. I'd have them all in zoos. 

That would be a hell of a zoo. 

The judge smiled. Yes, he said. Even so." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 23:14:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3535-once-there-were-brook-trout-in-the-streams-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once there were brook trout in the streams in the mountains. You could see them standing in the amber current where the white edges of their fins wimpled softly in the flow. They smelled of moss in your hand. Polished and muscular and torsional. On their backs were vermiculate patterns that were maps of the world in its becoming. Maps and mazes. Of a thing which could not be put back. Not be made right again. In the deep glens where they lived all things were older than man and they hummed of mystery." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2008 23:14:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Summer add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3085-the-truth-about-the-world-he-said-is-that-anything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The truth about the world, he said, is that anything is possible. Had you not seen it all from birth and thereby bled it of its strangeness it would appear to you for what it is, a hat trick in a medicine show, a fevered dream, a trance bepopulate with chimeras having neither analogue nor precedent, an itinerant carnival, a migratory tentshow whose ultimate destination after many a pitch in many a mudded field is unspeakable and calamitous beyond reckoning. 

The universe is no narrow thing and the order within it is not constrained by any latitude in its conception to repeat what exists in one part in any other part. Even in this world more things exist without our knowledge than with it and the order in creation which you see is that which you have put there, like a string in a maze, so that you shall not lose your way. For existence has its own order and that no man's mind can compass, that mind itself being but a fact among others." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
