<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/976632-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/976632-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 19:24:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440516-weight-loss-does-not-make-people-happy-or-peaceful-being</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 19:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/440516-weight-loss-does-not-make-people-happy-or-peaceful-being]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Weight loss does not make people happy.  Or peaceful.  Being thin does not address the emptiness that has no shape or weight or name.  Even a wildly successful diet is a colossal failure because inside the new body is the same sinking heart." -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287216-i-shall-never-get-out-of-this-there-are-two</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 16:17:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/287216-i-shall-never-get-out-of-this-there-are-two]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall never get out of this! There are two of me now:
This new absolutely white person and the old yellow one, 
And the white person is certainly the superior one. 
She doesn't need food, she is one of the real saints.
 At the beginning I hated her, she had no personality --
She lay in bed with me like a dead body
 And I was scared, because she was shaped just the way I was  

Only much whiter and unbreakable and with no complaints.
I couldn't sleep for a week, she was so cold. 
I blamed her for everything, but she didn't answer.
 I couldn't understand her stupid behavior!
 When I hit her she held still, like a true pacifist.
 Then I realized what she wanted was for me to love her:
She began to warm up, and I saw her advantages.

  Without me, she wouldn't exist, so of course she was grateful.
 I gave her a soul, I bloomed out of her as a rose
 Blooms out of a vase of not very valuable porcelain, 
And it was I who attracted everybody's attention,
 Not her whiteness and beauty, as I had at first supposed.
 I patronized her a little, and she lapped it up --
 You could tell almost at once she had a slave mentality.

  I didn't mind her waiting on me, and she adored it.
 In the morning she woke me early, reflecting the sun
 From her amazingly white torso, and I couldn't help but notice
 Her tidiness and her calmness and her patience: 
She humored my weakness like the best of nurses,
 Holding my bones in place so they would mend properly.
In time our relationship grew more intense.

  She stopped fitting me so closely and seemed offish.
 I felt her criticizing me in spite of herself,
 As if my habits offended her in some way. 
She let in the drafts and became more and more absent-minded.
 And my skin itched and flaked away in soft pieces
 Simply because she looked after me so badly. 
Then I saw what the trouble was: she thought she was immortal.

She wanted to leave me, she thought she was superior,
 And I'd been keeping her in the dark, and she was resentful -- 
Wasting her days waiting on a half-corpse!
 And secretly she began to hope I'd die.
Then she could cover my mouth and eyes, cover me entirely,
 And wear my painted face the way a mummy-case 
Wears the face of a pharaoh, though it's made of mud and water.

  I wasn't in any position to get rid of her. 
She'd supported me for so long I was quite limp -- 
I had forgotten how to walk or sit, 
So I was careful not to upset her in any way
 Or brag ahead of time how I'd avenge myself. 
Living with her was like living with my own coffin: 
Yet I still depended on her, though I did it regretfully. 

I used to think we might make a go of it together --
 After all, it was a kind of marriage, being so close.
 Now I see it must be one or the other of us. 
She may be a saint, and I may be ugly and hairy,
 But she'll soon find out that that doesn't matter a bit. 
I'm collecting my strength; one day I shall manage without her,
 And she'll perish with emptiness then, and begin to miss me." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231044-i-want-to-taste-and-glory-in-each-day-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 16:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231044-i-want-to-taste-and-glory-in-each-day-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to taste and glory in each day, and never be afraid to experience pain; and never shut myself up in a numb core of nonfeeling, or stop questioning and criticizing life and take the easy way out. To learn and think: to think and live; to live and learn: this always, with new insight, new understanding, and new love." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180189-there-is-no-magic-cure-no-making-it-all-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 16:21:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/180189-there-is-no-magic-cure-no-making-it-all-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no magic cure, no making it all go away forever. There are only small steps upward; an easier day, an unexpected laugh, a mirror that doesn't matter anymore." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437-out-beyond-ideas-of-wrongdoing-and-rightdoing-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 16:21:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Jalal Ad-Din Rumi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/437-out-beyond-ideas-of-wrongdoing-and-rightdoing-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Out beyond ideas of wrongdoing 
and rightdoing there is a field.
I'll meet you there.

When the soul lies down in that grass
the world is too full to talk about." -- Jalal Ad-Din Rumi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233180-i-breathe-in-slowly-food-is-life-i-exhale-take</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2010 16:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/233180-i-breathe-in-slowly-food-is-life-i-exhale-take]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I breathe in slowly. Food is life. I exhale, take another breath. Food is life. And that's the problem. When you're alive, people can hurt you. It's easier to crawl into a bone cage or a snowdrift of confusion. It's easier to lock everybody out.
 But it's a lie." -- Laurie Halse Anderson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289762-in-the-end-just-three-things-matter-how-well-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 10:03:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Jack Kornfield]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/289762-in-the-end-just-three-things-matter-how-well-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the end, just three things matter:

How well we have lived
How well we have loved
How well we have learned to let go" -- Jack Kornfield]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249024-imagine-not-being-frightened-by-any-feeling-imagine-knowing-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 22:50:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/249024-imagine-not-being-frightened-by-any-feeling-imagine-knowing-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Imagine not being frightened by any feeling.  Imagine knowing that nothing will destroy you.  That you are beyond any feeling, an state.  Bigger than.  Vaster than.  That there is no reason to use drugs because anything a drug could do would pale in comparison to knowing who you are.  To what you can understand, live, be, just by being with that presents itself to you in the form of the feelings you have..." -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 22:52:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Geneen Roth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/297593-you-are-not-a-mistake-you-are-not-a-problem]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You are not a mistake.  You are not a problem to be solved.  But you won't discover this until you are willing to stop banging your head against the wall of shaming and caging and fearing yourself. (p. 84)" -- Geneen Roth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62766-the-true-miracle-is-not-walking-on-water-or-walking</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 19:22:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62766-the-true-miracle-is-not-walking-on-water-or-walking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The true miracle is not walking on water or walking in air, but simply walking on this earth." -- Thich Nhat Hanh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231590-i-am-different-not-less</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 17:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Temple Grandin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231590-i-am-different-not-less]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am different,  not less " -- Temple Grandin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
