<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977059-britt-garrett]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977059-britt-garrett" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:22:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32157-i-thought-of-the-people-before-me-who-had-looked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:22:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Britt add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32157-i-thought-of-the-people-before-me-who-had-looked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I thought of the people before me who had looked down at the river and gone to sleep beneath it. I wondered about them. I wondered how they had done it--it, the physical act.

I simply wondered about the dead because their days had ended and I did not know how I would get through mine." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32161-anne-i-don-t-want-to-live-now</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:24:04 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Britt add a quote by Anne Sexton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32161-anne-i-don-t-want-to-live-now]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anne, I don't want to live. . . . Now listen, life is lovely, but I Can't Live It. I can't even explain. I know how silly it sounds . . . but if you knew how it Felt. To be alive, yes, alive, but not be able to live it. Ay that's the rub. I am like a stone that lives . . . locked outside of all that's real. . . . Anne, do you know of such things, can you hear???? I wish, or think I wish, that I were dying of something for then I could be brave, but to be not dying, and yet . . . and yet to [be] behind a wall, watching everyone fit in where I can't, to talk behind a gray foggy wall, to live but to not reach or to reach wrong . . . to do it all wrong . . . believe me, (can you?) . . . what's wrong. I want to belong. I'm like a jew who ends up in the wrong country. I'm not a part. I'm not a member. I'm frozen." -- Anne Sexton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32232-runaways-are-romantic-the-girls-are-waiflike-with-dyed-ratty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 14:54:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Britt add a quote by Bett Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32232-runaways-are-romantic-the-girls-are-waiflike-with-dyed-ratty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Runaways are romantic. The girls are waiflike with dyed ratty hair and baggy pants. They usually own a stray dog of the mutt variety and drag it along by a rope, plopping down in front of storefronts to beg for money from passersby. They're a mess. It is likely they'll charm you, make you think you're their best friend and savior only to end up using you and then they'll disappear. That's why they're romantic. They're there and then they're gone. Romance is always about people appearing in a flash out of nothing or people who are there and then suddenly are not. A magic trick." -- Bett Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
