<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977592-tim]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977592-tim" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 23:55:37 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201028-unless-we-have-the-courage-to-fight-for-a-revival</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 23:55:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/201028-unless-we-have-the-courage-to-fight-for-a-revival]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Unless we have the courage to fight for a revival of wholesome reserve between man and man, we shall perish in an anarchy of human values… . Socially it means the renunciation of all place-hunting, a break with the cult of the “star,” an open eye both upwards and downwards, especially in the choice of one’s more intimate friends, and pleasure in private life as well as courage to enter public life. Culturally it means a return from the newspaper and the radio to the book, from feverish activity to unhurried leisure, from dispersion to concentration, from sensationalism to reflection, from virtuosity to art, from snobbery to modesty, from extravagance to moderation." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283627-there-is-nothing-that-can-replace-the-absence-of-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 02:55:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/283627-there-is-nothing-that-can-replace-the-absence-of-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing that can replace the absence of someone dear to us, and one should not even attempt to do so. One must simply hold out and endure it. At first that sounds very hard, but at the same time it is also a great comfort. For to the extent the emptiness truly remains unfilled one remains connected to the other person through it. It is wrong to say that God fills the emptiness. God in no way fills it but much more leaves it precisely unfilled and thus helps us preserve -- even in pain -- the authentic relationship. Further more, the more beautiful and full the remembrances, the more difficult the separation. But gratitude transforms the torment of memory into silent joy. One bears what was lovely in the past not as a thorn but as a precious gift deep within, a hidden treasure of which one can always be certain." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330676-being-a-christian-is-less-about-cautiously-avoiding-sin-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 02:58:11 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Eric Metaxas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/330676-being-a-christian-is-less-about-cautiously-avoiding-sin-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being a Christian is less about cautiously avoiding sin than about courageously and actively doing God's will." -- Eric Metaxas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174458-just-as-christians-should-not-be-constantly-feeling-the-pulse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 03:02:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/174458-just-as-christians-should-not-be-constantly-feeling-the-pulse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Just as Christians should not be constantly feeling the pulse of their spiritual life, so too the Christian community has not been given to us by God for us to be continually taking its temperature. The more thankfully we daily receive what is given to us, the more assuredly and consistently will community increase and grow from day to day as God pleases" -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328974-judging-others-makes-us-blind-whereas-love-is-illuminating-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 03:02:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328974-judging-others-makes-us-blind-whereas-love-is-illuminating-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Judging others makes us blind, whereas love is illuminating. By judging others we blind ourselves to our own evil and to the grace which others are just as entitled to as we are." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217778-god-loves-human-beings-god-loves-the-world-not-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 03:02:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217778-god-loves-human-beings-god-loves-the-world-not-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["God loves human beings. God loves the world. Not an ideal human, but human beings as they are; not an ideal world, but the real world. What we find repulsive in their opposition to God, what we shrink back from with pain and hostility, namely, real human beings, the real world, this is for God the ground of unfathomable love." -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175144-being-free-means-being-free-for-the-other-because-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2011 15:18:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tim add a quote by Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175144-being-free-means-being-free-for-the-other-because-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Being free means &quot;being free for the other,&quot; because the other has bound me to him. Only in relationship with the other am I free" -- Dietrich Bonhoeffer]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
