<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977790-william-akin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977790-william-akin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 02:51:35 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163932-civil-disobedience-is-not-our-problem-our-problem-is-civil</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 02:51:35 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/163932-civil-disobedience-is-not-our-problem-our-problem-is-civil]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Civil disobedience is not our problem. Our problem is civil obedience. Our problem is that people all over the world have obeyed the dictates of leaders…and millions have been killed because of this obedience…Our problem is that people are obedient allover the world in the face of poverty and starvation and stupidity, and war, and cruelty. Our problem is that people are obedient while the jails are full of petty thieves… (and) the grand thieves are running the country. That’s our problem." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 01:38:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:47:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2032-there-is-nothing-to-writing-all-you-do-is-sit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and bleed." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:47:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12483-all-good-books-are-alike-in-that-they-are-truer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All good books are alike in that they are truer than if they had really happened and after you are finished reading one you will feel that all that happened to you and afterwards it all belongs to you: the good and the bad, the ecstasy, the remorse and sorrow, the people and the places and how the weather was. If you can get so that you can give that to people, then you are a writer." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52073-the-first-draft-of-anything-is-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:47:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/52073-the-first-draft-of-anything-is-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first draft of anything is shit." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84190-sometimes-i-write-drunk-and-revise-sober-and-sometimes-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:47:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Peter De Vries]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84190-sometimes-i-write-drunk-and-revise-sober-and-sometimes-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I write drunk and revise sober, and sometimes I write sober and revise drunk. But you have to have both elements in creation — the Apollonian and the Dionysian, or spontaneity and restraint, emotion and discipline." -- Peter De Vries]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36587-never-think-that-war-no-matter-how-necessary-nor-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2010 00:48:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36587-never-think-that-war-no-matter-how-necessary-nor-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never think that war, no matter how necessary, nor how justified, is not a crime." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312196-we-are-the-poem-s-ancient-band-of-twelve-that-proceeds</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 23:40:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Selma Lagerlöf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/312196-we-are-the-poem-s-ancient-band-of-twelve-that-proceeds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are the poem's ancient band of twelve that proceeds through the ages. There were twelve of us, when we ruled the world on the cloud-covered top of Olympus, and twelve when we lived as birds in Ygdrasil's green crown. Wherever poetry went forth, there we followed. Did we not sit, twelve men strong, at King Arthur's round table, and did twelve paladins not go in Charles the Twelfth's great army? On of us has been Thor, another Jupiter, as any man should be able to see in us yet today. The divine splendor can be sensed under the rags, the lion's mane under the donkey hide. Time has treated us badly, but when we are there, the smithy becomes Mount Olympus and the cavalier's wing a Valhalla." -- Selma Lagerlöf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133846-a-man-who-would-letterspace-lower-case-would-steal-sheep</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2011 02:08:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Robert Bringhurst]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/133846-a-man-who-would-letterspace-lower-case-would-steal-sheep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A man who would letterspace lower case would steal sheep, Frederic Goudy liked to say.  If this wisdom needs updating, it is chiefly to add that a woman who would letterspace lower case would steal sheep as well ." -- Robert Bringhurst]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54454-she-says-nothing-at-all-but-simply-stares-upward-into</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 02:15:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54454-she-says-nothing-at-all-but-simply-stares-upward-into]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She says nothing at all, but simply stares upward into the dark sky and watches, with sad eyes, the slow dance of the infinite stars." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22928-i-ve-had-it-with-these-cheap-sons-of-bitches-who</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 02:16:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Kenneth Rexroth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22928-i-ve-had-it-with-these-cheap-sons-of-bitches-who]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've had it with these cheap sons of bitches who claim they love poetry but never buy a book." -- Kenneth Rexroth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107828-i-write-for-one-and-only-one-purpose-to-overcome</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 02:16:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Kenneth Rexroth]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/107828-i-write-for-one-and-only-one-purpose-to-overcome]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I write for one and only one purpose, to overcome the invincible ignorance of the traduced heart. […] I wish to speak to and for those who have had enough of the Social Lie, the Economics of Mass Murder, the Sexual Hoax, and the Domestication of Conspicuous Consumption." -- Kenneth Rexroth]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37632-i-am-the-twentieth-century-i-am-the-ragtime-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 01:23:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37632-i-am-the-twentieth-century-i-am-the-ragtime-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the twentieth century. I am the ragtime and the tango; sans-serif, clean geometry. I am the virgin's-hair whip and the cunningly detailed shackles of decadent passion. I am every lonely railway station in every capital of Europe. I am the Street, the fanciless buildings of government. the cafe-dansant, the clockwork figure, the jazz saxophone, the tourist-lady's hairpiece, the fairy's rubber breasts, the travelling clock which always tells the wrong time and chimes in different keys. I am the dead palm tree, the Negro's dancing pumps, the dried fountain after tourist season. I am all the appurtenances of night." -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71496-what-are-the-stars-but-points-in-the-body-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 01:24:24 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/71496-what-are-the-stars-but-points-in-the-body-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What are the stars but points in the body of God where we insert the healing needles of our terror and longing?
--Gravity's Rainbow, V699" -- Thomas Pynchon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137080-if-you-aren-t-cute-you-may-as-well-be-clever</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2014 03:32:02 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by David Sedaris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/137080-if-you-aren-t-cute-you-may-as-well-be-clever]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you aren't cute, you may as well be clever." -- David Sedaris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33325-i-wonder-how-many-people-i-ve-looked-at-all-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2014 02:29:44 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33325-i-wonder-how-many-people-i-ve-looked-at-all-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wonder how many people I've looked at all my life and never seen." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706214-what-are-they-doing-he-whispered-the-pinball-machine-s-scoreboard</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 00:24:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[William add a quote by Christopher Boucher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/706214-what-are-they-doing-he-whispered-the-pinball-machine-s-scoreboard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What are they doing?” he whispered.
The pinball machine’s scoreboard was full, the bank’s windows fogged. They were so involved- so cofaithed- that they didn’t know we were there. 
The VW’s face joined, “Are they hurting each other?”
I took a breath. “There’s risk involved, because of what they can’t see. Plus the risk of trust. But no-they’re not hurting each other.”
The bank whispered something in the pinball machine’s ear and the pinball machine giggled.
“What are they saying to each other?” the VW said.
“They’re expressing their faith, VW-sharing it.”
Just then I heard a rustle, soft at first, then louder…Distracted by other things-the VW, the faith in the trees- I had forgotten to keep the mountain straight in my mind. I had let it go, and now it was changing, reversing itself, growing young: the leaves were turning from brown back to green… THIS was western Massachusetts-unpredictable; a changing moving bitch; a switcher of faces…how could I have many any progress here when mountains were mountains one moment and something else the next; when people were here one day and then GONE?" -- Christopher Boucher]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
