<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977942-sarah-the-pirate]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/977942-sarah-the-pirate" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 01:38:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 01:38:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Sylvia Plath]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7511-i-saw-my-life-branching-out-before-me-like-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn't quite make out. I saw myself sitting in the crotch of this fig tree, starving to death, just because I couldn't make up my mind which of the figs I would choose. I wanted each and every one of them, but choosing one meant losing all the rest, and, as I sat there, unable to decide, the figs began to wrinkle and go black, and, one by one, they plopped to the ground at my feet." -- Sylvia Plath]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20847-you-will-recognize-your-own-path-when-you-come-upon</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 01:41:00 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Sara Teasdale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20847-you-will-recognize-your-own-path-when-you-come-upon]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will recognize your own path when you come upon it because you will suddenly have all the energy and imagination you will ever need." -- Sara Teasdale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 01:48:20 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Jack Kerouac]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3831-the-only-people-for-me-are-the-mad-ones-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["the only people for me are the mad ones, the ones who are mad to live, mad to talk, mad to be saved, desirous of everything at the same time, the ones who never yawn or say a commonplace thing, but burn, burn, burn like fabulous yellow roman candles exploding like spiders across the stars." -- Jack Kerouac]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2008 23:16:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Robert Frost]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258-in-three-words-i-can-sum-up-everything-i-ve-learned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." -- Robert Frost]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2010 22:18:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/229-all-that-is-gold-does-not-glitter-not-all-those]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All that is gold does not glitter,
Not all those who wander are lost;
The old that is strong does not wither,
Deep roots are not reached by the frost.

From the ashes a fire shall be woken,
A light from the shadows shall spring;
Renewed shall be blade that was broken,
The crownless again shall be king." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 22:01:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by E.M. Forster]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102198-books-have-to-be-read-worse-luck-it-takes-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books have to be read (worse luck it takes so long a time). It is the only way of discovering what they contain. A few savage tribes eat them, but reading is the only method of assimilation revealed to the West." -- E.M. Forster]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 22:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/84171-critics-who-treat-adult-as-a-term-of-approval-instead]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Critics who treat 'adult' as a term of approval, instead of as a merely descriptive term, cannot be adult themselves. To be concerned about being grown up, to admire the grown up because it is grown up, to blush at the suspicion of being childish; these things are the marks of childhood and adolescence. And in childhood and adolescence they are, in moderation, healthy symptoms. Young things ought to want to grow. But to carry on into middle life or even into early manhood this concern about being adult is a mark of really arrested development. When I was ten, I read fairy tales in secret and would have been ashamed if I had been found doing so. Now that I am fifty I read them openly. When I became a man I put away childish things, including the fear of childishness and the desire to be very grown up." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147879-it-is-not-unknown-for-fathers-with-a-brace-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 16:59:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/147879-it-is-not-unknown-for-fathers-with-a-brace-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not unknown for fathers with a brace of daughters to reel off their names in order of birth when summoning the youngest, and I had long ago become accustomed to being called 'Ophelia Daphne Flavia, damn it." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242384-if-there-is-a-thing-i-truly-despise-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 17:00:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Alan Bradley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242384-if-there-is-a-thing-i-truly-despise-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is a thing I truly despise, it is being addressed as &quot;dearie.&quot; When I write my magnum opus, A Treatise Upon All Poison, and come to &quot;Cyanide,&quot; I am going to put under &quot;Uses&quot; the phrase &quot;Particularly efficacious in the cure of those who call one 'Dearie." -- Alan Bradley]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
