<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/978679-janice]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/978679-janice" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 13:10:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100515-freedom-is-not-in-doing-what-you-want-to-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2008 13:10:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Ardis whitman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100515-freedom-is-not-in-doing-what-you-want-to-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freedom is not in doing what you want to do, but in becoming what you want to be." -- Ardis whitman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 11:58:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70759-you-will-lose-someone-you-can-t-live-without-and-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You will lose someone you can’t live without,and your heart will be badly broken, and the bad news is that you never completely get over the loss of your beloved. But this is also the good news. They live forever in your broken heart that doesn’t seal back up. And you come through. It’s like having a broken leg that never heals perfectly—that still hurts when the weather gets cold, but you learn to dance with the limp." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41944-no-one-ever-told-me-that-grief-felt-so-like</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 11:59:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41944-no-one-ever-told-me-that-grief-felt-so-like]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No one ever told me that grief felt so like fear." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27470-and-now-these-three-remain-faith-hope-and-love-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Anonymous]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27470-and-now-these-three-remain-faith-hope-and-love-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And now these three remain: faith, hope and love. But the greatest of these is love." -- Anonymous]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:01:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6635-the-world-is-indeed-full-of-peril-and-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The world is indeed full of peril, and in it there are many dark places; but still there is much that is fair, and though in all lands love is now mingled with grief, it grows perhaps the greater." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121683-there-is-some-good-in-this-world-and-it-s-worth</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 12:03:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/121683-there-is-some-good-in-this-world-and-it-s-worth]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is some good in this world, and it's worth fighting for." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338860-i-am-not-a-genius-i-am-just-curious-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 15:02:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/338860-i-am-not-a-genius-i-am-just-curious-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am not a genius, I am just curious. I ask many questions. and when the answer is simple, then God is answering." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518093-i-have-nearly-finished-the-morte-d-arthur-the-book-itself</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 09:02:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/518093-i-have-nearly-finished-the-morte-d-arthur-the-book-itself]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have nearly finished 'The Morte D'Arthur'. ...The book itself is a glorious feast: I don't know how to explain its particular charm, because it is not like anything I ever read before: and yet in places like all of them... I am just longing for Saturday when I can plunge into it again." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398383-if-one-has-to-choose-between-reading-the-new-books</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2013 09:02:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/398383-if-one-has-to-choose-between-reading-the-new-books]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If one has to choose between reading the new books and reading the old, one must choose the old: not because they are necessarily better but because they contain precisely those truths of which our own age is neglectful." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73288-progress-means-getting-nearer-to-the-place-you-want-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 16:11:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73288-progress-means-getting-nearer-to-the-place-you-want-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Progress means getting nearer to the place you want to be. And if you have taken a wrong turning, then to go forward does not get you any nearer.
If you are on the wrong road, progress means doing an about-turn and walking back to the right road; and in that case the man who turns back soonest is the most progressive man." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641367-it-is-a-great-thing-to-start-life-with-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 12:07:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/641367-it-is-a-great-thing-to-start-life-with-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a great thing to start life with a small number of really good books which are your very own. You may not appreciate them at first. You may pine for your novel of crude and unadulterated adventure. You may, and will, give it the preference when you can. But the dull days come, and the rainy days come, and always you are driven to fill up the chinks of your reading with the worthy books which wait so patiently for your notice. And then suddenly, on a day which marks an epoch in your life, you understand the difference. You see, like a flash, how the one stands for nothing, and the other for literature. From that day onwards you may return to your crudities, but at least you do so with some standard of comparison in your mind. You can never be the same as you were before. Then gradually the good thing becomes more dear to you; it builds itself up with your growing mind; it becomes a part of your better self, and so, at last, you can look, as I do now, at the old covers and love them for all that they have meant in the past." -- Arthur Conan Doyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549062-upon-the-publication-of-goethe-s-epic-drama-the-faustian-legend</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 14:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by E.A. Bucchianeri]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/549062-upon-the-publication-of-goethe-s-epic-drama-the-faustian-legend]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Upon the publication of Goethe’s epic drama, the Faustian legend had reached an almost unapproachable zenith.  Although many failed to appreciate, or indeed, to understand this magnum opus in its entirety, from this point onward his drama was the rule by which all other Faust adaptations were measured.  Goethe had eclipsed the earlier legends and became the undisputed authority on the subject of Faust in the eyes of the new Romantic generation.  To deviate from his path would be nothing short of blasphemy." -- E.A. Bucchianeri]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11087-books-are-the-carriers-of-civilization-without-books-history-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 13:32:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Barbara Tuchman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11087-books-are-the-carriers-of-civilization-without-books-history-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the carriers of civilization. Without books, history is silent, literature dumb, science crippled, thought and speculation at a standstill.  Without books, the development of civilization would have been impossible.  They are engines of change (as the poet said), windows on the world and lighthouses erected in the sea of time.  They are companions, teachers, magicians, bankers of the treasures of the mind. Books are humanity in print.

[&lt;i&gt;Bulletin of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences&lt;/i&gt;, Vol. 34, No. 2 (Nov. 1980), pp. 16-32]" -- Barbara Tuchman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295147-the-books-transported-her-into-new-worlds-and-introduced-her</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2013 13:33:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Roald Dahl]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/295147-the-books-transported-her-into-new-worlds-and-introduced-her]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The books transported her into new worlds and introduced her to amazing people who lived exciting lives. She went on olden-day sailing ships with Joseph Conrad. She went to Africa with Ernest Hemingway and to India with Rudyard Kipling. She travelled all over the world while sitting in her little room in an English village." -- Roald Dahl]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/812883-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy-ending</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 13:55:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/812883-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy-ending]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The consolation of fairy-stories, the joy of the happy ending: or more correctly of the good catastrophe, the sudden joyous “turn” (for there is no true end to any fairy-tale): this joy, which is one of the things which fairy-stories can produce supremely well, is not essentially “escapist,” nor “fugitive.” In its fairy-tale--or otherworld--setting, it is a sudden and miraculous grace: never to be counted on to recur. It does not deny the existence of dyscatastrophe, of sorrow and failure: the possibility of these is necessary to the joy of deliverance; it denies (in the face of much evidence, if you will) universal final defeat and in so far is evangelium, giving a fleeting glimpse of Joy, Joy beyond the walls of the world, poignant as grief.

It is the mark of a good fairy-story, of the higher or more complete kind, that however wild its events, however fantastic or terrible the adventures, it can give to child or man that hears it, when the “turn” comes, a catch of the breath, a beat and lifting of the heart, near to (or indeed accompanied by) tears, as keen as that given by any form of literary art, and having a peculiar quality ... In such stories when the sudden “turn” comes we get a piercing glimpse of joy, and heart's desire, that for a moment passes outside the frame, rends indeed the very web of story, and lets a gleam come through." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7521-hope-is-a-good-breakfast-but-it-is-a-bad</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 09:49:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by Francis Bacon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7521-hope-is-a-good-breakfast-but-it-is-a-bad]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope is a good breakfast, but it is a bad supper." -- Francis Bacon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102964-turn-our-thoughts-in-the-next-place-to-the-characters</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 09:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/102964-turn-our-thoughts-in-the-next-place-to-the-characters]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...Turn our thoughts, in the next place, to the characters of learned men. The priesthood have, in all ancient nations, nearly monopolized learning. Read over again all the accounts we have of Hindoos, Chaldeans, Persians, Greeks, Romans, Celts, Teutons, we shall find that priests had all the knowledge, and really governed all mankind. Examine Mahometanism, trace Christianity from its first promulgation; knowledge has been almost exclusively confined to the clergy. And, even since the Reformation, when or where has existed a Protestant or dissenting sect who would tolerate a free inquiry? The blackest billingsgate, the most ungentlemanly insolence, the most yahooish brutality is patiently endured, countenanced, propagated, and applauded. But touch a solemn truth in collision with a dogma of a sect, though capable of the clearest proof, and you will soon find you have disturbed a nest, and the hornets will swarm about your legs and hands, and fly into your face and eyes.

[&lt;i&gt;Letters to John Taylor, 1814, XVIII, p. 484&lt;/i&gt;]" -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43949-the-longer-i-live-the-more-i-read-the-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 09:00:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Janice add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43949-the-longer-i-live-the-more-i-read-the-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The longer I live, the more I read, the more patiently I think, and the more anxiously I inquire, the less I seem to know...Do justly. Love mercy. Walk humbly. This is enough." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
