<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/978931-kristin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/978931-kristin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:04:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21553-i-never-asked-tolstoy-to-write-for-me-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 10:04:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21553-i-never-asked-tolstoy-to-write-for-me-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I never asked Tolstoy to write for me, a little colored girl in Lorain, Ohio. I never asked [James] Joyce not to mention Catholicism or the world of Dublin. Never. And I don't know why I should be asked to explain your life to you. We have splendid writers to do that, but I am not one of them. It is that business of being universal, a word hopelessly stripped of meaning for me.  Faulkner wrote what I suppose could be called regional literature and had it published all over the world. That's what I wish to do. If I tried to write a universal novel, it would be water. Behind this question is the suggestion that to write for black people is somehow to diminish the writing. From my perspective there are only black people. When I say 'people,' that's what I mean." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24210-i-believe-that-there-is-one-story-in-the-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24210-i-believe-that-there-is-one-story-in-the-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that there is one story in the world, and only one. . . . Humans are caught—in their lives, in their thoughts, in their hungers and ambitions, in their avarice and cruelty, and in their kindness and generosity too—in a net of good and evil. . . . There is no other story. A man, after he has brushed off the dust and chips of his life, will have left only the hard, clean questions: Was it good or was it evil? Have I done well—or ill?" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:25:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15417-when-a-child-first-catches-adults-out----when-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a child first catches adults out -- when it first walks into his grave little head that adults do not always have divine intelligence, that their judgments are not always wise, their thinking true, their sentences just -- his world falls into panic desolation. The gods are fallen and all safety gone. And there is one sure thing about the fall of gods: they do not fall a little; they crash and shatter or sink deeply into green muck. It is a tedious job to build them up again; they never quite shine. And the child's world is never quite whole again. It is an aching kind of growing." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22818-literature-was-not-promulgated-by-a-pale-and-emasculated-critical</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:26:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22818-literature-was-not-promulgated-by-a-pale-and-emasculated-critical]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature was not promulgated by a pale and emasculated critical priesthood singing their litanies in empty churches - nor is it a game for the cloistered elect, the tinhorn mendicants of low calorie despair.

Literature is as old as speech. It grew out of human need for it, and it has not changed except to become more needed.

The skalds, the bards, the writers are not separate and exclusive. From the beginning, their functions, their duties, their responsibilities have been decreed by our species.

--speech at the Nobel Banquet at the City Hall in Stockholm, December 10, 1962" -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/647-stuff-your-eyes-with-wonder-he-said-live-as-if</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/647-stuff-your-eyes-with-wonder-he-said-live-as-if]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stuff your eyes with wonder, he said, live as if you'd drop dead in ten seconds. See the world. It's more fantastic than any dream made or paid for in factories." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4567-the-books-are-to-remind-us-what-asses-and-fool</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:27:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4567-the-books-are-to-remind-us-what-asses-and-fool]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The books are to remind us what asses and fool we are. They're Caeser's praetorian guard, whispering as the parade roars down the avenue, &quot;Remember, Caeser, thou art mortal.&quot; Most of us can't rush around, talking to everyone, know all the cities of the world, we haven't time, money or that many friends. The things you're looking for, Montag, are in the world, but the only way the average chap will ever see ninety-nine per cent of them is in a book. Don't ask for guarantees. And don't look to be saved in any one thing, person, machine, or library. Do your own bit of saving, and if you drown, at least die knowing you were headed for shore." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:29:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11241-everyone-must-leave-something-behind-when-he-dies-my-grandfather]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone must leave something behind when he dies, my grandfather said. A child or a book or a painting or a house or a wall built or a pair of shoes made. Or a garden planted. Something your hand touched some way so your soul has somewhere to go when you die, and when people look at that tree or that flower you planted, you're there. 

It doesn't matter what you do, he said, so long as you change something from the way it was before you touched it into something that's like you after you take your hands away. The difference between the man who just cuts lawns and a real gardener is in the touching, he said. The lawn-cutter might just as well not have been there at all; the gardener will be there a lifetime." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:31:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ray Bradbury]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32374-and-when-he-died-i-suddenly-realized-i-wasn-t-crying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And when he died, I suddenly realized I wasn’t crying for him at all, but for the things he did. I cried because he would never do them again, he would never carve another piece of wood or help us raise doves and pigeons in the backyard or play the violin the way he did, or tell us jokes the way he did. He was part of us and when he died, all the actions stopped dead and there was no one to do them the way he did. He was individual. He was an important man. I’ve never gotten over his death. Often I think what wonderful carvings never came to birth because he died. How many jokes are missing from the world, and how many homing pigeons untouched by his hands? He shaped the world. He did things to the world. The world was bankrupted of ten million fine actions the night he passed on." -- Ray Bradbury]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18255-if-only-my-mother-had-a-book-to-hold-she</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:32:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Brock Clarke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18255-if-only-my-mother-had-a-book-to-hold-she]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If only my mother had a book to hold, she wouldn't have looked so lonely. And maybe this was another reason why people read: not so they would feel less lonely, but so that other people would think they looked less lonely with a book in their hands and therefore not pity them and leave them alone." -- Brock Clarke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2008 13:34:14 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1668-there-is-neither-happiness-nor-misery-in-the-world-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is neither happiness nor misery in the world; there is only the comparison of one state with another, nothing more. He who has felt the deepest grief is best able to experience supreme happiness. We must have felt what it is to die, Morrel, that we may appreciate the enjoyments of life. 
&quot; Live, then, and be happy, beloved children of my heart, and never forget, that until the day God will deign to reveal the future to man, all human wisdom is contained in these two words, 'Wait and Hope." -- Alexandre Dumas]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4740-memory-believes-before-knowing-remembers-believes-longer-than-recollects-longer</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:34:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4740-memory-believes-before-knowing-remembers-believes-longer-than-recollects-longer]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Memory believes before knowing remembers. Believes longer than recollects, longer than knowing even wonders." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16744-there-is-no-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:34:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16744-there-is-no-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no was." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18782-most-men-are-a-little-better-than-their-circumstances-give</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:35:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18782-most-men-are-a-little-better-than-their-circumstances-give]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most men are a little better than their circumstances give them a chance to be." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29324-wonder-go-on-and-wonder</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:35:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/29324-wonder-go-on-and-wonder]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wonder.  Go on and wonder." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:36:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3414-sometimes-i-can-hear-my-bones-straining-under-the-weight]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes I can hear my bones straining under the weight of all the lives I'm not living." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:36:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7692-if-there-is-no-love-in-the-world-we-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there is no love in the world, we will make a new world, and we will give it walls, and we will furnish it with soft, red interiors, from the inside out, and give it a knocker that resonates like a diamond falling to a jeweller's felt so that we should never hear it. Love me, because love doesn't exist, and I have tried everything that does." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:36:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9831-i-m-sorry-for-my-inability-to-let-unimportant-things-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I'm sorry for my inability to let unimportant things go, for my inability to hold on to the important things." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1676-what-about-a-teakettle-what-if-the-spout-opened-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:37:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1676-what-about-a-teakettle-what-if-the-spout-opened-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about a teakettle? What if the spout opened and closed when the steam came out, so it would become a mouth, and it could whistle pretty melodies, or do Shakespeare, or just
crack up with me? I could invent a teakettle that reads in Dad’s voice, so I could fall asleep, or maybe a set of kettles that sings the chorus of “Yellow Submarine,” which is a song by the Beatles, who I love, because entomology is one of my raisons d’être, which 
is a French expression that I know. Another good thing is that I could train my anus to talk when I farted. If I wanted to be extremely hilarious, I’d train it to say, “Wasn’t me!” every time I made an incredibly bad fart. And if I ever made an incredibly bad fart in the Hall of Mirrors, which is in Versailles, which is outside of Paris, which is in France, obviously, my anus would say, “Ce n’étais pas moi!”
What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboard down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16993-i-will-describe-my-eyes-and-then-begin-the-story</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:38:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16993-i-will-describe-my-eyes-and-then-begin-the-story]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will describe my eyes and then begin the story. My eyes are blue and resplendent. Now I will begin the story." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2477-sadness-of-love-without-release</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:38:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2477-sadness-of-love-without-release]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sadness of love without release." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28122-what-if-i-never-stop-inventing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:40:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28122-what-if-i-never-stop-inventing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What if I never stop inventing?" -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27667-do-i-love-you-my-god-if-your-love-were</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:42:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by William Goldman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27667-do-i-love-you-my-god-if-your-love-were]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do I love you? My God, if your love were a grain of sand, mine would be a universe of beaches." -- William Goldman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1730-always-do-sober-what-you-said-you-d-do-drunk-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:42:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1730-always-do-sober-what-you-said-you-d-do-drunk-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Always do sober what you said you'd do drunk. That will teach you to keep your mouth shut." -- Ernest Hemingway ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:42:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3273-if-people-bring-so-much-courage-to-this-world-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If people bring so much courage to this world the world has to kill them to break them, so of course it kills them. The world breaks every one and afterward many are strong at the broken places. But those that will not break it kills. It kills the very good and the very gentle and the very brave impartially. If you are none of these you can be sure it will kill you too but there will be no special hurry." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26751-i-had-gone-to-no-such-place-but-to-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:44:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26751-i-had-gone-to-no-such-place-but-to-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had gone to no such place but to the smoke of cafes and nights when the room whirled and you needed to look at the wall to make it stop, nights in bed, drunk, when you knew that that was all there was, and the strange excitement of waking and not knowing who it was with you, and the world all unreal in the dark and so exciting that you must resume again unknowing and not caring in the night, sure that this was all and all and all and not caring." -- Ernest Hemingway]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3989-the-more-clearly-one-sees-this-world-the-more-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:46:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3989-the-more-clearly-one-sees-this-world-the-more-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The more clearly one sees this world; the more one is obliged to pretend it does not exist." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7526-a-woman-half-dressed-seemed-to-have-some-power-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:46:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7526-a-woman-half-dressed-seemed-to-have-some-power-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman half dressed seemed to have some power, but a man was simply not as handsome as when he was naked, and not as secure as when he was clothed." -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32128-the-history-of-a-city-was-like-the-history-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:47:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by John Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32128-the-history-of-a-city-was-like-the-history-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The history of a city was like the history of a family—there is closeness and even affection, but death eventually separates everyone from each other.  It is only the vividness of memory that keeps the dead alive forever; a writer’s job is to imagine everything so personally that the fiction is as vivid as our personal memories.  " -- John Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44057-there-is-a-sacredness-in-tears-they-are-not-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Washington Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44057-there-is-a-sacredness-in-tears-they-are-not-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a sacredness in tears. They are not a mark of weakness, but of power. They speak more eloquently than ten thousand tongues. They are the messengers of overwhelming grief, of deep contrition and of unspeakable love." -- Washington Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28138-there-is-a-certain-relief-in-change-even-though-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2008 09:49:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Kristin add a quote by Washington Irving]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28138-there-is-a-certain-relief-in-change-even-though-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a certain relief in change, even though it be from bad to worse; as I have found in traveling in a stage coach, that it is often a comfort to shift one's position and be bruised in a new place." -- Washington Irving]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
