<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979086-john-holliday]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979086-john-holliday" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 23:58:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55512-i-believe-that-the-universe-was-formed-around-15-billion</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2008 23:58:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[John add a quote by Ronald P. Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55512-i-believe-that-the-universe-was-formed-around-15-billion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that the universe was formed around 15 billion years ago and that humans have evolved from their apelike ancestors over the past few million years.  I believe we are more likely to live a good life if all humans try to work together in a world community, preserving planet earth.  When decisions for groups are made in this world, I believe that the democratic process should be used.  To protect the individual, I believe in freedom of speech, freedom of the press, freedom of religion, freedom from religion, freedom of inquiry, and a wall of separation between church and state.  When making decisions about what is right or wrong, I believe I should use my intelligence to reason about the likely consequences of my actions.  I believe that I should try to increase the happiness of everyone by caring for other people and finding ways to cooperate.  Never should my actions discriminate against people simply because of their race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, age, or national origin.  I believe that ideas about what is right and wrong will change with education, so I am prepared to continually question ideas using evidence from experience and science.  I believe there is no valid evidence to support claims for the existence of supernatural entities and deities.  I will use these beliefs to guide my thinking and my actions until I find good reasons for revising them or replacing them with other beliefs that are more valid." -- Ronald P. Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
