<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979231-matthew]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979231-matthew" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:23:18 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221840-a-democracy-is-accounted-the-meanest-and-worst-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:23:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by John Winthrop]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221840-a-democracy-is-accounted-the-meanest-and-worst-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A democracy is ... accounted the meanest and worst of all forms of government." -- John Winthrop]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221841-democracy-is-the-most-vile-form-of-government</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:24:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by James Madison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221841-democracy-is-the-most-vile-form-of-government]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Democracy is the most vile form of government." -- James Madison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:25:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by John Adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/49810-i-do-not-say-that-democracy-has-been-more-pernicious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not say that democracy has been more pernicious on the whole, and in the long run, than monarchy or aristocracy. Democracy has never been and never can be so durable as aristocracy or monarchy; but while it lasts, it is more bloody than either. … Remember, democracy never lasts long. It soon wastes, exhausts, and murders itself. There never was a democracy yet that did not commit suicide. It is in vain to say that democracy is less vain, less proud, less selfish, less ambitious, or less avaricious than aristocracy or monarchy. It is not true, in fact, and nowhere appears in history. Those passions are the same in all men, under all forms of simple government, and when unchecked, produce the same effects of fraud, violence, and cruelty. When clear prospects are opened before vanity, pride, avarice, or ambition, for their easy gratification, it is hard for the most considerate philosophers and the most conscientious moralists to resist the temptation. Individuals have conquered themselves. Nations and large bodies of men, never." -- John Adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88664-when-the-people-find-that-they-can-vote-themselves-money</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:26:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/88664-when-the-people-find-that-they-can-vote-themselves-money]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the people find that they can vote themselves money  that will herald the end of the republic." -- Benjamin Franklin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221846-when-action-is-divorced-from-consequences-no-one-is-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:27:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by John Stossel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/221846-when-action-is-divorced-from-consequences-no-one-is-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When action is divorced from consequences, no one is happy with the ultimate outcome. If individuals can take from a common pot regardless of how much they put in it, each person has an incentive to be a free rider, to do as little as possible and take as much as possible because what one fails to take will be taken by someone else. Soon, the pot is empty and will not be refilled -- a bad situation even for the earlier takers." -- John Stossel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33210-a-nation-can-survive-its-fools-and-even-the-ambitious</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2010 13:28:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matthew add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33210-a-nation-can-survive-its-fools-and-even-the-ambitious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot survive treason from within. An enemy at the gates is less formidable, for he is known and carries his banner openly. But the traitor moves amongst those within the gate freely, his sly whispers rustling through all the alleys, heard in the very halls of government itself. For the traitor appears not a traitor; he speaks in accents familiar to his victims, and he wears their face and their arguments, he appeals to the baseness that lies deep in the hearts of all men. He rots the soul of a nation, he works secretly and unknown in the night to undermine the pillars of the city, he infects the body politic so that it can no longer resist. A murderer is less to fear." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero ]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
