<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979520-douglas]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/979520-douglas" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 18:01:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26449-experience-should-teach-us-to-be-most-on-our-guard</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 18:01:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Louis D. Brandeis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26449-experience-should-teach-us-to-be-most-on-our-guard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Experience should teach us to be most on our guard to protect liberty when the government's purposes are beneficent.  Men born to freedom are naturally alert to repel invasion of their liberty by evil-minded rulers.  The greatest dangers to liberty lurk in insidious encroachment by men of zeal, well-meaning but without understanding.&quot;

[&lt;i&gt;Olmstead v. U.S.&lt;/i&gt;, 277 U.S. 438 (1928) (dissenting)]" -- Louis D. Brandeis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242793-it-must-not-be-forgotten-that-it-is-especially-dangerous</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 18:06:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242793-it-must-not-be-forgotten-that-it-is-especially-dangerous]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It must not be forgotten that it is especially dangerous to enslave men in the minor details of life. For my part, I should be inclined to think freedom
less necessary in the great things than in the little ones, if it were possible to be secure of the one without the other." -- Alexis de Tocqueville]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242795-equality-has-a-built-in-revolutionary-force-lacking-in-such-ideas</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 18:56:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Robert Nisbet]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242795-equality-has-a-built-in-revolutionary-force-lacking-in-such-ideas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Equality has a built-in revolutionary force lacking in such ideas as justice or liberty. For once the ideal of equality becomes uppermost, it can become insatiable in its demands.
It is possible to conceive of human beings conceding that they have enough freedom or justice in a social order; it is not possible to imagine them ever declaring they have enough equality-once, that is, equality becomes a cornerstone of national policy. In this respect it resembles some of the religious ideals or passions that offer, just by virtue of the impossibility of ever giving them adequate representation in the actual world, almost unlimited potentialities for continuous onslaught against institutions." -- Robert Nisbet]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241736-as-part-of-moral-philosophy-the-concept-of-natural-liberty</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 06:35:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by John Chamberlain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/241736-as-part-of-moral-philosophy-the-concept-of-natural-liberty]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As part of &quot;moral philosophy,&quot; the concept of &quot;natural liberty&quot; clicks easily into place. Man, as an ethical integer, is either free to choose between good and bad courses within the
limits of his circumstances, or he is not. If he is not free, if he can
only accept what is handed to him from above (by fate, or by decree of the human agents of fate), then there is not much use in talking about morality or ethics. To make any sense of the idea
of morality, it must be presumed that the human being is responsible for his actions-and responsibility cannot be understood apart from the presumption of freedom of choice." -- John Chamberlain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240816-because-in-lenin-s-eyes-the-workers-were-only-workers-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 20:36:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Ludwig Von Mises]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/240816-because-in-lenin-s-eyes-the-workers-were-only-workers-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Because in [Lenin's] eyes the workers
were only workers and not also customers, he believed they were already slaves under capitalism, and that one did not change their status
when nationalizing all plants and shops.
Socialism substitutes the sovereignty of a dictator, or committee of dictators, for the sovereignty of the consumers. Along with the economic sovereignty of the citizens disappears also their political sovereignty. To the unique production plan that annuls any planning on the part of the consumers corresponds in the constitutional sphere the one party principle that deprives the citizens of any opportunity to plan the course of public affairs. Freedom is indivisible. He who has not the faculty to choose among various brands of canned food or soap, is also deprived of the power to
choose between various political  parties and programs and to elect the officeholders. He is no longer a man; he becomes a pawn in the hands of the supreme social engineer. Even his freedom to rear progeny will be taken
away by eugenics." -- Ludwig Von Mises]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33201-name-me-a-leader-who-has-a-better-idea-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:09:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Lee Iacocca]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33201-name-me-a-leader-who-has-a-better-idea-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Name me a leader who has a better idea for homeland security than making us take off our shoes in airports and throw away our shampoo?

" -- Lee Iacocca]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33202-i-do-not-know-any-moral-to-be-deduced-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:10:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by William Hazlitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33202-i-do-not-know-any-moral-to-be-deduced-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do not know any moral to be deduced from this view of the subject [of personal character], but one, namely, that we should mind our own business, cultivate our good qualities, if we have any, and irritate ourselves less about the absurdities of other people, which neither we nor they can help. I grant there is something in which I have said which I might be made to glance towards the doctrine of original sin, grace, election, reprobation, or the Gnostic Principle that acts did not determine the virtue or vice of the character; and in those doctrines, so far as they are deducible from what I have said, I agree -- but always with a salvo." -- William Hazlitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33203-americans-know-instinctively-that-when-they-see-lines-of-americans</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:13:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Jeffrey Lord]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33203-americans-know-instinctively-that-when-they-see-lines-of-americans]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Americans] know instinctively that when they see lines of Americans whose travel plans have been screwed up because they can't get a U.S. passport to travel to Mexico or Canada, when they realize 3 of the Fort Dix plotters were not only illegal aliens but were stopped 75 times (!!!) by various police authorities and never once had their status questioned, the very notion that a Washingtonized-immigration bill is going to &quot;solve the problem&quot; of immigration is hilarious nonsense." -- Jeffrey Lord]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33204-i-have-known-numbers-of-bourgeois-socialists-i-have-listened</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:14:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33204-i-have-known-numbers-of-bourgeois-socialists-i-have-listened]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have known numbers of bourgeois Socialists. I have listened by the hour to their tirades against their own class, and yet never, not even once, have I met one who had picked up proletarian table manners. Yet after all why not? Why should a man who thinks all virtue resides in the proletariat still take such pains to drink his soup silently? It can only be because in his heart he feels that proletarian manners are disgusting." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33205-on-the-other-hand-i-am-not-a-liberal-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:15:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Norman Mailer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33205-on-the-other-hand-i-am-not-a-liberal-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the other hand, I am not a liberal. The notion that man is a rational creature who arrives at reasonable solutions to knotty problems is much in doubt as far as I’m concerned. Liberalism depends all too much on having an optimistic view of human nature. But the history of the 20th century has not exactly fortified that notion. Moreover, liberalism also depends too much upon reason rather than any appreciation of mystery. If you start to talk about God with the average good liberal, he looks at you as if you are more than a little off. In that sense, since I happen to be—I hate to use the word religious, there are so many heavy dull connotations, so many pious self-seeking aspects—but I do believe there is a Creator who is active in human affairs and is endangered. I also believe there is a Devil who is equally active in our existence (and is all too often successful). So, I can hardly be a liberal. God is bad enough for them, but talk about the devil, and the liberal’s mind is blown. He is consorting with a fellow who is irrational if not insane. That is the end of real conversation." -- Norman Mailer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33207-if-you-robert-oppenheimer-intend-to-mount-heavy-mathematical-artillery</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:19:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Paul Ehrenfest]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33207-if-you-robert-oppenheimer-intend-to-mount-heavy-mathematical-artillery]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you [Robert Oppenheimer] intend to mount heavy mathematical artillery again during your coming year in Europe, I would ask you not only not to come to Leiden, but if possible not even to Holland, and just because I am really so fond of you and want to keep it that way. But if, on the contrary, you want to spend at least your first few months patiently, comfortably, and joyfully in discussions that keep coming back to the same few points, chatting about a few basic questions with me and our young people- and without thinking much about publishing (!!!)-why then I welcome you with open arms!!" -- Paul Ehrenfest]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33208-it-has-been-said-that-given-two-bettors-there-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:21:20 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Emile Borel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33208-it-has-been-said-that-given-two-bettors-there-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It has been said that, given two bettors, there is always one thief and one imbecile; that is true in certain cases when one of the two bettors is much better informed than the other, and knows it; but it can easily happen that two men of good faith, in complex matters where they possess exactly the same elements of information, arrive at different conclusions on the probabilities of an event, and that in betting together, each believes…that it is he who is the thief and the other the imbecile." -- Emile Borel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33210-a-nation-can-survive-its-fools-and-even-the-ambitious</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:25:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Marcus Tullius Cicero ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33210-a-nation-can-survive-its-fools-and-even-the-ambitious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A nation can survive its fools, and even the ambitious. But it cannot survive treason from within. An enemy at the gates is less formidable, for he is known and carries his banner openly. But the traitor moves amongst those within the gate freely, his sly whispers rustling through all the alleys, heard in the very halls of government itself. For the traitor appears not a traitor; he speaks in accents familiar to his victims, and he wears their face and their arguments, he appeals to the baseness that lies deep in the hearts of all men. He rots the soul of a nation, he works secretly and unknown in the night to undermine the pillars of the city, he infects the body politic so that it can no longer resist. A murderer is less to fear." -- Marcus Tullius Cicero ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33211-in-a-much-quoted-passage-in-his-inaugural-address-president</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:27:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Milton Friedman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33211-in-a-much-quoted-passage-in-his-inaugural-address-president]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In a much quoted passage in his inaugural address, President Kennedy said, &quot;Ask not what your country can do for you -- ask what you can do for your country.&quot; It is a striking sign of the temper of our times that the controversy about this passage centered on its origin and not on its content. Neither half of the statement expresses a relation between the citizen and his government that is worthy of the ideals of free men in a free society. The paternalistic &quot;what your country can do for you&quot; implies that government is the patron, the citizen the ward, a view that is at odds with the free man's belief in his own responsibility for his own destiny. The organismic, &quot;what you can do for your country&quot; implies that government is the master or the deity, the citizen, the servant or the votary. To the free man, the country is the collection of individuals who compose it, not something over and above them. He is proud of a common heritage and loyal to common traditions. But he regards government as a means, an instrumentality, neither a grantor of favors and gifts, nor a master or god to be blindly worshiped and served. He recognizes no national goal except as it is the consensus of the goals that the citizens severally serve. He recognizes no national purpose except as it is the consensus of the purposes for which the citizens severally strive." -- Milton Friedman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8029-a-good-many-times-i-have-been-present-at-gatherings</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by C.P. Snow]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8029-a-good-many-times-i-have-been-present-at-gatherings]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A good many times I have been present at gatherings of people who, by the standards of the traditional culture, are thought highly educated and who have with considerable gusto been expressing their incredulity of scientists. Once or twice I have been provoked and have asked the company how many of them could describe the Second Law of Thermodynamics. The response was cold: it was also negative. Yet I was asking something which is the scientific equivalent of: Have you read a work of Shakespeare's?
I now believe that if I had asked an even simpler question -- such as, What do you mean by mass, or acceleration, which is the scientific equivalent of saying, Can you read? -- not more than one in ten of the highly educated would have felt that I was speaking the same language. So the great edifice of modern physics goes up, and the majority of the cleverest people in the western world have about as much insight into it as their neolithic ancestors would have had." -- C.P. Snow]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33213-in-dictatorships-you-need-courage-to-fight-evil-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:31:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Nathan Sharansky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33213-in-dictatorships-you-need-courage-to-fight-evil-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In dictatorships you need courage to fight evil; in the free world you need courage to see evil." -- Nathan Sharansky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33214-the-rescue-of-drowning-men-is-a-duty-worth-dying</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:32:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by C. S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33214-the-rescue-of-drowning-men-is-a-duty-worth-dying]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The rescue of drowning men is… a duty worth dying for, but not worth living for. It seems to me that all political duties (among which I include military duties) are of this kind. A man may have to die for our country, but no man must, in an exclusive sense, live for his country." -- C. S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33215-you-ll-find-that-marriage-is-a-good-short-cut-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:34:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Kingsley Amis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33215-you-ll-find-that-marriage-is-a-good-short-cut-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You'll find that marriage is a good short cut to the truth. No, not quite that. A way of doubling back to the truth. Another thing you'll find is that the years of illusion aren't those of adolescence, as the grown-ups try to tell us; they're the ones immediately after it, say the middle twenties, the false maturity if you like, when you first get thoroughly embroiled in things and lose your head. Your age, by the way, Jim. That's when you first realize that sex is important to other people besides yourself. A discovery like that can't help knocking you off balance for a time." -- Kingsley Amis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33217-politicians-should-be-changed-regularly-like-diapers-and-for-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:36:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Richard Davies]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33217-politicians-should-be-changed-regularly-like-diapers-and-for-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Politicians should be changed regularly, like diapers, and for the same reason." -- Richard Davies]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33220-i-watched-with-incredulity-as-businessmen-ran-to-the-government</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2008 06:51:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by William E. Simon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33220-i-watched-with-incredulity-as-businessmen-ran-to-the-government]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I watched with incredulity as businessmen ran to the government in every crisis, whining for handouts or protection from the very competition that has made this system so productive.  I saw Texas ranchers, hit by drought, demanding government-guaranteed loans; giant milk cooperatives lobbying for higher price supports; major airlines fighting deregulation to preserve their monopoly status; giant companies like Lockheed seeking federal assistance to rescue them from sheer inefficiency; bankers, like David Rockefeller, demanding government bailouts to protect them from their ill-conceived investments; network executives, like William Paley of CBS, fighting to preserve regulatory restrictions and to block the emergence of competitive cable and pay TV.  And always, such gentlemen proclaimed their devotion to free enterprise and their opposition to the arbitrary intervention into our economic life by the state.  Except, of course, for their own case, which was always unique and which was justified by their immense concern for the public interest." -- William E. Simon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41111-where-recyling-takes-place-only-in-response-to-political-pressures</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 06:36:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Thomas Sowell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41111-where-recyling-takes-place-only-in-response-to-political-pressures]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Where recyling takes place only in response to political pressures and exhortations, it need not meet the test of being incrementally worth its incremental costs.  Accordingly, studies of government-imposed recycling programs in the United States have shown that what they salvage is usually worth less than the cost of salvaging it." -- Thomas Sowell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41117-they-intellectuals-coined-most-of-the-slogans-that-guided-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 06:51:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Ludwig Von Mises]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41117-they-intellectuals-coined-most-of-the-slogans-that-guided-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They [intellectuals] coined most of the slogans that guided the butcheries of Bolshevism, Fascism, and Nazism.  Intellectuals extolling the delights of murder, writers advocating censorship, philosophers judging the merits of thinkers and authors, not according to the value of their contributions but according to their achievements on battlefields, are the spiritual leaders of our age of perpetual strife." -- Ludwig Von Mises]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44901-no-weakness-of-the-human-mind-has-more-frequently-incurred</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2008 08:12:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Samuel Johnson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44901-no-weakness-of-the-human-mind-has-more-frequently-incurred]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No weakness of the human mind has more frequently incurred animadversion, than the negligence with which men overlook their own faults, however flagrant, and the easiness with which they pardon them, however frequently repeated." -- Samuel Johnson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45467-it-is-a-sound-interpretive-rule-that-anything-that-cannot-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 19:01:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Robert Higgs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45467-it-is-a-sound-interpretive-rule-that-anything-that-cannot-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a sound interpretive rule...that anything that cannot be accomplished except with the aid of threats or the actual exercise of violence against unoffending persons cannot be beneficial to one and all." -- Robert Higgs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45468-hope-is-one-of-the-theological-virtues-this-means-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 19:05:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45468-hope-is-one-of-the-theological-virtues-this-means-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hope is one of the Theological virtues.  This means that a continual looking forward to the eternal world is not (as some modern people think) a form of escapism or wishful thinking, but one of the things a Christian is meant to do.  It does not mean that we are to leave the present world as it is.  If you read history you will find that the Christians who did most for the present world were just those who thought most of the next." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45469-the-problem-for-free-market-economists-is-that-their-policy-recommendations</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2008 19:10:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Christopher Westley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45469-the-problem-for-free-market-economists-is-that-their-policy-recommendations]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The problem for free-market economists is that their policy recommendations at the dawn of a recession are not too sexy to the political mindset.  They involve either doing nothing to hinder price adjustments, or actively removing extra-market barriers to price adjustments.  This often involves short-term pain in exchange for long-term solutions, when politics rewards short-term solutions that result in long-term pain." -- Christopher Westley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56074-mr-langton-one-day-asked-him-samuel-johnson-how-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2008 10:03:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by James Boswell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56074-mr-langton-one-day-asked-him-samuel-johnson-how-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Mr. Langton one day asked him [Samuel Johnson] how he had acquired so accurate a knowledge of Latin, in which, I believe, he was exceeded by no man of his time; he said, 'My master whipt me very well. Without that, Sir, I should have done nothing.' He told Mr. Langton, that while Hunter was flogging his boys unmercifully, he used to say, 'And this I do to save you from the gallows.' Johnson, upon all occasions, expressed his approbation of enforcing instruction by means of the rod. 'I would rather (said he) have the rod to be the general terrour to all, to make them learn, than tell a child, if you do thus, or thus, you will be more esteemed than your brothers or sisters. The rod produces an effect which terminates in itself. A child is afraid of being whipped, and gets his task, and there's an end on't; whereas, by exciting emulation and comparisons of superiority, you lay the foundation of lasting mischief; you make brothers and sisters hate each other." -- James Boswell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58971-when-we-in-the-communist-countries-came-across-the-ideas</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 07:23:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Vaclav Klaus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58971-when-we-in-the-communist-countries-came-across-the-ideas]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we, in the communist countries, came across the ideas of Hayek and Aron, we had no problems to understand their importance. They gave us the much needed explanation of the somewhat peculiar prominence of intellectuals in our own society of that time. Our intellectuals, of course, did not like to hear it and did not want to recognize it because their peculiar prominence coexisted with the very debilitating absence of intellectual freedom, which the intellectuals value very highly." -- Vaclav Klaus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59028-you-say-there-are-persons-who-lack-education-and-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 10:48:45 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/59028-you-say-there-are-persons-who-lack-education-and-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You say: &quot;There are persons who lack education&quot; and you turn to the law.  But the law is not, in itself, a torch of learning which shines its light abroad.  The law extends over a society where some persons have knowledge and others do not; where some citizens need to learn, and others can teach.  In this matter of education, the law has only two alternatives: It can permit this transaction of teaching-and-learning to operate freely and without the use of force, or it can force human wills in  this matter by taking from some of them enough to pay the teachers who are appointed by government to instruct others, without charge.  But in the second case, the law commits legal plunder by violating liberty and property." -- Frederic Bastiat]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66125-in-politics-the-connection-between-what-you-pay-for-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2008 09:56:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Douglas add a quote by Lawrence W. Reed]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66125-in-politics-the-connection-between-what-you-pay-for-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In politics, the connection between what you pay for and what you actually get is problematic at best...
This is another way of asserting that your vote in the marketplace counts for so much more than your vote in the polling booth. Cast your dollars for the washing machine of your choice and that is what you get--nothing more and nothing less. Pull the lever for the politician of your choice and, most of the time (if you're lucky), you will get some of what you do want and much of what you don't. The votes of a special interest lobby may ultimately cancel out yours. As someone much wiser than me once said, &quot;[P]olitics may not be the oldest profession, but the results are often the same.&quot;

" -- Lawrence W. Reed]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
