<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980046-lindsay]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980046-lindsay" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 15:25:44 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33757-we-throw-ourselves-into-the-journey-and-when-it-s-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 15:25:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Aidan Hartley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33757-we-throw-ourselves-into-the-journey-and-when-it-s-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We throw ourselves into the journey and when it's done, even while having learned that all experience involves the loss of something beloved, what is ledt in the residue of memory is love." -- Aidan Hartley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33758-lizzie-and-i-arrived-in-the-polluted-heat-of-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 15:37:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Aidan Hartley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33758-lizzie-and-i-arrived-in-the-polluted-heat-of-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Lizzie and I arrived in the polluted heat of a London summer. We stood frozen at street corners as a blur of pedestrians burst out of the subways and spilled like ants down the pavements. The crowed bars, the expensive shops, the fashionable clothes - to me it all seemed a population rushing about to no avail...I stared at a huge poster of a woman in her underwear staring down at her own breasts. HELLO BOYS, she said. At the movies we witnessed sickening violence, except that this time we held tubs of popcorn between our legs and the gunfire and screams were broadcast in digital Dolby. We had escaped a skull on a battlefield, only to arrive in London, where office workers led lines of such tedium and plenty that they had to entertain themselves with all the f****** and killing on the big screen. So here then was the prosperous, democratic and civilized Western world. A place of washing machines, reality TV, Armani, frequent-flier miles, mortgages. And this is what the Africans are supposed to hope for, if they're lucky." -- Aidan Hartley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33760-re-entry-taught-me-a-new-sort-of-fear-that-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 15:41:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Aidan Hartley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33760-re-entry-taught-me-a-new-sort-of-fear-that-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Re-entry taught me a new sort of fear that was slow and dull rather than quick and thrilling...the hardest part of reentry to a humdrum life was not recovering from the bad stuff. It was missing the good times, the friendship, intensity, fear, sense of purpose, the sheer exotic escapism of it all." -- Aidan Hartley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33761-all-too-rarely-do-i-hear-people-asking-just-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 15:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Barack Obama]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33761-all-too-rarely-do-i-hear-people-asking-just-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All too rarely do I hear people asking just what it is that we've done to make so many children's hearts so hard, or what collectively we might do to right their moral compass - what values we must live by." -- Barack Obama]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33762-all-we-really-want-is-for-no-one-to-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:02:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33762-all-we-really-want-is-for-no-one-to-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All we really want is for no one to have a boring life, to be impressive, so we can be impressed. ~ on the friends we choose." -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33763-we-feel-that-to-reveal-embarrassing-or-private-things-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:09:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Dave Eggers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33763-we-feel-that-to-reveal-embarrassing-or-private-things-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We feel that to reveal embarrassing or private things, we have given someone something, that, like a primitive person fearing that a photographer will steal his soul, we identify our secrets, our past and their blotches, with our identity, that revealing our habits or losses or deeds somehow makes one less of oneself. " -- Dave Eggers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33769-they-were-real-people-who-entertained-and-argued-and-existed</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:23:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33769-they-were-real-people-who-entertained-and-argued-and-existed]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They were real people who entertained and argued and existed entirely independently from him, although he had set the thing in motion. They had different thoughts and beliefs. ~ on children growing up." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33770-they-caught-up-with-each-other-s-news-casually-leaving-long</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 16:28:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Lindsay add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33770-they-caught-up-with-each-other-s-news-casually-leaving-long]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They caught up with each other's news casually, leaving long, cosy gaps of silence in which to go to work on their muffins and coffees. Jerome - after two months of having to be witty and brilliant in a strange town among strangers - appreciated the gift of it. People talk about the happy quiet that can exist between two lovers, but this too was great; sitting between his sister and his brother, saying nothing, eating. ~ on the comforts of home." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
