<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980492-dottie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980492-dottie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 19:54:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23669-when-you-reread-a-classic-you-do-not-see-more</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 19:54:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Clifton Fadiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23669-when-you-reread-a-classic-you-do-not-see-more]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you reread a classic you do not see more in the book than you did before; you see more in you than there was before." -- Clifton Fadiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41008-we-should-be-familiar-with-the-great-histories-the-great</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 19:57:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Sterling W. Sill]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41008-we-should-be-familiar-with-the-great-histories-the-great]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should be familiar with the great histories, the great biographies.  We should be familiar with the great success stories, the great love stories, the great philosophies.  It would also be a good idea to memorize potent passages from great poetry and other literary works.  Our literature also may give us extra, pleasant hours as well as furnish contrasts and comparisons which may help us to evaluate and direct our own lives." -- Sterling W. Sill]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5437-no-man-is-an-island-entire-of-itself-every-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 20:09:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by John Donne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5437-no-man-is-an-island-entire-of-itself-every-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No man is an island, entire of itself; every man is a piece of the continent, a part of the main. If a clod be washed away by the sea, Europe is the less, as well as if a promontory were, as well as if a manor of thy friend's or of thine own were: any man's death diminishes me, because I am involved in mankind, and therefore never send to know for whom the bells tolls; it tolls for thee." -- John Donne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2644-he-has-achieved-success-who-has-lived-well-laughed-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He has achieved success who has lived well, laughed often, and loved much;
Who has enjoyed the trust of pure women, the respect of intelligent men and the love of little children;
Who has filled his niche and accomplished his task;
Who has never lacked appreciation of Earth's beauty or failed to express it;
Who has left the world better than he found it,
Whether an improved poppy, a perfect poem, or a rescued soul;
Who has always looked for the best in others and given them the best he had;
Whose life was an inspiration;
Whose memory a benediction." -- Bessie Anderson Stanley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30130-hell-is-empty-and-all-the-devils-are-here</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 13:08:32 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30130-hell-is-empty-and-all-the-devils-are-here]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Hell is empty and all the devils are here." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41057-i-hope-they-will-not-come-upon-us-now-king</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:51:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41057-i-hope-they-will-not-come-upon-us-now-king]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I hope they will not come upon us now.
King Henry:	We are in God's hand, brother, not in theirs." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41058-he-is-the-half-part-of-a-blessed-man-left</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:52:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41058-he-is-the-half-part-of-a-blessed-man-left]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He is the half part of a blessed man,
Left to be finished by such as she;
And she a fair divided excellence,
Whose fullness of perfection lies in him. " -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6618-o-wonder-how-many-goodly-creatures-are-there-here-how</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6618-o-wonder-how-many-goodly-creatures-are-there-here-how]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["O, wonder!
How many goodly creatures are there here!
How beauteous mankind is! O brave new world,
That has such people in't!" -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41060-i-was-actually-permitting-myself-to-experience-a-sickening-sense</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 21:58:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41060-i-was-actually-permitting-myself-to-experience-a-sickening-sense]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I was actually permitting myself to experience a sickening sense of disappointment: but rallying my wits, and recollecting my principles, I at once called my sensations to order; and it was wonderful how I got over the temporary blunder--how I cleared up the mistake of supposing Mr. Rochester's movements a matter in which I had any cause to take vital interest.  Not that I humbled myself by a slavish notion of inferiority: on the contrary, I just said--
	&quot;You have nothing to do with the master of Thornfield further than to receive the salary he gives you for teaching his protegee and to be grateful for such respectful and kind treatment as, if you do your duty, you have a right to expect at his hands. Be sure that is the only tie he seriously acknowledges between you and him, so don't make him the object of your fine feelings, your raptures, agonies, and so forth.  He is not of your order: keep to your caste; and be too self-respecting to lavish the love of the whole heart, soul, and strength, where such a gift is not wanted and would be despised." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41061-rochester-talking-to-jane-i-see-no-enemy-to-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:00:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41061-rochester-talking-to-jane-i-see-no-enemy-to-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Rochester talking to Jane:
I see no enemy to a fortunate issue but in the brow; and that brow professes to say,--'I can live alone, if self-respect and circumstances require me so to do.  I need not sell my soul to buy bliss.  I have an inward treasure, born with me, which can keep me alive if all extraneous delights should be withheld; or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give.' The forehead declares, 'Reason sits firm and holds the reins, and she will not let the feelings burst away and hurry her to wild chasms.  The passions may rage furiously, like true heathens, as they are; and the desires may imagine all sorts of vain things: but judgment shall still have the last word in every argument, and the casting vote in every decision.  Strong wind, earthquake-shock, and fire may pass by: but I shall follow the guiding of that still small voice which interprets the dictates of conscience'&quot; 
" -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41063-the-same-hostile-roof-now-again-rose-before-me-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:03:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41063-the-same-hostile-roof-now-again-rose-before-me-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The same hostile roof now again rose before me; my prospects were doubtful yet; and I had yet an aching heart:  I still felt as a wanderer on the face of the earth; but I experienced firmer trust in myself and my own powers, and less withering dread of oppression.  The gaping wound of my wrongs too, was now quite healed; and the flame of resentment extinguished.&quot;  (Bronte, p.264)

	&quot;A sneer, however, whether covert or open, had now no longer that power over me it once possessed; as I sat between my cousins, I was surprised to find how easy I felt under the total neglect of the one and the semi-sarcastic attentions of the other--Eliza did not mortify, nor Georgiana ruffle me.  The fact was, I had other things to think about within the last few months feelings had been stirred in me so much more potent than any they could raise--pains and pleasures so much more acute and exquisite had been excited, than any it was in their power to inflict or bestow--that their airs gave me no concern either for good or bad." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:05:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66560-i-care-for-myself-the-more-solitary-the-more-friendless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:07:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14876-prejudices-it-is-well-known-are-most-difficult-to-eradicate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Prejudices, it is well known, are most difficult to eradicate from the heart whose soil has never been loosened or fertilised by education: they grow there, firm as weeds among stones." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41068-he-was-fond-of-books-for-they-are-cool-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41068-he-was-fond-of-books-for-they-are-cool-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He was fond of books, for they are cool and sure friends" -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41069-sometimes-he-used-a-spade-in-his-garden-and-sometimes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Victor Hugo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/41069-sometimes-he-used-a-spade-in-his-garden-and-sometimes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes he used a spade in his garden, and sometimes he read and wrote.  He had but one name for these two kinds of labor; he called them gardening.  ‘The Spirit is a garden,’ said he" -- Victor Hugo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34437-i-had-not-intended-to-love-him-the-reader-knows</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:14:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/34437-i-had-not-intended-to-love-him-the-reader-knows]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had not intended to love him; the reader knows I had wrought hard to extirpate from my soul the germs of love there detected; and now, at the first renewed view of him, they spontaneously revived, great and strong! He made me love him without looking at me." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:14:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33882-i-will-keep-the-law-given-by-god-sanctioned-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I will keep the law given by God; sanctioned by man. Laws and principles are not for the times when there is no temptation: they are for such moments as this, when body and soul rise in mutiny against their rigour; stringent are they; inviolate they shall be. If at my individual convenience I might break them, what would be their worth?" -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 22:14:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no happiness like that of being loved by your fellow creatures, and feeling that your presence is an addition to their comfort." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135789-don-t-you-think-it-s-rather-nice-to-think-that-we-re</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Dottie add a quote by E. Nesbit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/135789-don-t-you-think-it-s-rather-nice-to-think-that-we-re]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't you think it's rather nice to think that we're in a book that God's writing? If I were writing a book, I might make mistakes. But God knows how to make the story end just right--in the way that's best for us.&quot;
Do you really believe that, Mother?&quot; Peter asked quietly.
Yes,&quot; she said, &quot;I do believe it--almost always--except when I'm so sad that I can't believe anything. But even when I don't believe it, I know it's true--and I try to believe it." -- E. Nesbit]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
