<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980541-matt]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980541-matt" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 23:43:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271026-reality-is-not-simply-there-it-does-not-simply-exist</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 23:43:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Paul Celan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/271026-reality-is-not-simply-there-it-does-not-simply-exist]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reality is not simply there, it does not simply exist: it must be sought out and won." -- Paul Celan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227438-seeing-clearly-is-not-so-difficult-to-achieve-and-yet</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Victor Serge]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/227438-seeing-clearly-is-not-so-difficult-to-achieve-and-yet]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["[Seeing clearly] is not so difficult to achieve, and yet it is rather unusual. To my mind, it is less a question of an exalted or shrewd intelligence than of good sense, goodwill and a certain sort of courage to enable one to rise above both the pressures of one's environment and the natural inclination to close one's eyes to facts, a temptation that arises from our immediate interests and from the fear which problems inspire in us. A French essayist has said: 'What is terrible when you seek the truth, is that you find it.' You find it, and then you are no longer free to follow the biases of your personal circle, or to accept fashionable cliches." -- Victor Serge]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27297-it-is-a-principle-of-nature-to-hate-those-whom</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:40:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Tacitus]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27297-it-is-a-principle-of-nature-to-hate-those-whom]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is a principle of nature to hate those whom you have injured." -- Tacitus]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827457-once-in-the-south-atlantic-i-saw-a-whaler-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 00:04:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Friedrich Reck-Malleczewen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/827457-once-in-the-south-atlantic-i-saw-a-whaler-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Once, in the South Atlantic, I saw a whaler in the process of killing a female accompanied by one of her offspring. The harpooner, a red-bearded Irishman, kept putting harpoons into the whale. The intestines were hanging out of the mangled body of the huge animal, and nevertheless it continued to swim back and forth in the water made red by its blood, trying with its shattered body to shield the little whale. Since then, and the sight of that harpooner's freckled face as he laughed derisively, and of that poor creature, faithful to the end, I have believed in the existence of Satan as I believe in the existence of God." -- Friedrich Reck-Malleczewen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236690-dan-who-was-writing-a-book-on-the-radical-activity</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:40:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Edmund Wilson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/236690-dan-who-was-writing-a-book-on-the-radical-activity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Dan, who was writing a book on the radical activity of the twenties and thirties, took the occasion of our trip to ask me about them. The whole thing seems to me so stale that I can't imagine anybody's now wanting to write about it, but we ran over the personalities and I told him a lot of stories. It seemed to me like that grisly museum of the early 1900's that I had had him visit at Niagara Falls: old stuffed two-headed calves, motheaten panthers attacking a stag, dried-up corpses from Indian graves, big bags made of rubber tires in which people had tried to shoot the falls--and around it all-powerful industrial life that no show of resistance could stop, which had ruined the landscape of the river and was crowding out everything else. " -- Edmund Wilson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63502-to-succeed-in-the-world-it-is-not-enough-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2013 10:45:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Voltaire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/63502-to-succeed-in-the-world-it-is-not-enough-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To succeed in the world it is not enough to be stupid - one must also be well-mannered." -- Voltaire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257868-three-prisoners-in-the-gulag-get-to-talking-about-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:41:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Roy Medvedev]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/257868-three-prisoners-in-the-gulag-get-to-talking-about-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Three prisoners in the gulag get to talking about why they are there. “I am here because I always got to work five minutes late, and they charged me with sabotage,” says the first. “I am here because I kept getting to work five minutes early, and they charged me with spying,” says the second. “I am here because I got to work on time every day,” says the third, “and they charged me with owning a western watch." -- Roy Medvedev]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723828-i-would-say-that-over-the-last-ten-or-fifteen</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:41:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Tim Yohannan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/723828-i-would-say-that-over-the-last-ten-or-fifteen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I would say that over the last ten or fifteen years, the way capitalism has developed in terms of conglomeration of power and wealth more and more in the hands of a few people and the way the media has affected how people think. What people think. I think that’s part of the technique, to just bombard people with so much bullshit information and so much bullshit that they can’t see the forest from the trees. I think it’s been highly effective. 

And I also think that with the defeat of any alternative, this is the reign of capitalism now — until it destroys the world or destroys itself or whatever it’s gonna do. So, I think that has been the change I have seen in the last twenty years. I don’t think that there’s an effective resistance on a large scale that can be mounted against the power that they have. It’s more a matter of them self-destructing and if there is going to be anything left for anybody else after that. If there is an after that.

Which is not to say that you shouldn’t fight. In other words, I don’t feel depressed by that. People should resist any way they can. They should try and cooperate any way they can and they should try to create environments where they can maintain some kind of sanity and they should try to have some fun. If you’re stuck on this plane, you do what you can do. Otherwise, you become a complete cynical fuckhead, which is a victory for them. If you have any self respect you have to resist." -- Tim Yohannan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/996248-grass-of-levity-span-in-brevity-flower-s-felicity-fire-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2014 12:43:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anonymous, compiled by John Timbs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/996248-grass-of-levity-span-in-brevity-flower-s-felicity-fire-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Grass of levity
Span in brevity 
Flower's felicity 
Fire of misery 
Wind's stability 
Is mortality" -- Anonymous, compiled by John Timbs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118274-let-s-just-call-things-what-they-are-when-a-man-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:40:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Matthew Scully]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118274-let-s-just-call-things-what-they-are-when-a-man-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let's just call things what they are. When a man's love of finery clouds his moral judgment, that is vanity. When he lets a demanding palate make his moral choices, that is gluttony. When he ascribes the divine will to his own whims, that is pride. And when he gets angry at being reminded of animal suffering that his own daily choices might help avoid, that is moral cowardice." -- Matthew Scully]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143428-we-should-realize-that-if-socrates-demanded-that-the-wisest</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2009 20:27:55 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Karl Raimund Popper]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143428-we-should-realize-that-if-socrates-demanded-that-the-wisest]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We should realize that, if [Socrates] demanded that the wisest men should rule, he clearly stressed that he did not mean the learned men; in fact, he was skeptical of all professional learnedness, whether it was that of the philosophers or of the learned men of his own generation, the Sophists. The wisdom he meant was of a different kind. It was simply the realization: how little do I know! Those who did not know this, he taught, knew nothing at all. This is the true scientific spirit." -- Karl Raimund Popper]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171293-there-are-men-who-call-land-theirs-yet-have-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2009 15:00:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/171293-there-are-men-who-call-land-theirs-yet-have-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are men who call land theirs, yet have never set eyes on that land and have never trodden it. There are men who call other men theirs, but yet have never set eyes on the other men, and their sole relation to those other men consists of doing them evil. " -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215074-in-his-comedy-dante-alighieri-names-virgil-with-many-tokens</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2012 23:42:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Georg Christoph Lichtenberg]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/215074-in-his-comedy-dante-alighieri-names-virgil-with-many-tokens]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In his &lt;i&gt;Comedy&lt;/i&gt;, Dante Alighieri names Virgil, with many tokens of respect, as his teacher, and yet as Herr Meinhard remarks, makes such ill use of him: clear proof that even in the days of Dante one praised the ancients without knowing why. This respect for poets one does not understand and yet wishes to equal is the source of the bad writing in our literature." -- Georg Christoph Lichtenberg]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228200-in-our-country-they-do-not-permit-any-information-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 21:22:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/228200-in-our-country-they-do-not-permit-any-information-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In our country they do not permit any information to be X-rayed through and through, nor any discussion to encompass all the facets of a subject. All this is invariably suppressed at the very beginning, so no ray of light should fall on the naked body of truth. And then all this is piled up in one formless heap covering many years, where it languishes for whole decades, until all interest and all means of sorting out the rusty blocks from all this trash are lost." -- Aleksandr I. Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254981-instruments-of-coercion-once-created-have-a-tendency-to-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2010 09:23:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by George F. Kennan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254981-instruments-of-coercion-once-created-have-a-tendency-to-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Instruments of coercion, once created, have a tendency to find their own natural masters." -- George F. Kennan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411141-if-english-was-good-enough-for-jesus-christ-it-s-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 12:07:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Miriam 'Ma' Ferguson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/411141-if-english-was-good-enough-for-jesus-christ-it-s-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If English was good enough for Jesus Christ, it’s good enough for us." -- Miriam 'Ma' Ferguson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/737099-consider-the-model-of-your-local-chain-pharmacy-where-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 18:50:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by John Eddy ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/737099-consider-the-model-of-your-local-chain-pharmacy-where-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Consider the model of [your] local chain pharmacy, where every addictive processed food sold in the front of the store ensures that you will eventually require everything sold by the pharmacy in back." -- John Eddy ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4079-a-new-scientific-truth-does-not-triumph-by-convincing-its</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2013 13:40:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Max Planck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4079-a-new-scientific-truth-does-not-triumph-by-convincing-its]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A new scientific truth does not triumph by convincing its opponents and making them see the light, but rather because its opponents eventually die, and a new generation grows up that is familiar with it." -- Max Planck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/810416-man-attracted-by-the-treasure-that-the-victory-over-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 18:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Bernard-Germain de La Cépède]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/810416-man-attracted-by-the-treasure-that-the-victory-over-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man, attracted by the treasure that the victory over the whale might afford him, has troubled the peace of their immense solitary abodes, violated their refuges, sacrificed all those which the icy, unapproachable polar deserts could not screen from his blow; and the war he has had made on them has been especially cruel because he has seen that it is large catches that make his commerce prosperous, his industry vital, his sailors numerous, his navigators daring, his pilots experienced, his navies strong and his power great.

Thus it is that these giants among giants have fallen beneath his arms; and because his genius is immortal and his science now imperishable, because he has been able to multiply without limit the imaginings of his mind, they will not cease to be the victims of his interest until they have ceased to exist. In vain do they flee before him; his art will transport him to the ends of the earth; they find no sanctuary except in nothingness." -- Bernard-Germain de La Cépède]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/828654-there-is-more-scholarly-work-on-the-life-habits-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 18:23:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Nick Bostrom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/828654-there-is-more-scholarly-work-on-the-life-habits-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is more scholarly work on the life-habits of the dung fly than on existential risks [to humanity]." -- Nick Bostrom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619406-when-i-think-of-antiquity-the-detail-that-frightens-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2012 19:23:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by George Orwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/619406-when-i-think-of-antiquity-the-detail-that-frightens-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When I think of antiquity, the detail that frightens me is that those hundreds of millions of slaves on whose backs civilization rested generation after generation have left behind them no record whatever. We do not even know their names. In the whole of Greek and Roman history, how many slaves' names are known to you? I can think of two, or possibly three. One is Spartacus and the other is Epictetus. Also, in the Roman room at the British Museum there is a glass jar with the maker's name inscribed on the bottom, 'FELIX FECIT'. I have a mental picture of poor Felix (a Gaul with red hair and a metal collar round his neck), but in fact he may not have been a slave; so there are only two slaves whose names I definitely know, and probably few people can remember more. The rest have gone down into utter silence." -- George Orwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859878-if-you-are-using-an-internet-service-for-free-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 18:00:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Robert W. McChesney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/859878-if-you-are-using-an-internet-service-for-free-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you are using an internet service for free, you are not the customer, you are the product." -- Robert W. McChesney]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/861974-interviewer-have-you-ever-been-envious-of-another-writer-wodehouse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 13:02:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/861974-interviewer-have-you-ever-been-envious-of-another-writer-wodehouse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["INTERVIEWER
Have you ever been envious of another writer?

WODEHOUSE
No, never. I’m really such a voracious reader that I’m only too grateful to get some stuff I can read." -- P.G. Wodehouse]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263425-eighty-five-percent-of-recorded-species-live-in-the-terrestrial-realm</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2013 11:09:06 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Richard E. Leakey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263425-eighty-five-percent-of-recorded-species-live-in-the-terrestrial-realm]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Eighty-five percent of recorded species live in the terrestrial realm, and the majority of these, some 850,000, are arthropods (that is, insects, spiders, and crustaceans). Most of the arthropod species are insects, and almost half of these are beetles, a fact that is said to have inspired a famous epigram from the British biologist J.B.S. Haldane. On being asked, one day, by some clerical gentlemen what his study of the natural world had revealed to him about God. Haldane is said to have replied that it indicated that He had &quot;an inordinate fondness of beetles." -- Richard E. Leakey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/979299-if-you-talk-to-people-nowadays-nothing-exists-unless-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 22:37:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by G. B. Edwards]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/979299-if-you-talk-to-people-nowadays-nothing-exists-unless-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you talk to people nowadays, nothing exists unless it has been seen on TV. It gives people the idea they have seen and know everything, when really they have seen and know nothing." -- G. B. Edwards]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1028218-an-introduction-to-poetry-readings-preaching-to-the-converted-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 14:07:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Nasty Nigel Lawrence]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1028218-an-introduction-to-poetry-readings-preaching-to-the-converted-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["An Introduction to Poetry Readings&quot;

Preaching to the converted, the tormented and perverted
Introspective melancholics, axe-grinding alcoholics
Welcome to a night of wine and words!
Who's that in the corner? What a beret! What panache! 
He's erudite and horny and he's high on cheap grenache
Fruity and mellifluous, he thinks he is mischievous
He's just a prick and devious, you'd better watch your back
For the arts are very crafty, then the room turns blank and drafty
And there's agonizing boredom still to come
Direct from minds like hovels, poems twice the length of novels
You may never see your family alive again
God is dead and who can blame him? When there's nights like this to shame him
If I was him I'd rise and just strike back
But the evening's just begun, and there's two hours yet to come
So please, &quot;Put your hands together for the first poet for this evening!" -- Nasty Nigel Lawrence]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053208-on-my-way-out-of-atlantic-city-at-quarter-after</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 18:44:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by James Howard Kunstler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1053208-on-my-way-out-of-atlantic-city-at-quarter-after]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On my way out of [Atlantic City] at quarter after seven in the morning, a young pump jockey at the gas station [...] mentioned that another man had lost $20,000 at Trop World a few hours earlier and had to be dragged out of the casino kicking and screaming. I asked if this happened a lot. &quot;Man,&quot; he said, &quot;there's a whole world of losers out there, and sooner or later they all end up here. Only they don't think they're losers. When they find out, it's like the surprise of their life." -- James Howard Kunstler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242036-the-regime-s-political-strategy-depends-on-planting-landmines-throughout-society</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 12:16:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Anwar Al-Bunni]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1242036-the-regime-s-political-strategy-depends-on-planting-landmines-throughout-society]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The regime's political strategy depends on planting landmines throughout society. But the mine doesn't explode if you place your leg on it - it explodes when you remove your leg from it. The regime planted the land mines, then placed our legs on them so that if the regime goes, society will explode." -- Anwar Al-Bunni]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497798-empathy-he-once-had-decided-must-be-limited-to-herbivores</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2014 19:54:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Matt add a quote by Philip K. Dick]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/497798-empathy-he-once-had-decided-must-be-limited-to-herbivores]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Empathy, he once had decided, must be limited to herbivores or anyhow omnivores who could depart from a meat diet. Because,ultimately, the empathic gift blurred the boundaries between hunter and victim, between the successful and the defeated." -- Philip K. Dick]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
