<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980574-nickilou]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/980574-nickilou" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 20:21:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124547-it-s-a-funny-thing-about-the-modern-world-you-hear</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 20:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Nickilou add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/124547-it-s-a-funny-thing-about-the-modern-world-you-hear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's a funny thing about the modern world. You hear girls in the toilets of clubs saying, &quot;Yeah, he fucked off and left me. He didn't love me. He just couldn't &lt;i&gt;deal&lt;/i&gt; with love. He was too fucked up to know &lt;i&gt;how&lt;/i&gt; to love me.&quot; Now, how did that happen? What was it about this unlovable century that convinced us we were, despite everything, eminently lovable as a people, as a species? What made us think that anyone who fails to love us is damaged, lacking, &lt;i&gt;malfunctioning&lt;/i&gt; in some way? And particularly if they replace us with a god, or a weeping madonna, or the face of Christ in a ciabatta roll---then we call them crazy. Deluded. Regressive. We are so convinced of the goodness of ourselves, and the goodness of our love, we cannot bear to believe that there might be something more worthy of love than us, more worthy of worship. Greeting cards routinely tell us everybody deserves love. No. Everybody deserves clean water. Not everybody deserves love all the time." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
