<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982119-natalie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982119-natalie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 17:57:59 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 17:57:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/36027-it-is-in-vain-to-say-human-beings-ought-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is in vain to say human beings ought to be satisfied with tranquillity: they must have action; and they will make it if they cannot find it. Millions are condemned to a stiller doom than mine, and millions are in silent revolt against their lot. Nobody knows how many rebellions besides political rebellions ferment in the masses of life which people earth. Women are supposed to be very calm generally: but women feel just as men feel; they need exercise for their faculties, and a field for their efforts, as much as their brothers do; they suffer from too rigid a restraint, to absolute a stagnation, precisely as men would suffer; and it is narrow-minded in their more privileged fellow-creatures to say that they ought to confine themselves to making puddings and knitting stockings, to playing on the piano and embroidering bags. It is thoughtless to condemn them, or laugh at them, if they seek to do more or learn more than custom has pronounced necessary for their sex." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 18:02:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1157-if-all-the-world-hated-you-and-believed-you-wicked]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If all the world hated you and believed you wicked, while your own conscience approved of you and absolved you from guilt, you would not be without friends." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4815-life-appears-to-me-too-short-to-be-spent-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 18:03:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4815-life-appears-to-me-too-short-to-be-spent-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life appears to me too short to be spent in nursing animosity or registering wrongs." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98889-a-great-deal-you-are-good-to-those-who-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 18:05:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/98889-a-great-deal-you-are-good-to-those-who-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A great deal; you are good to those who are good to you.  It is all I ever desire to be.  If people were always kind and obedient to those who are cruel and unjust, the wicked people would have it all their own way; they would never feel afraid, and so they would never alter, but would grow worse and worse.  When we are struck at without a reason, we should strike back again very hard; I am sure we should - so hard as to teach the person who struck us never to do it again." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263492-it-is-not-violence-that-best-overcomes-hate----nor</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2011 18:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/263492-it-is-not-violence-that-best-overcomes-hate----nor]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not violence that best overcomes hate -- nor vengeance that most certainly heals injury." -- Charlotte Bronte]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237824-the-key-to-your-happiness-is-to-own-your-slippers</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 00:36:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Abraham Verghese]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/237824-the-key-to-your-happiness-is-to-own-your-slippers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The key to your happiness is to own your slippers, own who you are, own how you look, own your family, own the talents you have, and own the ones you don't. If you keep saying your slippers aren't yours, then you'll die searching, you'll die bitter, always feeling you were promised more. Not only our actions, but also our omissions, become our destiny." -- Abraham Verghese]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280685-wasn-t-that-the-definition-of-home-not-where-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2011 00:36:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Abraham Verghese]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/280685-wasn-t-that-the-definition-of-home-not-where-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Wasn't that the definition of home?  Not where you are from, but where you are wanted" -- Abraham Verghese]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217151-as-for-will-woman-should-be-considered-superior-to-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2011 22:55:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by Donna Woolfolk Cross]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217151-as-for-will-woman-should-be-considered-superior-to-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As for will, woman should be considered superior to man for Eve ate of the apple for love of knowledge and learning, but Adam ate of it merely because she asked him." -- Donna Woolfolk Cross]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45451-isn-t-it-nice-to-think-that-tomorrow-is-a-new</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 22:18:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/45451-isn-t-it-nice-to-think-that-tomorrow-is-a-new]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Isn't it nice to think that tomorrow is a new day with no mistakes in it yet?" -- L.M. Montgomery]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655805-but-how-how-can-you-just-get-over-these-things</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2014 06:08:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Natalie add a quote by M. L. Stedman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/655805-but-how-how-can-you-just-get-over-these-things]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But how? How can you just get over these things, darling?...You've had so much strife but you're always happy. How do you do it?'
'I choose to...I can leave myself to rot in the past, spend my time hating people for what happened, like my father did, or I can forgive and forget.'
'But it's not that easy.'
He smiled that Frank smile. 'Oh, but my treasure, it is so much less exhausting. You only have to forgive once. To resent, you have to do it all day, every day. You have to keep remembering all the bad things...I would have to make a list, a very, very long list and make sure I hated the people on it the right amount. That I did a proper job of hating, too: very Teutonic! No' - his voice became sober- 'we always have a choice. All of us.'&quot; p.323" -- M. L. Stedman]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
