<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982311-e]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982311-e" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:22:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:22:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/360-good-friends-good-books-and-a-sleepy-conscience-this-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:23:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5934-i-ve-learned-that-people-will-forget-what-you-said-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've learned that people will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:23:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7572-i-have-always-imagined-that-paradise-will-be-a-kind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have always imagined that Paradise will be a kind of library." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:24:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by William Nicholson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9590-we-read-to-know-we-re-not-alone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We read to know we're not alone." -- William Nicholson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2009 13:26:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13146-never-trust-anyone-who-has-not-brought-a-book-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never trust anyone who has not brought a book with them." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2022-books-are-the-plane-and-the-train-and-the-road</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:26:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Anna Quindlen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2022-books-are-the-plane-and-the-train-and-the-road]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Books are the plane, and the train, and the road. They are the destination, and the journey. They are home." -- Anna Quindlen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:29:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19071-the-one-you-love-and-the-one-who-loves-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19152-i-think-the-only-way-to-get-through-this-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:29:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Shannon Hale]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19152-i-think-the-only-way-to-get-through-this-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I think the only way to get through this life is laughing hard and constantly, mostly at myself." -- Shannon Hale]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:32:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4986-i-can-believe-things-that-are-true-and-things-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can believe things that are true and things that aren't true and I can believe things where nobody knows if they're true or not. 

I can believe in Santa Claus and the Easter Bunny and the Beatles and Marilyn Monroe and Elvis and Mister Ed. Listen - I believe that people are perfectable, that knowledge is infinite, that the world is run by secret banking cartels and is visited by aliens on a regular basis, nice ones that look like wrinkled lemurs and bad ones who mutilate cattle and want our water and our women. 

I believe that the future sucks and I believe that the future rocks and I believe that one day White Buffalo Woman is going to come back and kick everyone's ass. I believe that all men are just overgrown boys with deep problems communicating and that the decline in good sex in America is coincident with the decline in drive-in movie theaters from state to state. 

I believe that all politicians are unprincipled crooks and I still believe that they are better than the alternative. I believe that California is going to sink into the sea when the big one comes, while Florida is going to dissolve into madness and alligators and toxic waste. 

I believe that antibacterial soap is destroying our resistance to dirt and disease so that one day we'll all be wiped out by the common cold like martians in War of the Worlds. 

I believe that the greatest poets of the last century were Edith Sitwell and Don Marquis, that jade is dried dragon sperm, and that thousands of years ago in a former life I was a one-armed Siberian shaman. 

I believe that mankind's destiny lies in the stars. I believe that candy really did taste better when I was a kid, that it's aerodynamically impossible for a bumble bee to fly, that light is a wave and a particle, that there's a cat in a box somewhere who's alive and dead at the same time (although if they don't ever open the box to feed it it'll eventually just be two different kinds of dead), and that there are stars in the universe billions of years older than the universe itself. 

I believe in a personal god who cares about me and worries and oversees everything I do. I believe in an impersonal god who set the universe in motion and went off to hang with her girlfriends and doesn't even know that I'm alive. I believe in an empty and godless universe of causal chaos, background noise, and sheer blind luck. 

I believe that anyone who says sex is overrated just hasn't done it properly. I believe that anyone who claims to know what's going on will lie about the little things too. 

I believe in absolute honesty and sensible social lies. I believe in a woman's right to choose, a baby's right to live, that while all human life is sacred there's nothing wrong with the death penalty if you can trust the legal system implicitly, and that no one but a moron would ever trust the legal system. 

I believe that life is a game, that life is a cruel joke, and that life is what happens when you're alive and that you might as well lie back and enjoy it." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66583-reading-is-one-form-of-escape-running-for-your-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:32:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66583-reading-is-one-form-of-escape-running-for-your-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Reading is one form of escape. Running for your life is another." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38221-stories-of-imagination-tend-to-upset-those-without-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:37:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38221-stories-of-imagination-tend-to-upset-those-without-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Stories of imagination tend to upset those without one." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:37:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1244-friendship-is-unnecessary-like-philosophy-like-art-it-has-no]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Friendship is unnecessary, like philosophy, like art.... It has no survival value; rather it is one of those things which give value to survival." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:39:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Joss Whedon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7507-remember-to-always-be-yourself-unless-you-suck]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember to always be yourself. Unless you suck." -- Joss Whedon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61535-i-suppose-i-ll-have-to-add-the-force-of-gravity</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2009 13:54:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[E add a quote by Lemony Snicket]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61535-i-suppose-i-ll-have-to-add-the-force-of-gravity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I suppose I'll have to add the force of gravity to my list of enemies." -- Lemony Snicket]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
