<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982902-krisha]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982902-krisha" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:53:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:53:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7901-you-know-you-re-in-love-when-you-can-t-fall-asleep]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know you're in love when you can't fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:54:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6805-sometimes-the-questions-are-complicated-and-the-answers-are-simple]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes the questions are complicated and the answers are simple." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:54:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3356-i-like-nonsense-it-wakes-up-the-brain-cells-fantasy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I like nonsense, it wakes up the brain cells. Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:54:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Robert Fulghum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/204561-we-re-all-a-little-weird-and-life-is-a-little]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We’re all a little weird. And life is a little weird. And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, we join up with them and fall into mutually satisfying weirdness—and call it love—true love." -- Robert Fulghum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101596-fantasy-is-a-necessary-ingredient-in-living-it-s-a-way</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 22:56:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101596-fantasy-is-a-necessary-ingredient-in-living-it-s-a-way]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fantasy is a necessary ingredient in living, it's a way of looking at life through the wrong end of a telescope." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55512-i-believe-that-the-universe-was-formed-around-15-billion</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2010 17:10:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Ronald P. Carver]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/55512-i-believe-that-the-universe-was-formed-around-15-billion]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that the universe was formed around 15 billion years ago and that humans have evolved from their apelike ancestors over the past few million years.  I believe we are more likely to live a good life if all humans try to work together in a world community, preserving planet earth.  When decisions for groups are made in this world, I believe that the democratic process should be used.  To protect the individual, I believe in freedom of speech, freedom of the press, freedom of religion, freedom from religion, freedom of inquiry, and a wall of separation between church and state.  When making decisions about what is right or wrong, I believe I should use my intelligence to reason about the likely consequences of my actions.  I believe that I should try to increase the happiness of everyone by caring for other people and finding ways to cooperate.  Never should my actions discriminate against people simply because of their race, religion, sex, sexual orientation, age, or national origin.  I believe that ideas about what is right and wrong will change with education, so I am prepared to continually question ideas using evidence from experience and science.  I believe there is no valid evidence to support claims for the existence of supernatural entities and deities.  I will use these beliefs to guide my thinking and my actions until I find good reasons for revising them or replacing them with other beliefs that are more valid." -- Ronald P. Carver]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128536-don-t-exist-live-get-out-explore-thrive-challenge-authority-challenge</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 18:18:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Brian Krans]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128536-don-t-exist-live-get-out-explore-thrive-challenge-authority-challenge]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Don't exist. 
Live.
Get out, explore.
Thrive.
Challenge authority. Challenge yourself.
Evolve.
Change forever.
Become who you say you always will. Keep moving. Don't stop. Start the revolution. Become a freedom fighter. Become a superhero. Just because everyone doesn't know your name doesn't mean you dont matter.
Are you happy? Have you ever been happy? What have you done today to matter? Did you exist or did you live? How did you thrive?
Become a chameleon-fit in anywhere. Be a rockstar-stand out everywhere. Do nothing, do everything. Forget everything, remember everyone. Care, don't just pretend to. Listen to everyone. Love everyone and nothing at the same time. Its impossible to be everything,but you can't stop trying to do it all.
All I know is that I have no idea where I am right now. I feel like I am in training for something, making progress with every step I take. I fear standing still. It is my greatest weakness.
I talk big, but often don't follow through. That's my biggest problem. I don't even know what to think right now. It's about time I start to take a jump. Fuck starting to take. Just jump-over everything. Leap.
It's time to be aggressive. You've started to speak your mind, now keep going with it, but not with the intention of sparking controversy or picking a germane fight. Get your gloves on, it's time for rebirth. There IS no room for the nice guys in the history books.
THIS IS THE START OF A REVOLUTION. THE REVOLUTION IS YOUR LIFE. THE GOAL IS IMMORTALITY. LET'S LIVE, BABY. LET'S FEEL ALIVE AT ALL TIMES. TAKE NO PRISONERS. HOLD NO SOUL UNACCOUNTABLE, ESPECIALLY NOT YOUR OWN. IF SOMETHING DOESN'T HAPPEN, IT'S YOUR FAULT.
Make this moment your reckoning. Your head has been held under water for too long and now it is time to rise up and take your first true breath.
Do everything with exact calculation, nothing without meaning. Do not make careful your words, but make no excuses for what you say. Fuck em' all. Set a goal for everyday and never be tired." -- Brian Krans]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117708-you-can-take-this-mouth-this-wound-you-want-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 19:35:29 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Daphne Gottlieb]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117708-you-can-take-this-mouth-this-wound-you-want-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["you can take this mouth
this wound you want
but you can't kiss
and make it
better." -- Daphne Gottlieb]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143729-if-you-can-keep-your-head-when-all-about-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 19:39:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Rudyard Kipling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/143729-if-you-can-keep-your-head-when-all-about-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can keep your head when all about you
Are losing theirs and blaming it on you,
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,
But make allowance for their doubting too;!" -- Rudyard Kipling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2336-on-the-surface-i-was-calm-in-secret-without-really</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 19:41:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Stanisław Lem]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2336-on-the-surface-i-was-calm-in-secret-without-really]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On the surface, I was calm: in secret, without really admitting it, I was waiting for something. Her return? How could I have been waiting for that? We all know that we are material creatures, subject to the laws of physiology and physics, and not even the power of all our feelings combined can defeat those laws. All we can do is detest them. The age-old faith of lovers and poets in the power of love, stronger than death, that finis vitae sed non amoris, is a lie, useless and not even funny. So must one be resigned to being a clock that measures the passage of time, now out of order, now repaired, and whose mechanism generates despair and love as soon as its maker sets it going? 

Must I go on living here then, among the objects we both had touched, in the air she had breathed? In the name of what? In the hope of her return? I hoped for nothing. And yet I lived in expectation. Since she had gone, that was all that remained. I did not know what achievements, what mockery, even what tortures still awaited me. I knew nothing, and I persisted in the faith that the time of cruel miracles was not past." -- Stanisław Lem]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28570-i-said-to-my-soul-be-still-and-wait-without</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 01:57:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by T.S. Eliot]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28570-i-said-to-my-soul-be-still-and-wait-without]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I said to my soul, be still and wait without hope, for hope would be hope for the wrong thing; wait without love, for love would be love of the wrong thing; there is yet faith, but the faith and the love are all in the waiting. Wait without thought, for you are not ready for thought: So the darkness shall be the light, and the stillness the dancing." -- T.S. Eliot]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25390-i-m-a-modern-man-a-man-for-the-millennium-digital</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2010 17:53:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25390-i-m-a-modern-man-a-man-for-the-millennium-digital]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I’m a modern man, a man for the millennium. Digital and smoke free. A diversified multi-cultural, post-modern deconstruction that is anatomically and ecologically incorrect. I’ve been up linked and downloaded, I’ve been inputted and outsourced, I know the upside of downsizing, I know the downside of upgrading. I’m a high-tech low-life. A cutting edge, state-of-the-art bi-coastal multi-tasker and I can give you a gigabyte in a nanosecond! 
I’m new wave, but I’m old school and my inner child is outward bound. I’m a hot-wired, heat seeking, warm-hearted cool customer, voice activated and bio-degradable. I interface with my database, my database is in cyberspace, so I’m interactive, I’m hyperactive and from time to time I’m radioactive. 

Behind the eight ball, ahead of the curve, ridin the wave, dodgin the bullet and pushin the envelope. I’m on-point, on-task, on-message and off drugs. I’ve got no need for coke and speed. I've got no urge to binge and purge. I’m in-the-moment, on-the-edge, over-the-top and under-the-radar. A high-concept, low-profile, medium-range ballistic missionary. A street-wise smart bomb. A top-gun bottom feeder. I wear power ties, I tell power lies, I take power naps and run victory laps. I’m a totally ongoing big-foot, slam-dunk, rainmaker with a pro-active outreach. A raging workaholic. A working rageaholic. Out of rehab and in denial! 

I’ve got a personal trainer, a personal shopper, a personal assistant and a personal agenda. You can’t shut me up. You can’t dumb me down because I’m tireless and I’m wireless, I’m an alpha male on beta-blockers. 

I’m a non-believer and an over-achiever, laid-back but fashion-forward. Up-front, down-home, low-rent, high-maintenance. Super-sized, long-lasting, high-definition, fast-acting, oven-ready and built-to-last! I’m a hands-on, foot-loose, knee-jerk head case pretty maturely post-traumatic and I’ve got a love-child that sends me hate mail. 

But, I’m feeling, I’m caring, I’m healing, I’m sharing-- a supportive, bonding, nurturing primary care-giver. My output is down, but my income is up. I took a short position on the long bond and my revenue stream has its own cash-flow. I read junk mail, I eat junk food, I buy junk bonds and I watch trash sports! I’m gender specific, capital intensive, user-friendly and lactose intolerant. 

I like rough sex. I like tough love. I use the “F” word in my emails and the software on my hard-drive is hardcore--no soft porn. 

I bought a microwave at a mini-mall; I bought a mini-van at a mega-store. I eat fast-food in the slow lane. I’m toll-free, bite-sized, ready-to-wear and I come in all sizes. A fully-equipped, factory-authorized, hospital-tested, clinically-proven, scientifically- formulated medical miracle. I’ve been pre-wash, pre-cooked, pre-heated, pre-screened, pre-approved, pre-packaged, post-dated, freeze-dried, double-wrapped, vacuum-packed and, I have an unlimited broadband capacity. 

I’m a rude dude, but I’m the real deal. Lean and mean! Cocked, locked and ready-to-rock. Rough, tough and hard to bluff. I take it slow, I go with the flow, I ride with the tide. I’ve got glide in my stride. Drivin and movin, sailin and spinin, jiving and groovin, wailin and winnin. I don’t snooze, so I don’t lose. I keep the pedal to the metal and the rubber on the road. I party hearty and lunch time is crunch time. I’m hangin in, there ain’t no doubt and I’m hangin tough, over and out!" -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 06:01:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100871-on-writing-aphorisms-and-ten-second-essays-1-a-beginning-ends</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2010 06:02:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Krisha add a quote by James Richardson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/100871-on-writing-aphorisms-and-ten-second-essays-1-a-beginning-ends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On Writing: Aphorisms and Ten-Second Essays 

1. A beginning ends what an end begins. 

2. The despair of the blank page: it is so full.

3. In the head Art’s not democratic. I wait a long time to be a writer good enough even for myself. 

4. The best time is stolen time.

5. All work is the avoidance of harder work. 

6. When I am trying to write I turn on music so I can hear what is keeping me from hearing.

7. I envy music for being beyond words. But then, every word is beyond music.

8. Why would we write if we’d already heard what we wanted to hear?

9. The poem in the quarterly is sure to fail within two lines: flaccid, rhythmless, hopelessly dutiful. But I read poets from strange languages with freedom and pleasure because I can believe in all that has been lost in translation. Though all works, all acts, all languages are already translation. 

10. Writer: how books read each other.

11. Idolaters of the great need to believe that what they love cannot fail them, adorers of camp, kitsch, trash that they cannot fail what they love. 

12. If I didn’t spend so much time writing, I’d know a lot more. But I wouldn’t know anything.

13. If you’re Larkin or Bishop, one book a decade is enough. If you’re not? More than enough.

14. Writing is like washing windows in the sun. With every attempt to perfect clarity you make a new smear.

15. There are silences harder to take back than words.

16. Opacity gives way. Transparency is the mystery.

17. I need a much greater vocabulary to talk to you than to talk to myself.

18. Only half of writing is saying what you mean. The other half is preventing people from reading what they expected you to mean.

19. Believe stupid praise, deserve stupid criticism.

20. Writing a book is like doing a huge jigsaw puzzle, unendurably slow at first, almost self-propelled at the end. Actually, it’s more like doing a puzzle from a box in which several puzzles have been mixed. Starting out, you can’t tell whether a piece belongs to the puzzle at hand, or one you’ve already done, or will do in ten years, or will never do. 

21. Minds go from intuition to articulation to self-defense, which is what they die of.

22. The dead are still writing. Every morning, somewhere, is a line, a passage, a whole book you are sure wasn’t there yesterday.

23. To feel an end is to discover that there had been a beginning. A parenthesis closes that we hadn’t realized was open).

24. There, all along, was what you wanted to say. But this is not what you wanted, is it, to have said it?" -- James Richardson]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
