<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982994-katy]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/982994-katy" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 17:26:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78762-when-that-slow-motion-silent-explosion-of-love-takes-place-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 17:26:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by vladimir nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78762-when-that-slow-motion-silent-explosion-of-love-takes-place-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When that slow-motion, silent explosion of love takes place in me, unfolding its melting fringes and overwhelming me with the sense of something much vaster, much more enduring and powerful than the accumulation of matter or energy in any imaginable cosmos, then my mind cannot but pinch itself to see if it is really awake.  I have to make a rapid inventory of the universe, just as a man in a dream tries to condone the absurdity of his position by making sure he is dreaming.  I have to have all space and all time participate in my emotion, in my mortal love, so that the edge of its mortality is taken off, thus helping me to fight the utter degradation, ridicule, and horror of having developed an infinity of sensation and thought within a finite existence." -- vladimir nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173282-and-i-know-why-our-friendship-must-be-kept-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2009 17:26:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Nick Cave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/173282-and-i-know-why-our-friendship-must-be-kept-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I know why our friendship must be kept a secret. Or they will kill You like they killed You in the Bible. And then we could not be together. If not for them we would live in this valley together. As best friends. But we must be careful, Jesus. I think I would die if anything happened to You...' - she cried ah think, for ah could hear her little sobs as she spoke - '...just close my eyes and die.' And she let fall a heavy tear, and it passed through the slats and exploded upon mah face, just below the right cheek. And as the droplet began to roll, ah caught it with mah tongue. And ah was shocked momentarily by that tear's sweetness, having known them only as bitter things - only bitter things - always bitter things." -- Nick Cave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73969-ada-girl-adored-girl-i-m-a-radiant-void-i-m</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 22:23:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by vladimir nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/73969-ada-girl-adored-girl-i-m-a-radiant-void-i-m]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ada girl, adored girl, [...] I'm a radiant void.  I'm convalescing after a long and dreadful illness.  You cried over my unseemly scar, but now life is going to be nothing but love and laughter, and corn in cans.  I cannot brood over broken hearts, mine is too recently mended." -- vladimir nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78767-you-know-i-still-feel-in-my-wrists-certain-echoes</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 16:12:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/78767-you-know-i-still-feel-in-my-wrists-certain-echoes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You know, I still feel in my wrists certain echoes of the pram-pusher’s knack, such as, for example, the glib downward pressure one applied to the handle in order to have the carriage tip up and climb the curb.  First came an elaborate mouse-gray vehicle of Belgian make, with fat autoid tires and luxurious springs, so large that it could not enter our puny elevator.  It rolled on sidewalks in a slow stately mystery, with the trapped baby inside lying supine, well covered with down, silk and fur; only his eyes moved, warily, and sometimes they turned upward with one swift sweep of their showy lashes to follow the receding of branch-patterned blueness that flowed away from the edge of the half-cocked hood of the carriage, and presently he would dart a suspicious glance at my face to see if the teasing trees and sky did not belong, perhaps to the same order of things as did rattles and parental humor.  There followed a lighter carriage, and in this, as he spun along, he would tend to rise, straining at his straps; clutching at the edges; standing there less like the groggy passenger of a pleasure boat than like an entranced scientist in a spaceship; surveying the speckled skeins of a live, warm world; eyeing with philosophic interest the pillow he had managed to throw overboard; falling out himself when a strap burst one day.  Still later he rode in one of those small contraptions called strollers; from initial springy and secure heights the child came lower and lower, until, when he was about one and a half, he touched ground in front of the moving stroller by slipping forward out of his seat and beating the sidewalk with his heels in anticipation of being set loose in some public garden.  A new wave of evolution started to swell, gradually lifting him again from the ground, when, for his second birthday, he received a four-foot-long, silver-painted Mercedes racing car operated by inside pedals, like an organ, and in this he used to drive with a pumping, clanking noise up and down the sidewalk of the Kurfurstendamm while from open windows came the multiplied roar of a dictator still pounding his chest in the Neander valley we had left far behind.  " -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82379-found-in-a-small-stone-cave-bitten-from-the-roadside</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2008 05:21:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Nick Cave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82379-found-in-a-small-stone-cave-bitten-from-the-roadside]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Found in a small stone cave bitten from the roadside, stitchless save for his great outsized boots and a plague of flies, fat on the human scrappage of dinners long past, Toad squatted in the slitted stomach of a warm child, eating loudly the face of her hapless, headless father, who sat a good foot off the ground impaled up the ass on a pointed post." -- Nick Cave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157879-can-we-feel-contrition-for-other-people-s-crimes-can-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2009 15:49:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Sven Lindqvist]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157879-can-we-feel-contrition-for-other-people-s-crimes-can-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can we feel contrition for other people's crimes? Can we feel contrition for crimes we have not committed personally, but have subsequently profited from? How can we formulate the criteria for contrition to make them applicable to collective responsibility for historical crimes? Perhaps like this:
We freely admit that our predecessors have done wrong and that we are profiting from it.
We ask forgiveness of those who were wronged and of their descendants.
We promise to do our best to make amends to those who were wronged for the effects that still remain.
The larger the collective, the more diluted the personal responsibility.  The less intimate the contrition, the greater the risk that it will just be hollow ceremony." -- Sven Lindqvist]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175789-our-best-yesterdays-are-now-foul-piles-of-crumpled-names</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 13:40:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/175789-our-best-yesterdays-are-now-foul-piles-of-crumpled-names]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our best yesterdays are now foul piles of crumpled names." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178298-there-exist-few-things-more-tedious-than-a-discussion-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 21:02:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178298-there-exist-few-things-more-tedious-than-a-discussion-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There exist few things more tedious than a discussion of general ideas inflicted by author or reader upon a work of fiction.  The purpose of this foreword is not to show that &quot;Bend Sinister&quot; belongs or does not belong to &quot;serious literature&quot; (which is a euphemism for the hollow profundity and the ever-welcome commonplace).  I have never been interested in what is called the literature of social comment (in journalistic and commercial parlance: &quot;great books&quot;).  I am not &quot;sincere,&quot; I am not &quot;provocative,&quot; I am not &quot;satirical.&quot;  I am neither a didacticist nor an allegorizer.  Politics and economics, atomic bombs, primitive and abstract art forms, the entire Orient, symptoms of &quot;thaw&quot; in Soviet Russia, the Future of Mankind, and so on, leave me supremely indifferent.  As in the case of my &quot;Invitation to a Beheading&quot; - with which this book has obvious affinities - automatic comparisons between &quot;Bend Sinister&quot; and Kafka's creations or Orwell's cliches would go merely to prove that the automaton could not have read either the great German writer or the mediocre English one." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190479-through-these-days-bunny-made-increasingly-frequent-and-protracted-visits</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2009 05:18:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Nick Cave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/190479-through-these-days-bunny-made-increasingly-frequent-and-protracted-visits]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Through these days Bunny made increasingly frequent and protracted visits to the bathroom, beating off with a single-minded savagery intense even by Bunny's standards.  Now, sitting on the sofa with a large Scotch, his cock feels and looks like something that has been involved in a terrible accident - a cartoon hotdog, maybe, that has made an unsuccessful attempt to cross a busy road.
The boy sits beside him and the two of them are locked in a parenthesis of mutual zonkedness. Bunny Junior stares blankly at the encyclopedia open in his lap.  His father watches the television, smokes his fag and drinks his whisky, like an automaton. 
After a time, Bunny turns his head and looks at his son and clocks the way he stares at his weird encyclopedia. He sees him but he can't really believe he is there.  What does this kid want?  What is he supposed to do with him?  Who is he?  Bunny feels like an extinct volcano, lifeless and paralysed.  Yeah, he thinks, I feel like an extinct volcano - with a weird little kid to look after and a mangled sausage for a dick." -- Nick Cave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207033-in-the-hysterical-technocracy-of-modern-music-sorrow-is-sent</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2009 06:33:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Nick Cave]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/207033-in-the-hysterical-technocracy-of-modern-music-sorrow-is-sent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the hysterical technocracy of modern music, sorrow is sent to the back of the class where it sits, pissing its pants in mortal terror." -- Nick Cave]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247932-the-answer-to-all-questions-of-life-and-death-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 05:42:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/247932-the-answer-to-all-questions-of-life-and-death-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The answer to all questions of life and death, &quot;the absolute solution&quot; was written all over the world he had known: it was like a traveller realising that the wild country he surveys is not an accidental assembly of natural phenomena, but the page in a book where these mountains and forests, and fields, and rivers are disposed in such a way as to form a coherent sentence; the vowel of a lake fusing with the consonant of a sibilant slope; the windings of a road writing its message in a round hand, as clear as that of one's father; trees conversing in dumb-show, making sense to one who has learnt the gestures of their language... Thus the traveller spells the landscape and its sense is disclosed, and likewise, the intricate pattern of human life turns out to be monogrammatic, now quite clear to the inner eye disentangling the interwoven letters.  And the word, the meaning which appears is astounding in its simplicity: the greatest surprise being perhaps that in the course of one's earthly existence, with one's brain encompassed by an iron ring, by the close-fitting dream of one's own personality - one had not made by chance that simple mental jerk, which would have set free imprisoned thought and granted it the great understanding." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252274-there-is-only-one-real-number-one-and-love-apparently</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 07:47:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katy add a quote by Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252274-there-is-only-one-real-number-one-and-love-apparently]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is only one real number: one.  And love, apparently, is the best exponent of this singularity." -- Vladimir Nabokov]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
