<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/983508-megan-evans]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/983508-megan-evans" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 00:57:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33558-there-are-three-lessons-i-would-write--three-words-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 00:57:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Friedrich Von Schiller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33558-there-are-three-lessons-i-would-write--three-words-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are three lessons I would write-
Three words, as with a burning pen, 
In tracings of eternal light,
Upon the heart of men.

Have hope! though clouds environ round,
And gladness hides her face in scorn,
Put thou the shadow from thy brow,
No night but hath its morn.

Have love! not love alone for one, 
But man as man thy brother call,
And scatter like the circling sun,
Thy charities on all." -- Friedrich Von Schiller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27854-if-you-can-walk-with-the-crowd-and-keep-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 00:59:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Rudyard Kipling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27854-if-you-can-walk-with-the-crowd-and-keep-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you can walk with the crowd and keep your virtue, or walk with Kings-nor lose the common touch; If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you; If all men count with you, but none too much; If you can fill the unforgiving minute with 60 seconds worth of distance run- Yours is the earth and everything that's in it, And-which is more-you'll be a man my son." -- Rudyard Kipling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33563-america-for-me-tis-fine-to-see-the-old-world</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 01:09:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Megan add a quote by Henry Van Dyke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/33563-america-for-me-tis-fine-to-see-the-old-world]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["America for Me

'Tis fine to see the Old World and travel up and down
Among the famous palaces and cities of renown,
To admire the crumblyh castles and the statues and kings
But now I think I've had enough of antiquated things.

So it's home again, and home again, America for me!
My heart is turning home again and there I long to be,
In the land of youth and freedom, beyond the ocean bars,
Where the air is full of sunlight and the flag is full of stars.

Oh, London is a man's town, there's power in the air;
And Paris is a woman's town, with flowers in her hair;
And it's sweet to dream in Venice, and it's great to study Rome;
But when it comes to living there is no place like home.

I like the German fir-woods in green battalions drilled;
I like the gardens of Versailles with flashing foutains filled;
But, oh, to take your hand, my dear, and ramble for a day
In the friendly western woodland where Nature has her sway!

I know that Europe's wonderful, yet something seems to lack!
The Past is too much with her, and the people looking back.
But the glory of the Present is to make the Future free--
We love our land for what she is and what she is to be.

Oh, it's home again, and home again, America for me!
I want a ship that's westward bound to plough the rolling sea,
To the blessed Land of Room Enough, beyond the ocean bars,
Where the air is full of sunlight and the flag is full of stars." -- Henry Van Dyke]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
