<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/985147-michelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/985147-michelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 23:41:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13089-it-s-pain-that-changes-our-lives</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2008 23:41:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Steve Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13089-it-s-pain-that-changes-our-lives]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It's pain that changes our lives." -- Steve Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 15:31:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Pablo Neruda]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8750-i-love-you-without-knowing-how-or-when-or-from]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I love you without knowing how, or when, or from where. I love you simply, without problems or pride: I love you in this way because I do not know any other way of loving but this, in which there is no I or you, so intimate that your hand upon my chest is my hand, so intimate that when I fall asleep your eyes close." -- Pablo Neruda]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 15:33:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Plato]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12860-every-heart-sings-a-song-incomplete-until-another-heart-whispers]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every heart sings a song, incomplete, until another heart whispers back. Those who wish to sing always find a song. At the touch of a lover, everyone becomes a poet." -- Plato]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17195-love-is-a-wonderful-gift-it-s-a-present-so-precious</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 17:50:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Douglas Pagels]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17195-love-is-a-wonderful-gift-it-s-a-present-so-precious]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love is a wonderful gift. It's a present so precious words can barely begin to describe it.  Love is a feeling, the deepest and sweetest of all.  It's incredibly strong and amazingly gentle at the very same time.  It is a blessing that should be counted every day.  It is nourishment for the soul.  It is devotion, constantly letting each person know how supportive it's certainty can be. Love is a heart filled with affection for the most important person in your life. Love is looking at the special someone who makes your world go around and absolutely loving what you see. Love gives meaning to one's world and magic to a million hopes and dreams.  It makes the morning shine more brightly and each season seem like it's the nicest one anyone ever had. Love is an invaluable bond that enriches every good thing in life.  It gives each hug a tenderness, each heart a happiness, each spirit a steady lift.  Love is an invisible connection that is exquisitely felt by those who know the joy, feel the warmth, share the sweetness, and celebrate the gift! " -- Douglas Pagels]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 17:51:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Sarah Dessen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37490-no-relationship-is-perfect-ever-there-are-always-some-ways]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No relationship is perfect, ever. There are always some ways you have to bend, to compromise, to give something up in order to gain something greater...The love we have for each other is bigger than these small differences. And that's the key. It's like a big pie chart, and the love in a relationship has to be the biggest piece. Love can make up for a lot." -- Sarah Dessen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27525-the-future-for-me-is-already-a-thing-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 17:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Michelle add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27525-the-future-for-me-is-already-a-thing-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The future for me is already a thing of the past -
You were my first love and you will be my last" -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
