<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/986934-alex]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/986934-alex" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:44:01 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:44:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22798-the-trouble-is-that-we-have-a-bad-habit-encouraged]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The trouble is that we have a bad habit, encouraged by pendants and sophisticates, of considering happiness as something rather stupid. Only pain is intellectual, only evil interesting. This is the treason of the artist: a refusal to admit the banality of evil and the terrible boredom of pain." -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:44:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/779-love-doesn-t-just-sit-there-like-a-stone-it-has]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Love doesn't just sit there, like a stone, it has to be made, like bread; remade all the time, made new." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4031-what-sane-person-could-live-in-this-world-and-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:45:22 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4031-what-sane-person-could-live-in-this-world-and-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What sane person could live in this world and not be crazy?" -- Ursula K. LeGuin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96119-people-who-deny-the-existence-of-dragons-are-often-eaten</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:44:56 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/96119-people-who-deny-the-existence-of-dragons-are-often-eaten]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who deny the existence of dragons are often eaten by dragons. From within." -- Ursula K. Le Guin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:46:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5686-if-more-of-us-valued-food-and-cheer-and-song]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If more of us valued food  and cheer and song above hoarded gold, it would be a merrier world." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:45:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26219-fantasy-is-escapist-and-that-is-its-glory-if-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fantasy is escapist, and that is its glory. If a soldier is imprisioned by the enemy, don't we consider it his duty to escape?. . .If we value the freedom of mind and soul, if we're partisans of liberty, then it's our plain duty to escape, and to take as many people with us as we can!" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:46:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/5238-i-have-claimed-that-escape-is-one-of-the-main]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I have claimed that Escape is one of the main functions of fairy-stories, and since I do not disapprove of them, it is plain that I do not accept the tone of scorn or pity with which 'Escape' is now so often used. Why should a man be scorned if, finding himself in prison, he tries to get out and go home? Or if he cannot do so, he thinks and talks about other topics than jailers and prison-walls?" -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27406-fairy-tale-does-not-deny-the-existence-of-sorrow-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:47:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27406-fairy-tale-does-not-deny-the-existence-of-sorrow-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Fairy tale does not deny the existence of sorrow and failure: the possibility of these is necessary to the joy of deliverance. It denies (in the face of much evidence, if you will) universal final defeat...giving a fleeting glimpse of Joy; Joy beyond the walls of the world, poignant as grief." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118220-fa-rie-contains-many-things-besides-elves-and-fays-and-besides</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:51:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/118220-fa-rie-contains-many-things-besides-elves-and-fays-and-besides]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Faërie contains many things besides elves and fays, and besides dwarfs, witches, trolls, giants, or dragons; it holds the seas, the sun, the moon, the sky; and the earth, and all things that are in it: tree and bird, water and stone, wine and bread, and ourselves, mortal men, when we are enchanted." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51721-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:53:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/51721-the-consolation-of-fairy-stories-the-joy-of-the-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The consolation of fairy stories, the joy of the happy ending; or more correctly, the good catastrophe, the sudden, joyous &quot;turn&quot; (for there is no true end to a fairy tale); this joy, which is one of the things that fairy stories can produce supremely well, is not essentially escapist or fugitive. In it's fairy tale or other world setting, it is a sudden and miraculous grace, never to be counted on to reoccur. It does not deny the existence of dyscatastrophe, or sorrow and failure, the possibility of these is necessary to the joy of deliverance. It denies, (in the face of much evidence if you will) universal final defeat and in so far is evangelium, giving a fleeting glimpse of Joy, Joy beyond the walls of the world, poignant as grief." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85350-celtic-is-a-magic-bag-into-which-anything-may-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:53:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/85350-celtic-is-a-magic-bag-into-which-anything-may-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Celtic 'is a magic bag, into which anything may be put, and out of which almost anything may come . . . Anything is possible in the fabulous Celtic twilight, which is not so much a twilight of the gods as of the reason." -- J. R. R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:54:26 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The weather had freshened almost to coldness, for the wind was coming more easterly, from the chilly currents between Tristan and the Cape; the sloth was amazed by the change; it shunned the deck and spent its time below. Jack was in his cabin, pricking the chart with less satisfaction than he could have wished: progress, slow, serious trouble with the mainmast-- unaccountable headwinds by night-- and sipping a glass of grog; Stephen was in the mizentop, teaching Bonden to write and scanning the sea for his first albatross. The sloth sneezed, and looking up, Jack caught its gaze fixed upon him; its inverted face had an expression of anxiety and concern. 'Try a piece of this, old cock,' he said, dipping his cake in the grog and proffering the sop. 'It might put a little heart into you.' The sloth sighed, closed its eyes, but gently absorbed the piece, and sighed again.

    Some minutes later he felt a touch upon his knee: the sloth had silently climbed down and it was standing there, its beady eyes looking up into his face, bright with expectation. More cake, more grog: growing confidence and esteem. After this, as soon as the drum had beat the retreat, the sloth would meet him, hurrying toward the door on its uneven legs: it was given its own bowl, and it would grip it with its claws, lowering its round face into it and pursing its lips to drink (its tongue was too short to lap). Sometimes it went to sleep in this position, bowed over the emptiness.

    'In this bucket,' said Stephen, walking into the cabin, 'in this small half-bucket, now, I have the population of Dublin, London, and Paris combined: these animalculae-- what is the matter with the sloth?' It was curled on Jack's knee, breathing heavily: its bowl and Jack's glass stood empty on the table. Stephen picked it up, peered into its affable bleary face, shook it, and hung it upon its rope. It seized hold with one fore and one hind foot, letting the others dangle limp, and went to sleep.

    Stephen looked sharply round, saw the decanter, smelt to the sloth, and cried, 'Jack, you have debauched my sloth." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146302-why-there-you-are-stephen-cried-jack-you-are-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:56:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/146302-why-there-you-are-stephen-cried-jack-you-are-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why there you are, Stephen,' cried Jack. 'You are come home, I find.'

That is true,' said Stephen with an affectionate look: he prized statements of this kind in Jack." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157383-there-is-a-systematic-flocci-nauci-nihili-pilification-of-all-other-aspects-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 04:56:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157383-there-is-a-systematic-flocci-nauci-nihili-pilification-of-all-other-aspects-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is a systematic flocci-nauci-nihili-pilification of all other aspects of existence that angers me." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12387-criticism---however-valid-or-intellectually-engaging---tends-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 16:03:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12387-criticism---however-valid-or-intellectually-engaging---tends-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Criticism - however valid or intellectually engaging - tends to get in the way of a writer who has anything personal to say. A tightrope walker may require practice, but if he starts a theory of equilibrium he will lose grace (and probably fall off)." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8235-oft-it-may-be-chance-that-old-wives-keep-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 16:12:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/8235-oft-it-may-be-chance-that-old-wives-keep-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Oft it may be chance that old wives keep in memory word of things that once were heedful for the wise to know." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253993-let-the-unseen-days-be-today-is-more-than-enough</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2012 13:43:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Alex add a quote by J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/253993-let-the-unseen-days-be-today-is-more-than-enough]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let the unseen days be. Today is more than enough." -- J.R.R. Tolkien]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
