<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/987785-gail]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/987785-gail" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 09:25:16 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116082-when-acog-american-college-of-obstetricians-and-gynecologists-claims-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 09:25:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Jennifer Block]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116082-when-acog-american-college-of-obstetricians-and-gynecologists-claims-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When ACOG (American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists) claims that home birth and midwives are unsafe, they imply that the women who choose it and the midwives that provide it are acting irresponsibly and selfishly.  They stigmatize normal birth just as the political right has stigmatized abortion.  And they stigmatize women.  
&quot;Our country has created a mythology of women who are irresponsible and don't care,&quot; says Paltrow.  &quot;We talk about welfare queens, crack moms, and murderous women who have abortions.&quot; A culture that allows such language to permeate our national subconscious inevitably dehumanizes all women, including mothers. Lyon argues that this thinking perpetuates a phrase often invoked in exam rooms and delivery rooms: The goal is to have a healthy baby.  &quot;This phrase is used over and over and over to shut down women's requests,&quot; she says.  &quot;The context needs to be that the goal is a healthy mom.  Because mothers never make decisions without thinking about that healthy baby.  And to suggest otherwise is insulting and degrading and disrespectful.&quot; 
What's best for women is best for babies. 
...
The goal is to have a healthy family.  " -- Jennifer Block]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116083-a-absorbed-in-our-discussion-of-immortality-we-had-let</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2008 09:37:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/116083-a-absorbed-in-our-discussion-of-immortality-we-had-let]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A: Absorbed in our discussion of immortality, we had let night fall without lighting the lamp, and we couldn't see each other's faces. With an offhandedness or gentleness more convincing than passion would have been, Macedonio Fernandez' voice said once more that the soul is immortal. He assured me that the death of the body is altogether insignificant, and that dying has to be the most unimportant thing that can happen to a man.  I was playing with Macedonio's pocketknife, opening and closing it. A nearby accordion was infinitely dispatching La Comparsita, that dismaying trifle that so many people like because it's been misrepresented to them as being old... I suggested to Macedonio that we kill ourselves, so we might have our discussion without all that racket. 
Z: (mockingly) But I suspect that at the last moment you reconsidered. 
A: (now deep in mysticism) Quite frankly, I don't remember whether we committed suicide that night or not." -- Jorge Luis Borges]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218578-from-diana-to-deborah-8-may-1998-talking-of-language</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 19:59:28 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Charlotte Mosley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218578-from-diana-to-deborah-8-may-1998-talking-of-language]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["(from Diana to Deborah, 8 May 1998)
Talking of language difficulty Tony Lambton says Selwyn Lloyd introduced him to Khrushchev saying 'He's the best shot in England,' and the translator said 'Lord Lambton is to be shot tomorrow.'  Khrushchev thought it quite normal but patted him on the shoulder kindly." -- Charlotte Mosley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231597-but-i-think-she-would-have-been-happy-with-fabrice</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2010 12:37:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Nancy Mitford]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/231597-but-i-think-she-would-have-been-happy-with-fabrice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But I think she would have been happy with Fabrice,' I said.  'He was the great love of her life, you know.'
Oh, dulling,' said my mother, sadly.  'One always thinks that.  Every, every time." -- Nancy Mitford]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242208-a-ballad-of-going-down-to-the-store-first-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 20:46:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Ilya Kaminsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242208-a-ballad-of-going-down-to-the-store-first-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A Ballad of Going Down to the Store

First I went down to the street
by means of the stairs, 
just imagine it, 
by means of the stairs.  

Then people known to people unknown
passed me by and I passed them by. 
Regret
that you did not see
how people walk,
regret!

I entered a complete store:
lamps of glass were glowing. 
I saw somebody - he sat down - 
and what did I hear? what did I hear? 
rustling of bags and human talk. 

And indeed,
indeed,
I returned. 

--Miron Bialoszewski (Poland, 1922-1983)" -- Ilya Kaminsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144250-you-re-not-dostoevsky-said-the-citizeness-who-was-getting-muddled</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2010 12:18:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Mikhail Bulgakov]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144250-you-re-not-dostoevsky-said-the-citizeness-who-was-getting-muddled]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're not Dostoevsky,' said the citizeness, who was getting muddled by Koroviev. Well, who knows, who knows,' he replied.
    'Dostoevsky's dead,' said the citizeness, but somehow not very confidently.
    'I protest!' Behemoth exclaimed hotly. 'Dostoevsky is immortal!" -- Mikhail Bulgakov]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318741-the-outing-an-outburst-of-anger-near-the-road-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 21:17:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/318741-the-outing-an-outburst-of-anger-near-the-road-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Outing

An outburst of anger near the road, a refusal to speak on the path, a silence in the pine woods, a silence across the old railroad bridge, an attempt to be friendly in the water, a refusal to end the argument on the flat stones, a cry of anger on the steep bank of dirt, a weeping among the bushes." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420417-it-is-hard-for-people-who-have-not-lived-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 08:11:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/420417-it-is-hard-for-people-who-have-not-lived-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is hard for people who have not lived in Los Angeles to realize how radically the Santa Ana figures in the local imagination. The city burning is Los Angeles's deepest image of itself; Nathanael West perceived that, in The Day of the Locust; and at the time of the 1965 Watts riots what struck the imagination most indelibly were the fires.  For days one could drive the Harbor Freeway and see the city on fire, just as we had always known it would be in the end. Los Angeles weather is the weather of catastrophe, of apocalypse, and, just as the reliably long and bitter winters of New England determine the way life is lived there, so the violence and the unpredictability of the Santa Ana affect the entire quality of life in Los Angeles, accentuate its impermanence, its unreliability. The wind shows us how close to the edge we are." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4368-when-the-shadow-of-the-sash-appeared-on-the-curtains</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2011 08:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by William Faulkner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4368-when-the-shadow-of-the-sash-appeared-on-the-curtains]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the shadow of the sash appeared on the curtains it was between seven and eight o' clock and then I was in time again, hearing the watch. It was Grandfather's and when Father gave it to me he said I give you the mausoleum of all hope and desire; it's rather excruciating-ly apt that you will use it to gain the reducto absurdum of all human experience which can fit your individual needs no better than it fitted his or his father's. I give it to you not that you may remember time, but that you might forget it now and then for a moment and not spend all your breath trying to conquer it. Because no battle is ever won he said. They are not even fought. The field only reveals to man his own folly and despair, and victory is an illusion of philosophers and fools." -- William Faulkner]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35178-but-the-fact-of-it-was-that-i-liked-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2013 00:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35178-but-the-fact-of-it-was-that-i-liked-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the fact of it was that I liked it out there, a ruin devoid of human vanities, clean of human illusions, an empty place reclaimed by the weather where a woman plays an organ to stop the wind's whining and an old man plays ball with a dog named Duke.  I could tell you that I came back because I had promises to keep, but maybe it was because nobody asked me to stay. " -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93593-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 19:01:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Shirley Jackson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/93593-no-live-organism-can-continue-for-long-to-exist-sanely]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No live organism can continue for long to exist sanely under conditions of absolute reality; even larks and katydids are supposed, by some, to dream. Hill House, not sane, stood by itself against its hills, holding darkness within; it had stood so for eighty years and might stand for eighty more. Within, walls continued upright, bricks met neatly, floors were firm, and doors were sensibly shut; silence lay steadily against the wood and stone of Hill House, and whatever walked there, walked alone." -- Shirley Jackson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439211-can-a-man-who-s-warm-understand-one-who-s-freezing</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 10:27:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/439211-can-a-man-who-s-warm-understand-one-who-s-freezing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Can a man who's warm understand one who's freezing?" -- Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813326-like-a-tropical-storm-i-too-may-one-day-become</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 22:52:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Lydia Davis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/813326-like-a-tropical-storm-i-too-may-one-day-become]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like a tropical storm, I, too, may one day become ‘better organized." -- Lydia Davis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288117-next-please-always-too-eager-for-the-future-we-pick</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2013 02:26:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Gail add a quote by Philip Larkin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/288117-next-please-always-too-eager-for-the-future-we-pick]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["&lt;b&gt;Next, Please&lt;/b&gt;

Always too eager for the future, we
Pick up bad habits of expectancy.
Something is always approaching; every day
Till then we say,

Watching from a bluff the tiny, clear
Sparkling armada of promises draw near.
How slow they are! And how much time they waste,
Refusing to make haste!

Yet still they leave us holding wretched stalks
Of disappointment, for, though nothing balks
Each big approach, leaning with brasswork prinked,
Each rope distinct,

Flagged, and the figurehead with golden tits
Arching our way, it never anchors; it's
No sooner present than it turns to past.
Right to the last

We think each one will heave to and unload
All good into our lives, all we are owed
For waiting so devoutly and so long.
But we are wrong:

Only one ship is seeking us, a black-
Sailed unfamiliar, towing at her back
A huge and birdless silence. In her wake
No waters breed or break." -- Philip Larkin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
