<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/988141-chantelle]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/988141-chantelle" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 21:08:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186601-what-is-morality-she-asked-judgement-to-distinguish-right-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 21:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chantelle add a quote by Ayn Rand]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186601-what-is-morality-she-asked-judgement-to-distinguish-right-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is morality, she asked.
Judgement to distinguish right and wrong, vision to see the truth, and courage to act upon it, dedication to that which is good, integrity to stand by the good at any price. " -- Ayn Rand]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117517-children-should-draw-a-husband-wife</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 09:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chantelle add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/117517-children-should-draw-a-husband-wife]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA[". . . children should draw [a husband &amp; wife] nearer than ever, not separate you, as if they were all yours, and [your husband] had nothing to do but support them. . . . don't neglect husaband for children, don't shut him out of the nursery, but teach him how to help in it. His place is there as well as yours, and the children need him; let him feel that he has his part to do, and he will do it gladly and faithfully, and it will be better for you all. . . . That is the secret of our home happiness: he does not let business wean him from the little cares and duties that affect us all, and I try not to let domestic worries destroy my interest in his pursuits. Each do our part alone in many things, but at home we work together, always. . . . no time is so beautiful and precious to parents as the first years of the little lives given them to train. Don't let [your husband] be a stranger to the babies, for they will do more to keep him safe and happy in this world of trial and temptation than anything else, and through them you will learn to know and love one another as you should." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
