<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/988766-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/988766-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:38:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2690-i-went-to-the-woods-because-i-wished-to-live]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I went to the woods because I wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and see if I could not learn what it had to teach, and not, when I came to die, discover that I had not lived. I did not wish to live what was not life, living is so dear; nor did I wish to practise resignation, unless it was quite necessary. I wanted to live deep and suck out all the marrow of life, to live so sturdily and Spartan-like as to put to rout all that was not life, to cut a broad swath and shave close, to drive life into a corner, and reduce it to its lowest terms." -- Henry David Thoreau]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44341-a-library-is-not-a-luxury-but-one-of-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:41:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44341-a-library-is-not-a-luxury-but-one-of-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A library is not a luxury but one of the necessities of life." -- Henry Ward Beecher]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:56:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4641-jane-be-still-don-t-struggle-so-like-a-wild-frantic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Jane, be still; don't struggle so like a wild, frantic bird, that is rending its own plumage in its desperation.&quot;
&quot;I am no bird; and no net ensnares me; I am a free human being, with an independent will; which I now exert to leave you." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 14:17:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by C.S. Lewis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15139-i-am-a-product-of-endless-books-my-father-bought]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am a product [...of] endless books. My father bought all the books he read and never got rid of any of them. There were books in the study, books in the drawing room, books in the cloakroom, books (two deep) in the great bookcase on the landing, books in a bedroom, books piled as high as my shoulder in the cistern attic, books of all kinds reflecting every transient stage of my parents' interest, books readable and unreadable, books suitable for a child and books most emphatically not. Nothing was forbidden me. In the seemingly endless rainy afternoons I took volume after volume from the shelves. I had always the same certainty of finding a book that was new to me as a man who walks into a field has of finding a new blade of grass." -- C.S. Lewis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:57:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/38257-there-is-no-happiness-like-that-of-being-loved-by]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no happiness like that of being loved by your fellow creatures, and feeling that your presence is an addition to their comfort." -- Charlotte Brontë]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 14:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the most tired woman in the world. I am tired when I get up. Life requires an effort I cannot make. Please give me that heavy book. I need to put something heavy like that on top of my head. I have to place my feet under the pillows always, so as to be able to stay on earth. Otherwise I feel myself going away, going away at a tremendous speed, on account of my lightness. I know that I am dead. As soon as I utter a phrase my sincerity dies, becomes a lie whose coldness chills me. Don't say anything, because I see that you understand me, and I am afraid of your understanding. I have such a fear of finding another like myself, and such a desire to find one! I am so utterly lonely, but I also have such a fear that my isolation be broken through, and I no longer be the head and ruler of my universe. I am in great terror of your understanding by which you penetrate into my world; and then I stand revealed and I have to share my kingdom with you." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24384-life-is-a-process-of-becoming-a-combination-of-states</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 14:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by ANAIS NIN]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/24384-life-is-a-process-of-becoming-a-combination-of-states]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is a process of becoming, a combination of states we have to go through. Where people fail is that they wish to elect a state and remain in it. This is a kind of death." -- ANAIS NIN]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27860-life-is-so-constructed-that-an-event-does-not-cannot</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:58:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27860-life-is-so-constructed-that-an-event-does-not-cannot]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is so constructed that an event does not, cannot, will not, match the expectation." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 14:11:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66336-pain-and-suffering-are-always-inevitable-for-a-large-intelligence]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Pain and suffering are always inevitable for a large intelligence and a deep heart. The really great men must, I think, have great sadness on earth." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65976-life-is-truly-known-only-to-those-who-suffer-lose</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 15:02:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by anaïs nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65976-life-is-truly-known-only-to-those-who-suffer-lose]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["life is truly known only to those who suffer, lose, endure adversity, &amp; stumble from defeat to defeat." -- anaïs nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 15:02:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7142-all-happy-families-are-alike-each-unhappy-family-is-unhappy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All happy families are alike; each unhappy family is unhappy in its own way." -- Leo Tolstoy  ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11097-freethinkers-are-those-who-are-willing-to-use-their-minds</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 15:02:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11097-freethinkers-are-those-who-are-willing-to-use-their-minds]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Freethinkers are those who are willing to use their minds without prejudice and without fearing to understand things that clash with their own customs, privileges, or beliefs. This state of mind is not common, but it is essential for right thinking..." -- Leo Tolstoy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1590-i-don-t-want-to-be-at-the-mercy-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 14:12:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1590-i-don-t-want-to-be-at-the-mercy-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't want to be at the mercy of my emotions. I want to use them, to enjoy them, and to dominate them." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22876-a-ruffled-mind-makes-a-restless-pillow</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22876-a-ruffled-mind-makes-a-restless-pillow]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A ruffled mind makes a restless pillow." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23764-better-to-be-without-logic-than-without-feeling</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:58:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23764-better-to-be-without-logic-than-without-feeling]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Better to be without logic than without feeling." -- Charlotte Brontë ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/913-the-aim-of-life-is-self-development-to-realize-one-s-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 22:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Oscar Wilde]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/913-the-aim-of-life-is-self-development-to-realize-one-s-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The aim of life is self-development. To realize one's nature perfectly - that is what each of us is here for." -- Oscar Wilde]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:01:11 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bob Moorehead]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22242-the-paradox-of-our-time-in-history-is-that-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The paradox of our time in history is that we have taller buildings but 
shorter tempers, wider Freeways, but narrower viewpoints.  We spend more, 
but have less, we buy more, but enjoy less. We have bigger houses and 
smaller families, more conveniences, but less time.  We have more degrees 
but less sense, more knowledge, but less judgment, more experts, yet more 
problems, more medicine, but less wellness.

We drink too much, smoke too much, spend too recklessly, laugh too little, 
drive too fast, get too angry, stay up too late, get up too tired, read too 
little, watch TV too much, and pray too seldom.  We have multiplied our 
possessions, but reduced our values.  We talk too much, love too seldom, and 
hate too often.

We've learned how to make a living, but not a life. We've added years to 
life not life to years.  We've been all the way to the moon and back, but 
have trouble crossing the street to meet a new neighbor.  We conquered outer 
space but not inner space.  We've done larger things, but not better things.

We've cleaned up the air, but polluted the soul. We've conquered the atom, 
but not our prejudice.  We write more, but learn less.  We plan more, but 
accomplish less.  We've learned to rush, but not to wait.  We build more 
computers to hold more information, to produce more copies than ever, but we 
communicate less and less.

These are the times of fast foods and slow digestion, big men and small 
character, steep profits and shallow relationships.

These are the days of two incomes but more divorce, fancier houses, but 
broken homes.  These are days of quick trips, disposable diapers, throwaway 
morality, one night stands, overweight bodies, and pills that do everything 
from cheer, to quiet, to kill.  It is a time when there is much in the 
showroom window and nothing in the stockroom.  A time when technology can 
bring this letter to you, and a time when you can choose either to share 
this insight, or to just hit delete...

Remember, to spend some time with your loved ones, because they are not 
going to be around forever.  Remember, say a kind word to someone who looks 
up to you in awe, because that little person soon will grow up and leave 
your side.

Remember, to give a warm hug to the one next to you, because that is the 
only treasure you can give with your heart and it doesn't cost a cent.

Remember, to say, &quot;I love you&quot; to your partner and your loved ones, but most 
of all mean it.  A kiss and an embrace will mend hurt when it comes from 
deep inside of you.

Remember to hold hands and cherish the moment for someday that person might 
not be there again.  Give time to love, give time to speak! And give time to 
share the precious thoughts in your mind." -- Bob Moorehead]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:03:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Shel Silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7096-listen-to-the-mustn-ts-child-listen-to-the-don-ts-listen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Listen to the mustn'ts, child. Listen to the don'ts. Listen to the shouldn'ts, the impossibles, the won'ts. Listen to the never haves, then listen close to me... Anything can happen, child. Anything can be." -- Shel Silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27897-it-was-missing-a-piece-and-it-was-not-happy</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:03:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by shel silverstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27897-it-was-missing-a-piece-and-it-was-not-happy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was missing a piece.
And it was not happy.
So it set off in search
of its missing piece.
And as it rolled
it sang this song - &quot;Oh I'm lookin' for my missin' piece
I'm lookin' for my missin' piece
Hi-dee-ho, here I go,
Lookin' for my missin' piece." -- shel silverstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4231-when-we-strive-to-become-better-than-we-are-everything</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:04:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4231-when-we-strive-to-become-better-than-we-are-everything]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better, too." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10502-remember-that-wherever-your-heart-is-there-you-will-find</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:04:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10502-remember-that-wherever-your-heart-is-there-you-will-find]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Remember that wherever your heart is, there you will find your treasure." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17552-humankind-cannot-gain-something-without-first-giving-something-in-return</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:04:51 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17552-humankind-cannot-gain-something-without-first-giving-something-in-return]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humankind cannot gain something without first giving something in return. To obtain, something of equal value must be lost. This is Alchemy's First Law of Equivalent Exchange. In those days, we really believed that to be the world's one, and only, truth." -- Hiromu Arakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:04:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15864-everyone-seems-to-have-a-clear-idea-of-how-other]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everyone seems to have a clear idea of how other people should lead their lives, but none about his or her own." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430-life-is-too-short-or-too-long-for-me-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:06:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/430-life-is-too-short-or-too-long-for-me-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is too short, or too long, for me to allow myself the luxury of living it so badly." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9616-everything-tells-me-that-i-am-about-to-make-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:06:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9616-everything-tells-me-that-i-am-about-to-make-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything tells me that I am about to make a wrong decision, but making mistakes is just part of life. What does the world want of me? Does it want me to take no risks, to go back to where I came from because I didn't have the courage to say &quot;yes&quot; to life?" -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16154-we-are-afraid-of-losing-what-we-have-whether-it-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:06:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16154-we-are-afraid-of-losing-what-we-have-whether-it-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are afraid of losing what we have, whether it's our life or our possessions and property. But this fear evaporates when we understand that our life stories and the history of the world were written by the same hand." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:07:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12405-tell-your-heart-that-the-fear-of-suffering-is-worse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell your heart that the fear of suffering is worse than the suffering itself. And that no heart has ever suffered when it goes in search of its dreams, because every second of the search is a second's encounter with God and with eternity." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12948-life-always-waits-for-some-crisis-to-occur-before-revealing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:07:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12948-life-always-waits-for-some-crisis-to-occur-before-revealing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life always waits for some crisis to occur before revealing itself at its most brilliant." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15756-it-is-said-that-the-darkest-hour-of-the-night</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:07:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Thomas Fuller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15756-it-is-said-that-the-darkest-hour-of-the-night]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It  is said that the darkest hour of the night comes just before the dawn." -- Thomas Fuller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2831-what-is-hell-i-maintain-that-it-is-the-suffering</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 23:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2831-what-is-hell-i-maintain-that-it-is-the-suffering]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What is hell? I maintain that it is the suffering of being unable to love." -- Fyodor Dostoevsky]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
