<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/989283-chris-pisarczyk]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/989283-chris-pisarczyk" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 14:30:06 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3046-i-tell-you-we-are-here-on-earth-to-fart</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 14:30:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3046-i-tell-you-we-are-here-on-earth-to-fart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I tell you, we are here on Earth to fart around, and don't let anybody tell you different." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801-my-alma-mater-was-books-a-good-library-i-could</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 14:43:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Malcolm X]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/801-my-alma-mater-was-books-a-good-library-i-could]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My alma mater was books, a good library.... I could spend the rest of my life reading, just satisfying my curiosity." -- Malcolm X]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11132-every-moment-in-your-life-is-a-turning-and-every</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2008 14:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11132-every-moment-in-your-life-is-a-turning-and-every]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Every moment in your life is a turning and every one a choosing. Somewhere you made a choice. All followed to this. The accounting is scrupulous. The shape is drawn. No line can be erased. I had no belief in your ability to move a coin to your bidding. How could you? A person's path through the world seldom changes and even more seldom will it change abruptly. And the shape of your path was visible from the beginning." -- Cormac McCarthy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 21:27:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Joshua Ferris]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11811-yet-for-all-the-depression-no-one-ever-quit-when]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Yet for all the depression no one ever quit.  When someone quit, we couldn't believe it. 'I'm becoming a rafting instructor on the Colorado River,' they said.  'I'm touring college towns with my garage band.'  We were dumbfounded. It was like they were from another planet.  Where had they found the derring-do?  What would they do about car payments?  We got together for going away drinks on their final day and tried to hide our envy while reminding ourselves that we still had the freedom and luxury to shop indiscriminately." -- Joshua Ferris]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40782-be-thankful-that-you-have-a-life-and-forsake-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2008 11:15:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Richard Dawkins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40782-be-thankful-that-you-have-a-life-and-forsake-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be thankful that you have a life, and forsake your vain and presumptuous desire for a second one." -- Richard Dawkins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69703-people-who-see-life-as-anything-more-than-pure-entertainment</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2008 14:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by George Carlin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/69703-people-who-see-life-as-anything-more-than-pure-entertainment]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People who see life as anything more than pure entertainment are missing the point." -- George Carlin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13797-like-so-many-americans-she-was-trying-to-construct-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2008 13:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13797-like-so-many-americans-she-was-trying-to-construct-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Like so many Americans, she was trying to construct a life that made sense from things she found in gift shops." -- Kurt Vonnegut]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 13:02:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3172-and-i-urge-you-to-please-notice-when-you-are]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I urge you to please notice when you are happy, and exclaim or murmur or think at some point, 'If this isn't nice, I don't know what is." -- Kurt Vonnegut Jr.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14941-what-we-become-depends-on-what-we-read-after-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 09:59:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14941-what-we-become-depends-on-what-we-read-after-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What we become depends on what we read after all of the professors have finished with us.  The greatest university of all is a collection of books." -- Thomas Carlyle]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77686-we-can-spend-our-lives-letting-the-world-tell-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2008 09:42:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77686-we-can-spend-our-lives-letting-the-world-tell-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We can spend our lives letting the world tell us who we are. Sane or insane. Saints or sex addicts. Heroes or victims. Letting history tell us how good or bad we are. Letting our past decide our future. Or we can decide for ourselves. And maybe it's our job to invent something better." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108047-i-merely-say-that-all-reading-for-pleasure-is-escape</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 13:30:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/108047-i-merely-say-that-all-reading-for-pleasure-is-escape]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I merely say that all reading for pleasure is escape, whether it be Greek, mathematics, astronomy, Benedetto Croce, or The Diary of the Forgotten Man. To say otherwise is to be an intellectual snob, and a juvenile at the art of living." -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 13:49:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Raymond Chandler]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/39985-in-everything-that-can-be-called-art-there-is-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In everything that can be called art there is a quality of redemption. It may be pure tragedy, if it is high tragedy, and it may be pity and irony, and it may be the raucous laughter of the strong man. But down these mean streets a man must go who is not himself mean, who is neither tarnished nor afraid.

The detective in this kind of story must be such a man. He is the hero; he is everything. He must be a complete man and a common man and yet an unusual man. He must be, to use a rather weathered phrase, a man of honor -- by instinct, by inevitability, without thought of it, and certainly without saying it. He must be the best man in his world and a good enough man for any world. I do not care much about his private life; he is neither a eunuch nor a satyr; I think he might seduce a duchess and I am quite sure he would not spoil a virgin; if he is a man of honor in one thing, he is that in all things.

He is a relatively poor man, or he would not be a detective at all. He is a common man or he could not go among common people. He has a sense of character, or he would not know his job. He will take no man's money dishonestly and no man's insolence without due and dispassionate revenge. He is a lonely man and his pride is that you will treat  him as a proud man or be very sorry you ever saw him. He talks as the man of his age talks -- that is, with rude wit, a lively sense of the grotesque, a disgust for sham, and a contempt for pettiness.

The story is the man's adventure in search of a hidden truth, and it would be no adventure if it did not happen to a man fit for adventure. He has a range of awareness that startles you, but it belongs to him by right, because it belongs to the world he lives in. If there  were enough like him, the world would be a very safe place to live in, without becoming too dull to be worth living in.  " -- Raymond Chandler]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122315-i-can-t-understand-why-a-person-will-take-a-year</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 19:49:25 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Fred Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/122315-i-can-t-understand-why-a-person-will-take-a-year]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I can't understand why a person will take a year or two to write a novel when he can easily buy one for a few dollars." -- Fred Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2009 13:44:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2253-live-as-if-you-were-to-die-tomorrow-learn-as]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever." -- Mahatma Gandhi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65705-progress-isn-t-made-by-early-risers-it-s-made-by-lazy</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2009 08:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Robert Heinlein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/65705-progress-isn-t-made-by-early-risers-it-s-made-by-lazy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Progress isn't made by early risers. It's made by lazy men trying to find easier ways to do something." -- Robert Heinlein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2009 13:42:38 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Mark Twain]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/4-whenever-you-find-yourself-on-the-side-of-the-majority]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect." -- Mark Twain]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21-man-is-so-intelligent-that-he-feels-impelled-to-invent</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 14:05:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21-man-is-so-intelligent-that-he-feels-impelled-to-invent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Man is so intelligent that he feels impelled to invent theories to account for what happens in the world.  Unfortunately, he is not quite intelligent enough, in most cases, to find correct explanations. So that when he acts on his theories, he behaves very often like a lunatic." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16293-that-men-do-not-learn-very-much-from-the-lessons</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 14:07:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16293-that-men-do-not-learn-very-much-from-the-lessons]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That men do not learn very much from the lessons of history is the most important of all the lessons that history has to teach." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19561-you-never-see-animals-going-through-the-absurd-and-often</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2009 14:18:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Aldous Huxley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19561-you-never-see-animals-going-through-the-absurd-and-often]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You never see animals going through the absurd and often horrible fooleries of magic and religion. . . . Dogs do not ritually urinate in the hope of persuading heaven to do the same and send down rain. Asses do not bray a liturgy to cloudless skies. Nor do cats attempt, by abstinence from cat's meat, to wheedle the feline spirits into benevolence. Only man behaves with such gratuitous folly. It is the price he has to pay for being intelligent but not, as yet, quite intelligent enough." -- Aldous Huxley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178828-a-couple-of-months-ago-i-became-depressed-by-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 13:33:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Nick Hornby]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/178828-a-couple-of-months-ago-i-became-depressed-by-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A couple of months ago, I became depressed by the realization that I'd forgotten pretty much everything I've ever read. I have, however, bounced back: I am now cheered by the realization that if I've forgotten everything I've ever read then I can read some of my favorite books again &lt;i&gt;as if for the first time&lt;/i&gt;." -- Nick Hornby]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53739-it-was-true-that-i-didn-t-have-much-ambition-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 11:21:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53739-it-was-true-that-i-didn-t-have-much-ambition-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was true that I didn’t have much ambition, but there ought to be a place for people without ambition, I mean a better place than the one usually reserved. How in the hell could a man enjoy being awakened at 6:30 a.m. by an alarm clock, leap out of bed, dress, force-feed, shit, piss, brush teeth and hair, and fight traffic to get to a place where essentially you made lots of money for somebody else and were asked to be grateful for the opportunity to do so?" -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54787-the-difference-between-a-democracy-and-a-dictatorship-is-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 11:22:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Bukowski C.]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54787-the-difference-between-a-democracy-and-a-dictatorship-is-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The difference between a democracy and a dictatorship is that in a democracy you vote first and take orders later; in a dictatorship you don't have to waste your time voting" -- Bukowski C.]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128870-there-s-nothing-to-mourn-about-death-any-more-than-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 12:01:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/128870-there-s-nothing-to-mourn-about-death-any-more-than-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There's nothing to mourn about death any more than there is to mourn about the growing of a flower. What is terrible is not death but the lives people live or don't live up until their death. They don't honor their own lives, they piss on their lives. They shit them away. Dumb fuckers. They concentrate too much on fucking, movies, money, family, fucking. Their minds are full of cotton. They swallow God without thinking, they swallow country without thinking. Soon they forget how to think, they let others think for them. Their brains are stuffed with cotton. They look ugly, they talk ugly, they walk ugly. Play them the great music of the centuries and they can't hear it. Most people's deaths are a sham. There's nothing left to die." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111163-that-was-all-a-man-needed-hope-it-was-lack</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 12:26:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Charles Bukowski]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/111163-that-was-all-a-man-needed-hope-it-was-lack]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That was all a man needed: hope.  It was lack of hope that discouraged a man." -- Charles Bukowski]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90634-sometimes-immersed-in-his-books-there-would-come-to-him</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 13:29:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by John Edward Williams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/90634-sometimes-immersed-in-his-books-there-would-come-to-him]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sometimes, immersed in his books, there would come to him the awareness of all that he did not know, of all that he had not read; and the serenity for which he labored was shattered as he realized the little time he had in life to read so much, to learn what he had to know." -- John Edward Williams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58139-what-good-is-knowledge-if-it-just-floats-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 20:40:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Don DeLillo]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58139-what-good-is-knowledge-if-it-just-floats-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What good is knowledge if it just floats in the air? It goes from computer to computer. It changes and grows every second of every day. But nobody actually knows anything." -- Don DeLillo]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223954-the-sophists-had-this-idea-forget-this-idea-of-what-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 14:48:18 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/223954-the-sophists-had-this-idea-forget-this-idea-of-what-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The Sophists had this idea: Forget this idea of what's true or not—what you want to do is rhetoric; you want to be able to persuade the audience and have the audience think you're smart and cool. And Socrates and Plato, basically their whole idea is, &quot;Bullshit. There is such a thing as truth, and it's not all just how to say what you say so that you get a good job or get laid, or whatever it is people think they want." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54522-but-the-problem-with-readers-the-idea-we-re-given-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 11:24:46 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Zadie Smith]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/54522-but-the-problem-with-readers-the-idea-we-re-given-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But the problem with readers, the idea we're given of reading is that the model of a reader is the person watching a film, or watching television. So the greatest principle is, &quot;I should sit here and I should be entertained.&quot; And the more classical model, which has been completely taken away, is the idea of a reader as an amateur musician. An amateur musician who sits at the piano, has a piece of music, which is the work, made by somebody they don't know, who they probably couldn't comprehend entirely, and they have to use their skills to play this piece of music. The greater the skill, the greater the gift that you give the artist and that the artist gives you. That's the incredibly unfashionable idea of reading. And yet when you practice reading, and you work at a text, it can only give you what you put into it. It's an old moral, but it's completely true." -- Zadie Smith]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162504-there-is-no-shortage-of-good-days-it-is-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2010 21:20:59 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Chris add a quote by Annie Dillard]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/162504-there-is-no-shortage-of-good-days-it-is-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is no shortage of good days.  It is good lives that are hard to come by.  A life of good days lived in the senses is not enough.  The life of sensation is the life of greed; it requires more and more.  The life of the spirit requires less and less; time is ample and its passage sweet.  Who would call a day spent reading a good day?  But a life spent reading -- that is a good life." -- Annie Dillard]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
