<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/990-diego]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/990-diego" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 16:26:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764841-morrie-talked-about-his-most-fearful-moments-when-he-felt</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2013 16:26:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/764841-morrie-talked-about-his-most-fearful-moments-when-he-felt]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Morrie talked about his most fearful moments, when he felt his chest locked in heaving surges or when he wasn't sure where his next breath would come from. These horrifying times, he said, and his first emotions were horror, fear, anxiety. But once he recognized the feel of those emotions, their texture, their moisture, the shiver down the back, the quick flash of heat that crosses your brain - then he was able to say, &quot;Okay,. This is fear. Step away from it. Step away." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776645-as-my-visits-with-morrie-go-on-i-begin-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2013 23:58:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/776645-as-my-visits-with-morrie-go-on-i-begin-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["As my visits with Morrie go on, I begin to read about death, how different cultures view the final passage. There is a tribe in the North American Arctic, for example, who believe that all things on earth have a soul that exists in a miniature form of the body that hold it -so that a deer has a tiny deer inside it, and a man has a tiny man inside him. When the large being dies, that tiny form lives on. It can slide into something being born nearby, or it can go to a temporary resting place in the sky, in the belly of a great feminine spirit, where it waits until the moon can send it back to earth.

Sometimes, they say, the moon is so busy with the new souls of the world that it disappears from the sky. That is why we have moonless nights. But in the end, the moon always returns, as do we all.

That is what they believe." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269526-most-of-us-all-walk-around-as-if-we-re-sleepwalking</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 14:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Diego add a quote by Mitch Albom]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/269526-most-of-us-all-walk-around-as-if-we-re-sleepwalking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Most of us all walk around as if we're sleepwalking. We really don't experience the world fully, because we're half-asleep, doing things we automatically think we have to do." -- Mitch Albom]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
