<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/991494-ursula]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/991494-ursula" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 10:42:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158271-knowing-that-everything-comes-to-an-end-is-a-gift</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 10:42:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Tobias Wolff]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/158271-knowing-that-everything-comes-to-an-end-is-a-gift]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing that everything comes to an end is a gift of experience, a consolation gift for knowing that we ourselves are coming to an end.  Before we get it we live in a continuous present, and imagine the future as more of that present.  Happiness is endless happiness, innocent of its own sure passing.  Pain is endless pain." -- Tobias Wolff]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 21:00:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26290-the-weather-had-freshened-almost-to-coldness-for-the-wind]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The weather had freshened almost to coldness, for the wind was coming more easterly, from the chilly currents between Tristan and the Cape; the sloth was amazed by the change; it shunned the deck and spent its time below. Jack was in his cabin, pricking the chart with less satisfaction than he could have wished: progress, slow, serious trouble with the mainmast-- unaccountable headwinds by night-- and sipping a glass of grog; Stephen was in the mizentop, teaching Bonden to write and scanning the sea for his first albatross. The sloth sneezed, and looking up, Jack caught its gaze fixed upon him; its inverted face had an expression of anxiety and concern. 'Try a piece of this, old cock,' he said, dipping his cake in the grog and proffering the sop. 'It might put a little heart into you.' The sloth sighed, closed its eyes, but gently absorbed the piece, and sighed again.

    Some minutes later he felt a touch upon his knee: the sloth had silently climbed down and it was standing there, its beady eyes looking up into his face, bright with expectation. More cake, more grog: growing confidence and esteem. After this, as soon as the drum had beat the retreat, the sloth would meet him, hurrying toward the door on its uneven legs: it was given its own bowl, and it would grip it with its claws, lowering its round face into it and pursing its lips to drink (its tongue was too short to lap). Sometimes it went to sleep in this position, bowed over the emptiness.

    'In this bucket,' said Stephen, walking into the cabin, 'in this small half-bucket, now, I have the population of Dublin, London, and Paris combined: these animalculae-- what is the matter with the sloth?' It was curled on Jack's knee, breathing heavily: its bowl and Jack's glass stood empty on the table. Stephen picked it up, peered into its affable bleary face, shook it, and hung it upon its rope. It seized hold with one fore and one hind foot, letting the others dangle limp, and went to sleep.

    Stephen looked sharply round, saw the decanter, smelt to the sloth, and cried, 'Jack, you have debauched my sloth." -- Patrick O'Brian]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258046-she-often-spoke-to-falling-seeds-and-said-ah-hope</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 18:51:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258046-she-often-spoke-to-falling-seeds-and-said-ah-hope]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She often spoke to falling seeds and said, &quot;Ah hope you fall on soft ground,&quot; because she had heard seeds saying that to each other as they passed. The familiar people and things had failed her so she hung over the gate and looked up the road towards way off. She knew now that marriage did not make love. Janie's first dream was dead, so she became a woman." -- Zora Neale Hurston]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292191-she-is-leaving-him-not-all-at-once-which-would</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 21:38:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Debra Dean]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/292191-she-is-leaving-him-not-all-at-once-which-would]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is leaving him, not all at once, which would be painful enough, but in a wrenching succession of separations. One moment she is here, and then she is gone again, and each journey takes her a little farther from his reach. He cannot follow her, and he wonders where she goes when she leaves." -- Debra Dean]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299692-scientists-want-to-search-for-alien-signals-because-that-s-what</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2010 16:57:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Manu Joseph]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299692-scientists-want-to-search-for-alien-signals-because-that-s-what]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Scientists want to search for alien signals because that's what gets them publicity. They are like Jesus Christ.&quot;

&quot;Jesus Christ?&quot; Nambodri asked, with a faintly derogatory chuckle.

&quot;Yes. They are exactly like Jesus Christ. You know that he turned water into wine.&quot;

&quot;I've heard that story.&quot;

&quot;From the point of view of pure chemistry, it is more miraculous to make wine into water than water into wine. But he did not do that. Because if he had gone to someone's house and converted their wine into water, they would have crucified him much earlier. He knew, Jana. He knew making water into wine was a more popular thing to do." -- Manu Joseph]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167714-some-people-i-am-told-have-memories-like-computers-nothing</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 07:46:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ursula add a quote by Wallace Stegner]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167714-some-people-i-am-told-have-memories-like-computers-nothing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Some people, I am told, have memories like computers, nothing to do but punch the button and wait for the print-out.  Mine is more like a Japanese library of the old style, without a card file or an indexing system or any systematic shelf plan.  Nobody knows where anything is except the old geezer in felt slippers who has been shuffling up and down those stacks for sixty-nine years.  When you hand him a problem he doesn't come back with a cartful and dump it before you, a jackpot of instant retrieval.  He finds one thing, which reminds him of another, which leads him off to the annex, which directs him to the east wing, which sends him back two tiers from where he started.  Bit by bit he finds you what you want, but like his boss who seems to be under pressure to examine his life, he takes his time." -- Wallace Stegner]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
