<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/991848-jacob]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/991848-jacob" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:06:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148981-either-greed-belongs-in-a-war-zone-or-it-doesn-t</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:06:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148981-either-greed-belongs-in-a-war-zone-or-it-doesn-t]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Either greed belongs in a war zone, or it doesn't. You can't unleash it in the name of sparking an economic boom and then be shocked when Halliburton overcharges for everything from towels to gas, when Parsons' sub, sub, sub-contractor builds a police academy where the pipes drip raw sewage on the heads of army cadets and where Blackwater investigates itself and finds it acted honorably. That's just corporations doing what they do and Iraq is a privatized war zone so that's what you get. Build a frontier, you get cowboys and robber barons." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149103-i-wonder-if-being-sane-means-disregarding-the-chaos-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:06:43 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149103-i-wonder-if-being-sane-means-disregarding-the-chaos-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I wonder if being sane means disregarding the chaos that is life, pretending only an infinitesimal segment of it is reality." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13620-it-is-no-measure-of-health-to-be-well-adjusted</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:06:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by J. Krishnamurti]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13620-it-is-no-measure-of-health-to-be-well-adjusted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is no measure of health to be well adjusted to a profoundly sick society." -- J. Krishnamurti]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:07:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by John Steinbeck]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/328134-socialism-never-took-root-in-america-because-the-poor-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Socialism never took root in America because the poor see themselves not as an exploited proletariat but as temporarily embarrassed millionaires." -- John Steinbeck]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148980-writing-s-funny-it-s-like-walking-down-a-hall-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 07:06:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/148980-writing-s-funny-it-s-like-walking-down-a-hall-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing's funny, it's like walking down a hall in the dark looking for the light switch, and suddenly you find it, flip it on, and then you discover the hallway you passed through is papered with the novel you've written." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47778-life-s-greatest-comfort-is-being-able-to-look-over-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 08:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47778-life-s-greatest-comfort-is-being-able-to-look-over-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life's greatest comfort is being able to look over your shoulder and see people worse off, waiting in line behind you." -- Chuck Palahniuk]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149102-the-question-then-is-not-about-changing-people-it-s-about</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2009 18:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Bill Moyers]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/149102-the-question-then-is-not-about-changing-people-it-s-about]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The question, then, is not about changing people; it's about reaching people. I'm not speaking simply of better information, a sharper and clearer factual presentation to disperse the thick fogs generated by today's spin machines. Of course, we always need stronger empirical arguments to back up our case. It would certainly help if at least as many people who believe, say, in a &quot;literal devil&quot; or that God sent George W. Bush to the White House also knew that the top 1 percent of households now have more wealth than the bottom 90 percent combined. Yes, people need more information than they get from the media conglomerates with their obsession for nonsense, violence and pap. And we need, as we keep hearing, &quot;new ideas.&quot; But we are at an extraordinary moment. The conservative movement stands intellectually and morally bankrupt while Democrats talk about a &quot;new direction&quot; without convincing us they know the difference between a weather vane and a compass. The right story will set our course for a generation to come." -- Bill Moyers]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157556-to-build-a-better-world-we-need-to-replace-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2009 08:56:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/157556-to-build-a-better-world-we-need-to-replace-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To build a better world we need to replace the patchwork of lucky breaks and arbitrary advantages today that determine success--the fortunate birth dates and the happy accidents of history--with a society that provides opportunities for all." -- Malcolm Gladwell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164428-anyway-the-thing-is-that-we-need-to-understand-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2009 10:27:55 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Shlomo Ben-Ami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/164428-anyway-the-thing-is-that-we-need-to-understand-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Anyway, the thing is that we need to understand that with all — frankly, with all due respect for the requirements of international law, at the end of the day, at the end of the day, a peace process is a political enterprise. And there are things that governments can do and things that they cannot do, because if you do things that leave you without political support, then you can do nothing. You can write poetry, not make peace." -- Shlomo Ben-Ami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198046-a-story-begins-with-this-nebulous-feeling-that-s-hard-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2009 07:06:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Michael Chabon]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198046-a-story-begins-with-this-nebulous-feeling-that-s-hard-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A story begins with this nebulous feeling that’s hard to get a hold of and you’re testing your feelings and assumptions, testing what you believe. They end up turning into keepsakes and mementos –like amber in which a memory gets trapped." -- Michael Chabon]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242934-how-much-longer-is-the-world-willing-to-endure-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2010 06:26:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Bertrand Russell]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/242934-how-much-longer-is-the-world-willing-to-endure-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How much longer is the world willing to endure this spectacle of wanton cruelty?" -- Bertrand Russell]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291070-the-urge-to-know-scrapes-against-the-inability-to-know</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 07:53:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/291070-the-urge-to-know-scrapes-against-the-inability-to-know]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The urge to know scrapes against the inability to know." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366985-i-don-t-remember-when-exactly-i-read-my-first-comic</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2011 09:49:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Edward Said]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/366985-i-don-t-remember-when-exactly-i-read-my-first-comic]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I don't remember when exactly I read my first comic book, but I do remember exactly how liberated and subversive I felt as a result." -- Edward Said]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397124-praise-be-to-god-who-has-so-disposed-matters-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2011 11:21:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Ahmad Al-Tifashi]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/397124-praise-be-to-god-who-has-so-disposed-matters-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Praise be to God, Who has so disposed matters that pleasant literary anecdotes may serve as an instrument for the polishing of wits and the cleansing of rust from our hearts." -- Ahmad Al-Tifashi]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324231-to-say-a-person-is-a-happy-person-or-an</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 06:59:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/324231-to-say-a-person-is-a-happy-person-or-an]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To say a person is a happy person or an unhappy person is ridiculous. We are a thousand different kinds of people every hour." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473973-in-short-i-am-amenable-to-criticism-but-only-within</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 17:36:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/473973-in-short-i-am-amenable-to-criticism-but-only-within]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In short, I am amenable to criticism, but only within the sphere of what I am trying to do; I will not pretend to do otherwise." -- Flannery O'Connor]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431250-leave-home-leave-the-country-leave-the-familiar-only-then</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 17:36:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/431250-leave-home-leave-the-country-leave-the-familiar-only-then]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Leave home, leave the country, leave the familiar.  Only then can routine experience--buying bread, eating vegetables, even saying hello--become new all over again." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539401-by-nature-a-storyteller-is-a-plagiarist-everything-one-comes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 17:35:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/539401-by-nature-a-storyteller-is-a-plagiarist-everything-one-comes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["By nature, a storyteller is a plagiarist. Everything one comes across--each incident, book, novel, life episode, story, person, news clip--is a coffee bean that will be crushed, ground up, mixed with a touch of cardamom, sometimes a tiny pinch of salt, boiled thrice with sugar, and served as a piping-hot tale." -- Rabih Alameddine]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558247-culture-jamming-is-enjoying-a-resurgence-in-part-because-of</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 10:01:35 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Naomi Klein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/558247-culture-jamming-is-enjoying-a-resurgence-in-part-because-of]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Culture jamming is enjoying a resurgence, in part because of technological advancements but also more pertinently, because of the good old rules of supply and demand. Something not far from the surfaces of the public psyche is delighted to see the icons of corporate power subverted and mocked. There is, in short, a market for it. With commercialism able to overpower the traditional authority of religion, politics and schools, corporations have emerged a the natural targets for all sorts of free-floating rage and rebellion. The new ethos that culture jamming taps into is go-for-the-corporate-jugular." -- Naomi Klein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695488-i-want-to-be-two-people-at-once-one-runs</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 07:02:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Peter Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695488-i-want-to-be-two-people-at-once-one-runs]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I want to be two people at once. One runs away." -- Peter Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695496-that-is-what-we-are-what-we-do-nose-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2013 07:06:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Peter Heller]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/695496-that-is-what-we-are-what-we-do-nose-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["That is what we are, what we do: nose a net, push push, a net that never exists. The knots in the mesh as strong as our own believing. Our own fears." -- Peter Heller]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702313-but-to-be-perfectly-frank-this-childish-idea-that-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 06:41:09 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by John Green]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/702313-but-to-be-perfectly-frank-this-childish-idea-that-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But to be perfectly frank, this childish idea that the author of a novel has some special insight into the characters in the novel...it's ridiculous. That novel was composed of scratches on a page, dear. The characters inhabiting it have no life outside of those scratches. What happened to them? They all ceased to exist the moment the novel ended." -- John Green]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752725-how-skillful-to-tax-the-middle-class-to-pay-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2013 08:34:42 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Howard Zinn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/752725-how-skillful-to-tax-the-middle-class-to-pay-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["How skillful to tax the middle class to pay for the relief of the poor, building resentment on top of humiliation! How adroit to bus poor black youngsters into poor white neighborhoods, in a violent exchange of impoverished schools, while the schools of the rich remain untouched and the wealth of the nation, doled out carefully where children need free milk, is drained for billion-dollar aircraft carriers. How ingenious to meet the demands of blacks and women for equality by giving them small special benefits, and setting them in competition with everyone else for jobs made scares by an irrational, wasteful system. How wise to turn the fear and anger of the majority toward a class of criminals bred - by economic inequity - faster than they can be put away, deflecting attention from the huge thefts of national resources carried out within the law by men in executive offices." -- Howard Zinn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783529-it-does-wonders-for-my-own-psyche-to-turn-envy</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2013 07:43:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Hillman Curtis]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/783529-it-does-wonders-for-my-own-psyche-to-turn-envy]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It does wonders for my own psyche to turn envy into inspiration. No matter how successful we become, we're never above that." -- Hillman Curtis]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798931-time-is-different-for-a-tree-than-for-a-man</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2013 19:32:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by George R.R. Martin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/798931-time-is-different-for-a-tree-than-for-a-man]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time is different for a tree than for a man. Sun and soil and water, these are the things a weirwood understands, not days and years and centuries. For men, time is a river. We are trapped in its flow, hurtling from past to present, always in the same direction. The lives of trees are different. They root and grow and die in one place, and that river does not move them. The oak is the acorn, the acorn is the oak." -- George R.R. Martin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500777-my-preference-is-for-prose-with-more-silence-in-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2013 12:43:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Anthony Doerr]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/500777-my-preference-is-for-prose-with-more-silence-in-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My preference is for prose with more silence in it, language that contains more pockets of strangeness." -- Anthony Doerr]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138569-when-dealing-with-people-remember-you-are-not-dealing-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:40:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Dale Carnegie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/138569-when-dealing-with-people-remember-you-are-not-dealing-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When dealing with people, remember you are not dealing with creatures of logic, but with creatures bristling with prejudice and motivated by pride and vanity." -- Dale Carnegie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856740-why-talk-about-what-we-want-that-is-childish-absurd</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 11:43:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by Dale Carnegie]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/856740-why-talk-about-what-we-want-that-is-childish-absurd]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Why talk about what we want? That is childish. Absurd. Of course, you are interested in what you want. You are eternally interested in it. But no one else is. The rest of us are just like you: we are interested in what we want." -- Dale Carnegie]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920916-sentimentality-the-ostentatious-parading-of-excessive-and-spurious-emotion-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 13:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920916-sentimentality-the-ostentatious-parading-of-excessive-and-spurious-emotion-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Sentimentality, the ostentatious parading of excessive and spurious emotion, is the mark of dishonesty, the inability to feel; the wet eyes of the sentimentalist betray his aversion to experience, his fear of life, his arid heart; and it is always, therefore, the signal of secret and violent inhumanity, the mask of cruelty." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920918-any-writer-i-suppose-feels-that-the-world-into-which</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 13:09:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jacob add a quote by James Baldwin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/920918-any-writer-i-suppose-feels-that-the-world-into-which]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Any writer, I suppose, feels that the world into which he was born is nothing less than a conspiracy against the cultivation of his talent--which attitude certainly has a great deal to support it. On the other hand, it is only because the world looks on his talent with such frightening indifference that the artist is compelled to make his talent important." -- James Baldwin]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
