<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/993740-sarah]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/993740-sarah" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 06:35:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252628-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2013 06:35:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/252628-perhaps-the-greatest-charity-comes-when-we-are-kind-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Perhaps the greatest charity comes when we are kind to each other, when we don't judge or categorize someone else, when we simply give each other the benefit of the doubt or remain quiet. Charity is accepting someone's differences, weaknesses, and shortcomings; having patience with someone who has let us down; or resisting the impulse to become offended when someone doesn't handle something the way we might have hoped. Charity is refusing to take advantage of another's weakness and being willing to forgive someone who has hurt us. Charity is expecting the best of each other.

None of us need one more person bashing or pointing out where we have failed or fallen short. Most of us are already well aware of the areas in which we are weak. What each of us does need is family, friends, employers, and brothers and sisters who support us, who have the patience to teach us, who believe in us, and who believe we're trying to do the best we can, in spite of our weaknesses. What ever happened to giving each other the benefit of the doubt? What ever happened to hoping that another person would succeed or achieve? What ever happened to rooting for each other?" -- Marvin J. Ashton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254266-tell-me-what-it-is-like-to-die-i-answered</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 05:35:56 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Martine Leavitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/254266-tell-me-what-it-is-like-to-die-i-answered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Tell me what it is like to die,&quot; I answered.
 He dismounted from his horse, looking at me strangely the whole while. &quot;You experience something similar every day,&quot; he said softly. &quot;It is as familiar to you as bread and butter.&quot;
 &quot;Yes,&quot; I said. &quot;It is like every night when I fall asleep.&quot;
 &quot;No. It is like every morning when you wake up." -- Martine Leavitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136964-if-untimely-death-came-only-those-who-deserved-that-fate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 05:36:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Martine Leavitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/136964-if-untimely-death-came-only-those-who-deserved-that-fate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If untimely death came only those who deserved that fate, Keturah, where would choice be? No one would do good for its own sake, but only to avoid an early demise. No one would speak out against evil because of his own courageous soul, but only to live another day. The right to choose is man's great gift, but one thing is not his to choose--the time and means of death." -- Martine Leavitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299882-each-man-when-he-dies-sees-the-landscape-of-his</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2013 05:36:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sarah add a quote by Martine Leavitt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/299882-each-man-when-he-dies-sees-the-landscape-of-his]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Each man, when he dies, sees the landscape of his own soul." -- Martine Leavitt]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
