<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/993828-stephanie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/993828-stephanie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 08:45:25 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3972-i-speak-to-everyone-in-the-same-way-whether-he</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 08:45:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3972-i-speak-to-everyone-in-the-same-way-whether-he]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I speak to everyone in the same way, whether he is the garbage man or the president of the university." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 09:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Arundhati Roy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2689-to-love-to-be-loved-to-never-forget-your-own]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To love. To be loved. To never forget your own insignificance. To never get used to the unspeakable violence and the vulgar disparity of life around you. To seek joy in the saddest places. To pursue beauty to its lair. To never simplify what is complicated or complicate what is simple. To respect strength, never power. Above all, to watch. To try and understand. To never look away. And never, never to forget." -- Arundhati Roy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20928-who-are-you-to-judge-the-life-i-live-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 09:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bob Marley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20928-who-are-you-to-judge-the-life-i-live-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Who are you to judge the life I live?
I know I'm not perfect
-and I don't live to be-
but before you start pointing fingers...
make sure you hands are clean!" -- Bob Marley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20714-calvin-isn-t-it-strange-that-evolution-would-give-us-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 09:09:36 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Bill Watterson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/20714-calvin-isn-t-it-strange-that-evolution-would-give-us-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["CALVIN:
Isn't it strange that evolution would give us a sense of humor?

When you think about it, it's weird that we have a physiological response to absurdity. We laugh at nonsense. We like it. We think it's funny.

Don't you think it's odd that we appreciate absurdity? Why would we develop that way? How does it benefit us?

HOBBES:
I suppose if we couldn't laugh at the things that don't make sense, we couldn't react to a lot of life." -- Bill Watterson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 10:37:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Neil Gaiman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7640-have-you-ever-been-in-love-horrible-isn-t-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Have you ever been in love? Horrible isn't it? It makes you so vulnerable. It opens your chest and it opens up your heart and it means that someone can get inside you and mess you up." -- Neil Gaiman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2008 10:38:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17194-people-think-a-soul-mate-is-your-perfect-fit-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People think a soul mate is your perfect fit, and that's what everyone wants. But a true soul mate is a mirror, the person who shows you everything that is holding you back, the person who brings you to your own attention so you can change your life.  

A true soul mate is probably the most important person you'll ever meet, because they tear down your walls and smack you awake.  But to live with a soul mate forever?  Nah. Too painful.  Soul mates, they come into your life just to reveal another layer of yourself to you, and then leave.  

A soul mates purpose is to shake you up, tear apart your ego a little bit, show you your obstacles and addictions, break your heart open so new light can get in, make you so desperate and out of control that you have to transform your life, then introduce you to your spiritual master..." -- Elizabeth Gilbert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76115-it-was-being-a-runner-that-mattered-not-how-fast</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2008 15:51:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by John Bingham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/76115-it-was-being-a-runner-that-mattered-not-how-fast]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was being a runner that mattered, not how fast or how far I could run. The joy was in the act of running and in the journey, not in the destination. We have a better chance of seeing where we are when we stop trying to get somewhere else. We can enjoy every moment of movement, as long as where we are is as good as where we'd like to be. That's not to say that you need to be satisfied  forever with where you are today. But you need to honor what you've accomplished, rather than thinking of what's left to be done (p. 159)." -- John Bingham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 11:53:19 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7480-real-isn-t-how-you-are-made-said-the-skin-horse]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Real isn't how you are made,' said the Skin Horse. 'It's a thing that happens to you. When a child loves you for a long, long time, not just to play with, but REALLY loves you, then you become Real.'

'Does it hurt?' asked the Rabbit. 

'Sometimes,' said the Skin Horse, for he was always truthful. 'When you are Real you don't mind being hurt.' 

'Does it happen all at once, like being wound up,' he asked, 'or bit by bit?' 

'It doesn't happen all at once,' said the Skin Horse. 'You become. It takes a long time. That's why it doesn't happen often to people who break easily, or have sharp edges, or who have to be carefully kept. Generally, by the time you are Real, most of your hair has been loved off, and your eyes drop out and you get loose in the joints and very shabby. But these things don't matter at all, because once you are Real you can't be ugly, except to people who don't understand." -- Margery Williams Bianco]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 11:55:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3160-today-you-are-you-that-is-truer-than-true-there]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Today you are You, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is Youer than You." -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16373-you-re-off-to-great-places-today-is-your-day-your</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 11:56:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Dr. Seuss]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16373-you-re-off-to-great-places-today-is-your-day-your]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You're off to Great Places!
Today is your day!
Your mountain is waiting,
So... get on your way!" -- Dr. Seuss]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 11:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1858-for-most-of-history-anonymous-was-a-woman]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For most of history, Anonymous was a woman." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30840-cakes-have-gotten-a-bad-rap-people-equate-virtue-with</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2008 12:21:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Stephanie add a quote by Jeanne Ray]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/30840-cakes-have-gotten-a-bad-rap-people-equate-virtue-with]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cakes have gotten a bad rap. People equate virtue with turning down dessert. There is always one person at the table who holds up her hand when I serve the cake. No, really, I couldn’t she says, and then gives her flat stomach a conspiratorial little pat. Everyone who is pressing a fork into that first tender layer looks at the person who declined the plate, and they all think, That person is better than I am. That person has discipline. But that isn’t a person with discipline; that is a person who has completely lost touch with joy. A slice of cake never made anybody fat. You don’t eat the whole cake. You don’t eat a cake every day of your life. You take the cake when it is offered because the cake is delicious. You have a slice of cake and what it reminds you of is someplace that’s safe, uncomplicated, without stress. A cake is a party, a birthday, a wedding. A cake is what’s served on the happiest days of your life. This is a story of how my life was saved by cake, so, of course, if sides are to be taken, I will always take the side of cake." -- Jeanne Ray]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
