<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/994170-connie]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/994170-connie" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:18:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1976-disbelief-in-magic-can-force-a-poor-soul-into-believing</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1976-disbelief-in-magic-can-force-a-poor-soul-into-believing]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Disbelief in magic can force a poor soul into believing in government and business." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160-our-lives-are-not-as-limited-as-we-think-they</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:20:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/160-our-lives-are-not-as-limited-as-we-think-they]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our lives are not as limited as we think they are; the world is a wonderfully weird place; consensual reality is significantly flawed; no institution can be trusted, but love does work; all things are possible; and we all could be happy and fulfilled if we only had the guts to be truly free and the wisdom to shrink our egos and quit taking ourselves so damn seriously." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12409-there-are-only-two-mantras-yum-and-yuck-mine-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:21:09 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12409-there-are-only-two-mantras-yum-and-yuck-mine-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two mantras, yum and yuck, mine is yum." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13856-if-you-believe-in-peace-act-peacefully-if-you-believe</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:21:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/13856-if-you-believe-in-peace-act-peacefully-if-you-believe]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If you believe in peace, act peacefully; if you believe in love, acting lovingly; if you believe every which way, then act every which way, that's perfectly valid - but don't go out trying to sell your beliefs to the system. You end up contradicting what you profess to believe in, and you set a bum example. If you want to change the world, change yourself." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:22:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12019-when-we-re-incomplete-we-re-always-searching-for-somebody-to-complete]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When we're incomplete, we're always searching for somebody to complete us. When, after a few years or a few months of a relationship, we find that we're still unfulfilled, we blame our partners and take up with somebody more promising. This can go on and on--series polygamy--until we admit that while a partner can add sweet dimensions to our lives, we, each of us, are responsible for our own fulfillment. Nobody else can provide it for us, and to believe otherwise is to delude ourselves dangerously and to program for eventual failure every relationship we enter." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6652-humans-have-evolved-to-their-relatively-high-state-by-retaining</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:24:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6652-humans-have-evolved-to-their-relatively-high-state-by-retaining]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Humans have evolved to their relatively high state by retaining the immature characteristics of their ancestors. Humans are the most advanced of mammals – although a case could be made for the dolphins – because they seldom grow up. Behavioral traits such as curiosity about the world, flexibility of response, and playfulness are common to practically all young mammals but are usually rapidly lost with the onset of maturity in all but humans. Humanity has advanced, when it has advanced, not because it has been sober, responsible and cautious, but because it has been playful, rebellious, and immature." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16729-in-the-haunted-house-of-life-art-is-the-only</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:25:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/16729-in-the-haunted-house-of-life-art-is-the-only]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the haunted house of life, art is the only stair that doesn't creak." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19775-time-passed-art-came-off-the-walls-and-became-rituals</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:30:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/19775-time-passed-art-came-off-the-walls-and-became-rituals]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Time passed. Art came off the walls and became rituals. Ritual became religion. Religion spawned science. Science led to big business. And big business, if it continues on its present, mindless trajectory, could land those lucky enough to survive its ultimate legacy back into caves again." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11360-life-is-pure-adventure-and-the-sooner-we-realize-that</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:43:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Maya Angelou]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/11360-life-is-pure-adventure-and-the-sooner-we-realize-that]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is pure adventure, and the sooner we realize that, the quicker we will be able to treat life as art." -- Maya Angelou]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15083-the-most-common-way-people-give-up-their-power-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:44:15 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Alice Walker]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15083-the-most-common-way-people-give-up-their-power-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don't have any." -- Alice Walker]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:51:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Allen Saunders]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/467-life-is-what-happens-to-you-while-you-re-busy-making]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Life is what happens to you while you're busy making other plans." -- Allen Saunders]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:55:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by A.A. Milne]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1336-piglet-sidled-up-to-pooh-from-behind-pooh-he-whispered]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Piglet sidled up to Pooh from behind. &quot;Pooh?&quot; he whispered.
&quot;Yes, Piglet?&quot;
&quot;Nothing,&quot; said Piglet, taking Pooh's hand. &quot;I just wanted to be sure of you." -- A.A. Milne]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15143-if-jesus-came-back-and-saw-what-was-being-done</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2008 14:59:59 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Woody Allen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15143-if-jesus-came-back-and-saw-what-was-being-done]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If Jesus came back and saw what was being done in his name, he'd never stop throwing up." -- Woody Allen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21669-you-can-t-study-the-darkness-by-flooding-it-with-light</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2008 22:25:17 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Edward Abbey]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21669-you-can-t-study-the-darkness-by-flooding-it-with-light]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["You can't study the darkness by flooding it with light." -- Edward Abbey]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28201-i-didn-t-come-out-of-a-cereal-box</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2008 20:46:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Bob Dylan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/28201-i-didn-t-come-out-of-a-cereal-box]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I didn't come out of a cereal box. " -- Bob Dylan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/758-whether-we-and-our-politicians-know-it-or-not-nature</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 13:28:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/758-whether-we-and-our-politicians-know-it-or-not-nature]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Whether we and our politicians know it or not, Nature is party to all our deals and decisions, and she has more votes, a longer memory, and a sterner sense of justice than we do." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746-let-us-have-the-candor-to-acknowledge-that-what-we</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2008 13:32:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Wendell Berry]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/746-let-us-have-the-candor-to-acknowledge-that-what-we]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Let us have the candor to acknowledge that what we call &quot;the economy&quot; or &quot;the free market&quot; is less and less distinguishable from warfare." -- Wendell Berry]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 12:22:49 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/25747-the-beet-is-the-most-intense-of-vegetables-the-radish]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The beet is the most intense of vegetables. The radish, admittedly, is more feverish, but the fire of the radish is a cold fire, the fire of discontent not of passion. Tomatoes are lusty enough, yet there runs through tomatoes an undercurrent of frivolity. Beets are deadly serious.

Slavic peoples get their physical characteristics from potatoes, their smoldering inquietude from radishes, their seriousness from beets.

The beet is the melancholy vegetable, the one most willing to suffer. You can't squeeze blood out of a turnip...

The beet is the murderer returned to the scene of the crime. The beet is what happens when the cherry finishes with the carrot. The beet is the ancient ancestor of the autumn moon, bearded, buried, all but fossilized; the dark green sails of the grounded moon-boat stitched with veins of primordial plasma; the kite string that once connected the moon to the Earth now a muddy whisker drilling desperately for rubies.

The beet was Rasputin's favorite vegetable. You could see it in his eyes." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126098-all-depression-has-its-roots-in-self-pity-and-all-self-pity</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2009 12:23:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Connie add a quote by Tom Robbins]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126098-all-depression-has-its-roots-in-self-pity-and-all-self-pity]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All depression has its roots in self-pity, and all self-pity is rooted in people taking themselves too seriously.&quot;

At the time Switters had disputed her assertion.  Even at seventeen, he was aware that depression could have chemical causes.

&quot;The key word here is roots,&quot; Maestra had countered. &quot;The roots of depression. For most people, self-awareness and self-pity blossom simultaneously in early adolescence. It's about that time that we start viewing the world as something other than a whoop-de-doo playground, we start to experience personally how threatening it can e, how cruel and unjust. At the very moment when we become, for the first time, both introspective and socially conscientious, we receive the bad news that the world, by and large, doesn't give a rat's ass. Even an old tomato like me can recall how painful, scary, and disillusioning that realization was. So, there's a tendency, then, to slip into rage and self-pity, which if indulged, can fester into bouts of depression.&quot;

&quot;Yeah but Maestra - &quot;

&quot;Don't interrupt. Now, unless someone stronger and wiser - a friend, a parent, a novelist, filmmaker, teacher, or musician - can josh us out of it, can elevate us and show us how petty and pompous and monumentally useless it is to take ourselves so seriously, then depression can become a habit, which, in tern, can produce a neurological imprint. Are you with me? Gradually, our brain chemistry becomes conditioned to react to negative stimuli in a particular, predictable way. One thing'll go wrong and it'll automatically switch on its blender and mix us that black cocktail, the ol' doomsday daiquiri, and before we know it, we're soused to the gills from the inside out. Once depression has become electrochemically integrated, it can be extremely difficult to philosophically or psychologically override it; by then it's playing by physical rules, a whole different ball game. That's why Switters my dearest, every time you've shown signs of feeling sorry for yourself, I've played my blues records really loud or read to you from The Horse's Mouth. And that's why when you've exhibited the slightest tendency toward self-importance, I've reminded you that you and me - you and I: excuse me - may be every bit as important as the President or the pope or the biggest prime-time icon in Hollywood, but none of us is much more than a pimple on the ass-end of creation, so let's not get carried away with ourselves. Preventive medicine, boy. It's preventive medicine.&quot;

&quot;But what about self-esteem?&quot;

&quot;Heh! Self-esteem is for sissies. Accept that you're a pimple and try to keep a lively sense of humor about it. That way lies grace - and maybe even glory." -- Tom Robbins]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
