<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/995595-aimee]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/995595-aimee" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 08:17:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 08:17:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by Anais Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/31920-i-am-the-most-tired-woman-in-the-world-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I am the most tired woman in the world. I am tired when I get up. Life requires an effort I cannot make. Please give me that heavy book. I need to put something heavy like that on top of my head. I have to place my feet under the pillows always, so as to be able to stay on earth. Otherwise I feel myself going away, going away at a tremendous speed, on account of my lightness. I know that I am dead. As soon as I utter a phrase my sincerity dies, becomes a lie whose coldness chills me. Don't say anything, because I see that you understand me, and I am afraid of your understanding. I have such a fear of finding another like myself, and such a desire to find one! I am so utterly lonely, but I also have such a fear that my isolation be broken through, and I no longer be the head and ruler of my universe. I am in great terror of your understanding by which you penetrate into my world; and then I stand revealed and I have to share my kingdom with you." -- Anais Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 11:46:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/717-be-patient-toward-all-that-is-unsolved-in-your-heart]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Be patient toward all that is unsolved in your heart and try to love the questions themselves, like locked rooms and like books that are now written in a very foreign tongue. Do not now seek the answers, which cannot be given you because you would not be able to live them. And the point is, to live everything. Live the questions now. Perhaps you will then gradually, without noticing it, live along some distant day into the answer." -- Rainer Maria Rilke]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311787-and-i-submit-that-this-is-what-the-real-no-shit</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2012 12:34:16 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/311787-and-i-submit-that-this-is-what-the-real-no-shit]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I submit that this is what the real, no-shit value of your liberal arts education is supposed to be about: How to keep from going through your comfortable, prosperous, respectable adult life dead, unconscious, a slave to your head and to your natural default setting of being uniquely, completely, imperially alone, day in and day out." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97640-words-are-easy-like-the-wind-faithful-friends-are-hard</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 12:59:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by William Shakespeare]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/97640-words-are-easy-like-the-wind-faithful-friends-are-hard]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Words are easy, like the wind; Faithful friends are hard to find." -- William Shakespeare]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170923-however-rare-true-love-may-be-it-is-less-so</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 13:04:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Aimee add a quote by albert einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170923-however-rare-true-love-may-be-it-is-less-so]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["However rare true love may be, it is less so than true friendship." -- albert einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
