<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/995816-april]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/995816-april" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 13:41:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46984-when-your-kids-accomplish-something-it-means-much-more-than</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 13:41:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Greg Mortenson]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/46984-when-your-kids-accomplish-something-it-means-much-more-than]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When your kids accomplish something it means much more than anything you've done." -- Greg Mortenson]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47268-in-those-moments-of-moving-through-the-streets-with-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 12:32:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/47268-in-those-moments-of-moving-through-the-streets-with-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In those moments of moving through the streets with people who share one's beliefs comes the rare and magical possibility of a kind of populist communion...At such times it is as though the still small pool of one's own identity has been overrun by a great flood, bringing its own grand collective desires and resentments, scouring out that pool so thoroughly that one no longer feels fear or sees the reflections of oneself but is carried along on that insurrectionary surge. These moments when individuals find others who share their dreams, when fear is overwhelmed by idealism or by outrage, when people feel a strength that surprises them, are moments in which they become heroes—for what are heroes but those so motivated by ideals that fear cannot sway them, those who speak for us, those who have power for good? A person who never feels it is condemned to cynicism and isolation. In those moments everyone becomes a visionary, everyone becomes a hero." -- Rebecca Solnit]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12577-the-limits-of-my-language-means-the-limits-of-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 12:35:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/12577-the-limits-of-my-language-means-the-limits-of-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The limits of my language means the limits of my world." -- Ludwig Wittgenstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58391-and-my-difficulties-were-these-i-found-each-plant-each</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 18:42:06 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jamaica Kincaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/58391-and-my-difficulties-were-these-i-found-each-plant-each]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And my difficulties were these: I found each plant, each new turn in the road, each new turn in the weather, from cold to hot and then back again, each new set of boulders so absorbing, so new, and the newness so absorbing, and I was so in need of an explanation for each thing, that I was often in tears, troubling myself with questions, such as what am I and what is the thing in front of me." -- Jamaica Kincaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70836-a-gardener-is-a-person-of-all-kinds-but-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2008 18:43:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Jamacia Kincaid]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/70836-a-gardener-is-a-person-of-all-kinds-but-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["a gardener is a person of all kinds, but in particular a gardener is a person who at least once in the gardening year feels the urge to possess completely at least one plant." -- Jamacia Kincaid]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
