<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/996207-elka]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/996207-elka" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 21:57:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 21:57:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35446-what-about-little-microphones-what-if-everyone-swallowed-them-and]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["What about little microphones? What if everyone swallowed them, and they played the sounds of our hearts through little speakers, which could be in the pouches of our overalls? When you skateboarded down the street at night you could hear everyone's heartbeat, and they could hear yours, sort of like sonar. One weird thing is, I wonder if everyone's hearts would start to beat at the same time, like how women who live together have their menstrual periods at the same time, which I know about, but don't really want to know about. That would be so weird, except that the place in the hospital where babies are born would sound like a crystal chandelier in a houseboat, because the babies wouldn't have had time to match up their heartbeats yet. And at the finish line at the end of the New York City Marathon it would sound like war." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64707-forget-trying-to-pass-for-normal-follow-your-geekdom-embrace</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 22:06:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Bruce Sterling]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/64707-forget-trying-to-pass-for-normal-follow-your-geekdom-embrace]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Forget trying to pass for normal.  Follow your geekdom.  Embrace nerditude.  In the immortal words of Lafcadio Hearn, a geek of incredible obscurity whose work is still in print after a hundred years, “Woo the muse of the odd.”  You may be a geek.  You may have geek written all over you.  You should aim to be one geek they'll never forget.  Don't aim to be civilized.  Don’t hope that straight people will keep you on as some sort of pet.  To hell with them.  You should fully realize what society has made of you and take a terrible revenge.  Get weird.  Get way weird.  Get dangerously weird.  Get sophisticatedly, thoroughly weird, and don't do it halfway.  Put every ounce of horsepower you have behind it.  Don't become a well-rounded person.  Well-rounded people are smooth and dull.  Become a thoroughly spiky person.  Grow spikes from every angle.  Stick in their throats like a pufferfish." -- Bruce Sterling]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35457-when-the-socialized-self-is-experienced-as-a-limitation-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2008 22:08:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by John Gray  (the art critic, not the other guy)]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35457-when-the-socialized-self-is-experienced-as-a-limitation-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When the socialized self is experienced as a limitation the human body is prized not for what it discloses of personality but for the promise it offers of leaving personality behind.

Even when the body is used as an instrument of personal liberation it is freedom from personality that is the goal.

Alongside the meanings in terms of which we habitually understand our lives there is another region of experience, at once terrifying and somehow enticing, where no trace of meaning can be found." -- John Gray  (the art critic, not the other guy)]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72348-there-is-of-course-a-chicken-and-egg-element-here-does-someone</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2008 17:49:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Steven Kurutz]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/72348-there-is-of-course-a-chicken-and-egg-element-here-does-someone]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is, of course, a chicken-and-egg element here: does someone gravitate to the role of Eddie van Halen because he shares similar personality traits or did portraying Eddie Van Halen give rise to those qualities?" -- Steven Kurutz]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313466-i-did-not-know-then-that-this-is-what-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 13:18:46 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Ta-Nehisi Coates]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/313466-i-did-not-know-then-that-this-is-what-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I did not know then that this is what life is - just when you master the geometry of one world, it slips away, and suddenly again, you're swarmed by strange shapes and impossible angles." -- Ta-Nehisi Coates]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18601-never-play-cards-with-a-man-called-doc-never-eat</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 19:55:37 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Nelson Algren]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18601-never-play-cards-with-a-man-called-doc-never-eat]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never play cards with a man called Doc. Never eat at a place called Mom's. Never sleep with a woman whose troubles are worse than your own." -- Nelson Algren]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126904-if-stone-sober-people-can-fuck-like-they-re-out-of-their</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2009 00:54:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Stephen King]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/126904-if-stone-sober-people-can-fuck-like-they-re-out-of-their]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If stone-sober people can fuck like they're out of their minds -- can actually be out of their minds while caught in that throe -- why shouldn't writers be able to go bonkers and still stay sane?" -- Stephen King]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66311-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live-we-look-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 14:25:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[elka add a quote by Joan Didion]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/66311-we-tell-ourselves-stories-in-order-to-live-we-look-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We tell ourselves stories in order to live...We look for the sermon in the suicide, for the social or moral lesson in the murder of five.  We interpret what we see, select the most workable of the multiple choices.  We live entirely, especially if we are writers, by the imposition of a narrative line upon disparate images, by the &quot;ideas&quot; with which we have learned to freeze the shifting phantasmagoria which is our actual experience." -- Joan Didion]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
