<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998007-sukikabuki-young-domingo]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998007-sukikabuki-young-domingo" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:45:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265261-there-are-two-kinds-of-anger-hot-and-cold-boys</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:45:39 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265261-there-are-two-kinds-of-anger-hot-and-cold-boys]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are two kinds of anger: hot and cold. Boys and girls experience both, but as they grow up the anger separates according to the sex. Boys need hot anger to survive. They need inclination to fight, the drive to sink the knife into the flesh, the energy and initiative of fury. It's a requirement of hunting, of defense, of pride. Maybe of sex too. And girls need cold anger. They need the cold simmer, the ceaseless grudge, the talent to avoid forgiveness, the sidestepping of compromise. They need to know when they say something that they will never back down, ever, ever. It's the compensation for a more limited scope in the world. Cross a man and you struggle, one of you wins, you would adjust and go on -- or you lie there dead. Cross a woman and the universe is changed, once again, for cold anger requires an eternal vigilance in all matters of slight and offense." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152432-cross-a-man-and-you-struggle-one-of-you-wins</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/152432-cross-a-man-and-you-struggle-one-of-you-wins]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Cross a man and you struggle, one of you wins, you adjust and go on - or you lie there dead. Cross a woman and the universe is changed, once again, for cold anger requires an eternal vigilance in all matters of slight and offense" -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179723-it-may-merely-be-apocryphal-that-when-the-wizard-saw</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179723-it-may-merely-be-apocryphal-that-when-the-wizard-saw]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It may merely be apocryphal that when the Wizard saw the glass bottle he gasped, and clutched his heart. The story is told in so many ways, depending on who is doing the telling, and what needs to be heard at the time. It is a matter of history, however, that shortly thereafter, the Wizard absconded from the Palace. He left in the way he had first arrived-- a hot-air balloon-- just a few hours before seditious ministers were to lead a Palace revolt and to hold an execution without trial." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191265-so-she-listened-hard-and-she-began-to-evolve-because</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:48:52 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/191265-so-she-listened-hard-and-she-began-to-evolve-because]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["So she listened hard. And she began to evolve, because stories work their magic that way. They build conviction and erode conviction in equal measure." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179551-we-are-loping-sequences-of-chemical-conversions-acting-ourselves-converted</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:49:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179551-we-are-loping-sequences-of-chemical-conversions-acting-ourselves-converted]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We are loping sequences of chemical conversions, acting ourselves converted.  We are twists of genes acting ourselves twisted; we are wicks of burning neuroses acting ourselves wicked.  And nothing to be done about it.  And nothing to be done about it." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42193-in-the-lives-of-children-pumpkins-turn-into-coaches-mice</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/42193-in-the-lives-of-children-pumpkins-turn-into-coaches-mice]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In the lives of children, pumpkins turn into coaches, mice and rats turn into men.  When we grow up, we realize it is far more common for men to turn into rats." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276624-it-was-mild-monsters-like-these-that-made-jack-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:51:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276624-it-was-mild-monsters-like-these-that-made-jack-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It was mild monsters like these that made Jack the Ripper go after young women, she decided: who could tolerate yielding the world to someone who behaved as if she had given birth to the very world herself?" -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276625-thanks-to-our-artists-we-pretend-well-living-under-canopies</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:51:50 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276625-thanks-to-our-artists-we-pretend-well-living-under-canopies]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Thanks to our artists, we pretend well, living under canopies of painted clouds and painted gods, in halls of marble floors across which the sung Masses paint hope in deep impatsi of echo. We make of the hollow world a fuller, messier, prettier place, but all our inventions can't create the one thing we require: to deserve any fond attention we might accidentally receive, to receive any fond attention we don't in the course of things deserve. We are never enough to ourselves because we can never be enough to another. Any one of us walks into any room and reminds its occupant that we are not the one they most want to see. We are never the one. We are never enough." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276642-people-always-did-like-to-talk-didn-t-they-that-s-why</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:52:02 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276642-people-always-did-like-to-talk-didn-t-they-that-s-why]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["People always did like to talk, didn't they? That's why I call myself a witch now: the Wicked Witch of the West, if you want the full glory of it. As long as people are going to call you a lunatic anyway, why not get the benefit of it? It liberates you from convention." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276643-the-real-thing-about-evil-said-the-witch-at-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:52:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/276643-the-real-thing-about-evil-said-the-witch-at-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The real thing about evil,&quot; said the Witch at the doorway, &quot;isn't any of what you said. You figure out one side of it - the human side, say - and the eternal side goes into shadow. Or vice versa. It's like the old saw: What does a dragon in its shell look like? Well no one can ever tell, for as soon as you break the shell to see, the dragon is no longer in its shell. The real disaster of this inquiry is that it is the nature of evil to be secret." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62037-and-of-the-witch-in-the-life-of-a-witch</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:52:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62037-and-of-the-witch-in-the-life-of-a-witch]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And of the Witch? In the life of a Witch, there is no &quot;after&quot;, in the &quot;ever after&quot; of a Witch there is no &quot;happily&quot;; in the story of a Witch, there is no afterword. Of that part that is beyond the life story, beyond the story of the life, there is-alas, or perhaps thank mercy-no telling. She was dead, dead, and gone, and all that was left of her was the carapace of her reputation for malice." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258731-what-is-the-use-of-beauty-i-have-lived-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 01:52:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Gregory Maguire]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/258731-what-is-the-use-of-beauty-i-have-lived-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["...What is the use of beauty? i have lived my life surrounded by painters, and still I do not know the answer. But i suspect, some days, that beauty helps protect the spirit of mankind, swaddle it and succor it, so that we might survive. Beauty is no end in itself, but if it makes or lives less miserable so that we might be more kind-well, then, lets have beauty, painted on our porcelain, hanging on our walls, ringing through our stories." -- Gregory Maguire]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201-then-came-the-march-past-the-victims-the-two-men</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:24:05 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1201-then-came-the-march-past-the-victims-the-two-men]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Then came the march past the victims. The two men were no longer alive. Their tongues were hanging out,
swollen and bluish. But the third rope was still moving: the child, too light, was still breathing...
And so he remained for more than half an hour, lingering between life and death, writhing before our eyes.
And we were forced to look at him at close range. He was still alive when I passed him. His tongue was still
red, his eyes not yet extinguished.

Behind me, I heard the same man asking:
&quot;For God's sake, where is God?&quot;
And from within me, I heard a voice answer:
&quot;Where He is? This is where--hanging here from this gallows...&quot;

That night, the soup tasted of corpses." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37319-never-shall-i-forget-that-night-the-first-night-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:24:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37319-never-shall-i-forget-that-night-the-first-night-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Never shall I forget that night, the first night in camp, which has turned my life into one long night, seven times cursed and seven times sealed....Never shall I forget those moments which murdered my God and my soul and turned my dreams to dust. Never shall I forget these things, even if I am condemned to live as long as God Himself. Never." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167491-for-the-survivor-who-chooses-to-testify-it-is-clear</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:24:26 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/167491-for-the-survivor-who-chooses-to-testify-it-is-clear]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["For the survivor who chooses to testify, it is clear: his duty is to bear witness for the dead and for the living. He has no right to deprive future generations of a past that belongs to our collective memory. To forget would be not only dangerous but offensive; to forget the dead would be akin to killing them a second time." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82774-he-explained-to-me-with-great-insistence-that-every-question</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:24:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/82774-he-explained-to-me-with-great-insistence-that-every-question]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["He explained to me with great insistence that every question posessed a power that did not lie in the answer." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210323-blessed-be-god-s-name-why-but-why-would-i-bless</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:25:07 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210323-blessed-be-god-s-name-why-but-why-would-i-bless]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Blessed be God's name? Why, but why would I bless Him? Every fiber in me rebelled. Because He caused thousands of children to burn in His mass graves? Because he kept six crematoria working day and night, including Sabbath and the Holy Days? Because in His great might, He had created Auschwitz, Birkenau, Buna, and so many other factories of death? How could I say to Him: Blessed be Thou, Almighty, Master of the Universe, who chose us among all nations to be tortured day and night, to watch as our fathers, our mothers, our brothers, end up in the furnaces? Praised be Thy Holy Name, for having chosen us to be slaughtered on Thine altar?" -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212729-they-are-committing-the-greatest-indignity-human-beings-can-inflict</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:25:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212729-they-are-committing-the-greatest-indignity-human-beings-can-inflict]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["They are committing the greatest indignity human beings can inflict on one  another:  telling people who have suffered excruciating pain and loss that their pain and loss were illusions. (v)" -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210382-one-day-when-i-was-able-to-get-up-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/210382-one-day-when-i-was-able-to-get-up-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One day when I was able to get up, I decided to look at myself in the mirror on the opposite wall. I had not seen myself since the ghetto. From the depths of the mirror, a corpse was contemplating me. The look in his eyes as he gazed at me has never left me." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212727-we-cannot-indefinitely-avoid-depressing-subject-matter-particularly-it-it</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:26:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/212727-we-cannot-indefinitely-avoid-depressing-subject-matter-particularly-it-it]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We cannot indefinitely avoid depressing subject matter, particularly it it is true, and in the subsequent quarter century the world has had to hear a story it would have preferred not to hear - the story of how a cultured people turned to genocide, and how the rest of the world, also composed of cultured people, remained silent in the face of genocide. (v)" -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:27:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/677-the-opposite-of-love-is-not-hate-it-s-indifference-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The opposite of love is not hate, it's indifference. The opposite of art is not ugliness, it's indifference. The opposite of faith is not heresy, it's indifference. And the opposite of life is not death, it's indifference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346-there-may-be-times-when-we-are-powerless-to-prevent</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:27:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/346-there-may-be-times-when-we-are-powerless-to-prevent]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There may be times when we are powerless to prevent injustice, but there must never be a time when we fail to protest." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/18490-we-must-always-take-sides-neutrality-helps-the-oppressor-never]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We must always take sides.  Neutrality helps the oppressor, never the victim.  Silence encourages the tormentor, never the tormented." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7811-when-a-person-doesn-t-have-gratitude-something-is-missing-in</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:27:44 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/7811-when-a-person-doesn-t-have-gratitude-something-is-missing-in]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When a person doesn’t have gratitude, something is missing in his or her humanity. A person can almost be defined by his or her attitude toward gratitude." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14260-there-is-divine-beauty-in-learning-to-learn-means-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:27:53 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/14260-there-is-divine-beauty-in-learning-to-learn-means-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There is divine beauty in learning...  To learn means to accept the postulate that life did not begin at my birth.  Others have been here before me, and I walk in their footsteps.  The books I have read were composed by generations of fathers and sons, mothers and daughters, teachers and disciples.  I am the sum total of their experiences, their quests.  And so are you." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68627-one-person-of-integrity-can-make-a-difference</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/68627-one-person-of-integrity-can-make-a-difference]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["One person of integrity can make a difference." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53618-which-is-worse-killing-with-hate-or-killing-without-hate</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:28:10 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53618-which-is-worse-killing-with-hate-or-killing-without-hate]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Which is worse? Killing with hate or killing without hate?" -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50735-to-forget-the-dead-would-be-akin-to-killing-them</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:28:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50735-to-forget-the-dead-would-be-akin-to-killing-them]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["To forget the dead would be akin to killing them a second time." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50737-human-suffering-anywhere-concerns-men-and-women-everywhere</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:28:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/50737-human-suffering-anywhere-concerns-men-and-women-everywhere]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Human suffering anywhere concerns men and women everywhere." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53617-only-the-guilty-are-guilty-their-children-are-not</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2010 02:28:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Sukikabuki add a quote by Elie Wiesel]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/53617-only-the-guilty-are-guilty-their-children-are-not]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Only the guilty are guilty. Their children are not." -- Elie Wiesel]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
