<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998266-katie-dubik-schwarz]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998266-katie-dubik-schwarz" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 03:26:21 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32997-your-problem-is-how-you-are-going-to-spend-this</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 03:26:21 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/32997-your-problem-is-how-you-are-going-to-spend-this]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Your problem is how you are going to spend this one and precious life you have been issued. Whether you're going  to spend it trying to look good and creating the illusion that you have power over circumstances, or whether you are going to taste it, enjoy it and find out the truth about who you are." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40095-writing-and-reading-decrease-our-sense-of-isolation-they-deepen</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 03:26:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40095-writing-and-reading-decrease-our-sense-of-isolation-they-deepen]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Writing and reading decrease our sense of isolation.  They deepen and widen and expand our sense of life: they feed the soul.  When writers make us shake our heads with the exactness of their prose and their truths, and even make us laugh about ourselves or life, our buoyancy is restored.  We are given a shot at dancing with, or at least clapping along with, the absurdity of life, instead of being squashed by it over and over again.  It's like singing on a boat during a terrible storm at sea.  You can't stop the raging storm, but singing can change the hearts and spirits of the people who are together on that ship." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 03:26:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Anne Lamott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/40086-e-l-doctorow-said-once-said-that-writing-a-novel-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["E.L. Doctorow said once said that 'Writing a novel is like driving a car at night. You can see only as far as your headlights, but you can make the whole trip that way.' You don't have to see where you're going, you don't have to see your destination or everything you will pass along the way. You just have to see two or three feet ahead of you. This is right up there with the best advice on writing, or life, I have ever heard." -- Anne Lamott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303127-success-means-having-the-courage-the-determination-and-the-will</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:54:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by George Sheehan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/303127-success-means-having-the-courage-the-determination-and-the-will]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Success means having the courage, the determination, and the will to become the person you believe you were meant to be." -- George Sheehan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74272-there-are-those-of-us-who-are-always-about-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:55:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by George sheehan/nora sheeh]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/74272-there-are-those-of-us-who-are-always-about-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are those of us who are always about to live. We are waiting until things change, until there is more time, until we are less tired, until we get a promotion, until we settle down / until, until, until. It always seems as if there is some major event that must occur in our lives before we begin living." -- George sheehan/nora sheeh]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123992-the-distance-runner-is-mysteriously-reconciling-the-separations-of-body</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:55:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by George Sheehan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/123992-the-distance-runner-is-mysteriously-reconciling-the-separations-of-body]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The distance runner is mysteriously reconciling the separations of body and mind, of pain and pleasure, of the conscious and the unconscious.  He is repairing the rent, and healing the wound in his divided self.  He has found a way to make the ordinary extraordinary; the commonplace unique; the everyday eternal." -- George Sheehan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688859-running-is-just-such-a-monestary---a-retreat-a-place</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 10:55:41 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by George Sheehan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/688859-running-is-just-such-a-monestary---a-retreat-a-place]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Running is just such a monestary-- a retreat, a place to commune with God and yourself, a place for psychological and spiritual renewal." -- George Sheehan]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2013 03:27:24 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9557-it-doesn-t-interest-me-what-you-do-for-a-living]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It doesn't interest me what you do for a living. I want to know what you ache for, and if you dare to dream of meeting your heart's longing.
It doesn't interest me how old you are. I want to know if you will risk looking like a fool for love, for your dream, for the adventure of being alive. 
It doesn't interest me what planets are squaring your moon. I want to know if you have touched the center of your own sorrow, if you have been opened by life's betrayals or have become shriveled and closed from fear of further pain!I want to know if you can sit with pain, mine or your own, without moving to hide it or fade it, or fix it. 
I want to know if you can be with joy, mine or your own, if you can dance with wildness and let the ecstasy fill you to the tips of your fingers and toes without cautioning us to be careful, to be realistic, to remember the limitations of being human. 
It doesn't interest me if the story you are telling me is true. I want to know if you can disappoint another to be true to yourself; if you can bear the accusation of betrayal and not betray your own soul; if you can be faithlessand therefore trustworthy. 
I want to know if you can see beauty even when it's not pretty, every day,and if you can source your own life from its presence. 
I want to know if you can live with failure, yours and mine, and still stand on the edge of the lake and shout to the silver of the full moon, “Yes!”
It doesn't interest me to know where you live or how much money you have. I want to know if you can get up, after the night of grief and despair, weary and bruised to the bone, and do what needs to be done to feed the children. 
It doesn't interest me who you know or how you came to be here. I want to know if you will stand in the center of the fire with me and not shrink back. 
It doesn't interest me where or what or with whom you have studied. I want to know what sustains you, from the inside, when all else falls away. 
I want to know if you can be alone with yourself and if you truly like the company you keep in the empty moments." -- Oriah Mountain Dreamer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56650-now-i-know-i-ve-got-a-heart-because-it-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 03:33:22 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by L. Frank Baum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/56650-now-i-know-i-ve-got-a-heart-because-it-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I know I've got a heart because it is breaking.
- Tin Man" -- L. Frank Baum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220560-i-shall-take-the-heart-for-brains-do-not-make</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2013 03:33:29 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by L. Frank Baum]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/220560-i-shall-take-the-heart-for-brains-do-not-make]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I shall take the heart. For brains do not make one happy, and happiness is the best thing in the world.
" -- L. Frank Baum]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43294-the-grand-essentials-to-happiness-in-this-life-are-something</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 16:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by George Washington Burnap]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/43294-the-grand-essentials-to-happiness-in-this-life-are-something]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The grand essentials to happiness in this life are something to do, something to love, and something to hope for." -- George Washington Burnap]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494910-someone-once-said-anyone-can-be-great-under-rosy-circumstances</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 18:20:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jack Gantos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/494910-someone-once-said-anyone-can-be-great-under-rosy-circumstances]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Someone once said anyone can be great under rosy circumstances, but the true test of character is measured by how well a person makes decisions during difficult times." -- Jack Gantos]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/803983-my-youthful-dream-of-becoming-a-writer-has-been-realized</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 18:21:54 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Katie add a quote by Jack Gantos]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/803983-my-youthful-dream-of-becoming-a-writer-has-been-realized]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My youthful dream of becoming a writer has been realized. I am so pleased I did not let my young self down." -- Jack Gantos]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
