<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998329-tina]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998329-tina" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:29:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 13:29:39 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/159480-i-know-it-is-hard-for-you-young-mothers-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I know it is hard for you young mothers to believe that almost before you can turn around the children will be gone and you will be alone with your husband.  You had better be sure you are developing the kind of love and friendship that will be delightful and enduring.  Let the children learn from your attitude that he is important.  Encourage him.  Be kind.  It is a rough world, and he, like everyone else, is fighting to survive.  Be cheerful.  Don't be a whiner." -- Marjorie Pay Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 10:24:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/27611-aim-high-but-do-not-aim-so-high-that-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Aim high, but do not aim so high that you totally miss the target. What really matters is that he will love you, that he will respect you, that he will honor you, that he will be absolutely true to you, that he will give you the freedom of expression and let you fly in the development of your own talents. He is not going to be perfect, but if he is kind and thoughtful, if he knows how to work and earn a living, if he is honest and full of faith, the chances are you will not go wrong, that you will be immensely happy." -- Gordon B. Hinckley]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361338-our-children-take-their-flight-into-the-future-with-our</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 10:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/361338-our-children-take-their-flight-into-the-future-with-our]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Our children take their flight into the future with our thrust and with our aim. And even as we anxiously watch that arrow in flight and know all the evils that can deflect its course after is has left our hand, nevertheless we take courage in remembering that the most important factor in determining that arrow's destination will be the stability, strength, and unwavering certainty of the holder of the bow." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365198-on-this-upward-and-sometimes-hazardous-journey-each-of-us</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 11:07:01 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365198-on-this-upward-and-sometimes-hazardous-journey-each-of-us]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["On this upward and sometimes hazardous journey, each of us meets our share of daily challenges. If we are not careful, as we peer through the narrow lens of self-interest, we may feel that life is bringing us more than our fair share of trials--that somehow others seem to be getting off more lightly.

But the tests of life are tailored for our own best interests, and all will face the burdens best suited to their own mortal experience. In the end we will realize that God is merciful as well as just and that all the rules are fair. We can be reassured that our challenges will be the ones we needed, and conquering them will bring blessings we could have received in no other way." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365294-in-such-times-as-we-are-in-whether-the-threats</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 11:09:57 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365294-in-such-times-as-we-are-in-whether-the-threats]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In such times as we are in, whether the threats be global or local or in individual lives, I too pray for the children. Some days it seems that a sea of temptation and transgression inundates them, simply washes over them before they can successfully withstand it, before they should have to face it. And often at least some of the forces at work seem beyond our personal control. Well, some of them may be beyond our control, but I testify with faith in the living God that they are not beyond His." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365302-i-believe-that-in-our-own-individual-ways-god-takes</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 11:10:31 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/365302-i-believe-that-in-our-own-individual-ways-god-takes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I believe that in our own individual ways, God takes us to the grove or the mountain or the temple and there shows us the wonder of what His plan is for us. We may not see it as fully as Moses or Nephi or the brother of Jared did, but we see as much as need to see in order to know the Lord's will for us and to know that He loves us beyond mortal comprehension." -- Jeffrey R. Holland]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 16:39:04 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/594379-no-no-it-s-not-all-random-if-it-really-was]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["no, no, it's not all random, if it really was all random, the universe would abandon us completely. and the universe doesn't. it takes care of its most fragile creations in ways we can't see. like with parents who adore you blindly. and a big sister who feels guilty for being human over you. and a little gravelly-voiced kid whose friends have left him over you. and even a pink-haired girl who carries your picture in her wallet. maybe it is a lottery, but the universe makes it all even out in the end. the universe takes care of all its birds." -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616327-do-people-look-the-same-when-they-go-to-heaven</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2013 16:39:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by R.J. Palacio]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/616327-do-people-look-the-same-when-they-go-to-heaven]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do people look the same when they go to heaven, mommy?&quot;
&quot;I don't know. I don't think so.&quot;
&quot;Then how do people recognize each other?&quot;
&quot;I don't know, sweetie. They just feel it. You don't need your eyes to love, right?" -- R.J. Palacio]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94296-vice-is-a-monster-of-so-frightful-mien-as-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2014 18:15:31 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Alexander Pope]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/94296-vice-is-a-monster-of-so-frightful-mien-as-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Vice is a monster of so frightful mien
As to be hated needs but to be seen;
Yet seen too oft, familiar with her face,
We first endure, then pity, then embrace." -- Alexander Pope]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2014 13:29:25 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Tina add a quote by Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/218975-no-pain-that-we-suffer-no-trial-that-we-experience]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No pain that we suffer, no trial that we experience is wasted. It ministers to our education, to the development of such qualities as patience, faith, fortitude and humility. All that we suffer and all that we endure, especially when we endure it patiently, builds up our characters, purifies our hearts, expands our souls, and makes us more tender and charitable, more worthy to be called the children of God . . . and it is through sorrow and suffering, toil and tribulation, that we gain the education that we come here to acquire and which will make us more like our Father and Mother in heaven." -- Orson F. Whitney]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
