<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998422-mountainlaurel]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998422-mountainlaurel" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 06:07:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44905-it-is-not-true-that-we-have-only-one-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 06:07:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by S.I. Hayakawa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44905-it-is-not-true-that-we-have-only-one-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["It is not true that 'we have only one life to live'; if we can read, we can live as many more lives and as many kinds of lives as we wish." -- S.I. Hayakawa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35657-i-often-feel-sorry-for-people-who-don-t-read-good</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 14:50:32 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Scott Corbett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/35657-i-often-feel-sorry-for-people-who-don-t-read-good]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I often feel sorry for people who don't read good books; they are missing a chance to lead an extra life." -- Scott Corbett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80900-we-shouldn-t-teach-great-books-we-should-teach-a-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 14:51:14 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by B. F. Skinner ]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/80900-we-shouldn-t-teach-great-books-we-should-teach-a-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["We shouldn't teach great books; we should teach a love of reading. Knowing the contents of a few works of literature is a trivial achievement. Being inclined to go on reading is a great achievement." -- B. F. Skinner ]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44971-my-best-friend-is-a-person-who-will-give-me</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2008 14:52:12 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/44971-my-best-friend-is-a-person-who-will-give-me]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My Best Friend is a person who will give me a book I have not read." -- Abraham Lincoln]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 12:52:08 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/6702-i-declare-after-all-there-is-no-enjoyment-like-reading]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I declare after all there is no enjoyment like reading! How much sooner one tires of any thing than of a book! -- When I have a house of my own, I shall be miserable if I have not an excellent library." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 12:52:18 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2579-do-not-read-as-children-do-to-amuse-yourself-or]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Do not read, as children do, to amuse yourself, or like the ambitious, for the purpose of instruction. No, read in order to live." -- Gustave Flaubert]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2008 12:52:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Toni Morrison]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/321-if-there-s-a-book-that-you-want-to-read-but]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If there's a book that you want to read, but it hasn't been written yet, then you must write it." -- Toni Morrison]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26342-now-i-must-give-one-smirk-and-then-we-may</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 11:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[MountainLaurel add a quote by Jane Austen]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/26342-now-i-must-give-one-smirk-and-then-we-may]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Now I must give one smirk, and then we may be rational again.&quot; Catherine turned away her head, not knowing whether she might venture to laugh. &quot;I see what you think of me,&quot; said he gravely -- &quot;I shall make but a poor figure in your journal tomorrow.&quot; 

My journal!&quot;

Yes, I know exactly what you will say: Friday, went to the Lower Rooms; wore my sprigged muslin robe with blue trimmings -- plain black shoes -- appeared to much advantage; but was strangely harassed by a queer, half-witted man, who would make me dance with him, and distressed me by his nonsense.&quot; 

Indeed I shall say no such thing.&quot; 

Shall I tell you what you ought to say?&quot; 

If you please.&quot; 

I danced with a very agreeable young man, introduced by Mr. King; had a great deal of conversation with him -- seems a most extraordinary genius -- hope I may know more of him. That, madam, is what I wish you to say.&quot; 

But, perhaps, I keep no journal.&quot; 

Perhaps you are not sitting in this room, and I am not sitting by you. These are points in which a doubt is equally possible. Not keep a journal! How are your absent cousins to understand the tenour of your life in Bath without one? How are the civilities and compliments of every day to be related as they ought to be, unless noted down every evening in a journal? How are your various dresses to be remembered, and the particular state of your complexion, and curl of your hair to be described in all their diversities, without having constant recourse to a journal? My dear madam, I am not so ignorant of young ladies' ways as you wish to believe me; it is this delightful habit of journaling which largely contributes to form the easy style of writing for which ladies are so generally celebrated. Everybody allows that the talent of writing agreeable letters is peculiarly female. Nature may have done something, but I am sure it must be essentially assisted by the practice of keeping a journal." -- Jane Austen]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
