<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998865-ron]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/998865-ron" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 20:37:27 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101996-when-you-find-your-path-you-must-not-be-afraid</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 20:37:27 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Paulo Coelho]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/101996-when-you-find-your-path-you-must-not-be-afraid]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["When you find your path, you must not be afraid. You need to have sufficient courage to make mistakes. Disappointment, defeat, and despair are the tools God uses to show us the way." -- Paulo Coelho]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 20:37:40 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/15610-emotions-in-my-experience-aren-t-covered-by-single-words-i]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Emotions, in my experience, aren't covered by single words. I don't believe in &quot;sadness,&quot; &quot;joy,&quot; or &quot;regret.&quot; Maybe the best proof that the language is patriarchal is that it oversimplifies feeling. I'd like to have at my disposal complicated hybrid emotions, Germanic train-car constructions like, say, &quot;the happiness that attends disaster.&quot; Or: &quot;the disappointment of sleeping with one's fantasy.&quot; I'd like to show how &quot;intimations of mortality brought on by aging family members&quot; connects with &quot;the hatred of mirrors that begins in middle age.&quot; I'd like to have a word for &quot;the sadness inspired by failing restaurants&quot; as well as for &quot;the excitement of getting a room with a minibar.&quot; I've never had the right words to describe my life, and now that I've entered my story, I need them more than ever. " -- Jeffrey Eugenides]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 08:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2795-she-is-too-fond-of-books-and-it-has-turned]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["She is too fond of books, and it has turned her brain." -- Louisa May Alcott]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1611-others-have-seen-what-is-and-asked-why-i-have</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2010 08:37:58 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Pablo Picasso]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/1611-others-have-seen-what-is-and-asked-why-i-have]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Others have seen what is and asked why. I have seen what could be and asked why not. " -- Pablo Picasso]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217203-nobody-likes-being-alone-that-much-i-don-t-go-out</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 04:31:17 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217203-nobody-likes-being-alone-that-much-i-don-t-go-out]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Nobody likes being alone that much. I don't go out of my way to make friends, that's all. It just leads to disappointment. " -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23833-altruism-is-for-those-who-can-t-endure-their-desires-there-s</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 04:39:27 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Stephen Dunn]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/23833-altruism-is-for-those-who-can-t-endure-their-desires-there-s]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Altruism is for those
who can't endure their desires.
There's a world

as ambiguous as a moan,
a pleasure moan
our earnest neighbors

might think a crime.
It's where we could live.
I'll say I love you,

Which will lead, of course,
to disappointment,
but those words unsaid

poison every next moment.
I will try to disappoint you
better than anyone else has.

--Mon Semblable" -- Stephen Dunn]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22116-no-matter-how-busy-you-may-think-you-are-you</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 22:24:51 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Atwood H. Townsend]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/22116-no-matter-how-busy-you-may-think-you-are-you]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["No matter how busy you may think you are, you must find time for reading, or surrender yourself to self-chosen ignorance." -- Atwood H. Townsend]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17762-there-are-no-uninteresting-things-only-uninterested-people</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 22:24:57 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/17762-there-are-no-uninteresting-things-only-uninterested-people]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are no uninteresting things, only uninterested people." -- G.K. Chesterton]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83394-artists-to-my-mind-are-the-real-architects-of-change</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 22:43:42 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/83394-artists-to-my-mind-are-the-real-architects-of-change]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Artists to my mind are the real architects of change, and not the political legislators who implement change after the fact. " -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113543-the-first-and-most-important-thing-an-individual-can-do</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 22:43:47 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113543-the-first-and-most-important-thing-an-individual-can-do]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The first and most important thing an individual can do is to become an individual again, decontrol himself, train himself as to what is going on and win back as much independent ground for himself as possible" -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134938-the-best-way-to-keep-something-bad-from-happening-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 22:45:01 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/134938-the-best-way-to-keep-something-bad-from-happening-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The best way to keep something bad from happening is to see it ahead of time... and you can't see it if you refuse to face the possibility." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186357-knowing-you-might-not-make-it-in-that-knowledge-courage</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 22:46:50 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/186357-knowing-you-might-not-make-it-in-that-knowledge-courage]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Knowing you might not make it... in that knowledge courage is born." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286320-dream-long-enough-and-dream-hard-enough-you-will-come</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 22:51:58 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by William S. Burroughs]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/286320-dream-long-enough-and-dream-hard-enough-you-will-come]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["dream long enough and dream hard enough
you will come to know
dreaming can make it so..." -- William S. Burroughs]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 11:04:41 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Anaïs Nin]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/350-i-with-a-deeper-instinct-choose-a-man-who-compels]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I, with a deeper instinct, choose a man who compels my strength, who makes enormous demands on me, who does not doubt my courage or my toughness, who does not believe me naïve or innocent, who has the courage to treat me like a woman." -- Anaïs Nin]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113033-i-ve-always-rejected-being-understood-to-be-understood-is-to</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 01:46:54 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/113033-i-ve-always-rejected-being-understood-to-be-understood-is-to]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I've always rejected being understood.  To be understood is to prostitute oneself.  I prefer to be taken seriously for what I'm not, remaining humanly unknown, with naturalness and all due respect" -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21558-there-are-ships-sailing-to-many-ports-but-not-a</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 01:47:03 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/21558-there-are-ships-sailing-to-many-ports-but-not-a]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are ships sailing to many ports, but not a single one goes where life is not painful." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62412-literature-is-the-most-agreeable-way-of-ignoring-life</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 01:47:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/62412-literature-is-the-most-agreeable-way-of-ignoring-life]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Literature is the most agreeable way of ignoring life." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131038-my-past-is-everything-i-failed-to-be</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 01:47:08 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/131038-my-past-is-everything-i-failed-to-be]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["My past is everything I failed to be." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265211-everything-around-me-is-evaporating-my-whole-life-my-memories</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 01:49:12 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/265211-everything-around-me-is-evaporating-my-whole-life-my-memories]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything around me is evaporating. My whole life, my memories, my imagination and its contents, my personality - it's all evaporating. I continuously feel that I was someone else, that I felt something else, that I thought something else. What I'm attending here is a show with another set. And the show I'm attending is myself." -- Fernando Pessoa]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217657-and-i-want-to-play-hide-and-seek-and-give-you-my</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 15:31:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Sarah Kane]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/217657-and-i-want-to-play-hide-and-seek-and-give-you-my]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["And I want to play hide-and-seek and give you my clothes and tell you I like your shoes and sit on the steps while you take a bath and massage your neck and kiss your feet and hold your hand and go for a meal and not mind when you eat my food and meet you at Rudy's and talk about the day and type up your letters and carry your boxes and laugh at your paranoia and give you tapes you don't listen to and watch great films and watch terrible films and complain about the radio and take pictures of you when you're sleeping and get up to fetch you coffee and bagels and Danish and go to Florent and drink coffee at midnight and have you steal my cigarettes and never be able to find a match and tell you about the tv programme I saw the night before and take you to the eye hospital and not laugh at your jokes and want you in the morning but let you sleep for a while and kiss your back and stroke your skin and tell you how much I love your hair your eyes your lips your neck your breasts your arse your

and sit on the steps smoking till your neighbour comes home and sit on the steps smoking till &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; come home and worry when you're late and be amazed when you're early and give you sunflowers and go to your party and dance till I'm black and be sorry when I'm wrong and happy when you forgive me and look at your photos and wish I'd known you forever and hear your voice in my ear and feel your skin on my skin and get scared when you're angry and your eye has gone red and the other eye blue and your hair to the left and your face oriental and tell you you're gorgeous and hug you when you're anxious and hold you when you hurt and want you when I smell you and offend you when I touch you and whimper when I'm next to you and whimper when I'm not and dribble on your breast and smother you in the night and get cold when you take the blanket and hot when you don't and melt when you smile and dissolve when you laugh and not understand why you think I'm rejecting you when I'm not rejecting you and wonder how you could think I'd ever reject you and wonder who you are but accept you anyway and tell you about the tree angel enchanted forest boy who flew across the ocean because he loved you and write poems for you and wonder why you don't believe me and have a feeling so deep I can't find words for it and want to buy you a kitten I'd get jealous of because it would get more attention than me and keep you in bed when you have to go and cry like a baby when you finally do and get rid of the roaches and buy you presents you don't want and take them away again and ask you to marry me and you say no &lt;i&gt;again&lt;/i&gt; but keep on asking because though you think I don't mean it I do always have from the first time I asked you and wander the city thinking it's empty without you and want what you want and think I'm losing myself but know I'm safe with you and tell you the worst of me and try to give you the best of me because you don't deserve any less and answer your questions when I'd rather not and tell you the truth when I really don't want to and try to be honest because I know you prefer it and think it's all over but hang on in for just ten more minutes before you throw me out of your life and forget who I am and try to get closer to you because it's beautiful learning to know you and well worth the effort and speak German to you badly and Hebrew to you worse and make love with you at three in the morning and somehow somehow somehow communicate some of the overwhelming undying overpowering unconditional all-encompassing heart-enriching mind-expanding on-going never-ending love I have for you." -- Sarah Kane]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95904-ginger-you-know-what-the-greatest-tragedy-is-in-the</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 22:58:38 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Terry Pratchett]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/95904-ginger-you-know-what-the-greatest-tragedy-is-in-the]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Ginger:  You know what the greatest tragedy is in the whole world?... It's all the people who never find out what it is they really want to do or what it is they're really good at.  It's all the sons who become blacksmiths because their fathers were blacksmiths.  It's all the people who could be really fantastic flute players who grow old and die without ever seeing a musical instrument, so they become bad plowmen instead.  It's all the people with talents who never even find out.  Maybe they are never even &lt;i&gt;born&lt;/i&gt; in a time when it's even possible to find out.  It's all the people who never get to know what it is that they can really be.  &lt;i&gt;It's all the wasted chances&lt;/i&gt;." -- Terry Pratchett]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see</guid>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 23:03:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/156662-everything-is-more-complicated-than-you-think-you-only-see]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Everything is more complicated than you think. You only see a tenth of what is true. There are a million little strings attached to every choice you make; you can destroy your life every time you choose. But maybe you won't know for twenty years. And you'll never ever trace it to its source. And you only get one chance to play it out. Just try and figure out your own divorce. And they say there is no fate, but there is: it's what you create. Even though the world goes on for eons and eons, you are here for a fraction of a fraction of a second. Most of your time is spent being dead or not yet born. But while alive, you wait in vain, wasting years, for a phone call or a letter or a look from someone or something to make it all right. And it never comes or it seems to but doesn't really. And so you spend your time in vague regret or vaguer hope for something good to come along. Something to make you feel connected, to make you feel whole, to make you feel loved." -- Charlie Kaufman]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 16:44:15 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by douglas adams]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/3278-i-may-not-have-gone-where-i-intended-to-go]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I may not have gone where I intended to go, but I think I have ended up where I needed to be." -- douglas adams]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144862-in-ireland-you-go-to-someone-s-house-and-she-asks</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 16:45:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by C.E. Murphy]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/144862-in-ireland-you-go-to-someone-s-house-and-she-asks]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["In Ireland, you go to someone's house, and she asks you if you want a cup of tea. You say no, thank you, you're really just fine. She asks if you're &lt;I&gt;sure&lt;/I&gt;. You say of course you're sure, really, you don't need a thing. Except they pronounce it &lt;I&gt;ting&lt;/I&gt;. You don't need a &lt;I&gt;ting&lt;/I&gt;. Well, she says then, I was going to get myself some anyway, so it would be no trouble. Ah, you say, well, if you were going to get yourself some, I wouldn't mind a spot of tea, at that, so long as it's no trouble and I can give you a hand in the kitchen. Then you go through the whole thing all over again until you both end up in the kitchen drinking tea and chatting. 

In America, someone asks you if you want a cup of tea, you say no, and then you don't get any damned tea.

I liked the Irish way better." -- C.E. Murphy]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61032-a-woman-knows-very-well-that-though-a-wit-sends</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 16:45:36 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Virginia Woolf]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/61032-a-woman-knows-very-well-that-though-a-wit-sends]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["A woman knows very well that, though a wit sends her his poems, praises her judgment, solicits her criticism, and drinks her tea, this by no means signifies that he respects her opinions, admires her understanding, or will refuse, though the rapier is denied him, to run through the body with his pen." -- Virginia Woolf]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86685-i-told-her-tea-bags-were-just-a-convenience-for</guid>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 16:46:21 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Frank McCourt]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/86685-i-told-her-tea-bags-were-just-a-convenience-for]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I told her tea bags were just a convenience for people with busy lives and she said no one is so busy they can't take  time to make a decent cup of tea and if you are that busy you don't deserve a decent cup of tea for what is it all about anyway?  Are we put into this world to be busy or to chat over a nice cup of tea?" -- Frank McCourt]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179690-i-had-no-illusions-about-you-he-said-i-knew</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 17:46:19 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/179690-i-had-no-illusions-about-you-he-said-i-knew]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I had no illusions about you,' he said. 'I knew you were silly and frivolous and empty-headed. But I loved you. I knew that your aims and ideals were vulgar and commonplace. But I loved you. I knew that you were second-rate. But I loved you. It's comic when I think how hard I tried to be amused by the things that amused you and how anxious I was to hide from you that I wasn't ignorant and vulgar and scandal-mongering and stupid. I knew how frightened you were of intelligence and I did everything I could to make you think me as big a fool as the rest of the men you knew. I knew that you'd only married me for convenience. I loved you so much, I didn't care. Most people, as far as I can see, when they're in love with someone and the love isn't returned feel that they have a grievance. They grow angry and bitter. I wasn't like that. I never expected you to love me, I didn't see any reason that you should. I never thought myself very lovable. I was thankful to be allowed to love you and I was enraptured when now and then I thought you were pleased with me or when I noticed in your eyes a gleam of good-humored affection. I tried not to bore you with my love; I knew I couldn't afford to do that and I was always on the lookout for the first sign that you were impatient with my affection. What most husbands expect as a right I was prepared to receive as a favor." -- W. Somerset Maugham]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129637-if-they-invent-a-car-that-runs-on-stupid-jokes</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 17:47:10 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Haruki Murakami]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/129637-if-they-invent-a-car-that-runs-on-stupid-jokes]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["If they invent a car that runs on stupid jokes, you could go far." -- Haruki Murakami]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37722-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 17:47:34 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/37722-beware-the-irrational-however-seductive-shun-the-transcendent-and-all]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Beware the irrational, however seductive. Shun the 'transcendent' and all who invite you to subordinate or annihilate yourself. Distrust compassion; prefer dignity for yourself and others. Don't be afraid to be thought arrogant or selfish. Picture all experts as if they were mammals. Never be a spectator of unfairness or stupidity. Seek out argument and disputation for their own sake; the grave will supply plenty of time for silence. Suspect your own motives, and all excuses. Do not live for others any more than you would expect others to live for you." -- Christopher Hitchens]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48969-from-what-i-have-observed-when-the-anesthesia-of-love</guid>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 17:48:07 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Ron add a quote by Amy Tan]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/48969-from-what-i-have-observed-when-the-anesthesia-of-love]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["From what I have observed, when the anesthesia of love wears off, there is always the pain of consequences.  You don't have to be stupid to marry the wrong man." -- Amy Tan]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
