<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/99965-jim-hahn]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/99965-jim-hahn" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 06:36:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130000-there-are-many-premium-writers-yes-tolstoy-yes-he-wrote</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2011 06:36:43 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/130000-there-are-many-premium-writers-yes-tolstoy-yes-he-wrote]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are many premium writers, yes? Tolstoy, yes? He wrote &lt;i&gt;War&lt;/i&gt;, and also &lt;i&gt;Peace&lt;/i&gt;, which are both premium books." -- Jonathan Safran Foer]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say</guid>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 18:59:16 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/177489-i-do-things-like-get-in-a-taxi-and-say]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["I do things like get in a taxi and say, &quot;The library, and step on it." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198946-but-when-you-talk-about-nabokov-and-coover-you-re-talking</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 04:25:33 -0800</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/198946-but-when-you-talk-about-nabokov-and-coover-you-re-talking]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["But when you talk about Nabokov and Coover, you’re talking about real geniuses, the writers who weathered real shock and invented this stuff in contemporary fiction. But after the pioneers always come the crank turners, the little gray people who take the machines others have built and just turn the crank, and little pellets of metafiction come out the other end. The crank-turners capitalize for a while on sheer fashion, and they get their plaudits and grants and buy their IRAs and retire to the Hamptons well out of range of the eventual blast radius. There are some interesting parallels between postmodern crank-turners and what’s happened since post-structural theory took off here in the U.S., why there’s such a big backlash against post-structuralism going on now. It’s the crank-turners fault. I think the crank-turners replaced the critic as the real angel of death as far as literary movements are concerned, now. You get some bona fide artists who come along and really divide by zero and weather some serious shit-storms of shock and ridicule in order to promulgate some really important ideas. Once they triumph, though, and their ideas become legitimate and accepted, the crank-turners and wannabes come running to the machine, and out pour the gray pellets and now the whole thing’s become a hollow form, just another institution of fashion. Take a look at some of the critical-theory Ph.D. dissertations being written now. They’re like de Man and Foucault in the mouth of a dull child. Academia and commercial culture have somehow become these gigantic mechanisms of commodification that drain the weight and color out of even the most radical new advances. It’s a surreal inversion of the death-by-neglect that used to kill off prescient art. Now prescient art suffers death-by acceptance. We love things to death, now. Then we retire to the Hamptons." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2858-all-journeys-have-secret-destinations-of-which-the-traveler-is</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 16:18:48 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Martin Buber]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/2858-all-journeys-have-secret-destinations-of-which-the-traveler-is]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["All journeys have secret destinations of which the traveler is unaware." -- Martin Buber]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2012 06:31:33 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by David Foster Wallace]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/77749-the-really-important-kind-of-freedom-involves-attention-and-awareness]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The really important kind of freedom involves attention, and awareness, and discipline, and effort, and being able truly to care about other people and to sacrifice for them, over and over, in myriad petty little unsexy ways, every day." -- David Foster Wallace]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170356-the-connection-was-so-bad-and-i-couldn-t-talk-at</guid>
		<pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2012 16:40:28 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by J.D. Salinger]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/170356-the-connection-was-so-bad-and-i-couldn-t-talk-at]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["The connection was so bad, and I couldn’t talk at all during most of the call. How terrible it is when you say I love you and the person at the other end shouts back ‘What?" -- J.D. Salinger]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2012 18:32:34 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[Jim add a quote by Albert Einstein]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/987-there-are-only-two-ways-to-live-your-life-one]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle." -- Albert Einstein]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
