<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <channel>
    <xhtml:meta xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" name="robots" content="noindex" />
    <title></title>
    <copyright><![CDATA[Copyright (C) 2014 Goodreads Inc. All rights reserved.]]>
    </copyright>
    <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/999943-april-erwin]]></link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/list_rss/999943-april-erwin" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:53:23 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <image>
      <title></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/home.xml]]></link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>41</height>
      <url>https://www.goodreads.com/home.xmlimages/layout/goodreads_logo_144.jpg</url>
    </image>
    	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410460-here-and-there-among-men-there-are-those-who-pause</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410460-here-and-there-among-men-there-are-those-who-pause]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["Here and there among men, there are those who pause in the hurried rush to listen to the call of a life that is more real… He who sees and hears too much is cursed for a dreamer, a fanatic, or a fool, by the mad mob who, having eyes, see not, ears and hear not, and refuse to understand… Only when we can no longer strive in the battle for earthly honors or material wealth, do we turn to the unseen but more enduring things of life; and.. we strive to hear and see the things we have so long refused to consider. Pete knew a world unseen by us, and we, therefore, fancied ourselves wiser than he. The wind in the pines, the rustle of the leaves, the murmur of the brook, the growl of thunder, and the voices of the night were all understood and answered by him. The flowers, the trees, the rocks, the hills, the clouds were to him, not lifeless things, but living friends, who laughed and wept with him as he was gay or sorrowful. ‘Poor Pete,’ we said. Was he in truth, poorer or richer than we?" -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<guid>https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410459-i-never-understood-until-the-past-months-why-the-master</guid>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2013 09:53:23 -0700</pubDate>
		<title>
			<![CDATA[April add a quote by Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</title>
		<link>
	    <![CDATA[https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/410459-i-never-understood-until-the-past-months-why-the-master]]>
		</link>
		<description>
	    <![CDATA["…I never understood until the past months why the Master so often withdrew alone into the wilderness. There is not only food and medicine for one’s body; there is also healing for the heart and strength for the soul in nature. One gets very close to God…in these temples of God’s own building." -- Harold Bell Wright]]>
		</description>
	</item>

  </channel>
</rss>
